Do you know why you're here?
You've been a very bad boy.
And I've brought you here to punish you and teach you a lesson.
Are you ready to learn?
Oh, look at these fucking balls.
I'm going to fucking pull them and stretch them.
Because you've been a bad fucking man.
I'm playing with your cock like a woman's emotion fucking piece of shit
piece of shit
you like when i have you by the fucking balls
i think i want to play with your asshole turn around for me
I'm gonna spank you for being a bad little boy
fucking red little ass
bad little fucking boy
you need to learn your lessons
I think I need some tools for this job you've been very very cruel and
I'm cold-hearted, so I will show you no mercy.
I don't know if I'm being hard enough on you.
What do you think?
I think it's not good enough.
You want to fucking slap your balls?
I bet you don't.
You're a bad fucking piece of shit if I'm gonna do what I want to.
Pathetic little hopeless man.
Oh, you thought you were time.
Have you had enough yet?
I don't think so.
I need a break.
Break for me.
Your back looks pretty nice.
I think I've done a good job.
I could do this all day.
I just think I'm running out of places that aren't red.
I want you to be as red as my little outfit here.
Maybe I'll train your asshole later.
I think it's time to run to my next toy.
You're going to learn your place as a man today.
Bring me my throne, slave.
And get on your fucking hands and knees.
Good boy, I'll spare the rod on you.
Get back in your fucking cage, you piece of shit.
It's hard to find good slaves these days.
Come kneel before me.
Now learn your lesson today.
Oh
Grovel at my feet, you pathetic little man.
This is your new place.
are you crying yet you pathetic little piece of shit did i make you cry
you shouldn't be fucking crying
merciless
You can't take anymore. You can't
Pathetic what a worthless little slave
come play with the mistress. Do you want to go back in your cage?
You won't get any food or drink until you're ready to play.
Now crawl to your cage you little piece of shit.