to hear about that so uh Wow speaking of freaks
So, for all the idiots out there, let's go ahead and introduce yourself.
My name is Natasha Nice.
How old are you?
And I'm 23.
Where are you from?
I was born in France, and I was raised in Southern Cali.
Wow.
So I'm a Cali girl, Valley girl.
I love it, I love it.
Dig it.
Okay, that's what's up.
Yeah.
So thank you for coming over.
I know I paged you last night and was like, hey, can you come over here?
Yeah.
Well, I wasn't doing anything today.
I figured it's sunny.
Mr. Potato Head.
Oh, stop it.
Look at him.
Isn't that old school? Yeah, I said, oh, I gotta get that.
I was like, I gotta pick that up.
Got the interchangeable parts and everything.
Can I play with them? Yeah, of course you can.
Oh my god, I have not seen one of these in a long time.
Remember Mr. Potato Head?
Mrs. Potato Head.
Kids probably.
They had, yeah, they had the little family.
Right, right, right.
But his back opens, too, though.
Yeah, but, you know, we ain't, we ain't, we ain't.
Are we not interested?
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Potato Head.
Mr. Potato Head.
There you go.
I don't know, you're kind of a big guy.
You think I can bring out the style with this?
Oh, maybe, maybe.
Yeah, you know.
Maybe.
Rock this at the MTV Awards or something?
Oh, you know, yeah.
Potato Head is getting jealous.
BET Awards, maybe.
Yeah, BET Awards, they want to set that at the BET, you know.
Neon green? I think they would.
Alright, yeah.
So you used to play with Mr. Potato Head when you were younger?
Wait, wait, wait. She's 23, man. Did they even have a potato head in her?
Well, my older sister did, so I encountered him in her room.
And then, yeah, you can put the eyes upside down.
What the fuck is this?
You can just make him look like a little weirdo.
It's kind of like it's his penis, you know, except with two eyes.
That's a good one.
So how did we go there?
I don't know. That's just where it goes.
They should definitely look good, I agree.
Hmm, mustache, I don't know.
Well, I have an idea.
That's a good thing you brought that up.
What's up?
So, yeah, you understand what I'm saying?
I mean, I know you probably don't, but...
So, like, what does this have to do with anything?
You'll see, just trust me.
Just trust me.
All right.
Oh, dressing room?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, just want her to trust me.
Hmm.
Just...
They kind of knew, baby, let me help you.
Bam, bam.
Yeah, there you go.
Whoa.
It almost hit me in the face.
Be careful.
Just put your mouth on him right there.
I'm scared.
Whoa.
That's huge.
Do it again for me.
Looks like a nose.
Mr. Potato Head nose.
Nice.
Bite that.
You're so bad.
I know this.
This is new.
Has a chick ever made you nut with a
through the boxers blowjob before?
No, but I think she can.
That would be hot. Wouldn't it?
It would come out through the boxers.
pussy yeah we're gonna nut through the box
that is so funny i like the way it's wet yeah that's hot
I'm going to go hang these up and never use them again.
I want you to sign these motherfuckers, you know.
Right by the wet spot?
Yeah.
Who does that?
This thing is huge.
I do.
We do.
Wow.
Look at that.
The size of my face.
There you go.
Nice.
You going to smell it?
You going to smell it clean?
Yeah.
Beautiful. I like that. I like that there are two hands on there.
I like corn on the cob.
Yeah baby. Beautiful.
Beautiful.
Pretty ass eyes.
Shit!
No you did pretty good.
Better than some.
Best dash.
Let me see your pretty ass eyes.
Wow.
Please, get up on me, dear, I can't help it.
Get up on me, dear, I can't help it.
Why you trying to hide from me?
Why you hiding from me?
Oh, you're so close.
Damn.
Oh, that looks fucking stupid.
Yes.
Wow.
Very pure.
I don't want to look at that pussy.
OK.
Oh.
Now you get what I was saying, now, I mean.
No.
Not yet?
I still don't get it, but I don't care.
I like it.
Oh my gosh.
He's licking my asshole.
Is he really?
Oh shit, I gotta see this.
Oh my god.
No hands, that's that 3G, that 4G shit.
Wireless.
wireless head right there.
That's that Mr. Potato head, huh?
She's giving a Mr. Potato head.
See, that's what I was trying to explain.
That's what I was trying to say.
We call him Mr. Potato, see?
Oh, I see.
You'll see, I'll show you a little bit later.
What do you want?
You want this?
Oh, wow.
You want a little bit of this?
I want you to taste that mother fucker.
Oh, damn.
Damn, I'm big on this.
Pussy looks like Mrs. Potato Head.
That looks nice.
Damn.
Oh, you're a fucking bad girl, bad girl.
Fuck, it's all over my ass.
Give it to me, right there.
I'm just a man.
I'm so creative.
And now.
This right pussy tastes so good.
Ow.
Face in the air.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, shit.
Yes, I owe you right there.
Give it all to me.
Give it all.
Open my legs.
You fucking...
Oh, that's a big dick.
That's a big dick.
Oh, shit.
Open that pussy all up.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Let me touch you.
Move it.
Don't touch me.
Make it look nasty, woman.
Oh
Nice like when you like when you look at me
young girl.
You little young girl.
Get on your grown woman shit.
I got a big dick. You got a big dick. I know.
Oh my god.
So cute.
That's him?
Don't stop. Don't stop.
What you doing?
Oh fuck.
What you doing honey?
What you doing?
That's right.
Oh fuck.
What you doing?
You dirtying my dick?
You got a cane on you?
No.
Suck the juice off this motherfucker.
You got a fucking little pussy.
That's right.
You squeezing right there.
Yeah.
Take your pussy juice off that bitch.
And you do it special.
Yeah.
Oh, do that again.
God damn.
Did you see this bitch spit on it?
I got it.
Right here.
That's for you.
Look at that.
You see that?
Hell yeah.
Fuck your pussy.
Fuck your little homegirl.
That's right, that's right.
You spread them legs, man. You spread them legs.
Spread them legs.
My balls are in my fucking crotch.
There you go.
Give it back.
Oh, shit.
Oh, that's a big day.
damn he had to jump off it and uh i think he's trying to hold him back so
Oh, these are, these are contacts, right?
Those are, these are contacts, yes, what do you think, what do you think?
They look good.
Good?
They really look good, I have to say, yeah.
Yeah, thank you, thank you.
Did your nose get a little bigger, or?
Um, my nose?
Yeah.
Uh, no.
It just looks a little different.
No.
I am just having a blast.
I know, I haven't seen you in such a long time.
It makes me just feel so silly.
I know.
Yeah?
Let's go for it.
Oh my god.
Oh, what?
Stop it!
You're just, you're making me smile.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh my god, just, your teeth are just a pearly white.
Oh yeah, I've been...
Such a beautiful smile.
Thank you, I work on it, you know.
Oh, okay, Wes is coming, Wes is back out now.
Oh.
You ready to get back to business?
Yes, I am.
Alright, cool, cool.
And Natasha, it's really nice to see you again, too.
Oh yeah, you too.
You good?
What y'all was doin'?
Oh, we were just...
What fuckin' nice shoe is this, man?
That's mine.
Oh, my God.
What size is this, man?
Like a 7 1â„2.
Oh, my God, dude.
Wow.
Yeah.
Yeah, but...
That's, uh...
That's interesting.
Look at that.
A footer.
Yeah, you better put...
Yeah, you better put two hands up there, girl.
That's ridiculous.
Look at that.
Wow.
So, my dick is about the same size as your feet, huh?
Yep.
That's, uh...
That's pretty accurate.
Oh, that's longer than your feet, though.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I meant.
It's bigger than the feet, yeah.
Wow.
You, uh, you have a big dick.
Yeah.
No, you just got a small pussy.
Bring it here.
Come here.
Bring that motherfucker here.
Let me see.
Oh, you're so nice.
Nice.
Ooh.
Where are my titties?
Damn.
Ugh.
That's beautiful.
Mm.
Damn.
Yeah.
Bad aim.
Better? Progress?
Yes.
That's nice right there.
We love you too.
Damn.
Fuck yeah.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Smash.
Oh, what's going on?
Oh, mm-mm.
Bad boy.
Oh, I think it is.
Oh, shit.
A little appetizer.
Oh.
Mm-mm-mm.
You want it?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, you want it.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, fuck.
I can't stop smiling.
I'm getting a little excited.
Hell yeah.
Nice.
Don't choke on your food.
Exactly.
That's nice.
That looks fucking beautiful Natasha.
Wait.
We can see you.
There you go.
That looks beautiful too.
Yeah.
Damn.
Come here, let's go here.
I'll show you.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Oh.
What about this end?
Okay.
Nice.
Oh.
Do I have something on my face?
No.
Damn, Natasha.
That was pretty crazy.
That was a good idea.
That was some good ass shit.
So, did you have a good time?
I did.
You did, really?
Yeah.
Enjoyed yourself?
I'm a little cock drunk.
Are you?
Yeah.
A little bit.
So what are you about to get into now?
I don't know.
I think I'll just kick it here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Maybe take a little nap.
Oh.
Why hello.
I think Mr. Potato Head enjoyed it, too.
Mr. Potato Head.
I think Mr. Potato Head's ready to go for round two.
You down for it?
Oh, yeah.
I don't discriminate.
All right.
Have fun, Mr. Potato Head.
Bye.
Till next time.
bang bros
it's best website