You're going to do anything that I want, aren't you?
Yes, Mistress.
Get up in there.
Oh, you like that.
Yes, Mistress.
Thank you, Mistress.
Oh, I didn't say you were done.
Thank you.
Yes, there you go.
You're starting to get it.
Thank you, Mistress.
Sniff my ass, little slave boy.
Doesn't it smell like a goddess?
Yes, Mistress.
Get over here and take my boots off.
The other one.
Yes, Mistress.
Oh, there you go.
Don't forget about the other one.
Yes, Mistress.
I don't think you're doing a good enough job.
there you go
you're doing a good job
little slave boy
I'm going to make you do this every day
I'm just going to suck my toes
whenever I ask you to
yes mistress
and you're going to like it
whether you like it or not
yes mistress
Try to fit both.
There you go.
Oh.
Is it going to fit?
Might have to shove it a little more in there.
Oh.
That's my slave boy.
Choke on my toes once more.
That's a good slave.
You better get used to it.
say thank you one more time
thank you
good slave
that feels so good on my toes
you're just going to make me feel good
all the time
Look right here at my pussy the whole time you're sucking my toes.
This is what's going to control you.
Suck my toes like you're licking my pussy.
Stop staring at my pussy.
Yes, mistress.
Harder sleeve boy.
Do you like staring at my pussy while you suck on my toes?
Of course you do, slave.
We can't forget about my ass.
No, mistress.
Get over here.
Yes, mistress.
my g-string is so tiny it barely covers my asshole
oh
bury your face in my ass slave boy
Okay, back to my feet.
Yes, mistress.
Come on, slave boy.
Well, you can do better than that.
That's what I like to see.
You think you can get used to this every day?
Yes, Mistress.
Because you're going to do it every day.
Whatever makes you happy, Mistress.
Okay, I think you've been good enough.
I'm going to go put you back in your cage.
Yes, mistress.
Come on.
Here's more.
Here, kiss my toes goodnight.
Yes, mistress.
Oh, that's good.
Once more.
That's a good boy.