Could you just go get it for me and bring it back up here?
OK.
Sure.
Here you go, ma'am.
Oh, thank you.
You know what, Robbie?
Would you mind assembling this for me?
There's something in here that needs to be put together.
Could you do that for me?
Sure.
Yeah.
You can just do it right over there.
Right over here?
Mm-hmm.
OK.
What the hell is this?
Oh. Um, well,
it's something that's supposed to help me and my boyfriend
in our relationship. I've never seen anything like this.
Oh, really? Oh, it's really kind of fun.
Well, I guess it's all
done. Um...
Great.
Do you want me to throw the box away?
Um...
Well, no. Let's...
I should probably test it out first.
Um...
You can just leave the box there.
Would you mind helping me
test it out?
Uh...
It's really simple.
What? I don't understand.
Well, you would just lay down right here.
Yeah, your head right there.
Just want to make sure it's straight.
A weird, like, sleeping aid or something?
Kind of.
Yeah.
Like this?
That's kind of comfortable.
Good.
I could use a little nap.
Do you want to just see if that
helps me to fall asleep?
No, it's definitely not.
It is very comfortable.
Well.
I could fall asleep like this.
Okay.
It seems to be really sturdy.
Oh my God.
What the hell?
No, no, no, just calm down.
Is that your?
That's, yeah.
That's definitely what this is for.
Oh my God.
Can you, like, is it like right in your face?
Oh, yes it is.
Now if you would just stick your tongue out for me.
Oh.
Very nice.
I've never had an ass in my face like this.
Oh really?
Yeah.
You should definitely.
I can't believe I'm licking your asshole.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, it's hot now.
I'm only getting me sleep down here.
No, it's not really bad for sleeping.
Yeah, it's right there, yeah, right in that little.
Oh, oh, okay.
I'm a little tired.
Oh, I bet you are.
Don't do that.
Don't do that. Kiss me. Kiss me.
He has a little message.
So this is to help your relationship with your boyfriend.
Oh yeah.
Do you see how it works now?
I think you should leave it here.
Maybe I could improve everybody's relationship.
Maybe I could improve everybody's productivity this way.
What's that?
Why don't you stand up?
Come up?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Just scoot your head out there.
Stand up next to me.
Oh my god.
Is that my reward?
Part of it.
What's the rest?
Why don't you stand up.
Okay.
I'm just going to sit right here because it's really comfortable.
Oh my.
I'm excited.
I think I should maybe take these down.
No, you take them down.
Okay.
Oh my.
Oh.
I'm excited.
I think I should maybe take these down.
Oh, you take them down.
Yeah.
Holy moly.
Oh my.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, my.
Oh, she's so good.
Shrimp.
Show me the left hand.
Oh my face is red okay.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Oh, look at that.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a beautiful breast.
Oh.
Oh, you're going to get the other one wet.
Oh, look at that.
You lick my balls gently.
Oh
You should just clean that up for me, you're a chandler, right?
My face is all wet now.
Something else looks a little wet.
Yeah, but that's a good news, that's a good news for my supply.
Oh my.
Oh.
It's beautiful.
Do you like that?
Oh, yes.
Yes, you can put your face in there.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mmm.
Yeah, is that good?
Good, good.
This is exactly what my boyfriend never does.
I'll do it every day for you.
Okay.
You're hired.
Oh, yes, get in there, get in there, buttonhole.
Get in there a little more.
Oh, yes, make it really smooth, thank you.
Can I, I know I'm just a janitor, but you're an executive.
Do you think I could maybe?
Yes, you do have a really nice dick for a janitor.
At least I could just rub on it.
Yeah, why don't you rub on it and see what happens?
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh gosh, that is turning me on.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my.
And when do we go for it?
Go for it?
Yeah, just, let's just.
Just do it?
Just stick it in?
Yeah, sure.
We don't have to tell anybody, just do it.
Just do it.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, I can't believe this.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh, I need to take two liters more often.
Oh, I love you.
Every day I see you and your sexy short skirts
that you wear and your cleavage.
Yes.
I never knew what was underneath.
Little did I ever think that I'd get
and I don't mean to see it, but to fuck it.
Yes, yes, I love when you broom under my desk.
Oh gosh.
Yeah, go, get it, go for it, yes.
Oh, it's all the way in.
Oh my gosh, yes it is.
Oh gosh!
Oh, your palms are looking a little dry there.
Uh-huh.
There you go.
Yeah.
There he is.
So hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, gosh, run.
Oh, run now.
Oh, my gosh.
No.
Oh, I mean, you like that, some more?
Yeah, why don't you?
Oh, god.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
Mmm.
Ah!
Oh!
Oh.
Look at my ball again.
You should just lick my butthole.
Lick your butthole?
Yeah. Really, really good.
Oh, it's called eating ass.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, God, yes, Rodney.
Good.
So your boyfriend doesn't do that?
No?
He doesn't deserve that chair.
But you do.
Oh, you deserve it.
Oh, my goodness.
Yes, yes, you deserve it, you deserve that chair.
Oh my goodness, you are a messenger.
Yes, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Keep going, keep going, Rodney, good.
Yes, in the chair, in the chair.
Oh, this one came off a lot easier.
Oh yeah, they both do.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I just wanted to watch you struggle.
I assumed, let me struggle.
Shame on you.
Yes, shame on you.
Bad girl.
Whatever.
Let me struggle with that zipper.
yes.
Is that okay?
Come down on your knees.
Oh my god.
Your boobs are just way too dry.
I know, what should we do?
That's it.
There you go.
Oh, don't lick it off.
That's my job.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
Yeah.
Ah.
Mm.
Oh.
I think my dick
needs more sucking.
Yeah.
Oh.
Put your hands behind your back
One of the top executives in the company.
Just minutes after I swept the floor under your feet.
It kind of turned me on when you did that.
I'm going to have to lay down here.
Let you crawl between my legs.
Lay on your stomach.
Get down on your stomach. That's it.
Bounce your boobs on my balls.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, and they're all wet too.
Sexy, tasty drool.
Do you like that?
Is that nice for you?
Slide down.
Lay on your stomach.
That's it.
There you go.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my.
Sloppy mess.
Oh.
Put your hands down by your side.
Like that.
There we go.
Oh.
A little bit.
Something dirty and nasty about it, isn't there?
A little bit, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean...
As long as we're going in that direction, you really want to be dirty.
What are we going to do?
You can lick the janitor's ass.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Dirty girl.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Mm.
I bet you don't like your boyfriend's ass.
Sometimes.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's it, yeah.
There you go.
If you shake it good enough, I'll stick my cock back in your pussy.
it some more.
There we go, oh yeah.
Before I go back in, I'm going to lick this butthole a little more.
Yeah.
All right.
Fuck yeah.
It's so hard.
Yes.
Oh my God.
It's so hard.
Oh, yeah, oh God.
Oh, it's so hard.
Fuck, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, my God yes.
Oh.
Yes, brother.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
This is so good.
Oh, God.
You like that, don't you?
Give me your hand.
Oh my God.
totally gave it a real test run.
No?
I need to lay down and put my head in it?
Yeah, I think you do.
Go ahead.
To make sure it works.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm going to shake those boobs a little before I sit on it.
This is a great chair.
Yeah.
I like it.
Oh, that kind of tickles and it feels good.
Oh, I must not be doing it rough enough.
Oh my, there we go.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that feels good.
You are a dirty girl.
Oh yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh.
Yeah.
Now.
Dirty girl.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
My balls are feeling neglected.
Oh.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Ooh, yeah.
Ooh.
Are you feeling somewhere?
Okay, here.
Come over here.
Stand up.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Wow.
Yes!
Oh no, oh god, no, no, no, no, no.
Tell me you like that, yeah, do you like that?
Yes.
yes.
Oh my god, oh my god, yes.
Oh, God, she has a remedy.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
One more thing, because I'm going to build a home very soon for the wife.
Oh, shit.
I do.
Oh, God.
Do you like it?
No.
Get down on your knees here.
There, yeah.
What do you think?
Getting dry again.
Maybe you should wet them a little bit.
I see you every day sitting in your office chair.
Yeah?
I'm not masturbating.
I'm not.
I'm coming in your mouth.
Really?
While you're sitting at work.
Oh jeez.
I'm going to go back over to your desk.
Let's do it.
I'm coming in your mouth.
Okay.
I'm sure you have a lot of work to do.
I'm so excited.
The trimmer does work.
Oh my gosh, I'm so excited.
I fantasized about this so many times.
Oh, every day I see you in your short skirt sitting at your desk.
Yeah.
And that you'd return the favor.
Oh my god.
And yet it happened today.
It's a night night.
Oh god
and it was so good.
I'm just a juiciness
of my tongue beating the juiciness
of your ass.
I couldn't have been any
nicer.
Oh.
Oh gosh. And look at these flowers.
It just fits
It's so great in my mouth.
Oh, you're no fun.
off.
Yeah.
I'll just tell him it's like something else.
You would.
I kind of want to just sit here until it dries up.
Alright, well I'm sure you've got a lot of work to do.
Oh yeah, that.
So I'll let you get back to work.
Okay.
Alright?
Bye.
Alright, goodnight.
Toodles.
Thanks, Rodney.
Okay, I'll let you get back to work.
Thank you.