So, how are you doing today?
I'm good. How are you?
Good. What's your name?
I'm Stella Cox.
I believe it's red. Red.
Red. What does red mean?
That I'm not willing to continue, I think.
And that's one.
Yeah. And then there's yellow, if I want to slow things down. Right?
looking forward to today.
Just enjoying the scene, see how it goes,
see how much of it I can take.
OK, cool.
Want to come inside?
Sure.
Cool.
Let's do this.
Thank you.
As you see, as you see, you see, you see
You're not a little fucking girl, aren't you, huh?
You want that back in your mouth.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Hold that in there.
Oh, yes.
Get back in your fucking mouth.
Yes, put that in there or something.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Oh, put that in there.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, you're all done, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yes, more.
Oh, yes.
More? Yes.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, you filthy girl, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah, that's it, all the way down there.
Oh.
Oh, open your mouth.
Oh, yes.
Thank you, sir.
Yeah, what was that?
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Fuck, yes.
Yes.
Yes, you fuck.
You want some water?
Please.
No one told you to fucking smile.
No one told you to smile.
Come here, put it in your fucking mouth.
Yes.
I'm going to rub it all over your fucking face.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can do it.
Stop it.
I'm going to open it back up.
What?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, spit it out.
Spit it all over yourself.
What?
Fuckin' cock.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, baby.
Put that back in your fuckin' mouth.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Stick your tongue out.
Stick your fuckin' tongue out.
Yes.
Stick it out.
Fuck.
oh yes oh fuck yes
oh yeah shake that
oh fuck yes
oh yes
Yeah, stay down there.
Thank you, sir.
Open your fucking mouth.
Open your mouth again.
Yeah, you keep those fucking eyes open.
Keep your fucking eyes open.
No one told you to take it out.
Put it back in.
Yes
Open that mouth wider.
Stick that tongue out.
Stick it out.
Yes.
Thank you, sir.
I can't hear you I can't hear you
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Jack!
Spit that out. Spit that out.
Spit that out.
Spit it out.
Yes. Yes.
Yeah, you wanna feel that ass,
the fucking ass, don't you?
Yes. You feel that ass?
Just beg me for it.
I can't hear you.
What are you on?
Say it.
My IP.
This is my IP.
Yes.
My IP.
Oh.
oh shit oh yeah oh my god
Oh, yes.
Yes, I like it in your face, don't you?
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, I can't breathe, man.
Fuck.
Oh, yes, that was so good.
Oh, yes.
Oh, no.
Oh my god.
Oh
Oh, thanks.
Ah!
You like that little pink flamingo in your mouth?
Now fly, birdie, fly.
Put it back in your fucking mouth.
Open your mouth.
Open your fucking mouth.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Look at me, yes, please, please.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my god.
Oh, yes.
Ah, shit.
Really?
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Just look at me.
Oh, yes.
Look at me.
It's OK.
You need a little girl, huh?
You like all your little toys, little girl?
I can give you some real cock.
Yes, I'm gonna be able to have my toy.
Yes, just use me.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, look at that little house.
It's good for me.
Oh, yes.
I'm gonna be back in there.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes, a little more to that crack.
Yes, I'm inside my hole.
Yes, fuck me, yes.
Oh, yes.
You little fucking dirty little girl.
Yes.
You're a fucking whore.
I'm going to use all your little whore holes.
Yes, please, sir.
Yes, please use me.
Use you for what?
For your pleasure.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yeah, put that down your fucking throat.
You want to suck on that fucking lollipop?
Yeah, open your fucking mouth. Open your throat.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yes, open that fucking mouth.
Oh, yes.
Why don't you put some too in your fucking mouth?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Mmm.
Oh.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Please, sir.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes, put it back.
Oh my God, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
You're going to sink your own fucking cum.
Taste that your own fucking cum.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, thank you, sir, yes!
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
You're very fucking slow, huh?
Yes, yes.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck yes.
beg me for it
oh yes please sir
please
beg me for it
I can't hear you
oh my god yes please sir
fuck me more
oh yeah oh my god
oh shit
oh my god it is so good
thank you sir
Oh, my God.
Let me just turn up the volume.
You ain't going to come all over that?
I can't breathe.
You asked me before you came.
I can't hear you
beg me for it
oh my god please sir make me come
please sir make me come
oh yes
oh yes sir
thank you sir
Oh, my God, yes, yes, yes, sir.
Come on.
before. I want to hear you come.
Come for me.
Thank you, sir!
Yes!
Oh my god!
You had enough, huh?
Oh, please, sir, when you come, all of me.
Yes.
Oh, sir, please come for me.
Oh, yes, sir.
Thank you for that time.
Oh, please, sir, come for me.
Oh, I want to have you come.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, oh so good, oh yeah, thank you so much.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh come for me sir, please, please.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my god.
Yes.
That's a good girl.
Oh, eat that.
Eat that.
Yes, eat that.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much, sir.
Hey, so you had fun today?
Yes, it was great.
Thank you so much for having me.
You liked all the stuffed animals surrounding you?
Yes, the setup was really nice.
How did you like choke it on a pink flamingo?
That was quite a unique experience.
Was it? Was that first?
Yeah.
Oh, we did it first today.
See?
That's good. That's good. At least I got something first.
Hopefully it won't be the last.
No, pink flamingos in your mouth is a national pastime.
Yeah.
It's the American way.
Cool.
So what was probably, what was your favorite thing about doing this today?
You like that one the best?
What was like the hardest, maybe like least easiest one?
This is the hardest? Yeah. Okay.
And was there anything that you were worried about doing this year?
I was worried that you were gonna put it right on my clit. I saw that.
Yeah, so that was like my general reaction.
see you soon
alright
sweet