🎵
Action.
Tell me.
Okay.
Hmm.
Hi, uh, can you send Preston up, please?
Thanks.
You're as nice as you wanted to see me.
Uh, hi Preston.
Uh, please sit down.
Sure.
Uh, listen Preston.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
And it entails you watching a lot of porn.
Um, no, I don't think it's me.
I don't think it's me.
Well, it's coming directly from your computer.
We monitor all of our employees
and what they do with our computers.
So...
You know, sometimes I know I notice that things pop up,
but I just...
Well, I actually noticed you clicking them
so that they would pop up.
And you seem to watch a lot of a particular type of porn.
It's just a pattern, right?
It is.
I mean, it could be from the night crew?
Um, no, it's not.
But there's like, um, you know, like,
big-tittied office sluts,
or bang-your-boss floor,
or oh my god, those tits are huge on that desk.
And I just...
I just thought it was a little ironic.
It could be the janitor. I mean, I've seen him on my computer at night.
I think you know very well who's watching all that porn.
All that fake tape porn.
All those office sluts.
You don't actually think that that's how it goes, do you?
Big-titted bosses don't actually fuck guys like you.
Please, please don't fire me, I mean, I just don't, I really need my job.
Then you shouldn't have been watching so much porn.
You have a pretty nice cock, from what I can tell.
You do know that those movies are all bullshit, right?
Bosses don't fuck people.
Just wondering what it looks like under here.
Take your pants off.
I really don't think I should be doing this.
Um, it's okay.
I'm the boss.
The door's locked.
You really do have a nice cock.
And you don't wear underwear.
I wonder if it's because you whip it out so frequently.
Is this how you stroke it when you're at your desk?
Well, you have a really nice cock.
It's really nice. I'll give you that much.
With a cock like this, you could probably hook a lot of girls.
I wonder if you've ever had sex in public before?
No, you wouldn't do that.
Are you sure?
Not even bend over?
Katie?
Over your desk?
Not really.
Just once.
Okay, that's fine.
I don't mind.
I can feel whatever it is like brushing into your shaft.
Is this how they do it in the porn house?
That you haven't been watching?
Admit it.
You've been watching porn.
A little bit.
Office porn, specifically.
About big, tittied bosses.
Haven't you, Preston?
Yeah.
So you wanna fuck me then?
I thought about it.
That's a fair assumption, yeah.
Thought about doing what, exactly?
Just...
Just fucking you.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
What about, um...
Checking me out?
Mm-hmm.
Wow, you have nice balls too.
I don't know if you've noticed, but I've been doing this for a while now
I've been doing this for a while now
Sit down.
Are you sure we shouldn't be doing this?
Don't worry about that.
That's none of your business.
Sit down.
Are you sure we should be doing this?
Don't worry about that. That's none of your business.
I saw this in a porno once, I always wanted to do it.
It's like you're watching a porno, right?
Is this like your favorite porno?
Porno?
Does it make you feel like you're a fucking porn star?
You dirty boy.
Watching big tits on your screen all day.
I have to punish you now.
I'm going to torment you.
With my big tits.
Is that how you like it?
Oh.
Oh, that's nice.
I can't believe this.
It's your fantasy, isn't it?
Yes.
What you see in your head every day.
Oh, my God.
This is my fantasy.
You know you like that, you pervert.
Porn watcher.
In my time.
Oh yeah, pinch my nipple. Pinch both of them.
Do it while I pick your cock.
Oh, it can be pretty skanky too.
Oh, that feels so good.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my goodness.
Stand up.
Yeah.
Oh, like my pussy.
Oh my gosh.
Oh yes, that's good Preston.
Yeah right there, right there.
oh
yes
Yeah, Andres.
Oh, gosh.
Breathe.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Breathe.
Oh, yes, Preston.
Good.
Oh, God.
Oh.
I have to take the stitches.
Yeah.
Yes, pump.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Good.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, yeah.
You like that?
Yeah.
Is it just like your white fantasies?
Is it?
Can you hug me?
Oh, no, Jesus.
Oh, you feel so good.
Oh.
Oh, it's all so juicy.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, Preston.
Yes.
Oh, God, yes, please.
Harder, Preston.
Harder.
Oh.
Oh my goodness.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
Come on spank your balls.
Spank your balls.
Yeah.
Take a little charge.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, god.
Oh, my God.
Let's get this.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, god.
Come on.
Enjoy your ass's pussy.
You like that?
Yes.
Good.
You...
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
You missed.
Oh, my God, Ian.
Oh, yes.
Oh, Lord.
Oh, freedom.
Oh, that feels so good.
Oh, my God, that tickles, amazing.
Oh
oh
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Yeah, it's a field of fuckin' balls.
Oh, it's incredible.
Yeah?
Your wildest dream?
Oh my god.
It's my fantasy.
You freakin' fucking.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, Curly up.
Yeah, switch on and kiss him together.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, yes.
Oh, man.
Oh
Oh my god.
Sss.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, oh my god.
You fucking bastard.
Yeah.
Oh fuck me like in the porn movies.
Oh.
Oh my god.
You make me a porn star.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, God, yes, yes, yes, oh, my goodness.
Oh, please don't flip me like a dirty little porn star.
Uh-huh, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Oh, my God.
Ooh, ah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, shit.
Yes, yes, kiss my legs.
Kiss my legs.
Yeah.
Ugh.
I just wanna tell you.
Bro.
Tell you.
What?
Okay.
Ugh.
For fuck's sake.
Oh God she hasn't...
Oh no.
Oh my God.
No.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
No.
Yes.
Huh?
Oh.
Oh yes!
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, let me move her.
Oh, my God, yes.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, oh, yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh, my God, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh
yes
oh my god yes
yes yes yes
Oh my God.
Oh my god!
You...
Oh my god...
Ugh!
What the fuck...
Oh my god...
Oh fuck, oh my god...
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh my god, Forest.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh.
Oh, you want me to come?
You want me to come?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I'm gonna cry.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes.
Let me taste.
No.
Oh, yes.
Why don't you turn this way?
I just wanted to feel your cock in between my tits one more time.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God, it feels so good.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, God.
I'm so excited about your love.
Oh, look at his tits.
Oh, my God, I can't even wait.
Oh, my gosh.
It's making my mouth water.
These tits wrapped around your cock, don't you naughty boy.
Oh my god I'm so excited.
Ah.
Mm.
Oh, yes.
Ha ha.
Yeah, I want him to catch me.
He's a Chicano with his face.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes, you're cute.
Ha.
Ha, ha.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
I miss mom.
Does this mean you're not going to fire me?
No, you're still fired.
Now you're still fired.
you