Yo, I got this bitch, yo!
No, I ain't letting your ass go!
Take that shit off!
You ain't in control no more!
She ain't in control no more!
I don't know what you want to control right here!
No, you ain't in control!
We gonna take you out of your yard!
I'm sorry, but I love comebacks!
It's Angelina, baby!
Yeah, fuck her up, y'all!
What do you mean?
Oh, I got a comeback here.
This is really much trouble right now.
Oh, my God.
Turn around. Turn around.
Yeah, smack that ass.
Yeah.
Big music.
Bruise that hoe. Bend that ass over.
We ain't letting shit go.
We ain't letting shit go. Bend that ass over.
I ain't had pussy in three years.
I said a lot, I said a lot.
Oh, I want this asshole.
I want to take this asshole, yeah.
Oh, no.
Stop it.
Oh, my God.
Slut.
No, buddy.
That's the only kind of slut in my city, motherfucker.
Participate.
He's trying to suck some black dick, boy.
Your enemy gathered.
Nah, she ain't a warrior. She's a warrior.
You're on the dick block now, bitch!
You're on the dick block, bitch!
There we go, there we go.
Spillin' that shit, spillin' that shit, baby, spillin' that shit, spillin' that shit.
Open that mouth, I'll tell you why.
She's starting to like this shit.
Oh, yeah, hey, open your mouth, open your mouth.
I'm gonna spit in your mouth, spit in your mouth.
Ah, yeah, suck that dick, man.
There we go, there we go.
Brush your teeth for my dick, brush your teeth for my dick.
There we go, there we go, there we go.
You know, I'll give you some fucking nasty ass work, huh?
Yeah, you can jump on it.
Have me in prison for three fucking years treating me like shit.
Three years treating me like shit.
Now you sucking my dick.
Yeah.
Put your hands on some dicks.
Put some right here.
I stopped stroking.
There we go, make some convict music baby, there we go, there we go, good shit good shit,
Yeah, you little snow bunny hoe.
Beat her thing.
Look at this in your behavior, little bitch.
Hey, no, no, no.
Hold up.
Here's your graduation.
Shit, yeah, keep stroking, baby.
Keep stroking.
Yeah, I'm stroking it.
I'm stroking it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Keep stroking it.
Ooh, what do you mean?
Yeah, there we go.
There we go.
Perfect, yeah.
Yeah, keep your hands.
Keep your hands.
I can buy it, baby.
I can buy it, baby. There we go.
There you go. There you go.
Double shot, bitch.
Oh, shit.
Get in that motherfucker.
Go around. Go around. Go around.
Go around. Go around.
Yeah, you a snob, buddy.
Fuck that little snob.
Everybody.
Put that shit in her fucking ribs.
Oh, there we go, there we go.
Get in that shit.
Look at that Johnson & Johnson. Look at that Johnson & Johnson, baby.
You're talking dick and bollocks right now, you know what I'm saying?
You're talking dick and bollocks.
There you go, baby.
What is this?
What do you want?
Oh, my God.
Sherri and Kerry, we all haven't seen in a while, baby.
We all getting some today. We all getting some.
I got that dog shit in the way, in the way here.
I'm about to kick it up.
There's somebody going for the robbery.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, hey, hey.
What up?
Keep it quiet for a second.
Oh, it's been too long, baby.
All right, all right.
Oh, shit.
Listen up.
Here you go.
You don't want to hear your mouth no more, I'm tired of hearing your mouth, it's bullshit.
You like all these convicts inside you baby?
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit,
oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit,
I don't really feel like it, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me, feel me
Yeah, suck some dick, suck all the fucking dick, you snob, you suck all the fucking dick.
It's been too fucking long baby, you'll get it, you'll get it, all of today baby.
All that shit.
Shit.
Open up wide for that dick. Open up wide for that dick.
You're gonna put it down that throat. You're gonna get it down that throat.
I got a load for you, bitch.
Hold on, watch out.
Hold up. Suck his dick and fuck him.
Let's go you stupid white bitch, let's go.
Put her ass on fucking lockdown, put her in fucking solitary, get her, put her ass on
that bitch while we go.
Bitch, tell her bitch.
Keep gobbling that dick.
It's just the beginning, you're going to suck the whole fucking prison.
You're gonna fuck the whole prison when we're done with you.
Smack that shit, yeah, shrug that dick.
Yeah.
Squeeze that motherfucker tight.
Squeeze that motherfucker real tight, yeah.
You hear what he said? Squeeze that motherfucker real tight.
Real tight.
Big ass.
She's a little worried about some big ass titties right there.
Open that motherfucker.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
You nasty slut.
Yeah.
Don't you get the balls too?
Unless you get the balls like that.
Yeah, you don't get it, you shit.
You don't talk about me, you don't talk about Jack.
You don't talk about me, you don't talk about me.
You don't talk about me right now.
Here you go, baby, here you go.
There you go, ride that shit, there.
Ride that thing.
Yeah, there you go, pound that pussy, there you go.
Pound that pussy, there you go.
There you go, there you go.
Lock that bitch down!
Fuck this bitch ass.
Fuck this bitch ass shit.
There we go.
Oh my God!
I'm on the fucking jungle, baby.
I'm on the jungle, baby.
Keep fucking. Keep fucking.
You need some help? Keep fucking.
Get on that dick. Get on that black cock.
Get in there.
There we go.
Fucking nasty.
Holy shit.
There we go.
Choke on that shit. Choke on that dick, girl.
Choke on that dick. Fucking cum slack.
Snow bunny whore, let's go, there we go, you fucking nasties
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
There you go, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go,
there you go.
Oh my god, come on now, just let me go, I'll forget about this.
Nah, nah, you're going to get low, baby, you're going to get low right now, baby, you're going
to get low right now.
Get that shit, baby, get that shit, get that shit, there we go, ooh, shit, god damn, baby,
god damn, baby, god damn, get that shit, baby, that shit, get that shit, baby, there we go,
Take this...
Ugh!
Take that shit.
Take that fucking dick.
Ugh!
Take that shit.
Suck that motherfucker. Oh, it's still coming.
It's still coming.
Whew!
Bad motherfucking girl. Bad motherfucking girl.
But you're cute for us, though.
Eat every bit of that. Swallow that shit clean.
Come on, let's stop now.
I think it's time to get in this bitch.
Uh-huh.
She's talking double love.
Yeah, yeah, come on, girl.
Come on now.
No, please, guys, just let me go.
Forget about this episode.
There won't be any consequences for you.
Just let me go.
She's gonna take some more cum out of you.
You don't take some cum out of your mouth first.
Open up your teeth.
Get a little whore.
There you go, you little fucking white slut.
You ready?
You ready for this cum?
Let me know you're ready.
Put it in your fucking mouth.
That's what three years you gave my man right there, three years, that's three years of
Let him out, baby.
Let him get some more.
Convict me.
Give him some more of this pussy, baby.
Give him some more of this fucking piss.
Please convict.
Come on now.
Let me just go.
And we'll report this episode, please.
Bitch suck that dick.
Suck that dick.
This is our day, baby.
This is our day.
Suck that dick.
Look at those big ass titties.
Oh my god.
We got another cell coming down to get your ass nicks.
We got some more loads coming for you, baby.
Two years worth of loads, baby.
It's our day.
We fucking suck that dick.
Get that shit slim. Get that shit slim.
You like that shit, baby? Talk to me. You like that shit? Say yes.
Say yes with your mouth. Say yes. There you do. Yeah, you like that shit. There we go.
Somebody's getting there. Everybody share. Sharing is caring, baby.
Open that shit right up. Open that shit right up. Right there.
That's right. That's right. That's right.
You got Johnson & Johnson right now, baby. You ready for it?
There we go. Tell me you love your big cock in your mouth.
I love your big cock.
Say it in your mouth. Say it. Say it.
You gotta love your big cock.
Oh, there we go. Say it again. Tell me you love your big cock.
I love my big cock.
Oh, there we go, baby. Good shit. Good shit. Good shit.
Keep sucking that dick, baby.
There we go.
Keep sucking that dick.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Say it one more time. Say it one more time.
Oh, there we go.
There we go, there we go, that's a good spot, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, there we go, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
I don't want to be such a fucking slut.
Give me some more dicks. Come on, Jared's carrying.
Jared's carrying.
Ah, shit.
There you go.
Get your ass over here.
Get your fucking ass over here.
Oh, you little hoe.
You little hoe.
There you go.
It's not a fucking dance.
What's your ass?
It's harsh, man.
All right, don't get assed, baby.
Come suck his dick.
Get some ass to mouth, baby.
There you go.
Oh, shit.
Ass to mouth.
All the way down that throat.
All the way down that tooth, baby.
Turn that ass up some, baby.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Get that shit, Convict.
Convict Gang Bang, baby.
Convict Gang Bang, good shit, bruh.
There we go.
Get that shit, man.
Get that shit.
Knock that shit out of the park, baby.
Oh yeah, she's lovin' it, baby, she's lovin' it, get that shit, slim in the zone, baby, slim in the zone, look at that shit, baby, look at her mouth, look at her mouth, look at her mouth, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that shit, how that
Oh shit, oh shit, fuck baby, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit,
Oh shit!
Three years, baby, I'm telling you that.
Shit.
Sharon, it's Karen, baby.
I'm gonna put it in your mouth.
Ask him, my baby.
Keep sucking that dick, baby.
Ask him, Ralph.
You're so nasty.
Who told you you're so nasty?
Three years, baby.
Three years.
You're gonna put us in prison for three years.
I'm gonna fucking kill you, baby.
You're all dead.
Three years.
I'm gonna fucking kill some of his head.
You all are dead.
Turn around right here, turn around right here.
I think you're trying to fill her up.
Yeah?
Yeah, relax.
You're trying to get airtight with me?
What are you gonna do to me?
Watch that back.
It's about time we get the D.P. on that ass.
Keep fucking with me.
Get some of that shit.
Got it?
There we go.
Shit, there we go.
You ready for this?
Let's get air fucking tight, baby.
Air tight.
Air tight, baby.
There we go.
Shit, there we go.
Get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling, get a sling.
Oh my god, guys!
Here you go.
Here you go, shit.
Shit, open that ass back up, girl.
Open that ass back up, girl.
I'm ready for you.
Are you ready for me, girl?
Shit.
Shit, Aria.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he was on that hill slugging.
Puff-puff passing on your ass now.
You probably got something to worry about. Holy shit.
There we go, baby. There we go, baby.
There we go.
Shit, baby.
Turn around, sir.
Oh my god, keep fucking me, yes, there we go, oh yeah, just like that, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, right there, oh, stay on that tip, there we go, yes, there we go, baby, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes,
I'm gonna jump over there with you again, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson, Johnson
Here we go. Here we fucking go, baby.
Turn that shit up. Turn that shit up.
Turn this bitch up. Turn this bitch up.
Three years in the making, baby.
Nasty. Go.
Air tight this bitch. Air tight this bitch.
Here we fucking go.
You talk about all that shit for three years.
Now you're gonna say, shit, ho.
Nasty, ho.
Here we go. Here we go.
Fucking clean this shit off my dick.
Clean this shit off my dick.
Clean this shit right off my dick.
Yes, that's it.
Oh, you hurt.
Yes.
You made my dick dirty, make my dick get soft.
You make my dick hard again.
Open that mouth up.
Shrug it with your fucking hand.
Before I gag you over that one more.
Keep getting that shit.
I'm not getting that shit, baby.
That's a massive thing.
There it is.
Oh my gosh.
Messy bitch.
Oh yes.
There it is.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh shit.
She likes this shit.
ahhhhhh
it's right up my fucking
oh shit
shit
eat that shit up
you want some more?
here you go
a little more
there we go
yes
oh yes
Yes!
Make her shut up!
Ugh!
Yeah!
You know what?
I got you.
I'll make her shut up.
Put this in your fucking mouth.
Yeah, shut up.
Put this in your mouth.
Put this in your fucking mouth.
Air tight, baby.
Air fucking tight.
Oh my god, guys, please, if you come for me now, I swear I'll give you a deal.
No one else will be notified about this.
I can't believe what we just did.
Like, this is so bad.
I just want you to come with me.
I'm not picking you in the face with your pussy.
Yes, I just want to beg you to come for me.
Yes, give me that cup.
I want it all over my face.
You know, and that when you want to.
Yes, let me jerk off your cup.
That's a good sleep.
You ready for a sleep?
Right here. Open up. Open up.
Take that fucking blast.
Fuck yeah.
You're so fucking good.
Keep taking that back up for me.
Just take all that cum out. I got some more for you.
Yes.
Keep cumming for me. Yes.
You filthy motherfucker.
Oh my tits are covered in cum already.
Oh look at that.
Yeah, nice and fucking shiny.
Talk that dirty shit up.
Yeah, just say what you want.
I just want to fuck my pants.
Fuck my pants.
Yeah, I can pull over my tits and come on over my face.
Just wait and fuck you.
Look at that, my face is already covered in fucking fuck.
Take that.
I don't even know how many loads I took already.
I need more.
Take more.
Let me lick you all.
Oh shit.
Beautiful.
Oh yes.
My mouth is so fucking full it counts.
You're so nasty.
It's so fucking horny.
Which one?
I just love your
big black hacks inside me.
Oh
fuck yes.
You're like watching me play with my pussy for years after you fucked the shit out of it.
Here we go, here we go.
Just like that.
That's been three years baby, three years.
Fuck yeah.
It's like a drive, it's like a drive, it's like a drive.
Wow baby, god damn.
Yeah, I'm just going to scoop out where they come.
Yes.
Slap on it.
I'm gonna let you go last year.
Oh my god, I love your cum.
I think I need one more though.
Are you gonna let me go after this?
We'll let you go.
Yes, come on.
One last cum shot.
Let me see what you got.
Let me see this.
I don't want to take it all.
Me slut.
Biggest fucking slut in this prison.
Talk to my man.
Talk to him.
Oh, no, it must have been fucking hard for you.
Fuck you.
Now I'm all filled up with the spunk.
So what's the deal?
The deal?
The deal, I guess I'm going to have to let you go.
I mean, nobody can know that you fucked me.
Please don't tell anyone.
You won't tell no one.
Yes, I'm going to let you go.
You're going to be pardoned for this.
Yeah, you're going to get this convict beat down.
You got me this time.
Sure, no one's gonna know.
It's never happened, it wasn't even here.