Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.
Your father is ridiculous.
You know?
Yep.
It's just so annoying.
He's always doing this and it's like right at the last minute.
Like I'm starving and he's just like, oh, I gotta go to work.
It's like, who does that?
People work.
They make money.
Shit comes up.
It's like he doesn't even care about me or something.
Like, who doesn't care about their own girlfriend?
Makes me feel really unsatisfied.
You know?
Definitely. People at work, shit comes up. Sucks.
me like it's been ages since he's made me come
give me what that's like a big deal right I just yeah that's uh like I'm
your girlfriend and you don't even take care of me in the bedroom like the
it's kind of like between you guys that's like between me and him but he's
not here it's like you know I mean private information
no but I mean like I have to talk to somebody and he won't listen to me so
So like...
And I'm the one that you want to...
Your boyfriend's son?
I mean...
About coming?
You wouldn't do that to your girlfriends, right?
with you.
They forget stuff.
And they gotta come back and get it.
Your dad forgets stuff.
I don't think you would forget some really important stuff, though.
Yeah, like...
dinner.
Like, um...
Sometimes you just don't forget dinner.
Yes, dinner.
Or, um, maybe how to make a girl happy?
Um...
Yeah.
I mean...
You could probably make me very happy.
Yeah, um...
You know?
It's just a thought.
That would be great.
Dad's girlfriend.
You are my dad's girlfriend.
Follow the bouncing ball.
You are my dad's girlfriend. Stay away.
Okay, but um.
He's not here.
And all the more reason to have faith and trust.
Who is here?
Yes.
Son.
Your boyfriend.
I'll squeeze your boobs.
Yeah, just, that's it.
You don't have to go any further if you don't want to.
Okay, perfect.
That's it.
Great tits, Bob.
Thank you.
There we go.
Maybe like that a little bit.
Just do this.
Mm-hmm.
There we go.
I'm going to come from the other side.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, that was a great fucking test.
Okay.
Oh, good.
Hi, bad boy.
You're really fucking horny, aren't you?
What?
You're really horny.
I have knees.
Yeah.
Your dad never told you I'm a nymphomaniac?
Not really.
A little sex freak?
Yeah.
Didn't care to share that information.
No, he didn't.
You kind of look a lot like him.
Yeah.
He's a lot like him.
He is my dad.
I'm coming out of a gutter that I do crazy bad things.
I can't believe that.
I know.
You're coming out of there.
I know it's dead.
I know.
It's not my fault, it's the one that was supposed to satisfy me.
Oh my god, look at what a nice cock.
Oh my goodness.
Such a nice girl.
Don't tease me now. Put it in there. There you go.
That's it.
Don't you dare tease me.
That's it. Good girl.
oh
girl
that's it
oh
yes good girl
that's it
yes
mm
that girl
Yes, yes, yes.
Good girl.
That's it.
Oh.
Oh, good girl.
That's it.
Good girl, good girl, good girl.
Come here.
Come to me.
That's it.
Open your mouth.
Open the mouth.
Yeah.
That's it.
Hold still.
Let me fuck that mouth.
Yeah, let me fuck that little fucking mouth.
Okay.
Come here.
Good girl.
Yes.
That's it.
No, no, no. You keep sucking that in.
Yeah.
Put those fucking tits right there.
That's it.
Good girl.
Get in.
That's my coffee.
Can you give it to me, Ray?
What do you want?
Please, give it to me, please.
I want your Harcock.
Who's Harcock?
Yours.
My boyfriend's sons.
That a girl.
Between my big tits.
Can I have it, please?
Good girl.
That's a good girl.
You like being a naughty little bitch, don't you?
Don't act like you haven't thought about fucking me before.
Fucking my big tits.
I know you've thought about it.
You like that?
Nice and slow.
That's it. Squeeze it hard. Nice and hard.
Oh, yeah. You like that?
You like how that feels wrapped around your hard cock?
You like big, fat, juicy titties wrapped around you?
Oh, I know you do.
I know you've wanted them before.
I know you've thought about it before.
Does that feel nice?
Oh, my gosh, it feels good for me.
Spit it out. Spit it out.
Oh, let it grow, let it grow.
Oh, it's so hot.
It's so slippery.
It's okay.
Put it in that mouth, put it in that mouth.
Oh, what a nice cock you have.
Good girl, that's nice and slow.
Get nice and low.
That's it.
Let it grow.
That's it girl, arch it back.
There you go.
That's it, oh, good girl.
Come on.
Yes, now put it back in those tits.
Put it right back in those tits.
That's it.
Is that keeping your cock nice and warm?
Little chunky titties?
Is that what you like?
Is that your dad's slutty girlfriend?
Is that what kids are up to these days?
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, make it nice and hot.
and make it dissapear
Ah, I don't want to be naked.
Dad doesn't take care of me.
He just leaves me clothed.
In the longest bedroom.
What are you going to do to me?
Do you love my pussy?
Ignored pussy?
Oh god, dad never does this.
Oh my god.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
Get in there.
Get in there, little crumbs nice and wet.
Oh.
Oh, you're so hairy.
Oh, my goodness.
Mm.
So manly.
Ugh!
Oh my gosh, I'm touching so long.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, glorious.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh my gosh, it's sensitive, it's sensitive.
Oh my goodness.
Oh yeah, he's a nice, soft dog.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, you're so good.
You're a good boy, Jesus.
Oh.
So good.
Oh, I wish your dad did this.
Come here.
That's it.
There you go.
Oh, gosh.
Nice big thing.
That's it.
There you go.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Oh, God, yeah.
You pussy.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
God, yeah.
And you know what your dad forgot to give me?
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh yeah, oh my god, yes.
Do it, come on.
Oh my god, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Stare at my toes.
Give them attention.
Dad, give them attention.
You, you.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh my God.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm so sorry.
Oh my God.
You alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Go ahead!
Let go!
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Let go.
That's it.
Oh my God.
Oh my gosh.
There you go.
You're such a good boy.
Oh
Oh my god
Oh my goodnes my pretty pussy
Oh my god. Oh yeah.
Oh my goodness.
My precious pussy.
Oh my god.
Oh my goodness.
This chunky mini lips.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, yeah.
Oh my God, no it's end today.
Oh, you're bigger than your dad's car.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, you.
Oh
I'm here.
Where the fuck did those ghosts come from?
Oh my gosh, you...
God, you...
I see it!
oh
Yes.
Please, I can't breathe.
It's so cold.
Don't cry.
Oh, please.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, how could you?
How could you fucking hurt this kid just like that?
Just like that?
You...
Oh, you...
You punched my friend like that?
Oh...
Oh, you...
It's so good.
Oh
I'm so fucking dead.
Oh, yes.
Good job.
Ahhhhh.
Ahhh.
Oh, my God!
Oh, God!
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Yes.
Push it, push it.
Oh!
Yes.
Yes!
Ahhhh!
Oh my god!
It's been hard!
Fucking hard!
You already needed so bad!
Ahhhh!
Oh my god! Yes!
Oh
Oh, that's it.
Good girl.
That's it.
Yes.
Oh.
Good girl.
That's it.
Yes.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay, good boy.
Oh, it's okay.
Oh my God, yes.
Yes, you make it stick to these bones.
Oh, it's funny, yes.
Oh my...
Oh my gosh I feel.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Yeah, that's good.
Oh my god, yeah.
I'm so good.
Let's hear it.
Oh my god, yeah.
Look at that fucking cock.
Oh, oh, hmm.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Chef.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Oh my god.
Oh my...
Your little six leg...
Oh my gosh.
Oh god...
Oh my god.
Oh my...
Oh god...
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's so good, so good.
That's it.
Good girl, good girl.
It's okay.
I didn't get any sleep last night.
I'm so sorry, I just can't get school.
I don't know if you're going to get to school
and I don't know where you're going.
I don't know if we're going to get to school,
but it's just so sad.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Like I said,
Oh my God.
That's it.
Yeah,
that's it.
That's good for his feet.
Are you with me?
I can't f**king see my teeth.
It's so hard in between.
Oh my God.
I can't open it.
I can't.
Oh my...
Please I f**king can't open it.
I can't.
It's hard.
Oh it's so fucking hard.
I'm so tired.
It's hard.
I don't want to die.
Oh god, it's so fucking hard.
Oh, it's so bad.
Oh, my God, yeah.
It's so hard.
Oh, that's so hard.
Oh.
Oh, it's so hard.
Oh, man.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Girl.
Yeah.
Open it up.
That's it.
That a girl.
Oh, you're so nice.
Oh, fuck.
Good girl.
Fuck.
Oh, my god.
You should clean this up before your dad gets home.
Naughty America.
Nobody.
Does it better.