Another day, another day of work.
Oh, hey.
How are you?
Busy working.
I see that.
God, it's like you're constantly calling me.
Every day, though.
I know, but the pool needs to be cleaned.
Really?
The leaves fall from the sky and they fall into the pool.
Why are you constantly requesting me for it?
I have 300 other employees at my company.
Mm-hmm.
Um, because you do such a good job every single time.
The pool is always just so blue and it's really nice.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Okay.
You do a really good job at that flash.
Like, the water just looks so nice.
I try my best.
Yeah, and I love the way you hook your skimmer onto this, um...
What is this called? A rod?
Yeah.
A nice hard rod.
Yes, it's a rod.
That's a rod. That is a rod.
Some of things are rods.
Yeah.
I bet you have many nice rods at your company.
Yes, I do.
I do.
From your company?
Yeah.
Long and thick.
Oh.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah.
Well, um...
Well, uh, I gotta get back to work.
Oh, that's fine.
I'm, I'm just gonna sunbathe a little bit.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, that's great.
Really, every single day, unbelievable.
Oh um, oh Flash?
Hey Flash?
Hey, Flash.
Come here.
Yeah?
Yeah, come here.
What's up, what's up?
Um, sit down.
Oh, man.
Hard work, huh?
Yeah, yesterday.
I need this break.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just, I'm taking a break myself,
just laying down and tanning.
I'm gonna need to tan my breasts, though,
so I don't get any tan lines, you know?
Oh, wow.
What do you think?
Nice.
They're real, you know?
They're real 34Ds.
All these girls in this city have fake silicone breasts.
Yeah.
But not me.
They're quite a handful.
Very lovely.
Yeah.
I gotta get back to work.
It'll take a second.
Flash, please, just help me out a little bit.
going.
What time your husband calls?
Um, much later.
Later?
Yeah, he's probably at another state or something.
Okay.
Yeah, he probably needs another stain or something.
Here, it'll be fine.
OK, cool.
All right.
Let me take this off.
Oh, yes, just like that flash.
Oh, that's so great.
It's so silky smooth.
It's cool?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, you're so good with your hands, Flash.
It's incredible.
Oh, my God, yes.
I don't know, the sun's coming out.
What if I get burnt?
I got something to block that sun.
Yeah?
Something big?
Maybe a shade maybe?
Maybe we could go inside for a minute.
Oh my goodness.
It's huge.
It's a raspberry.
I knew it.
Oh my goodness.
It's so big.
It's so sexy.
Oh my goodness.
It's so big.
Oh my goodness, it's huge.
It's a raspberry.
I knew it.
Oh my goodness, it's so big.
So sexy.
Oh, yes.
mm.
Oh, that's such a big dick, oh my god.
I knew it.
Yeah, baby.
Have I ever shown you my, um, my guest house?
Not yet.
I want to show you.
Let's go.
Wow.
Mm-hmm. Not yet.
I'm so glad you can put your feet.
Nice and break.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, yes, baby.
Oh, yes.
Oh shit.
Hot!
Oh my God.
You've been tense before.
Pretending like you're just an innocent poor man.
Yeah, I remember that shit.
Oh my God.
Those big hairs around your big black eye.
Yeah.
Oh God, I'm so good.
Stay right there.
Oh my God, yes baby.
Stay right there for Natasha.
this?
Are you gonna eat it flash?
Oh fuck, eat it flash.
Oh my god, it's so big.
Oh god, it's so fucking big.
Oh my god.
Oh yes.
Yes, you do.
Oh.
Oh, baby.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, good you.
Oh, yes.
Time my ass off like, please.
Oh.
Oh, good, you know what a good wife is.
Yeah, you do.
Oh, yeah, you do.
I have
baby.
Oh, gosh, here it comes.
Oh, my God.
You're so sexy.
Here, take baby.
It's so big.
Oh my god, it's so fucking big.
That's it baby, that's it baby, that's it baby.
That's it, baby. That's it, baby. That's it, baby.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
My whole pussy.
Oh, shit.
Oh, he's growling at me.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, make me nervous.
Yeah, make me come here every day.
Fuck, yeah.
You cheap whore.
Oh no!
Oh shit!
Oh yes!
Oh my goodness!
Oh God!
That's so good!
want.
Yes, yes, oh my god, it's so pretty.
It's so pretty.
Oh, yes.
Clap, clap, yes, make me a little more,
make me a little smile, oh my god, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh, fuck.
Oh my God, that's huge.
Oh my God, it's fucking huge.
Oh my God.
It's huge.
Oh my god, it's fucking huge.
Oh my god, it gets so big.
Oh my god, Ian.
Oh, you always fuck little sluts like me
with your juicy flesh.
Oh my god.
Fuck you.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh my God, oh please, fuck me harder, Flush, fuck me harder.
Oh my God, yes, oh, oh, fuck, oh,
you wanna be rough with me?
Yeah, fuck you, fuck you rough with me.
Oh my God, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, it's so big, it's so big, can I taste it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm,
It's so big, it barely fit down my throat.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
This baby, my baby, yes.
Oh!
Uh-huh, oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I'm sick of your ass now.
You, oh, fuck.
Rest in peace.
Ooh, ah.
Mm, yes.
Get back in there.
You, oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, you.
Oh my god, yes!
Oh my god! Oh my god! This is fucking big!
Oh fuck! You stretched me out so much!
Oh fuck! Fuck!
Oh shit! Oh shit!
ah
someone got excited
someone got fucking excited
oh
fuck
oh my god
oh
oh god yeah
ah
oh
fuck yes
Oh my god, that's so fucking sad.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh fuck you.
Oh fuck.
What is that?
Are you trying to mean it?
Yeah, but then ask me, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, it's so big.
Oh my god, I've never had a big dick in my ass.
I've just had little white dicks in my ass.
Oh my god, you're so big, Flash.
Oh, shit.
I can do it.
I don't want a fucking dick in my ass.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, fuck you.
Fuck you.
You...
Mmm, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, go...
Ahhh!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck, yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Search that asshole!
Oh my God, yes!
Oh my God, it's in.
I've never had such a big dick in my ass before.
Oh...
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, Flash!
Flash, you're so big!
Oh, shit!
Yes, yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh my god, Flash!
Slow it down!
Oh, shit!
Meow!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, you like that?
Yeah, you like that.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Okay.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, yes!
Yes, oh my god.
Fuck yeah!
Fuck!
Oh fuck.
It's a fucking big dick!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Oh fuck, it's so big.
Yes, baby.
Give me some more.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, baby.
It's so big.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Mm.
Oh my god, my ass tastes so good off your dick.
I was one to taste it off your cock flesh.
I had no idea it was so big.
I love you.
Mm.
Oh my god, oh fleshy pussy is so good.
Please don't take that away from me, Flash.
Oh, you have no idea how much I've wanted it.
I knew that they liked it when my husband is away.
Oh, yes, yes, like that, Papa.
Like that, Papa.
Oh
Okay, oh my God, it's so big.
I've wanted you for so long.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, you're gonna take it away from me just like that?
Come on, after all I've done to get you to fuck me?
Oh my God, you give me more than that, yes.
Oh my god, he had to flush.
Oh god, please.
I'm so sorry.
Come here.
Yeah.
Do you want me to taste my ass?
Come here.
No.
I'm hungry.
You want me to taste my ass?
Mmm.
I just want you to taste my ass.
That tastes so good.
Mmm.
Yes.
That tastes so good.
They help you.
Mmm.
Fuck you.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Yeah, here it comes.
Ahh...
Um...
Oh my God.
Ayy.
Why don't you make sure you come over tomorrow, okay?
Why?
Yeah, the pool needs to be cleaned.
Oh my god, just clean it.
No, it needs to be cleaned again.
Oh my fucking god.
And why don't you make sure to bring over a few friends, okay?
Just make sure they're black.