DEMONIC VOICE
Hi!
Hello, madam.
How are you?
I'm doing good, madam.
That's nice.
Aww, you're here too.
Yes, madam.
Your name is?
Damien.
Damien, and you're Buffy.
Yes, madam.
Yes, okay.
Hi, how are you?
That's nice.
Well, I am so excited
because today you guys are gonna watch me fuck two big balls.
Oh my, and they are so delicious.
Aren't you guys excited?
Yes, madam.
Two inches have you grown?
Anyways, and you oh you're wearing a thingy
That's good
Anyways, so that's the first surprise
Yes, ma'am.
Can you sound more excited because this is putting me to sleep?
Are you ready for an amazing cuckold session?
Yes, ma'am.
Good, very good.
Stop staring at my tits.
My eyes are up here.
Okay.
Now, back to that sex.
You guys are actually getting laid today.
For real.
For real, you're actually getting laid.
I know you've been wanting it for a really long time.
Right?
Yes, ma'am.
How long?
A really long time.
And how badly have you wanted it?
Very bad, ma'am.
That's great.
Yes, ma'am.
How long?
A really long time.
How long and how badly have you wanted it?
Very bad, ma'am.
That's great.
You're definitely going to get it today.
Definitely.
Oh, I see you guys salivating at the mouth.
That's really great.
Good.
Be grateful.
Because you guys are gonna fuck her!
Hmm.
Yeah!
Isn't this what you've always wanted?
Yes. Yes, ma'am.
Yes? Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am. That's what I thought.
She has a mouth.
You can fit quite a few fingers in there.
And she even has
pink pussy
with tiny little bumps inside and a really big asshole.
So you guys can double penetrate her.
Anyways, we'll just do whatever I say,
but as you can see, she's a little limp,
kind of like you two.
So you're gonna blow her up.
Yes, ma'am.
I didn't say you would blow her up.
You're gonna blow her up.
Yeah.
There you go.
I know you like to blow.
Blow harder, Bucky.
Good.
Keep blowing.
Not bad, huh?
You're going to get some too, don't you worry.
And keep blowing.
I'm going to have to kill it till I get here.
Oh my.
Oh my goodness.
It's really filling me up.
Hmm.
It's pretty good.
Okay, that's enough, stop.
You, I want you to blow.
Take her gloves.
Good job.
Why don't you come here and suck her face?
Okay.
here and suck on her fingers.
And as I stop, I don't care about your lung capacity.
OK.
All right, and when she's full, obviously you
stop and you plug her up.
All right, well, I think this little girl is horny.
Aren't you?
Who wants to fuck her mouth?
Come on, just pretend it's mine.
Who wants to-
Come on!
Somebody- How about you?
Okay.
Get hard with that thing.
And then you're gonna stand up,
and you're gonna put it in her mouth.
Okay...
I know this is why I don't fuck with white boys, but...
Um, the faster the better, you know? I have some friends coming over.
That's bad.
How horny she is.
Just pretend it's me.
Come on, quickly.
And you,
can you watch?
See, I told you you were going to get something today.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Does that feel good?
Yes, ma'am.
Mm-hmm.
You're a good job at this.
You are?
Mm-hmm.
You should be a good job at it.
There you go.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Come on.
Harder than that.
See, this is why you don't walk around.
Yes, ma'am.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take care of her.
You like that asphalt?
Yeah.
You're going to be black soon.
Are you ready?
You're welcome, by the way.
Thank you, ma'am.
You're welcome.
Keep going.
Oh, is that tiny little bit hurting her?
A little bit, ma'am.
Great.
You guys are super bright.
Are you ready?
Yes, ma'am.
Stop!
Cut it out.
Wow, looks like it's kind of sharp.
Stand up.
He gets both because he's taller, that's how tall he is.
Look at her face.
Her face looks like you mean it.
That's not realistic. Hold her knees down.
You didn't come inside her, did you?
No, I didn't.
No.
Look at me when I clean your face up.
You didn't come inside her.
No, I didn't.
Look down.
Okay, now harder.
Harder.
This is not interesting at all.
Yeah, really make it better.
Harder, harder, this is not interesting at all.
Yeah, really make her get up.
And you squeeze her ass.
Spank her.
She's a bad girl.
Yeah, she's a bad girl.
Yeah, spank her and tell her she's a bad girl.
You're a bad girl.
Yeah, tell her she's a huge super slut.
You're a huge super slut.
Okay, and say it with feeling.
You don't care about her.
She fucked all your friends.
Squeeze her. Put your thumb in her ass.
Put both thumbs in her ass.
Spread it.
Yeah, there you go. Not bad, not too bad.
I think we're excited.
This is the best pussy you've had all year.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, you can come inside or I'm out if you want.
Well, you probably can't, but...
Okay.
This is kind of boring, guys.
No offense.
Um...
Well, listen, the bulls are going to be here soon, so stop.
Stop.
Are you calling yourself a what?
Why don't you guys lick my holes a little bit?
How about that?
Why don't we rock, paper, scissors
for who gets the ass and who gets the pussy?
Go.
You're the man.
That's two out of three.
No, never mind, you win.
You get my, you get my asshole out.
Go.
And they're gonna be here pretty soon,
so you better warm me up fast.
Yeah, you guys are good warm up for the bulls.
Yeah, warm me up.
Warm me up for the bulls.
Like warm.
This is cold.
Warm me up.
Really?
Like put your face in that.
Put your face in that.
This does nothing.
Keep warming me up for the pulls.
Come on, keep going.
Uh-huh.
Keep warming me up.
Never mind.
You, eat this.
Yeah.
Okay, you mean you can do it warm?
Okay, my clit is like an inch and a half higher,
higher to your left.
Okay.
Oh, wow, wow.
I mean, I'm just like wondering what shit this is.
Oh
They were leaving me kind of cold though, you can do your fucking job
It's all for us?
Yeah.
It's kind of what I think you guys are going to have.
Oh my gosh, you guys are so big.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, yes, I'm so glad you're here.
I know you don't want to hit my face.
Oh my gosh.
Fuck, yes.
The fuck you looking at?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, fuck this shit, man.
Look, I don't give a fuck about him.
I don't give a fuck about him.
You look at my dick, I'm going to fuck you up.
He's going to fuck you up, Damien.
Don't move me my balls.
Fuck this whole camera shit, man.
Fuck that shit.
We ain't doing none of that over here.
That's nuts.
You like that?
You're such losers.
Oh my God, you guys are so big.
Yeah.
Keep your eyes to yourself, too, over there.
See you over there trying to pee?
I'm going to fuck you up.
I'm going to knock him out.
Calm down.
We got it.
What?
Do not fuck with my balls.
Chill.
Oh my.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh my God, it's so big.
It's so big.
I love it.
I love serving you guys.
You're big cups.
Yes, Black Daddy.
Yes.
You know what? Come here. Come here, Puffy. Come here, Damien.
I just want to show you guys what real men are made of.
Look at this. And look at this.
Oh, my God. And look at this.
What is that? Oh, my God.
Now this. This is even more pathetic.
Oh, little guy.
Oh my goodness, you're a fucking strong chick.
Oh fuck, I'm the luckiest girl in the world.
Too close, get back to your fucking point.
Sit down.
Yeah, you're too close.
Hmm.
Oh.
Oh my.
My turn.
My turn, my turn.
Your turn?
Yes, come on.
You can get it in there.
Oh.
Yes.
That's big.
You okay?
Yeah.
It's not good.
What are you guys gonna do to me?
Dance.
Yeah.
It's a good answer.
I like that.
Yes.
Look at that.
Let's just wear it all day.
It means it so badly.
Yes, it does.
Yes.
Yes, baby.
Yes, everybody.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes, it's going to be.
It's a sexy little kiss.
It's real tight.
Open that mouth up for me.
Thank you very much.
Oh my God.
You're going to get loose up in that mouth.
Oh my, that's a lot of dick.
Don't fucking cry.
Yeah, that's a lot of dick.
You listen, right?
Yes Daddy yes please.
Yes please Daddy.
Oh fuck yes!
He's that dickhead in the back of that bus.
Yeah.
Oh my God it's dope.
You better understand that mother fucker came mother fucker.
Mother fucker came I'm gonna fuck you up.
Ok?
Oh shit.
Oh my God, it's so deep.
That's a lot of dick, huh?
Okay.
Let me see.
It's open?
Your mouth is open?
Yeah.
Oh, I want to feel that whole dick.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It's so deep.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Now bend it over for the home run.
My way.
My way?
Yes, black daddy.
Oh, God.
Open that up for me.
Arch that back.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
Fucking look at that.
Turn your head over there.
Look at that.
Oh, yeah.
Turn your head over there, look at the wall.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
We're going to keep this up.
And they must be paying bills.
Yes.
That's all they're good for.
So big.
Yes, baby.
She got some arms and neck like that.
Oh, she nasty.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good.
It's so big in there!
Oh god, oh god!
Yes!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh my god!
Oh god!
I want to taste it, can I taste it?
Open it, open it!
Oh yeah, swiveling that mama.
Come on, what are you doing with me?
What are you doing with me?
That guy?
Yeah.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
You're gonna taste this black dick?
Yes.
I don't really care if you do or not.
What you gonna do?
Oh.
Oh my God.
Whatever he wants, spread this on our asses.
Whatever he wants to do.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, he in the house.
Take it.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
How tight is it? It's good.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh.
Oh, my God. Can I touch this?
Yes. Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes, oh my God, that's real thick right there.
Yes, yes, oh my God, ah, ah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes!
Ahh!
Yeah!
Yes!
Kid, open your mouth.
Open your mouth.
Oh, yes!
Yeah.
Yeah!
Oh, good!
Ahhh.
Yes!
Oh, yes!
Yes, oh my god!
That's awesome.
Yes, yes, yes, ahh!
Oh, yes, yes!
I'm proud of you for winning.
Yeah.
I got the pool!
Oh my god.
I love you so much.
It's so cool.
Oh my God, that's all so big.
It's all my fault.
Oh, ah.
That's me, that's me.
Oh, she is, lady.
Yeah, she is.
I can feel my dick moving in her ass, huh?
You good?
Yeah, you good?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm gonna freak you.
She'll be in my face.
I can't anymore.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Mm, mm, mm.
Oh, my.
Personal ball licker.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, baby.
Hey, don't forget him.
You want a taste of this?
10 years later.
I don't care.
Now lick your lips with it.
No, like you love it.
Lick your lips with it.
Laugh.
Now swallow it.
Swallow it.
Good.
Keep your hand behind your back for the rest of the day.
Oh yeah, Rico, fuck her in the ass.
Can you put that in my ass, Black Daddy, please?
Good girl.
Do anything?
Yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Good girl.
Oh, yes.
You know how to talk to her.
Yes.
Good girl.
fucking hands like that yes
Don't move.
Do not fucking move.
Arch that back for me.
You poke this fucking asshole.
Just like that.
Yeah.
Straight butt fucking.
That's it.
Beautiful fucking music.
You better not be fucking standing.
Back up, motherfucker.
Back up.
Back up motherfucker
Make him feel it and watch.
He's jealous.
Yes, yes.
Please fuck my ass.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck yeah.
He's jealous.
Oh god, yes.
Oh, that's so good.
Yes it is.
Oh my god, it feels so good.
Kiss it, Jess.
It feels so good.
You better look at her and not me, homie.
Oh my God, it feels so good.
Come over here.
Right here, that's it.
That's it.
Right here, too.
You looking at me, motherfucker?
Stop looking at him.
Hold on.
If you fucking catch him again, I'll beat your motherfucking ass.
It's all pasty now.
Yeah, it's pasty now.
Fuckin' hoes.
Shit.
Hey, why don't you guys double-stuff me?
What do you think?
Ask us.
Will you please double-stuff me?
Please?
I did a good girl.
Okay.
Oh
Yes, it's so big.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
God damn.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
You fuck him, and I'll fuck you.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
It's so big.
Good.
Shake that fucking ass, motherfucker.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It's so fucking big.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Yeah, I'll go back in.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
What is this?
Oh my God.
Oh, my God!
Yes, come here.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
No cuckolds.
It's almost time for dessert.
Are you guys ready?
You better not be looking at me.
Don't look at them.
You bet.
Man, get on the ground.
Turn around and put your head towards the seat.
Oh, my God.
It's a tornado drill.
Come here, puppy.
It's almost time for some yummy dessert.
On your fucking knees.
Yeah.
Good.
Get away from him.
Yeah, get away from him.
You're not worthy, puppy.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Let me see those pretty fucking eyes.
Oh, shut the fucking cunt up.
Yes.
You hear that?
Shut the fucking door.
Yes.
Oh.
This ring was fucking pretty cheap.
No.
You're stroking this fucking dick when you suck, huh?
Yes, daddy.
You like pleasing us, huh?
You do?
Yes, I love pleasing you.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it feels so fucking good.
You like daddy, don't you?
Yeah.
I want you both to come in my tent.
Yes, I want you both to come in my tent.
Please.
I want you both to come in my tent.
Spit.
Spit on this.
Good girl.
Oh.
Yes.
Such a big love.
Oh, yeah...
Come on, baby.
Yes, yes...
Yes...
Oh, my God.
Thank you, Lord.
Thanks guys, you can go.
Buffy, Damien, come here.
Come here, I have something for you.
I haven't given it to you yet, don't be dumb.
You, lick that.
She's actually gonna do it.
Lick it?
can try do it finish that put your whole tongue on it slurp it
And quickly, please.
It's mostly down here.
Oh my gosh.
Like you mean it.
I know you're just passing little slaves, but I mean like you mean it.
There you go.
Eat it.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, go get your girlfriend.
Yes, ma'am.
today.
Thank you for your mouth, your ass, and just being here today.
Thank you for letting me fuck your mouth
And thank her for her asshole.
Thank you for your asshole.
Good, good. Not so bad.
Well, bye!