I'm so glad you've decided to try our new massage business, Mrs. White.
Why don't you lay back and let me know if you need anything.
Thank you. You have no idea how much I've needed this.
Thank you.
Ah!
No, no, not like that.
I'm so sorry.
I just basically watched a bunch of videos on the internet.
Oh my god, you're a sham. I'm going to report you.
So if you put your hand just down.
Oh, you're down there.
Oh, that's really good.
Yeah, right, right there.
Just down here.
Oh yeah, that's good.
That's where I need it.
Yeah.
Oh, this is so much better.
Oh yeah, that's good.
Yeah, this is much better than what you were doing before.
Yeah, like down like...
Are you fucking serious?
This is so unprofessional!
It's an advanced technique I learned.
I don't know what to say.
Look, I'll just go ahead and give you a refund.
No, you know what?
Yeah.
Yeah, massage those big tits.
Yeah, that's right you fucking pervert.
You gonna show me some more of that advanced technique of yours?
Yeah, you better massage them nice and well.
What kind of online videos are you watching?
Naughty America.
America.
What?
Brazzers.
Don't stop massaging them.
You should use that advanced technique on these tits.
Yeah.
Rub that cockle over there.
Yes, baby.
Yeah.
Let's see if it's pretty too.
Mmm.
You're gonna help me relax?
Yes, be right.
Yes.
That feels so good.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, my God, yes.
This is so fucking good.
So good.
Mm.
oh fuck you better give me when I came on here for
Oh, fuck, that feels so good, oh, yes, oh, now you're doing it right,
Oh, fuck.
I'm massaging everywhere, huh?
Mm, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Fuck, yeah, I should've, you know what I mean?
God, fuck, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, oh, fuck, oh, oh, yeah.
Oh my God, oh, that's pretty true, is there anything else?
Yeah, mm, oh, fuck, yeah, fuck those feet.
That's so good.
So fucking good.
Stick that fucking ass up.
Stick that pretty ass up.
Oh, fuck yes.
cook feels so good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Mm, mm, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, give it to me, fuck, yeah.
Mm, fuck, oh, yes, oh, my God, fuck.
Yeah, I feel so good in my little pussy, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh fuck
Oh my god
You're cooking so fucking hot inside me
I love it
Oh fuck you
Oh yeah
Let me slip around
Let me slip around on you
Yes
Yeah
Put that cock inside me
Fuck
Yes!
Oh fuck!
Oh yeah that's it!
Oh my god!
Oh my god your fucking
cook feels so good.
Fuck me from behind.
Yes.
Fucking take me.
Give me that fucking cook.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
that fucking ass on my cock.
Yeah, yeah, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck, yes, oh my god, that fucking cock feels so good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
That's strong, yes.
Oh, I can feel it getting harder, yeah.
You're so good at that, baby, you can do this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
it's revolutionary
and you know what
if you don't mind
I'm going to come back next week