Shhh, you gotta be extra quiet.
She's right there.
Yeah, man, she's fucking...
She's fucking super hot.
Wow.
She does this shit all the time, dude.
Yeah, I see her profile.
She has, like, a secret profile, like, online.
And she's always posting fucking shots like this and shit.
That's why I called you over so you didn't spy on her ass, man.
I wonder, like, where...
I'll tell you later.
Okay.
I'll send you a link.
Nah, she won't.
She always leaves her fucking window open.
I think her titties are like fucking 38 fucking triple Ds or some shit.
All natural, too.
Look at her titties, bro.
They're fucking huge.
Wow.
I'll just put this in my spank bank, you know?
I can jerk off to it later.
I'm so nervous.
Oh, look at those panties.
Wow, look, dude.
She's fucking hot, man
Yeah, that's my
Yeah, oh my god
I've always had the hots for her
I don't give a fuck, she's my stepsister
She's so fucking hot, dude
My god, bro
I love that, man
She's so sexy, man
Look at that ass, look at those titties
Fuck
Nah, nah, don't, don't
Let's not get caught
I don't know, her window's wide open
You think she sees us?
i'm so embarrassed right now
Is this your friend?
This is my friend, Logan.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
This is my step-sister, Angela.
Nice to meet you.
So, yeah, we should leave.
No, you can stay.
I really want to turn him on.
I want him to be good.
So I'm thinking like, do you think this angle is good?
Yeah, it fucking looks amazing.
What if I go like side angle?
one like where I pull it down so then you kind of get like the the sexy
decolletage and what do you think journey like that I honestly I kind of
Your advice.
What about if I...
No, I know.
You look amazing.
Trust me.
Oh, my God.
I mean, like...
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Oh, okay.
Hmm.
Wow.
Well, maybe...
Wow, that one's a good one.
Yeah.
What do you think?
I mean, let me see.
I mean, that's...
I think that looks...
That looks hot.
Yeah.
Right?
I think we should definitely send that one.
Wait.
I feel like maybe it would look better if I was just, like...
oh my god
you mean like that
okay yeah
we definitely
gotta go
we should go
don't go
please stay
I need
I need help
I really need
Angela
you're like
you're my stepsister
this isn't right
come on man
let's go
no stay
seriously
it doesn't
like
really it doesn't
bother me
you have a boyfriend too
I mean
I know
your boyfriend doesn't
he wouldn't mind
I'm taking selfies
for my boyfriend
okay like
I'm being really
that's a really good
girlfriend thing
how big are your tits oh they're actually 32 double g's double g's yeah
but i just want the right angle i was wrong by three letters
oh did you get triple d's you should have just gone through my laundry
No, I'm not going to do that.
Oh my god.
That's what I would have done.
time?
Like if I do, if I really twist I can get ass and side boob.
Oh my god.
Is that good?
Wow.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Or maybe it was just better before.
Oh, you know what?
Like maybe if I can like pull it together and like really squeeze them.
What do you think?
Or do you think that's too much?
Is that trying too, too hard?
I don't know, but I mean, what if, what if, what are you talking about?
Why would they find out?
You're taking fucking nudes in your room and we're in here.
You know what I mean?
I don't tell them about your personal business.
You're not going to tell them about mine.
He's going to get fucking pissed.
He's not.
I'm taking selfies.
I'm not taking photos of you.
And plus, it's like, I don't know why you guys worry so much.
what do you think hey baby I can't wait to do these big tits on you mmm
boy no no no no no I don't think so I mean I wish I would love him to come
Really like my selfies that much?
Okay, I need to see how much. Oh
My god, Tony, are all your friends this big? I don't know don't ask me
If it's that big, oh come on
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
Do whatever you want, man.
Do whatever you want.
You should be encouraging your friend to show off his assets.
I mean, it's fine, I guess.
Come on, I see.
Oh, my God.
What?
Is that real?
Really?
Oh, wow.
I am going to have to take a selfie with this fucking thing.
Shh.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, shit.
Okay, let me get my phone.
Let me get my...
Yeah, okay, just...
yeah stay like that all right i want to look at my like tips looking hot
oh my god oh oh can i touch it can i like this is happening oh my god
oh my god my boyfriend's gonna love this really
if you say so
wow what the hell
is this real where did you get this
oh i was just born with it
oh my god it's so nice
mmm fuck it's so big fuck legion oh my god I fucking love it oh my god
Wow. I am so impressed by this.
I like your titties, though.
Oh, do you?
Yeah.
Would you like to feel them against your cock?
I would like to feel that, yeah.
That looks so sexy.
Rub it on that nipple.
It's fucking hot.
And the other one.
Yeah, I love the way you grab them
yeah yeah really squeeze them look at that I can even my nipple
yeah you want to suck on that one too
No, you've got to do the boob drop.
Don't you know?
The boob drop.
It's like...
Yeah, that's fun.
Do it.
Go ahead, play with them.
Make them clap.
Oh, yeah.
I like that.
It's like a round of applause.
You're fun.
You should take your clothes off too.
Yeah, yeah do it hmm. I'll just tease you with these big tits
Wow, you want me to bounce them around your cock? They're so much fun. I
Like just sharing in the joys of my tits
sit down
you know what I'm going to do
I'm just going to like get my tits
all shiny and oiled up
they look so good
watch it drip down
doesn't that look good
looks fucking great
let's put some on your cock too
yeah
oh shit
Oh yes. Let's get that cock all lubed up. All oily.
Oh fuck. Nice and shiny.
Look at that. I can't make that big dick disappear between there.
That's never been done before. Wow, that looks amazing.
Yes. Look at that. Hands free titty fucking.
Holy shit.
Dead?
Gross.
Jiggle him around that dead.
Honey, you're just so talented.
I like to have fun with them.
If I was you, I would do the same.
I love the way just the head pops out like that.
Yeah, it's such a tease.
You like my top?
Yeah, it's so nice and big.
that's great in between your tits too though i think so wow
and i like look at that you can like carry that big titty
it's like a kickstand for your tits
Oh shit.
I jiggle around.
This is blowing my mind.
This is the first time that's ever been done to me.
Wow.
Well, I'm glad I could be the first.
Let me see if I can like balance it on there and just jiggle it.
I can't talk.
Let me get serious.
Yes
Wow, you're so fucking hot
You can squeeze it as hard as you want you're not gonna hurt that monster
Maybe we should try it.
Yeah, I want to see how this cock feels inside me.
Really?
It's so nice and big.
Come and stretch out my little pussy.
Yes, come over here.
Oh, fuck yes. Stick it in me.
I want that big dick in my pussy.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, it's so big.
It's big.
Oh, wow.
Your pussy is nice and tight, too.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
I guess every pussy is tight to you, there.
Oh, that's true.
With that big dick.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
That feels so good.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
I can't do it.
My knees are fucking thick.
Yeah, let me back it up on you.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you making my big tits bounce, too?
Yeah, that looks fucking good.
Yeah, can you see it from there?
I can, yeah.
I like that a lot.
Oh, my God.
Wow, they're fucking big, baby.
I want to come on that dick yes
oh there we go those big tits are bouncing
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck. Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you wanna see these big tits bouncing away? Fuck me.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I want you to stay right there. I'm gonna flip to missionary.
I am really glad to see these big tits bouncing.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, make those big tits bounce.
Oh, yes.
Look at those fucking tits.
Me too.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
I love the way you make them bounce.
Yeah?
Yes.
Me too.
You're slapping me right in the face.
Oh.
Mm, probably won't play with them.
Yeah, I don't like those big tits.
Mm, mm.
Mm, mm, fuck.
Oh, yeah, let me spread those pussy lips for you.
Look at that.
Oh, I want to see that, too.
Yeah, you want to see that?
Yeah, spread.
Can I have a taste?
Yes, please.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Oh my god, your dick is so fucking big.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god, oh, he's sucking some bones.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh shit. Yeah, it's just like bouncing everywhere.
Wow.
Fuck.
Fuck yes.
Yes. Oh yes.
Oh fuck yes.
up on top of you?
Come here, I want to ride you, well, let me taste myself, bangbros.com.
yes, oh, my God, your coat feels very good inside me, fuck, oh, fuck,
oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, oh, shit, yeah, oh, fuck.
Fuck.
I'm gonna take you for a ride.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
oh my god i can see it go in in this
Watching it love it
Oh, I love watching you go in.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
You want to get on top of me, okay?
Yeah, I love that.
Mm-hmm.
You want to have these big titties in your face?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god that felt so f**king good
Yes, yes, yes
Ow
F**k yes
Put it back in
Oh my god
Yes, am I f**king crazy with that coat?
Yeah, yeah
F**k yes
yeah oh yeah oh let me tease you with that pussy
mmm oh yeah I feel it stretching out that pussy while I take it
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, come on, give it to me again, like you did.
Give it to me, yeah, like...
Oh my God, it's so good.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Let me grind on it.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, would you come fuck me in Michigan?
Yeah.
Yes, come on in here.
Won't I be able to look at you like that again?
Oh, yeah, slap it on my clit.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, it looks so good.
Oh, yes.
Yes, oh my God, I would love to taste your cum.
Really?
Yeah.
You want it?
Yeah, I want it.
Yeah, you've got a nice big life for me.
I hope so.
Yeah, I'm gonna taste it.
Oh shit, yeah, you can make me.
Yeah, here's your fucking cum.
Yeah, oh my God, yes, give it to me.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm,
Oh, your cum tastes so good.
Fuck.
That was amazing.
I'm going to get some of my tits.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Get it all.
You're amazing.
I want every last drop.
I want to swallow it all up.
Please do.
Please.
This is sexy.
It tastes so good.