I
Hey babe, how's it going?
So much paperwork to grade, there's just so many of them.
I'm stressed out babe.
I know, but your students really appreciate everything you do for them.
Oh, thank you.
You let me worry about the final details about the wedding.
The wedding?
Fuck.
Oh, I'm just so swamped with work I completely forgot, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I know you've got your hands full.
You're the best.
I got it.
You stay here.
I can see you've got your hands full.
Thanks.
Who the hell could that be?
Honey, look who's here.
Hey.
It's one of your students.
Hi, professor.
What are you doing here?
Remember, silly?
Unless you guys get to work.
Make yourself at home, okay?
What the fuck are you doing here?
I told you, whatever we had is over.
Honestly, professor?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
What are you doing?
My soon-to-be wife is in the next room.
Get the fuck out of here.
Alright.
I just figured since I'm graduating next semester, maybe we could...
Did you miss these big tits, Professor?
Oh, yeah, I know you did.
Oh, you bad boy.
Creating papers, are you?
Sure you are.
I really hope she doesn't catch us.
Oh, we'd be in so much trouble.
She doesn't have breasts like I do. She's not as much of a slut as she.
Oh yes, no one's as big of a slut as your slutty student.
Yes.
Come on, don't show me this face.
She's so old.
I need to get in there.
I'm going to suck in these pigtails to get you up.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Breathe.
is he sleeping?
Is he OK?
Is he going to sleep?
Is he going to sleep, OK?
Yes.
Oh, don't be mad at me.
No.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
No.
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh my god, yes, that's so good.
Oh yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Enough.
Oh, this is real.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Yes, yes, yes, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
No.
No...
Yes...
Oh my God yes
Oh...
Oh sh...
Yes yes yes
Oh my God, this is so funny.
I'm so worried, guys.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yes.
Oh, you're just figuring that out, you slutty pussy.
You're a figure, you're a slutty student.
Come on, you're a slutty student, oh my God, yes.
Honey! Is everything okay in there?
Yeah babe, everything's fine. I just, uh, got my hands full over here.
Okay.
You think you can come to my house and just get fucked?
Teach me a lesson professor.
I can't keep it.
I'm so jealous of you.
You're a bad girl.
I'm such a bad goldfish.
Ooops!
Aargh!
Aaargh!
Waaargh!
Aaaargh!
Aaargh!
Mmm!
Mwa...
Ooops!
money
Ha ha ha!
Oh, I knew you'd miss us, yeah.
Talking about your fiance.
Oh, you little fucking slutty stupid.
Yeah, oh yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, Professor, yes.
Yes, Professor, yes, yes.
oh my god, yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Ah!
Ooh!
Mm!
Mm.
Mm, this is cool.
Do you want some more?
Okay.
Give me, give me, give me.
Oh, Mrs. Scott.
More, more, more pizza.
I'm not going to let you go.
That's very kind of you.
You're so nice.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, slap that dick on your face.
What?
Yes, professor.
Yes.
Oh, that's what the professor likes.
Yeah?
Yeah.
The professor?
Now suck on the head.
Just the head.
Fuck.
Fuck that one now.
Nice and slow.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
All...
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh...
All the way...
Ah...
Ohhh, that took a bit long.
Good student.
Ugh.
Oh, that's a good student.
I'm really gonna miss the wedding this call for you.
I miss it so much.
I'm really gonna miss it.
Play with your pussy, I'm gonna take my pants off.
Yes, please.
Please.
Oh, girl.
Spread that asshole for me.
Spread an asshole, professor?
Spread an asshole, please.
Spread an asshole.
Spread that asshole for me.
Spread that asshole, Professor?
That's a good girl.
I'm so excited now.
It's ok, it's ok.
It's ok...
Nighty Nighty...
Oh yes, you're gonna test me...
You're so good, Professor.
I'm just saying that's below my table.
You pervs.
Yes.
You should just go.
No, I'm going to go to my pictures.
I'm going to go to my pictures.
Yes, yes.
Ah.
It's okay, you're all right.
It's okay, okay.
It's okay.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, oh.
Oh, my God.
Everything's good here. We're all good. Bye
Soap me those tears.
There she is.
That's my new birthday.
Happy birthday.
I love you.
Oh no...
Oh yes...
I think it's this...
Oh...
Like, yes...
Oh yeah...
I see what I'm trying to...
Oh no...
Oh...
Oh my God, yes, this is what I needed so badly.
Oh my God, yes, this is what I needed, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, baby.
You want that dick?
So good.
Yes, yes.
Fucking pay for it.
Please give it to me.
Fuck.
Good girls, Cassie.
Oh, yes.
Just a little bit more, just a little bit more.
Yes.
He's right there.
Okay.
Right there.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh yes.
Please.
Oh my God.
I need him so bad.
It's so bad.
It really is.
Oh my God, it's so good.
Oh, it's so good.
I can't believe I slept in a used car.
Now I'm trying to keep a cool head from the desert.
Mm.
It's so wet.
So wet.
Oh my god.
It's so good.
You're so good to me, you're so good to me, so good to me.
Oh my god, yes.
You can't do this to me.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Please.
Oh my god!
This hurts so bad.
Stop.
Anto, come get his eyes.
It hurts so bad.
You're making it all so much easier.
Oh my goodness.
I'm going to touch my nose so much.
Yep, feel that, feel that sweating.
Oh yeah, feel that sweating.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, oh, yes.
Oh, I'm getting sensitive.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh my God.
My blood is so swollen for you, Professor.
Yes, oh, it's here.
Oh, fuck, I don't know where it could be.
Oh.
I'm so sorry, it's so wet.
Oh, shit.
I don't even get to get to my white couches.
Oh, my white couches.
They're so cold.
Please I need to sleep.
Oh, yes.
Oh my goodness.
It's so good.
Oh my God.
I can't help it.
I can't help it, it's so good.
Oh, it's so good.
That's not my fault.
I'm gonna get you someone better, yes?
You're gonna be all right.
You're gonna be all right, okay?
I'll get you.
Please help me out. You never want to fuck me anymore.
Yes.
Oh, I'm such a fool.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Put her back in there.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yes.
Perfect.
I love you.
Yes.
You're gonna get a little sick.
But it's too late.
It's too late.
Oh, it's you.
Oh.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
It's so funny.
Oh my God.
I was gonna cry.
I don't like it.
I can't.
Move.
That's it. Make the professor happy.
Yes. Make the professor happy.
Be a hard working student.
Yes.
You say it's so good.
Oh God. Oh God.
It's so good.
Oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's so amazing, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's crazy, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Yes, yes!
You like that, you like that, you like that.
Oh my God, you like that!
Being a good little student.
Oh.
Listen, just.
Here.
Just leave me alone.
Ooh.
Aw.
Just be nice to me.
Ooh.
Anything you say!
I know.
Ooh.
Just.
All.
Is it good?
Oh my god.
That's so good.
Oh my god, that's so good.
Oh my god.
That's so incredibly...
Yes.
Oh, perfection.
Oh
Oh!
Oh!!
Ha ha ha!
Oh!
You've just got a little extra credit there.
Yeah, I got a little.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Yes.
I mean it.
Let me break a shit out of this.
Oh!
Ha ha.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh!
Ha ha!
Ha!
Oh my god!
Oh, my feet hurt.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
That's fucking deep.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes.
All right.
Let's put your weight on me, baby.
Yes.
Yes, Professor.
Just like this.
Drop it, girl.
Yes.
Oh, God.
It's so good.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Mom, Please let me go
I want to go home
I'm trying to go home
Sweetheart
I'm begging you
Yes!
I can't stand this, it's so good, it's so good.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, yeah, attack that, attack, attack,
Please attack me, please attack me, I'm still in your sleep.
Oh, yes, please attack me, yes, oh god, it's so good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh my god, oh my god, oh.
Auntie Massey, mommy's home.
Oh yeah, come here!
Let's meet now.
Come on, cowboy, let's meet.
Oh.
Nobody's home.
There's nobody, there's nobody here.
Nobody's home, come on!
Yes, he is.
He is.
I can just see him.
He must be somewhere.
Come on.
I can't sleep.
Oh, God, yes, yes.
Oh shit, oh shit.
Oh my god, it's so good.
It's so good.
Oh my god.
It's the best.
That's it.
Take it.
I'm scared.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
She's here.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Hey babe, what do you think about...
Oh.
What the fuck?
Babe, I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
No, let me explain.
Oh my god, the wedding's off!
Let me explain.
Wait, let me explain.
I can explain this.