I already told you, I'm just getting mimosas with my girlfriends.
I don't...
No, it's fine, I told you it's fine.
Let me guess, uh, the husband?
Uh, maybe.
Oh, okay, just a little bit, okay.
Just a little bit.
Okay, so what mimosas can I help you with today?
Um, you could actually help me with some interracial mimosas.
Oh, okay, so you're like IR?
Yeah.
Okay, IR section. We've got a big, big section on IR.
Yeah? A big one?
A big one?
A big one.
Exactly.
Just like that.
Right over here in the corner.
That's our section over here.
Just follow along over.
Let's see.
Hold on.
Let me check this out.
Oh, sorry.
I was fixing the DVD that almost fell.
Yeah, right here.
Over here.
This is our video booth.
No, no, no.
Right here.
This is some other stuff.
These ones don't matter.
Oh, dog farts.
You know about the dog fart.
Oh, my God.
That's huge.
Look at that glory hole initiation.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God, that's huge.
Look at that, glory hole initiations number 21.
Wow, that's messy.
One of our bestsellers, one of our bestsellers.
You wanna check that out in the viewing booth?
Back here, you can check that out.
The viewing booth?
Yeah, the viewing booth.
What's a viewing booth?
Yeah, this right here, we can watch the videos
on your own in here.
We can watch the videos on my own?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, you can get in here and watch the video,
get a little sample.
I can watch the video here?
Yeah, that way your husband will never know
what you're doing.
My hair. No, not this one. Lucky number seven, everyone loves lucky hair.
Lucky number seven.
Yeah, lucky number seven.
Okay.
Yeah, your husband will never know, but you will have a nice, nice day.
Wow.
This place is weird.
Come inside.
Oh, a black dude comes here?
What?
Wow.
What are all these stains?
Porn?
Oh my god, there's porn out.
Wow.
Is it not racial porn?
all day.
Whatever.
Okay, whatever. You really need to stop calling me, by the way. Okay, bye.
God, it's so hot. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
What? Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Black tape goes here.
Oh my god.
I guess.
She's saying I look stupid.
Yeah.
Is that what you want?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm Natasha by the way.
Wow.
I'll just do one more of this.
Oh
Me I told you I'm having a momoto
The drinking one right now, I've got to go bye
you know what we are gonna do is we are gonna drink this
and then we are gonna take it home.
again, I'm gonna make it for my boyfriend
because he probably won't be a funny person
even with the funny look.
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm just gonna make it for my boyfriend.
He is gonna be a bad person,
he's gonna be a bad person.
I'm gonna make it for him.
I tell you what my brother's gonna do.
hmm
wow
wait
hmm
oh my god
wow
Oh my god, balls get through your tooth?
That's not...
Holy shit.
ah
mm
Oh my...
Oh my god, oh you guys, this is so exciting.
You know what those are?
Can you guess what that is?
So much spit.
Does anybody eat this?
I'm not a big fan
Kissing
No
What?
Kiss
No
Oh my god.
Should I fuck this?
I think I want to fuck this.
I can fuck this, right?
Oh my god, I can totally fuck this.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh my God, oh wow.
Oh shit that's big.
Oh my God, that is so much bigger than my husband.
Wow.
Oh my God.
Yes! Oh, honey, yes! Oh, we're getting excited!
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh, fuck, yeah!
Oh, honey!
Oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Come back, come back!
Yes! Yes!
It's so big!
so big.
in my ass?
Oh my god, oh my god, yes, ah, ah, ah, fuck.
Oh my god, that's huge, that is huge, oh my god.
So much bigger than my husband.
Oh my god, yeah, oh yeah, you like asshole, don't you?
Yes, you do, oh fuck, fuck yeah, oh my god, oh yeah.
right there oh fuck oh my god
yes yes oh god that's so great oh shit oh my god yeah
yes yes yes use me through the wall oh yeah
I'll use all these holes, please, please.
Oh, oh, oh, yes, use my holes.
Fuck, yeah, oh, God, stretch out that nice ass, mom.
Yes, oh my God, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, oh my God, you know what, though?
You know what, though, mister?
I wanna taste this ass, mom.
You stay right there.
You stay right there
Oh
Oh my god, so good
Oh, you don't even know
I wish you knew
Thanks for watching me and my office work viral Youtube videos!
Oh my gosh!
That is so good!
Oh my god, that is so good!
Thanks for watching and comments and loves!
Have a great day and see you tomorrow.
Bye, bye.
Show this video and give me 5000 likes.
Awww.
Ahhhh.
Yes.
Oh God I want more.
I want more.
Oh my goodness yes.
and like how much you call but I'm great. I am so great.
Okay, sweetheart. Bye.
Oops.
Ah.
uh-oh
ahh
hmm
Oh my goodness, it's so filthy in here.
God, I can't believe I put my feet on this filthy floor.
Um, I don't know what I'm supposed to do with this.
I don't know what to do.
Oh my god.
Oh my goodness.
My feet are probably dirtier than my shoes right now.
Okay, what else do we have?
What do we have?
Hmm
Huh?
Okay
Hmm
Huh?
Oops
Okay, that's not good.
Um...
That's not what you said.