It's really bad.
Really bad cramp.
I must be really dehydrated.
Are you okay?
Hey.
I just had a really bad cramp.
Where? In your leg right up there?
Yeah, just right here.
Do you have any water?
Oh, you know what? I don't have any water with me.
I might have some in my car.
It's really bad.
I just feel like I didn't drink enough
and I got dehydrated, Ronnie.
Do you mind if I rub it out for you?
Sure, anything.
Okay, come here.
Thank you.
Are you taking your vitamins, protein and all that?
You're running pretty fast up the hill there.
Have you seen me before?
Yeah, you ran right past me. I was sitting on the side taking a break.
Oh yes, I feel so much better.
Thank you so much.
Nope.
Oh gosh.
No problem. Sure.
It's good?
Yeah, thank you so much.
Thank you.
Can you help me up?
I want to see if I can walk.
Yeah, sure, sure, sure.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Oh.
Actually, it still really hurts.
Really?
Oh, man.
There you go.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, no problem.
Yeah.
Phew.
So yeah, I've come in.
This is me.
Nice.
I like it.
Yeah, thank you so much for coming.
Do you want a glass of water?
Maybe we can exchange numbers so I can send you a thank you card.
Yeah, that sounds good.
You've been so nice with me.
Yeah, I mean, no problem.
This is funny.
Down for water.
That's right.
In the kitchen, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah. So you want some water?
Thank you!
Feel better?
Oh gosh, I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
Okay.
So do you mind
waiting for me here for like five minutes
when I go upstairs fresh or not?
I just feel so sweaty from before.
Yeah, yeah, I'll wait here.
Are you sure? Yeah, I can drink my water.
I'll be five minutes, I promise.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Chad?
Yes?
Can you please come upstairs?
I need your help with something.
Yes.
Okay.
Hey, uh, ooh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was just wondering if you...
Yeah, here.
Oh, you're so silly right now.
With a nice gift.
A gift?
Yeah.
I saw the way you were looking at my tits before
Fuck yeah
Do you like playing with them?
Yes
You don't mind, do you?
No
Okay, I like to play with them too
Come on, nipples are nice and hard, alright?
Yeah
yeah I like this gift system yeah I can do some chores
You want to see me play with that?
Yes, yeah.
This is what I was doing with my foot.
Let me see your legs.
Yeah.
My leg is not hurting anymore.
I don't want it.
Yeah, it's fucking nice.
Yeah, just push your booty back a little bit.
Just like that.
That's fucking so nice.
You can jiggle it.
Mmm, yes.
That looks good.
Mmm.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's so fucking hot.
That's fucking nasty.
Yes.
Is it looking me on the teeth?
Fucking mistakes.
Yes.
True?
You just keep fucking looking at me.
That's it.
I'm so fucking hot.
Yes.
That's it.
Why?
Why is those fucking tits on my balls?
It's so fucking hot.
Damn, you're fucking nasty.
You're so fucking...
Yes.
It's so f***ing hot.
That's it.
Yeah, just come here.
Just f***ing touch it.
That's it.
There you go.
Oh, look at me.
That's it.
Thank you.
I want you to come to my mouth.
What are you doing?
Oh, thank you.
So cute with those fucking teeth.
Let's just rip them all off.
Keep sucking them.
Keep sucking that duck and then do a
smacking tail on that cat.
Yes.
Let me see those eyes.
That's it.
Oh, that's fucking cute.
Good girl.
Yes.
That's it.
Now lick it again.
So big and hard for me.
Where's my tooth?
Look at it.
It's so furry.
Oh, my dear dog.
I don't know if you're a dick or what, I think it's like that.
Yes.
Let's see what I need.
That's it.
Yes, give me those fucking tits, deal with those tits.
Put it under my license.
Fucking dirty tits.
There he is.
That's a dirty tip.
I feel so freaking good.
I'm a bit ticked.
I want more.
I'm so freaking wet from your dick.
You're gonna see.
I'm gonna stretch on the side of your pussy.
Yes.
I'm gonna take you right into your cock.
Up and down, just like that.
Yes.
Mmm.
I'm gonna turn you on.
Yes.
Keep saying it.
Mmm.
Gosh.
I want me to throw in your balls.
But they're full of slime.
Mmm.
You're ready for me.
You've been cutting and slapping all over my tits.
I can't taste anything anymore.
Good girl.
Cut those tits again, cut those tits.
Yes, nice and high.
Yes, put them together.
Do you like it when I squeeze them together nice and tight?
Yes.
Yeah.
That's it.
Yes.
Please, it's a hug.
You wanna fuck, don't you?
I can't wait to try your cat.
You want to?
Yeah.
In the right heart.
In the right.
I'm gonna put it in his hug.
Sweet.
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to have to say something.
I'm watching you play.
I'm like, fuck.
Fuck, you're dying.
I'm going to push you in the back of your ear.
Push me in the back of your ear.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
It's so hard for your dick.
Yes.
You're such a fucking novelist, man.
Get that acid in the air.
That's exactly what I want to see.
Yes.
Acid.
Goddamn.
So fucking nurturing.
Make love to that dick.
That's it.
Yes.
That's it. Come get on top of me.
Get on top of me.
People will say I'm right, but you're a dick.
That's it.
Oh yeah.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh shit. Yes. Yes.
Oh
Oh shit, I'm so tired.
Oh my god, I'm so tired.
Oh fuck, I'm so tired.
I'm so tired.
Oh my god, he has a little coat over his head.
Oh, my God.
You should try it right there.
Yeah.
There you go.
Just like that.
So good.