Yes, ma'am.
Can you sound more excited because this is putting me to sleep?
Are you ready for an amazing cuckold session?
Yes, ma'am.
Good. Very good.
Stop staring at my tits.
My eyes are up here.
Now, back to that second surprise.
You guys are actually getting laid today.
For real.
For real, you're actually getting laid.
I know you've been wanting it for a really long time.
Yes, madam.
Oh, that's great.
You're definitely going to get it today, Nellie.
Oh, I see you guys salivating at the mouth.
That's really great.
Good.
Be grateful.
Because you guys are going to fuck her.
Yeah.
It was what you always wanted.
Yes, madam.
I'm waiting for these big balls
Why don't you come here and suck on her fingers?
And then say stop.
I don't care about your lung capacity.
Okay.
Well, I think this little girl is horny.
Aren't you horny?
Who wants to fuck her mouth?
Come on, just pretend it's mine.
Who wants to- Come on! Somebody-
How about you? Okay. Get hard with that
thing. And then you're gonna stand up
and you're gonna put these- Mmm, okay.
I know this is why I don't fuck with white boys, but
but the faster the better, you know?
I have some friends coming over.
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah.
Just pretend it's me.
Come on, quickly.
And you, can you watch?
See, I told you we were gonna get some today.
This is why you don't work with me.
Yes, ma'am.
We're gonna go home.
Take care of her.
You like in that asphalt?
Yeah. Yeah.
you're welcome by the way
thank you madam
are you ready
yes madam
stop
I think it's kind of shrunk
Stand up.
He gets low because he's taller.
You didn't come inside her, did you?
No, I didn't, madam.
No?
Look at me when I pull your face up.
You didn't come inside her.
No, I didn't, madam.
Look down.
Okay, now look at me.
Harder. Harder. This is not interesting at all.
Yeah, really make her get up.
And you squeeze her ass.
Spank her. She's a bad girl.
Yeah. Spank her and tell her she's a bad girl.
You're a bad girl.
Yeah. Tell her she's a huge super slut.
You're a huge super slut.
Okay, and say it with feeling.
You don't care about her.
She fucked all your friends.
Squeeze it.
Put your thumb in her ass.
Oh, fuck you.
Put both thumbs in her ass.
Spread it.
Best pussy you've had all year.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
You can cum inside her mouth if you want.
Well, you probably can't, but...
Okay.
This is kind of boring, guys.
No offense.
Um, well, listen, the bulls are going to be here soon, so stop.
Stop.
Are you calling yourself or what?
Why don't you guys lick my holes a little bit?
How about that?
Go.
Best of three.
Never mind, you win. You get my...
You get my asshole out.
They're gonna be here pretty soon, so you better warm me up fast.
Yeah, you guys are good warm-up for the bulls. Yeah, warm me up.
Warm me up for the bulls.
Like, warm. This is cold.
Warm me up. Really. Like, put your face in that.
is like an inch and a half higher higher to your left okay
this show's sexy yes you're already ready for us
Do your fucking job
Oh, yes, I'm so glad you're here.
Yeah, that was a good one.
It hit me in the face.
Fuck, yes.
The fuck you looking at?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, fuck this shit, man.
Look, I don't give a fuck about him.
I don't give a fuck about him.
You look at my dick, I'm gonna fuck you up.
He's gonna fuck you up, Damien.
Don't leave me my bowl.
Fuck this whole camera shit, man.
Fuck that shit.
We ain't doing none of that over here.
That's nuts.
You like that?
You're such losers.
Oh my god, you guys are so big.
Yeah.
So much bigger than that?
Yeah?
It smells so good.
Oh.
Keep your eyes to yourself, too, over there.
See you over there trying to pee?
I'm about to fuck you up.
I'm about to pee you up.
Hell yeah, man.
I'm about to just knock you out.
Calm down.
We got it.
We're going to handle this.
What?
Oh, OK.
He just said that.
Do not fuck with my balls.
Chill.
Oh my god, it's so big.
You love serving us?
I love it.
I love serving you guys when you're big cops.
Yes, Black Dad.
You gonna stop my fucking dick?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, come on.
That's how you control the woman. Back up.
Oh, my.
Hold on. Listen.
You know what? Come here.
Come here, Fluffy. Come here, Damien.
I just want to show you guys
what real men are made of.
Look at this.
Oh, my God.
What is that?
Now this. This is even
more pathetic.
Oh, you don't cry.
This big fucking strong dick.
Fuck, I'm the luckiest girl in the world.
Too close, get back to your fucking point.
Sit down.
Yeah, you're too close.
You tired?
Yeah, come on.
You can get in there.
Yes.
That's big.
You like that?
Yeah
No fucking problem.
Yeah, that's a lot of dick.
You listen, right?
Yes, I listen.
Yes, I listen to daddy.
Yes, fuck daddy.
Yes, please. Oh, fuck yes.
It's that dick hitting in the back of that pussy.
Yeah.
Oh my god, it's dope.
You better not be staring at my fucking bitch, motherfucker.
Don't talk about that camera.
I'm gonna fuck you up.
That's a lot of dick, huh?
It's open?
Your mouth is open.
Yeah, slow.
Oh, I wanna feel that whole dick.
Oh my god, it's so cheap.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, damn.
Oh my goodness, now bend it over for the homer.
My way.
Yes.
Black Daddy.
Open that up for me.
Or step back.
That's it.
Good girl.
Yes.
What the fuck you looking at?
Turn your head over there.
Look at the wall.
Yes.
What the fuck?
I didn't even keep this up.
They must be paying bills.
Yes.
That's all they good for.
Oh, my God, it's so big.
Yes, baby.
She got some arms in that black thing?
Come here.
Oh, she nasty.
Yeah, that's good.
She white-booted.
Yeah, we're a little weird.
I got to ask you, you know, Mommy.
I get up.
Yes, Dad.
Yes, Black Tag.
You'll never know how that shit feels to make a bitch run from a dick.
It's so big in there.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah, swiggle in there, mama.
What are you doing?
Hi.
Sit down.
That's right.
I'm going to taste this black day.
Yes.
I don't really care if you do or not.
I'm going to taste something.
What you going to do?
Roll.
Yes.
Whatever he wants.
Spread this on his ass.
Whatever he wants to do.
Yes, oh my god, that's awesome.
I can feel all my holes.
Oh, she airs it.
Oh, yeah, she is.
I can feel my dick moving in her ass.
You're gonna shake your other hand.
I can't anymore.
Personal ball licker.
Yes, baby.
Look at that.
Don't use your hands. Take those hands off. Good girl. Take those.
That's my little sled.
Don't forget him.
You want to taste some of this?
Tang your sled.
I don't care.
Lick your lips with it. No, like you love it. Lick your lips with it.
Just swallow it.
Swallow it.
Good, good.
Keep your hand behind your back
for the rest of the day.
Yes.
Oh yeah, Rico, fuck her now.
Can I bring this?
Ask me.
Can you put that in my ass, Black Daddy?
Yes.
Do you want anything?
Yes, you know how to talk to me.
Yes, my buddy. Yes.
Oh God, it's so good inside my ass.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes.
I love my fat ass.
Don't move. Do not fucking move.
Arch that back for me.
You poke this fucking asshole just like that.
Just like that.
Straight butt fucking.
I'm gonna get one that'll make you mad.
Your check is there.
Let me check this one.
Fucking hell, I'm fucked up.
Complete.
Yeah, nice.
Clean that shit up.
Shrug that pussy while you suck in that dick.
You know who to give it to.
You're next.
Keep looking at that ground. Don't look at her, look at the ground.
Open your mouth.
Yes.
Oh my god, yes.
Make him feel it and watch.
He's jealous.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes, please fuck my ass.
Oh my god.
Oh god, yes.
We'll be here.
That's it.
Right here, too.
Right, motherfucker?
You looking at me, motherfucker?
Stop looking at him.
You fucking catching me?
Hey, why don't you guys double stuff me?
What do you think?
Ask us, girl.
Ask us.
Will you please double stuff me?
Please?
I'm such a good girl.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
I just hit you.
Yes, it's so much dick.
You're going to take all of it?
Yes, I'm going to take all you give me.
Pack it up.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
I'm going to fuck you, and you fuck him.
Okay, okay.
Oh, fuck, yes, that's so good.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
God damn.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Now, you can fuck him, but I'll fuck you.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, it's so big.
Yes, you make my day tingle.
Oh, yes.
You know I like it back there, you know I like it back there.
Yes, yes.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Yes, come here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yes.
Just like that.
Oh, my God.
Yes. No cuckolds.
It's almost time for dessert.
You guys ready?
You better not be looking.
Don't look at them.
Man, get on the ground.
Turn around and put your head towards the seat.
Tornadoes are at home.
Come here, Buffy.
I'm sorry.
On your fucking knee.
Yeah.
Good.
Did you get hurt?
Yeah, get away from him.
You're not worthy, puppy.
Yeah.
Let me see those pretty fuckers.
Spray those fucking pretty jerks.
No.
You're stroking this fucking dick on yourself.
Yes, sonny.
You like pleasing us?
Yes, I love pleasing you.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh yes, such a big one.
Oh my God, he got it all over my face.
Oh, fuck, yeah, man.
I have so much.
Fuck.
Get out of my face.
Just cover my face, buddy.
Oh, yeah.
Cover those tits.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes. Oh, my God.
Thanks, guys.
You can go.
Hey, Damien.
Finish that. Put your whole tongue on it. Slurp it.
Let me see. Okay, good.
Now you guys have deserved. You guys have earned this.
And quickly, please.
It's mostly down here. Like you mean it.
I know you're just passing little slaves,
but I mean like you mean it. Thank you.
Thank you for your mouth, your ass, and just being here today.
Okay.
Thank her for her service.
Thank you for your service.
Okay.
Thank you for letting me fuck you.
Because I'm worthless and nobody else would fuck me.
Good job.
I'm worthless and no one else will fuck me And thank her for her asshole
Thank you for your asshole Good, good, not so bad
Well, bye