Oh my god, you scared me.
Are you new?
Um, yes.
Hi, I'm Natasha.
I just started a few days ago.
I'm Charles, and you're still new.
Welcome to the office.
Thank you, Charles.
Hi Natasha, I just started a few days ago.
I'm Charles, and you still new. Welcome to the office.
Thank you, Charles.
You know what Natasha? You were really, really hot.
Um, thanks.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Um, what are you doing?
I'm just giving you a big warm welcome.
This is crazy. What if somebody walks in? We're at work.
Natasha. Natasha, Natasha, Natasha. Don't you worry about a thing.
Okay.
of schedule.
I don't know about that.
I think I'm going to need those numbers by Friday.
You got it, boss.
Wow, those are nice.
Her name is Natasha.
I know, Charles.
I'm the one that hired her.
I need those numbers by Friday.
Let me see it, let me see it, let me see it, let me see it.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes, my only good children.
Yes? Yes?
Sweet. Feed them to me.
Feed them.
Oh, that's so funny.
Shh.
Let me get this off.
Get your face in there.
Fuck you.
I need to get that pussy.
Oh, God.
I mean, I'm not gonna see.
I can't see just like that.
No.
Mmm.
You see?
Oh, oh, yes, yes, yes, oh yeah, I like that.
Oh, oh, I can't stop my pussy with your fingers, stop me.
Yeah, ah, ah, ah, fuck, yes, oh, I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it anymore, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, fuck.
Oh, yes, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Yes!
Ah!
Mm-hmm.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, keep thinking in there.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Oh.
Big cleanse.
Do you like how big my clit is?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, so good.
Can you show me that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Shhh.
Shh.
Oh my God.
Oh yes.
Oh, Sasha, I need those copies.
Uh...
These copies are good.
So you're settling in then?
Oh, um, I'm trying.
Well, good.
I'm glad you're fitting in.
I have lots of male co-workers for you to meet later.
Yes, that's it.
And hang your head off, a little this way.
Sure.
This is how we do it at the office.
Okay.
Yes.
That's very brave.
We call it Vic's Office.
Okay.
Oh, that's helping a lot.
Oh.
All the way down.
Here we go.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Impressive for a new girl.
I can feel that pussy clamp down every time.
Nice work.
Can I throw it?
There it is.
Awesome.
Let's do a nice smooth walk here.
There it is.
Oh
Mmm.
Good girl.
Look at that ass.
Oh fuck.
I'm going to have a seat, why don't you come sit with me for a minute.
You look like you're gonna get it.
It's so pretty.
It's so nice.
Not as pretty as you.
I'll give you one.
Oh.
Oh, we're down, yes.
You think it's ready for you to sit on?
You think so?
Oh yeah.
That's what kind of sucker you are.
Holy shit.
Right there?
Oh my god.
That's such a nice day.
I like soccer. You are.
Holy shit.
Right there?
Oh my god, that's such a nice day.
Oh, man, that's good.
Oh, it's a grind.
Yeah, it's a grind.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh my god, yes.
This is so good.
I'm so good.
Oh my god, yes, this is so good.
It's so good.
Please make sense.
Yes.
Oh god.
I can't breathe.
Oh yes.
Yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh
Whoa.
This is creepy.
Ah.
231 what?
Yes.
Turn.
Ah, ah, ah, oh, ah.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, god, I can't.
Oh.
Fuck yes!
That cockack.
Yes.
Oh, here.
Oh, fuck.
You, you, you, you!
Oh, oh...
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
No!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Yes!
I see Employee of the Month in here for a change.
You think so?
I know so.
I've got a pool around here.
I hope so.
I'm gonna fuck those titties.
You wanna fuck my tits?
That's how I know I'm coming for her.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Mm.
For the dead.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mm.
You fucking big tits.
Oh.
Mm.
Yeah, and I'll spit that out on my dick.
Yes.
Mm.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, God.
You guys are gonna make me a mess.
I'm gonna make a fucking mess.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
There's balls around him.
I can slap you with some balls.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Oh, back to those chest muscles.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Come here.
With your bones.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Kiss him when it comes in his mouth.
Every time.
Oh.
Open that mouth.
Yes.
Oh.
That's so nice.
So nice.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, that's so nice.
So nice.
Mm.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Is this pussy ready?
Ready?
Is it nice and wet?
It's very wet.
Let's get this off.
Ready?
Ready.
...
I missed. you did. I missed that time.
I know I missed that time you left the spa.
...
Oh my goodness, what did I do to deserve this?
So I just got off the phone with the main office.
Did you know that David's getting fired?
David?
Yeah, from accounting.
Oh, yeah, that guy's a fucking douchebag.
I know, but who do you think they're going to hire to replace him?
I don't know, maybe Mike?
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
Oh, well, you guys are still going at it.
I'm almost done.
Well, make sure you come on her face when you're done.
Yes, boss.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're a fucking idiot.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, oh.
You've got some fucking good pussy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's a girl, baby.
Is that what you want?
Oh, oh.
Oh....
Yes, yes, yes....
It's ok, baby.
You are going to be ok.
Yes, yes....
Yes.
Oh.
Please, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, oh.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes.
Wow.
Oh.
Yes.
That's it.
I want you to know.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh my god, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
This is the girl.
Oh yes.
Show it to me, show me that pussy.
Hey.
Hm.
Look at that.
Quiet.
Oh, quiet.
Give me a second.
Oh, God.
This way.
Oh, oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, good, yes.
Oh, oh, ooh.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, God.
Ah, oh, fuck, yes.
I need a few more.
Oh, God, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
Oh.
Ahh, could you make me come?
Make me come, make me come.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Mmm, yes.
Yes.
Oh yes.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
uh...
yes
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes!
I'm going to fuck this pussy till I come.
Okay.
Okay, how old do they smell, guys?
Yeah, smell my panties, maybe that's it, yeah.
Yeah, smell my panties.
Smell my panties, you little perv.
Yes, oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, God.
Oh.
I can't do this.
they are... they are coming through
look at these things
oh... oh fuck
this is... oh... oh shit
they've... they've taken all the babies
oh... oh fuck... oh fuck
laaaa... laaa... laaa...
fuck...
Oh my god.
Ah.
Ooh.
Mm.
Ah.
Natasha?
Hm?
When you're ready, Jack and Tom
would like to see you in the break room.
Oh.
OK.
Oh, great.
See you in a moment.
Welcome to the office.
Oh, thank you.
Pleasure meeting you.
Yeah, you too.