Oh my god, holy shit, what's up baby, fuck.
I thought I would cook you breakfast.
Oh my god, I just woke up and I'm like fuck,
where's Angela at and you're in here
with your fucking sexy ass and your titties, oh my god.
Like my outfit?
Hell yeah.
A little bit of a side thing.
But it's not my birthday, what's going on?
No, it doesn't need to be your birthday
for me to treat you.
Oh my god, look at these titties, they're like spilling.
I know, right?
Look at that side boob.
So what are you going to do, making some breakfast or something?
Yeah, I'll be kind of making you something, depending on what you've got.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
You didn't even buy eggs?
I haven't been grocery shopping, I'm sorry.
Well, I don't know what I'm going to make you. I mean, I've got butter.
something else I mean this is just my breakfast cooking outfit oh oh oops
sorry I mean they just they barely fit in here sir
squeeze them together for you I can serve these up for you for breakfast
Fuck, let me see that ass too.
Oh my god, these panties are fucking nice.
I'm so lucky.
I love having your hands on me.
Yeah, these are fucking hot.
Yeah.
Smell some tits.
Oh, your tits, fuck.
So big, look at that.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Bigger than my head.
Mm-hmm.
Look at the way they bounce and jiggle.
Fuck.
Mm, squeeze your hands around.
Look, you need like three or four hands to cover them.
far more than a handful take your 32 double G see the other one make that
That apron disappeared.
Look at that.
I love to tease you.
Yeah, keep teasing me.
Big, bouncing titties.
See them drop.
Let me see if I can make them jiggle like this.
Wow.
Yeah, I'm definitely hungry for those titties.
Do you want me to serve you up some big tit?
Oh yeah, definitely yeah.
You know those cities for breakfast baby.
Mmmmm.
Alright, I'll serve that up.
Maybe we should, um, glaze them with something though.
Oh really?
Well, there is some coconut oil here that I was thinking of using to cook.
Ohhhh.
Let's see.
Let's see what happens.
Oh look it's slowly going. Can you see the nipple through that?
Let's try the other tip. Look at it drip down. How's that?
It's amazing. Yes.
Yes.
Want to see my tits?
Yeah, baby.
I can see it through the apron.
Why don't you tease me?
Yeah.
Tease my nipples under there?
Look at that.
Yeah, let's see them titties, baby.
So shiny and oily.
It feels so nice.
Let me get this off.
Wouldn't you love to feel these oily tits around your cock?
Hell yes.
You look sexy that day.
Jiggling for you?
Yes.
They're getting me tanned on now.
Yeah, I want you to
grab them.
Yeah, look at that.
I'll make it disappear.
Isn't it soft?
Oh hell yeah, oh my goodness.
I love the way you grab them and touch them.
They're so fucking big.
Yeah, you got me playing with myself now.
Oh yeah, it's turning you on?
Yeah.
God, yes.
That was so slippery you can barely even grab onto that nipple.
I can't.
I can't even.
No, I think I should just forget about cooking for now.
Yeah, I think so, too.
Yeah, I can do that afterwards.
Hypnotic.
Yeah, that's why I'm just staring at the mirror.
I'm hypnotized right now.
So you're going to let me play with your cock or what?
Oh, fuck yeah.
Is that what you want?
That is what.
mmm yeah between these tits mmm mmm
there's big eyelid hits
hmm
that's how hard that gets you
Make that cock disappear
Jiggle is picked, it's around it
Mmm
So nice and big and oily
Look at all that
fucking spit
Ah
Fuck
Mmm
That's not
God damn, that's a lot of everything, huh?
I can't keep it in.
Let me see that down.
Fuck, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, God, baby, that feels so good.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God, yeah, I love the way you suck me.
Oh my god, yes, you feel so good.
Oh shit, yes.
Oh, here's how it feels like.
Feels like that cock in me.
Oh my god, yes.
Dry it down, it feels so good.
Yes.
Oh shit. Yes like that. Oh
Yes, fuck, oh my god
that is so fucking good yes yes
yes yeah like that
you can come on that cock yes
oh fuck yes yes yes
oh shit
oh my god yes it looks so good
Do I get out of that pussy?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, baby.
Fuck, like that.
Oh, man.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, I used that pussy.
I used that pussy.
don't stop, fuck, oh, god, yes, fuck, oh, fuck, yeah, mm,
Mm-hmm
Oh
Fuck
Yes, yes, I fucking cried in that glint on it.
Yes, come on in for that dick.
Yes.
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna drive somebody fucking crazy.
Yes.
Fuck.
Bangbros.com.
Oh, fuck.
oh shit oh fuck oh yeah oh yeah oh let me taste my fucking coffee
oh my god it tastes so good
He has big fucking tits.
Oh, so I drank that cock.
I'm gonna tease you with this.
Yes, spank it.
I'm gonna tease you.
Oh, give me that fucking cock back.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god it feels so fucking good, yes, I love these drinks.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh that feels so good, yes.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh fuck.
oh my god yeah it's so deep like that
oh god yeah i'm making this fucking big touch bounce
Yes, slap it on there.
Good, yeah.
You look so fucking purple.
It's hot.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, baby.
Yes, yes.
Oh, I can feel your balls slapping up against me.
Yeah, like that.
Oh, my God.
Fucking yes.
This is so good.
I love that when you get so deep like that.
Oh, yeah.
Are you ready for me to swallow it?
Oh, God.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
That actually made me hungry now.
I mean, you can still cook breakfast if you want.
I can do that for you.
Oh, my God.