I want you to know that I have accepted the slut wife challenge.
That's right.
You're going to be my little chastity husband bitch.
Little cuckold bitch.
cocks in public and you're just going to have to smile and take it.
All while you were at home being a little fucking cock-holed bitch.
He's gonna love my little pussy.
and you knowing that he's made this pussy his.
and you're a little pin prick of a cock.
Hmm, you're such a little cock it turns you on, huh?
You're so fucking pathetic.
Number three,
I'm gonna go out
and suck a stranger's cock
and I'm gonna send you selfies.
That big dick in my mouth, hey baby,
saved the best till last. I am going to have every single guy that I fuck
bear and I let them come deep inside my hole and then I'm gonna come home
that drifting out of my holes that you're eagerly eating which one of your
Suck it all out.
Gargle it, you little bitch.
tongue in there and taste your friends.
Get in there and thank me.
Look how turned on you are thinking about your wife being a hot slut.
Look at those balls filling up.
You want to come for me, don't you?
Go on.
Stroke that cock.
Show me just how turned on it makes you.
That's it.
Stroke it all the way from the base to the tip.
Up and down.
I want to see just how excited you are.
Want to see what a big load of cum you have for me?
Make it big, because I also want to see what a good little cum
eater you're going to be.
Going to practice for me, eating up your own cum,
so I can see you're going to do a good job eating up
your friends.
That's it.
Keep fucking stroking it for you, this slutty asshole.
the slutty asshole that you will never get to put your dick into.
That's it.
Keep fucking stroking.
Are you ready to come for me?
Not yet.
You come when I say.
How about a countdown?
Ten,
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
No, you're not coming yet.
Did you think it would be that easy?
Beg.
Beg for me to let you come.
Look at that cock throbbing for these big slutty tits.
Keep begging.
All right, we'll start again, ten, nine, keep stroking.
I'm going to let you come this time, I promise.
Eight, seven, six.
Keep stroking that pathetic little dick.
I know it's getting intense, isn't it?
I didn't tell you to stop there.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Come now.
Come now and a little.
That's it.
Try.
Good.
Now I'm going to start that challenge.
Best get to it.
I got a lot of your friends to get through.