Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.
Is that my shirt?
Oh, yeah.
It was the only one that was clean.
Is that okay?
I looked okay.
No.
No, it's fine.
That's the shirt that was hung in my room that was freshly steamed.
Yes.
Is it warm?
It is.
Just...
I don't know.
You, uh...
Go ahead.
You go ahead and enjoy that shirt.
Thanks.
I don't know why Chad hates me so much.
I know!
I'm gonna give Chad what every man wants.
Hot cocoa and whipped cream.
Hi.
I'm really sorry about your shirt.
I got...
I'm...
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
Steam another one.
It's okay.
You just...
I made you some hot cocoa.
Are you serious?
And I brought you some whipped cream.
Seriously?
Mm-hmm.
Do you like hot cocoa?
Yeah, I fucking love it.
Oh, that's great.
I love whipped cream too.
Oh my God, it's so good.
You just make this right now?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I just heat it up and...
All right.
Yeah, yeah.
It should be good.
Oh.
You like it?
Shit, no, it's good.
Oh, awesome.
That's fucking really good.
Yeah.
That's good.
Oh, awesome.
That's fucking really good.
Yeah, definitely put that whipped cream on there, definitely, yeah.
Fuck yeah.
Awesome.
I'm so happy you like it.
I love hot cocoa and whipped cream.
I'm sorry for being kind of like a dick.
This is kind of cool.
It's okay.
Yeah.
I just...
I don't know.
No one's ever, like, made me hot chocolate and whipped cream.
Exactly. But below the cherry. Mm-hmm. Do you have cherries?
bottles in the fridge.
Yeah.
He doesn't even use it at all.
A couple spoonfuls of whipped cream, yeah.
I have a problem.
Yeah, I've always wanted to like...
Like, you know what I mean?
I brought it into the bed.
Oh yeah, I ate it in bed too.
No, no, no.
I brought it to bed.
Oh, into the bedroom.
Yeah, but girls don't like that kind of stuff.
Well, I've wanted to do it with Brian,
but he's like finicky about like
sticky, wet stuff all over his body.
Seriously?
It'll just be a fantasy of mine
You can like lick it off. Uh-huh
Just like spray it on the nipples and like slowly lick around it
Yeah
That's funny. See, it's already melting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Can I have some? Yeah, yeah, you can have some.
Thank you.
Ah, come here. It's really good. You want some, okay? Sure. Open, open.
Hold on, hold on. Not too much. No, no.
Just a little, just a little bit. Right there. Just a little dollop.
I eat it.
I really do like regular sauce.
Let me do like one more.
Get that.
There we go.
One more.
Lean back.
Just a little bit right there.
One more.
That's what I do.
You want it.
A little bit.
Yeah.
a little bit right there. One more.
Why do you do that?
You want it.
A little bit?
Yeah.
Oh, it's really good.
It is?
One more.
Let me do one more.
Okay.
How do you spell for me?
I'm Matt.
I.
Yeah.
It's hot, it's so hot.
Where's Brian at?
I don't know, I didn't know that word.
Yeah? Yeah.
Let me get one.
Oh, it's right there.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, you taste so sweet.
I really like the sugar.
Yeah.
Yeah, just like that.
Just like that.
Oh my god, it's so cold.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
It's so hot, it's so hot, I wish Brian would do that.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, give yourself a whipped cream mustache.
Yes, oh, oh my God, it's so sexy.
It's like you just snorted whipped cream.
Mm.
That's it, that's about it.
Mm, oh my God, yes.
Oh my god, my nipples are already raw.
What are you going to do now?
What are you going to do?
Oh my god, yes!
Oh, it's so cold!
Oh, fuck!
Oh my god, yes.
Yeah.
Are you using it to eat whipped cream?
Yes.
Look at that.
Mmm.
Yes.
I'll keep going, please.
Oh my God, yes.
Mmm.
It tastes so good.
Yes.
I'll keep going, please.
That's it.
Mmm.
Oh my God, that's messy.
Oh my God.
That's so sexy.
That was sexy.
Oh my goodness.
Is it okay to say this?
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Oh my god, oh my god.
My nipples are so cold.
Oh yes, please eat it just like that.
Oh my god, oh my god.
My nipples are so cold.
Oh yes, please eat it just like that.
No, don't stop. Don't stop.
That's the way I want it.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, you gotta taste it.
Ah.
Uh huh.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, you're so good at that.
Uh huh.
Oh, fuck, yes.
You don't ever know that good thing in your life.
Yes.
Oh, pleasure to eat, I just love it.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Oh, oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, oh, mmm.
Oh God, you have to be proud of us.
oh
that's it
do it again
there you go
yeah
oh
oh my god, yes
put it all over
that's it, oh
fuck yes
oh
yes
fuck
oh
yes
that's it
That shit's so hot.
That's it.
Fuck yes.
Water's so sweet.
Yes. That's it.
Come here. Get up.
We're not done with this.
I'm here now.
Oh yeah, you like that don't you?
You love how I suck your cock?
That's such a big dick.
No.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, I love your balls.
I don't like it at all.
I love your claws.
They don't taste like whipped cream.
Oh
Oh my god, it's already melting because your cough is so hot, so warm.
Mmm.
That's it.
Oh.
Oh, I like this.
Oh, God, yes.
It's so fucking sweet.
Mmm.
Oh, God.
That's it.
Oh.
Mmm.
That's it.
Wow.
Mmm.
Oh.
Oh
Oh my god, yes!
Yes!
Oh, fuck, I'm so affected!
Oh, god!
Oh, yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Ha ha ha!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Oh, that's it.
There you go.
Yeah.
Mm.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god.
That feels so good.
Fuck you.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
Yeah.
That's it.
Ooh, you want this?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's it.
No, no, no, no.
I'm so scared.
No, no.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, yeah, put some more.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
I will do it.
Oh fuck.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Oh fuck.
That's it.
There you go.
Oh.
Oh god, it's all melted.
Oh Jesus.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh fuck yes.
I'm so fucking so fucked.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
That's it.
Yes.
Oh.
That's it.
There you go.
Okay.
That's it.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, yes!
Yes!
That way, Wesley!
Oh!
Yeah!
Oh god, yes!
Oh!
It's here!
Here!
Oh god, yes!
Oh!
Oh
That's it.
Oh, fuck, yeah, oh, God.
oh, my God, it feels so, oh, it feels so fucking good.
oh
yeah
yes
oh
yeah
make him bounce
make all of them bounce
oh
fuck yeah
yeah
oh
fuck yeah
Oh
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Mmm, good.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Fuck yeah.
Oh.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh my God.
You're a fucking ass.
You see?
Oh God, yes.
Oh.
Fuck, yes.
Yes.
Oh god.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, you're crazy, yes.
You're fucking.
It's so good.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh.
Fuck yes.
Oh
Oh, fuck, yes!
Big fuck!
Mmm, yes!
Yes, yes!
Yeah!
Oh, God, yeah!
Mmm, yeah!
Oh, fuck, yeah!
Yes!
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, gosh!
Oh, yeah. Oh, my God. Yes.
uh-huh
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
Oh shit, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, bloody fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Come here.
That's it.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, oh, oh god, yes!
Yes!
Ah, ah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh god, yeah.
Oh god, yes, please, fuck, I just need to...
Ah, ah.
Oh, fuck yeah!
Oh, God, it feels so good.
Oh.
Where's my ass again?
Oh, wait.
It's right there.
Oh.
Oh, my God, it's so hard.
Oh, my God, it's so big.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Do you like it?
Is it tight?
Yes. Oh, good, yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah. Yes, fuck my ass.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes. Fuck that asshole.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck you. Oh my god. Yes. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Oh my god. Yes
Oh
Fuck
Yes, oh
I feel it in my ass with that big cock.
Oh, God, yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, God, that feels so good.
Oh!
Oh, God, yeah.
Yeah, oh, God.
Mmm.
Yes, yes.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, oh, god yeah.
Oh, god yeah, stretch out that asshole.
Oh, you make a nice and long shot.
Yeah, spit that big dick in there.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, god yeah, yeah, yeah.
More?
Fuck.
Pump!
Get the fuck over here.
Let me just take that, let me just take that.
Oh, God, that felt good, baby.
That's it, that's it.
Oh, God, yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Shh.
No.
Oh.
No, don't have to whisper.
Oh, yes, God, let me just take that.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh my God, that feels so good.
Oh, God.
Oh, I can't do this.
That's it.
Fuck yes.
Oh, God.
That's it, Rebecca.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
Oh, good.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Fuck that ass.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes. Yeah.
Oh, this is so good.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, God. Yeah.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
That's it, just like that.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
That's it.
Oh.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, God, yeah, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck, yes.
That's it.
Oh, God, yeah.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
That's it.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
I'm covered in so much cream.
That's fucked up.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Still a little bit.
Oh my god, you're crazy.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's fucked up.
Yes, you like that?
Yeah.
You're fucking nerdy.
Oh my god, I'm covered in cum and whipped cream, oh my god, it's so cold.
Oh.
That's it, come here.
That's it.
Fuck.
Yeah.
That's it.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
That was hot.
We better clean up before Brian gets home.
Oh, shit, the couch.
This is his couch.
Uh, well.
Come on.
Go upstairs.
Go.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Naughty America.
Nobody.
You