So, how is my little bitch doing on this impaler?
Scoot that ass back.
I want to see you fucking yourself.
Scoot that.
Does that feel good?
to be a good little anal whore if it pleases you miss what does
mmm and us is spreading uh-huh so you can't see what I've got on but I can
I can tell you that I have a little surprise for you.
I'm really gonna make you my bitch today.
Yeah, do you like having that cockslap against your face?
If it pleases you, mistress.
Mm, it does.
Open that mouth.
Now, I want you to show me what a good little dick sucker you can be.
Yeah, I want you to gag on that cock.
Yes, there you go.
Let's see how far you can take it.
That's good.
Spit all over it.
You want it to be wet because you know where this is going, right?
Yes.
Don't wipe that fucking spit all over your face.
Back in that mouth.
Back in that slutty little mouth.
Yes, got it.
Rub that fucking spit all over you.
There you go.
Yes, let me fucking hear you gather that cup
all the way down to the balls, yes.
Hmm, good little fucking whore.
Hmm, let's see how that ass is going.
Yes, I like seeing that ass take it.
Let's see
how open it has become.
It's opening up.
I don't want to waste this.
Somebody's going to have to clean this.
taste your fucking ass
yeah
how does your fucking ass taste huh
like ass
that's right eat your fucking shit off of it
lick it all clean
I don't want any mess
left on that
back in that mouth
you daddy fucking whore
in your fucking shit off that dick
fucking pig
let's take a look
Did you clean your ass hole out good? Yes Mistress.
Let's hope that you stretched out this ass good for me.
Yes Mistress, I hope so.
My little bitch.
Oh, look at you taking it.
Four fingers already?
You little fucking slut.
Let me look in there.
Nice little pink hole.
Oh, look at you squirm.
Please, Mr.
My pulse is so sensitive.
Should I focus on your ass?
I'm just going to tease your ass with it.
You're going to fucking love it.
For the time I'm finished with you
You're gonna be addicted
To being a little fucking whore
Taking this cock
Look at you taking that dick
Just the head
Oh, I felt it pop in there.
Fuck, I'm going to be kind to you at first.
Oh, thank you, mistress.
Just ease it into you.
Those balls rubbing on your balls.
Good little anal whore.
Slut puppy.
Let's see that asshole stretch armpit.
Oh, yes.
Look at you squirming.
There you go.
Oh.
What do you say to your mistress?
Thank you, mistress.
Oh.
you like taking that cup oh if it pleases you mistress do you like taking
a little more lube yes please what kind of fucking anal whore are you
Look at your fucking
pre-com. You act like
you don't like being humiliated.
Look at it dripping down
there. You love
being my little anal bitch.
It hits my prostate.
Why don't we use some of that pre-karmas lube?
Ugh.
Mmm.
Yes.
I'll even be kind and put a little bit more on.
Just today.
Thank you very much.
Tickle that little asshole?
don't close up on me
there we go
take it
you said you couldn't take it in deep
look at that
are you ready to be a good
oh see now you see what it's like to be a real animal
that off.
It's transmission.
Yes.
Deep in that tight little man pussy.
It's going to be loose by the time I'm done with you.
You little fucking bitch.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
This isn't even a fucking big cock.
Are you kidding me?
Pathetic.
Mm.
Take it.
Take that fucking hot juice.
There you go.
Now you're starting to learn how to be a good little anal slut for me.
Yeah, there you go.
I want to see it going in deep.
All the way out like that.
I want you to take every fucking inch of that cock in and out of that ass.
Yeah.
Look at you, whinging like a little fucking bitch.
Grinding it in there.
Yeah.
There you go.
Taking that fucking dip.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, you're fucking moaning like a little fucking bitch.
Are you going to start squealing like a piggy for me, huh?
Fucking pathetic.
Oh, ah.
Oh, you're barely even fucking taking it.
Look at that.
That's just the fucking head.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Are you really that much of a little bitch?
All right, here you go.
Have some more lube.
I don't want to fucking hear about it.
I just want you to fucking take it.
I beg your pardon, mistress.
My body reacted.
I'm sorry.
Your body fucking reacted?
You've got an excuse for everything.
I'm going to train that out of you, too.
I'm going to train you to fucking love it.
Look at you arching your back like that, like a little fucking bitch.
Mmm.
Oh, my God.
You're moaning like you're taking a big dick.
You've got a thin little fucking thing in your ass,
and you're only taking the head.
You're really fucking struggling to keep those moans in, aren't you?
Does that feel better, huh?
Did I slap your fucking balls in the fucking cock?
Which would you rather?
It doesn't matter what you'd rather.
Just shut up.
Yes, fucking take it.
Fucking stretch that arsehole out.
Come on.
Arch it, arch it, big little fucking whore.
Yes, mistress.
Yes.
There you go.
Starting to open up for me?
Yeah.
I love seeing you squirm.
I love fucking humiliating you like this.
Oh.
Did you push my cock out?
I don't think I did, but it just happened.
I think it just happened.
It just happened?
Yes, mistress, I'm sorry.
I don't want to do anything that I can do at this point.
You got fucking lube dripping out of your asshole onto your fucking balls
and you're fucking complaining like I'm fucking you with a dry dick.
Such a little bitch.
I want to see how much you can fucking take for me.
Curling up like a little fucking bitch.
Good animal whores arch their backs.
Yes, mistress.
There you go.
Don't you want your ass to look fucking nice to me?
Presentable.
That's fucking right.
I want to see those hips pushing out.
Yes, mistress.
Arch that back.
Make it fucking pretty make it fucking
Fucking take it
Prove to me what you're willing to take for your fucking
Show me what you're fucking willing to take.
Oh, please.
Oh, my God.
Fucking pathetic.
Come here and taste your fucking ass.
Give me that fucking slutty little mouth of yours.
There you go.
Yes.
Taste it.
Taste your dirty fucking ass.
Rub it all over that fucking face.
Come on, I can't.
spit on it
that fucking face
you fucking whore
you barely even fucking take it
let me see how that ass is going
let me have a look
oh we have more work to do
but this is a good start
oh yeah you're gonna stay here all night by the time i come back hopefully
you are nice and relaxed oh stretched out for me
Thank me
Thank you mistress
Kiss my cock goodnight
I'll see you in the morning
Please don't leave me here all night
Oh shut the fuck up