When you run a business, as successful as mine,
it's essential to take some time off every once in a while
to refuel, refocus, and clear your mind.
Four times a year, I follow a strict relaxation ritual.
For a week at the end of each quarter,
I seclude myself in a private villa.
Chuck, I thought I told you not to bother me this week.
This better be important.
Just let me stop you right there.
You don't need me for this, okay?
I want you to figure this out on your own.
If you can't, then you're fired.
Chris! Martini! Now!
Look, I'll see you next week, okay?
Thank you.
They need to respect my wishes.
You respect my wishes, don't you Chris?
Of course you do.
Silly question.
Insubordination was impossible with him.
So when I wanted something, I just took it.
That's what I pay you for.
And he let me take it.
No questions asked.
You're gonna do everything that I ask on you.
You're gonna be a good toy boy for me.
Yes, that's right.
That pussy.
We'll see.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Mmm, my God, yes.
Fuck that face.
Good boy.
Yes.
Look up at me while you suck that clit.
Look up at me.
Yeah.
Good boy.
Stick that tongue in deep.
Mmm.
Oh my god, you make me fucking cum on that tongue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh fuck, yes, fuck, oh my god.
I'm having so much fun with this cock
You like your tits here, yeah?
Yeah, I need your tits
Now get right in there
Yes
Smell that fucking cock on my clit
I want you to fuck these big tits.
Yeah.
You're going to oil them up for me.
Mmm.
Get them nice and oily.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Yeah, get them all oiled up.
Those big natural tits are wrapped around that crotch.
I know.
Yeah, man.
You just came right down here.
She doesn't have it like that.
Bouncing.
Yes.
Fuck you, cock.
Yeah.
You shouldn't have left that cock on there.
Yeah, I'm bouncing.
Yeah, squeeze them. Squeeze them really tight.
Use them.
Yeah.
There you go. So slippery.
Yeah, fuck them.
Like that.
Yes.
So, so good.
Feel that cock getting hotter and hotter between them.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Yes.
Yeah, you grab them all.
Yeah.
So soft.
Spit it in my mouth.
Oh
I like the way they bounce, it's so fucking sexy.
Keep going, keep fucking them.
Yeah.
Yeah, yes, yes.
Stop, stop, stop.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry, this feels so good.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
You are definitely my new favorite boy today.
You're going to satisfy me so well with this cup.
Oh my god, yes, look at that.
Oh
Yeah, when you jiggle your fucking tits around her.
Yeah.
Yes.
Put it right in there.
Let me massage that too.
Yeah.
Jiggle them around.
Look at you.
Excited, huh?
Yeah.
Yes.
He's going to tease that fucking cock.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Just like that.
Oh, fuck.
Like watching it.
and then it disappear and then reappear between those titties.
Oh, yes.
Very nice.
Yeah, just slowly.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
You can't tease the tip like that.
See my tongue?
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh fuck.
I'm gonna wrap the fucking foreskin around it.
You wanna fuck them?
Do it.
Fuck those big tits.
Yeah, do it.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, I'll fuck this shit up.
Yeah.
oh my god taste your fucking pre-cum
make me fucking cum on this big dick
you're gonna be a good little boy toy and give me everything that i want
Yeah, that's right, you are going to give me everything that I ask for.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, that cock feels so good.
Oh, fuck yous, yous.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you're so fucking good.
Oh, swimming in that pussy.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, let me just tease it.
Let me just tease it.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Don't give me that fucking cock, oh my god!
Yeah, make those big tits bounce.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, yeah.
Move up here, move up here.
Yeah, come here.
Bring me that fucking cock.
Bring it to me just like that.
Yeah, let me fuck it.
Let me fuck it.
Put your fucking hands down and let me fucking take that cock.
No, you put them right down.
That's my fucking dick.
oh fuck yeah keep going like that i want you to make me come on
i want you to make that pussy come yes yeah keep going fuck yeah yeah yeah
yes yeah keep going keep going keep going keep going keep going keep going
It's so good, oh shit!
Oh my god.
Oh fuck yeah, tease me with that cock.
Yes.
Oh my god, yeah.
Yeah, just the tip, just tease me with it.
You feel so fucking good in that pussy.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck yes. Oh my oh my god. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes
I want you to keep fucking me with this big cock.
Make me fucking cum, yes, yes, yes, yes, cum
Oh my god, yes
I'm gonna make those fucking big tits bounce while you fuck me