Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.
Hey, babe.
Oh, I'm so excited. I can't wait till you come home tonight.
I have a really exciting surprise for you.
Um, what?
to work. Okay, babe. Bye.
It's so pretty though, what a shame, I'm going to try it on anyways.
I'm going to put it on your head.
It's very pretty.
Okay.
Pretty good.
Oh, is she.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh baby, you look so good, I really like it.
Yeah, I literally just walked in the door, class ran a little late, so.
I was expecting you to be home though, you're still at work?
Okay.
I mean, you've been working late, a lot lately, so.
I just like to hang out with my dad, you know?
And I think Natasha's kinda missing you a little bit.
But, alright, no dinner plans then.
I'll take care of myself.
Okay, for sure.
I'll see you when you get home, Dad.
Love you too.
Bye.
What the-
Oh, sh-
Don't you knock?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
It's not what it looks like.
I swear.
I don't give a shit what it looks like.
Get out of my room.
I thought you were cheating on my dad.
I'm sorry.
Leave.
Go.
Stop looking at me.
Sorry.
Go.
Oh my god.
Hi.
You thought I was cheating on him?
Yeah.
Obviously I was not cheating on him, I wouldn't cheat on him.
I can see that now.
Do you think I would cheat on him? You obviously...
I just, my mom cheated on him a lot, so...
Okay.
I don't know, it kind of just took me back.
You really should not.
I know, I know.
Anyways...
Right. Well, I'm sorry I yelled at you.
It's okay. It was deserved.
Just... it's a little awkward.
Yeah, I guess it's a little awkward. I mean...
But anyways...
Uh, like what do you mean?
Uh, I don't know, I was just, I kind of fucked you up right there.
You fucked me up, uh...
Bad choice of words.
Yeah.
I mean, she's not that big of a deal.
She's not here.
She's not here. I'll just finish, and then I'll meet up.
Okay.
You stare at them a lot.
You wear small bikinis around the pool.
That's so good in front of your father.
Oh my god.
You're a giver.
Okay.
I feel it's only right I do owe you.
You do owe me.
Okay.
Wow, you're very good at that.
Oh, she's giving me a lot of practice.
I bet.
Touch it like that, touch it.
Yeah, just mess it up.
Your ears are very similar, even your teeth.
Oh
Oh, oh, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, mother.
Put your face up here.
Oh, good.
Oh, yes.
Oh
I don't know how to do it.
Oh, it's a nice smooth calf.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, gosh.
Yes, my dad's girlfriend.
Oh, my God.
Your pussy's like velvet. I can see your eyes with you.
Oh, yes, yes.
You look a bit tense, you must be stressed.
Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna check all the time in your room.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, good.
I love you.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Do you mind if I tease it.
Yeah.
You sure?
Do you mind if I tease it enough by cutting you off?
Yeah.
Oh it's nice.
Oh yes.
Oh.
Oh
Oh, oh.
You don't speak to me again.
Yeah, you don't speak to me again.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck.
Mm.
Yeah.
Wait, is that somebody else?
Yes.
Fuck, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh
Lucas, no Lucas, let me, oh!
Oh, yes!
Oh!
Yes!
Keep doing that!
Just like that!
Yeah!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh, Lucas, yes!
Can you give me a hug?
Yes!
Oh my God!
I feel so weak.
Give it to me.
Oh my God!
Yes!
You're a fucking cuckoo
Ah, ah, ah
Oh, you
You
Oh
Spaz
You like watching your dad's girlfriend?
Oh
I like your mouth, it's so good.
My dad is a smart man to be with you.
Shh.
We're not going to tell him, okay?
Uh-huh.
He'd throw my ass out.
I don't know why I'm doing this
ok
oh
Oh my god, your pussy is so wet.
Yes! Oh yes!
Oh yes!
Yes! Oh my god, yes!
Oh god...
oh
Let's see here.
Perfect.
You got this, boy.
Let's see here.
Wow.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
That feels so good.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Ooh, I feel it in my back, yes.
Oh, ooh, making me so wet, yes, yes, uh huh.
Yeah, squeeze my butt, yes, oh I love that, yes, yes.
Mm-hmm, ooh, uh huh, yes, ah, ah, ah.
Oh
Oh, yeah, you can do
It was so intense, don't you agree?
Mm-hmm.
I do.
Let me see.
Oh, it feels so good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh god, it's so good.
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh god, yes.
Yes, please don't suck, no please don't suck.
Please fuck me, oh god, yes, yes.
You're gonna make me cry, don't stop touching me, Clay.
Don't stop touching me, Clay.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck, I'm gonna cry.
Oh, oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck, shit.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, you, oh.
Oh, oh, fuck, yes.
Oh yeah, yes.
Oh shit...
Yes, yes.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh my god.
This is amazing.
I didn't fuck you again.
Oh, it's okay. My dad's been late. I'm working on this.
Yes. Oh, God.
It's okay. It's fine.
Holy shit. Your pussy's way too fine.
Oh, God.
Oh my god, yes. The outtake is so good.
Oh, fuck right there.
Oh yeah, the balls too.
Holy shit.
Girls my age don't know anything about balls, holy fuck.
Not a girl your age.
Your father's girlfriend.
You definitely know what you're doing with a set of balls.
Oh shit.
I think my dad's gonna- is that him pulling up?
Is it?
Oh shit.
Naughty America.
Nobody.
Does it better.
Nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.