89? Yes. 88? Yes. Yeah, good job. So did you study much this weekend?
Yeah, it's been a whole week since I've heard from him.
Miss Natasha?
Yes, Alex, yes, my sweet Alex, what do you need, baby?
Yes, Alex, who's your big cock and you like to suck?
Alex?
Alex.
Sorry.
Did you want to talk about your grade?
Yeah, actually.
See, I don't know what's going on.
Hmm.
Oh, no, I'm definitely interested.
Um, well, what do you think is going on? Is the material maybe too hard?
Oh my god, yes, I'm always hard.
What?
Why don't you have a seat?
Look, you can tell me whatever's going on.
I can't help you if I don't know what the problem is.
Honestly, it's a little embarrassing.
and testosterone into something more productive. I think I've got an idea.
Good. Let's get started.
B?
Yes!
Nailed it!
Now, come over here and choose your prize.
No, not yet.
There's still lots to learn, and lots of rewards to earn.
Sit down.
The brain accounts for 2% of the body's mass.
What percent of the body's oxygen consumption does it account for?
5%?
20%?
75%?
Or 90%?
20%!
Yes!
That's it!
Now come get your A. You've earned it.
That's it.
Now come get your A.
You've earned it.
Nice.
Ooh.
Yes.
We have one question left before you retake the quiz.
to the human amygdala and pairs recognition
of which of the following facial expressions?
Fear, sadness, disgust, or anger.
Fear?
Yes, yes, good job.
You ready?
Alright, let's see if I can get it to work.
All right, now it's time to take the quiz again
to see if all of this was worth it.
For good luck.
Okay, time's up, bring me your test.
How do you think you did?
Great.
Very good.
100.
Amazing.
Very good.
100.
Amazing.
Any chance I can get some extra credit?
Um, why yes.
Yes you can.
You did such a good job.
Thank you.
I'm going to go get my coffee.
You did such a good job.
You did an amazing job.
Is that good?
I'm so proud of how well you did and how hard you worked
Good job
Yeah, touch that
Go ahead
Oh my god.
Good job.
You're a good looking student, I have.
Oh
Yes, you are dead.
You are these big tits wrapped around that cock.
Yes, you're dead, Alex.
You did such a good job.
Yes.
Fuck them. Fuck my tits, Alex.
Yes, they're gonna come.
There you go, yeah.
Yeah, I'll get you a bit more.
Yes.
Mmm.
Oh, yes.
Good.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
Get that cock over those big tits, yeah, yes, there you go.
Yes, oh, yes, that looks so pretty, there you go.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Oh.
Mm.
You want more of my tits, don't you?
Yes, you do.
You're dying for them.
Oh, yes, don't stop.
Yes, I'm so good.
Oh, yeah. Uh-huh.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Aren't they nice and warm?
Oh, and they squeeze around my cock so well.
Mm.
There you go.
Yes, oh, yes, you earn these big teeth.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I bet you love these tits, don't you?
I've been staring at them for years.
Why don't you pay them a little attention?
Oh, yes.
You have to hypnotize my lip.
Give me my nipple.
Yes.
You're sensitive.
Alex, you're really good at tit worship.
Worship my tits.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Worship them, Alex.
Oh, that's amazing.
Oh, she's doing so well.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Really good job.
You're really outstanding, Alex.
It's impeccable.
Yes.
Oh yes, oh yes, you naughty boy.
Bad naughty boy.
Come here.
Let me do something with you.
Have you done this before?
I'm so hungry.
I want to eat right now, can't wait.
I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry.
Let's eat, let's eat, let's eat.
I'm gonna try some.
Mmm.
Oh, it's spicy.
Fuck, my face.
I'm getting it.
I'm seriously getting it.
I'm gonna try it.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Oh yes, oh yes, oh fuck yes, oh, oh, oh, yes, oh.
I never thought of this.
You guys, haven't you?
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Why is she doing this?
Take her.
Oh.
Yes.
Yes, uh-huh, yes, come on, yes, yes, oh my God.
Oh, fuck, oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, yes, yes.
Oh, oh, come on, keep fucking,
Oh, there you go, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh, there you go.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Yes.
Come here.
Yes, I can hear you.
Oh, there you are.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, you're so good.
Yes.
Yes, Alex.
Oh, yes, I want to taste your eyes, yeah, come on.
Just look in your fantasy, come on, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, come on, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Oh, shit.
Oh, it's so good, oh, it's so good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck, yuck.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh, it's fucking me.
Oh, yes, oh, yes.
Yes, oh.
Oh
Um
here
Oh, oh.
Oh, you're so cheap.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Oh, God.
You young boys.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, God, your tic is so good.
Feels so good.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh
Oh my God.
Hmm yes.
Mmm, yes.
Oh.
Oh, God, yes.
Mmm, mmm.
Mmm.
Ahh.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Aww.
Yes.
Mmm.
Ahh.
Ohh.
Mmm.
Oh
Oh my god
Oh my God, yes, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Just keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Oh my, oh my.
Yes, that's the right thing.
Get a little break.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh
I'm going to fuck you in my chair.
Sit down.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it's a nice stick.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Fuck.
Where are you?
Oh
I'm a distracted young boy.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Mm.
Yes.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yes, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Mm-mm.
Oh.
Mm.
Ah.
I want you to fuck me some more.
Mm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, goodness.
How does your reward feel?
Oh, how does your reward feel?
It feels so good.
You're doing such a good job.
Oh, such a good job.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
It was so hard, yes you did, oh god.
I've never seen a student work so hard before.
Mm-hmm, that's so super sexy actually, oh god.
Oh, oh, yes, you're so sexy, oh god, yes, yes.
You earned this fucking pussy, you earned this pussy.
Yes, you did, oh god, it's so nice.
It's so nice.
You have a really big dick.
Yes.
Oh god.
Alex.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh god.
Yes.
Oh.
There it is.
Oh god.
It's so good.
Alex.
Oh god.
Oh.
I don't want to fuck my tits, Alex.
These tits that you've been staring at all semester?
Yeah.
You're all flushed.
Yes.
You like your teacher's big tits, Alex?
You know what I want from you, Alex?
I want you to cover these tits and my face with all of your cum.
Yes, I want you to cover me in your cum.
Keep fucking my tits.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Are you gonna cover my tits with your cup?
Yes, I know you are.
I know it's what you've been thinking about all semester.
Yeah, you're gonna cover them with your cup.
Yeah, I want it.
I want to feel that warm cup all over my big tits.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I want to see you explode all over me.
I want to feel a drop on my face.
Felix, we want you to come over here.
Please, we want you to just come over, come on, come on.
Come on.
Ah.
I have a really good job, Alex.
Really well done.
So, how do you think you did?
I think I nailed it.
That's for sure.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yes.