Hi.
Come in.
Of course.
So, what prompted you to come in today?
Well, since I've graduated, I've been thinking a lot about my future.
And I want a career, not just a job, you know?
Oh.
That's very mature of you.
The problem is, is I don't know where to start.
Hmm.
Well...
Oh!
Well, that's what I'm here for.
Is to, uh, guide you through it.
you can come out on top.
What kind of resources?
Oh, I thought, never mind. Yeah, okay, let's do it.
Great.
These shouldn't take you too long.
And remember, there are no wrong answers.
It's all about finding you a tight fit.
A what?
A right tit.
A right what?
The right fit.
It's all about finding you a career that's the right fit.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
So maybe like a carpenter, or a fitness trainer, or a massage therapist
Would you like that?
Yeah
Would you like a job that requires hands-on work?
Yes, there you go
Let's use those hands
Oh yes, that's a lot for gas.
Mm-hmm.
Keep going.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so nice you pinched those in the balls.
Oh
Don't see him, don't see him
He's not coming together
Feed me my dear
My mouth
Show me your teeth.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, gosh.
Someone's excited.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you like working with your hands, don't you?
Yeah, I think you do.
Well, you know, I really like working with my hands.
I can tell.
But are there any other areas that you think might be suited for me?
Well...
Oh, yes.
Mmm.
Oh, fuck yes.
mmm
do you like that?
do you like the way I work with my mouth?
mmm
ahh
Mmm
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna need to go to the bathroom.
Yeah.
Mmhmm.
Yeah, she...
Yeah.
Yeah, show me how hard you work.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Mmhmm.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Mmhmm.
Yes.
Yeah.
Mmhmm.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's it.
Mmhmm.
Yes, faster faster. Yes.
Ah, yes.
Oh, yes.
So sexy.
Mm, yes.
Mm.
Ah.
Yeah, keep going keep going yeah
It's so hard, yes, yes, it's so hard, yes, oh God, yes.
You sexy young stuff, those big tits, yes, mm-hmm, yeah.
Oh, yes, yes, oh come on, yeah, you fuckin' like it?
Oh yeah, you fuckin' like it?
That tick's so hard for me.
Oh, it's working so hard for me, yes, oh God.
So, keep going, oh my God, oh fuck, yeah.
Let me set that clock again.
Yea.
You sit right there.
OK.
Guess.
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
Guess.
Oh my God, it's a big, hard cock for me.
Oh my hair.
Fuck, yes.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah...
Fuck my face.
Oh yeah.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, I see it right there.
Yeah.
Fuck yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Give me a kiss.
You know, in my career, I also think it's very important to give back.
Oh yeah, it's definitely important.
It's definitely important.
I want to give you a face right there, yeah.
Mm, yes, mm, ah, yes, mm, yeah.
A little face in there, yes, yes, oh, God, yeah.
Ah, yes, good job, oh, great job, oh, yes, ooh, yeah.
Oh, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Yeah, suck that big clit.
Suck that big clit, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yes, keep going.
Keep going.
Keep going, yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh my god, you're gonna make me cum.
Oh fuck.
Yes.
Mmm.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh fuck, I'm cumming.
Oh.
Mmm.
Mmm, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Mmm.
Yes.
See, yes, oh yeah, mm, yeah, slobber all over it, yes.
Mm-hmm, mm, yes, I got my working animal, uh-huh.
Yeah, fucking go for it, spit on it, spit on it.
Oh, God, yes, it's fucking great.
Oh, my, yes, oh, fuck, yes, bite it.
Oh, my goodness, yes, ah, ah, oh, my God, oh, my God,
it's driving me crazy.
Oh, fuck, yes, fuck, oh, fuck, yes, slow now, yes, oh.
Now you stand up, you know, take my pants off.
I really wanna help you find a career
that you can enjoy and have fun with.
and really dive into deeply invest yourself in.
Oh God, it's the most fulfilling kind, you know?
Yeah, just really satisfy yourself with me.
I mean, yeah, oh God, oh my God, yes, oh, oh, yes, uh-huh.
Yes
Yes, oh my god, it's a big thing.
Oh god, you're so deep inside me right now.
Oh fuck, oh fuck, yes.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, shit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yes, yes, have it, have it now.
ohhh yeah
oh my goodness
omg
its so rough
oooh
oh god
oh my god
ostrich calicus
yeah ostrich
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, that's good.
Hurry up.
Oh, yes.
You're so good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
It's so good.
Um…
Uh…
Is it a nice dress…
Yes…
Oh, Thaddeus.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, you take care of yourself, and I'll just look out the window.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, it's so deep in there.
Oh, you're so cute.
So cute.
Always admired.
Yes.
Ooh.
Pinky.
I like it.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, look, I can show you.
Can you hear my asshole?
Yes.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, you wipe that little tight, huh?
That's a tight fit.
Mmm, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Stretch that ass a lot.
What?
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh my god, yes, stretch it out, stretch it out, yes.
It's so good, it's so good, yes.
Fuck, yes, fuck, oh my god.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, yeah, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, nice and slow.
Nice and slow.
Yeah, open it up.
Open it up so we can have some fun with it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, shit, yes.
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh, oh.
Yes.
Mmm.
Stretch that out.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
It's so big.
Yes.
Mmm.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh, fuck.
My asshole.
Please. Please.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, that's a safe fit right there.
Yes, it is.
Oh my god.
Oh, this is a safe fit.
It's so fucking tight.
Oh, god, yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, it's so cheap.
Oh, it's so cheap.
Oh, oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah, put it in there.
Fuck, fuck, oh my god, fuck.
Oh, yes, yes, oh, fuck, oh god, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Keep fucking, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh god, please, please.
Oh, oh, oh, oh my god, yes, this is so good, it's so good.
Yes, this is so good.
It's so good.
Oh.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh.
Ooh, yeah.
Mm.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, sheesh!
Oh good, you're stretching, that's it.
Awww.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, so good, so good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Awe, it's so amazing.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck yes.
Oh, oh, yes, oh, awe, awe.
Focus.
Like that, yes. Nice and tight.
Oh, yes! Yes!
Oh!
Mmm!
Oh, fuck!
Yes!
Oh, Lord, yes, it's so good!
Oh, God!
Oh!
Oh, please, give me a little more.
More. More.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Yeah, use those hands.
Use those hardworking hands.
Yeah, open my eyes for me.
Open my eyes.
Yes, for me. Yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh my god, yes.
So good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mm, so good.
Oh, so beautiful.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wow, yes. Yes.
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh, God, it's so cool!
So fucking tight, innit?
Yeah.
It's okay.
I hope you enjoy.
Oh
Oh my god.
Yes.
You wanna get a chance to do it?
Okay.
Oh.
Mm.
Fuck.
It's so good.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
You like that?
Like how it melts on my dick with my ass on?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh.
It's so good.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mm.
Yeah.
Sit up on the arm, David.
Let me get that thing, can I take it in my hand as well?
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, God.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, God, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Just break my ass.
Go ahead.
Oh, yes.
Oh, uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That's the last one I'll take.
Mm.
Oh.
Yes.
Don't look at me.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Oh my god, that must taste so good.
Oh fuck, it's all over.
Yeah.
Go ahead and get it.
Yeah, I know I'm getting some.
Mmm.
Come on, Sam.
That's the smell.
Mmm.
It's back here.
Oh, God.
Ah.
Mm.
Got you nice.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Mm.
Ah.
Yes, oh yes.
Second.
Yeah.
Ah.
Yes, oh, oh my god
Oh
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll take a nap.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, fuck you.
Yeah.
Mm, yeah.
Yes.
Oh yes.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh god, it's so bad.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Stay right there.
Don't touch it.
Oh, fuck it.
oh
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
It's so good.
Oh, yes.
Uh-huh.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God. Yes.
Yes.
It's so good.
Do you like that asshole?
Do you like that tight asshole?
Yes?
Oh my God, that was amazing.
Yeah?
Oh, oh my God.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
Fuck it.
Oh my.
Yes.
Fuck yes.
Mm.
Yes.
Oh fuck.
One more.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Mm.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you're gonna give me something?
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh.
I told you I was good with my hands.
Yeah, you are.
well done.
you