Naughty America. Nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.
Oh, it's working away. I'm always here by myself.
Oh, it works a lot. Sorry to hear that.
Sure. That's perfect.
Okay.
So, I'll leave you to it.
Thank you.
Hi babe. How are you? I miss you so much. Yeah, I feel very lonely.
you know the painters are here yeah they've done a great job I'm really
horny today I wish you were here you know I was thinking maybe you let me
My piss is really wet right now. Do you think I should go and fuck them?
were looking at me I need some cock today
I know. I'll talk to you later.
Oh my God!
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I can come back.
No, that's fine. Come here.
What are you doing?
I mean, I know what you're doing, but...
I was blaming myself, thinking about you two guys.
It's so horny right now.
And my husband is out of town.
I mean, he's out of town, but I don't want to get you in trouble.
And he's okay with it?
Yeah. Trust me. He enjoys it as much as I do.
And I've always had this fantasy about having sex with two-handed men.
And you just look so horny. I was looking at you before.
you see how wet my pussy is
oh my god
I'm so fucking horny right now
I should call it in here
Hey, Charles! Come check this out.
I told you she was ready. I saw it in your eyes.
I want to suck both of your cocks.
Wow, babe.
I love being a slutty wife.
Yes, babe.
Yes, that's good, don't you, baby?
Oh, yes.
Such a good, sweaty life.
Yes, what I do is do that.
Yes, but you're covering my face.
Sweet.
Yes, such a good, sweaty life.
Go back and forth like that.
Oh yeah. Oh fuck yes.
My turn baby. My turn.
Oh fuck yes. Here, fuck him up.
Fuck him up.
Yes. Oh look at that.
Baby.
It's your baby, baby.
Yes.
You're gonna fuck yeah.
You're gonna fuck, baby.
I'm so fucking ready for your cock.
It's so hot.
Fuck yes, who's the guy who saw it?
Oh my God, yeah.
oh fuck yeah baby you got a good little pussy
don't go stretching her out on me
Oh my god, this is so fucking hot.
I can't fucking breathe.
That's pretty big at all.
Yes.
Look at that hole.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
little pussy you have here, huh, baby?
Yeah. My husband would be
so proud of me.
You're gonna talk more about it, huh?
Yes.
One more time.
I think it's time we switch.
Yeah.
You wanna switch for us?
I'm gonna fuck you now.
Yes. I'm gonna fuck you, baby.
Yeah.
Turn around.
I'll see what you got here.
Let me taste you.
Mmm.
Look at your asses.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, we know.
That's it.
Don't you say some fucking word.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck. Yes.
Oh, Mary.
Oh, Mary Puss is the best.
Yes.
Oh my god, I have so fucking hot.
Oh, is he fucking up to some good, baby?
No, no, no.
You're just trying to make me feel fucked.
oh fuck yes just like that there you go that's what i fucking wanted baby
oh yes yes that feels good doesn't it baby
like this
fuck yes
yes that's it
It came to her fucking heart.
Are you ready for it baby?
I'm going to pour it from my arm to my cookie.
That's who you are.
Oh yes, are you having fun stretching my home?
Oh yes, so much fun baby.
I'm going to give you a cup and I'm going to let you go clean.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, shit. Yes, yes.
Oh, that feels so fucking good.
Uh, yeah.
Can you wear that cuff?
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
oh yeah, today, I want to have friends and way work,
oh yeah, suck your dick on your tongue, baby,
oh, let's switch, I want to feel both dicks,
You can see what's inside me.
Yes, when I tell him all about it.
My dirty adventure.
Oh my god.
Oh yes, but you're going to save me.
Fuck.
Probably both of you are fucking me at the same time.
Yeah
Oh yeah
Oh yeah, please, please, please
Please, please, please
Oh fuck, I have been abducted
Yes, yes
Oh fuck, take me out
Oh, that's so fucking good
Oh yes, yes
Oh shit, I'm gonna cum right now
That's it, c'mon baby, c'mon
Oh my gosh!
Oh yes!
Oh shit yes yes yes yes!
Ah!
I just rubbed my fucking ass.
I don't like to see it, but it's doing it.
Ah!
Let's switch it off.
Turn it around.
I want to try your
cock in my ass now.
Oh yeah.
Yes, now my turn, baby.
My turn.
Oh, come on.
Yes.
Yes, now his.
I don't want you both inside me again, please.
Oh, my gosh.
Yes, I'm gonna rub my pussy
Yes, I'm gonna see if it's liquid
Oh, yes, please, I'm so fucking ready for more
Oh, yes, oh, shit
It's so good
oh yes please keep playing oh don't you fucking stop
oh you're gonna make me come so fucking hard again
yes yes i want to come
oh shit
oh that's so fucking good oh yeah
Yes, I love to taste your dick now.
Oh, yes.
Oh, shit.
Shit, baby.
Come around, both of you.
Oh, jeez.
which kind of made me feel like I didn't know what to do with it.
I was like, I don't know what to do with it.
I don't know what to do with it.
oh my god
i think i should sweat it
I told you she was ready thank you for making my fantasy come true
We should take a picture for your husband.
Sure.
Let's do it.
I'll pose.
With two big dicks next to my face.
You're a wild woman.
Yes.
Take care.
I'll take it.
Come here.
Okay.
naughty america nobody nobody nobody does it better