I hope it's not too much trouble.
I ah, I love your house. It's so cute
It's just about time. Don't you think I know?
So, what did you want to do tonight?
or something, it's not even a big deal.
That works too.
I'll ride with your hubby.
Okay.
Alright, well I will see you in a few hours then.
Okay, bye.
Well, I guess I have a couple hours
till I have to get ready.
Mm-hmm. What should I do? I could go for a little orgasm.
I do have a while.
Oh, fuck this.
Oh yeah, that's nice.
So what's on tap for tonight, babe?
Dinner sounds good.
No, it's going to be great to meet your friend Natasha.
You speak so highly of her.
I can't wait.
Yeah.
So what time are you off?
Oh, how many more hours?
Oh, that's not that bad though.
She's, she's here?
What happened to the hotel?
Oh, we can talk about that later.
You know, we have the guest room, so that's no problem.
It works out perfect.
Let's make her feel at home.
I see.
Okay.
Well, how about this?
I'll just bring her with me to dinner
and you can meet us there.
All right, baby.
I love you too.
Bye.
Oh
Oh my god, that was a great show I'm so sorry I didn't
I didn't realize you were home.
It's quite alright, it's quite alright.
My wife was just talking to me on the phone
and she said to be a good host and introduce myself.
So I thought I'd introduce myself.
I had a little ruckus
and wanted to make sure you were okay.
I'm okay. You're Pete, obviously.
I'm Pete.
Natasha.
Very nice to meet you.
And cute, likewise.
I'll let you get ready.
Are those completely natural? Yes, they are completely natural. I was
I had those at Taylor's, at Taylor's.
They look great.
You like them?
As you know, the missus is very petite, so...
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, this is kind of a fantasy.
Oh, God.
I mean, do you want to just...
I mean, I am in your home.
I should have married her.
I know, but it'll just be a little appetizer.
It'll just be like a little appetizer
I won't tell her
You want to cut some tie?
Ya
Those eyes
Is that okay?
Ya
Oh my goodness
Oh gosh
Haven't gotten that in a while
Oh
You're so cute
Mmhmm
I see why she
likes you
It might be a little
wet
Oh, you're really good at that.
Oh, God.
Oh, gosh, you're so good.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, look at it.
Look at it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my Lord.
Yes.
Oh.
Turn around for me please.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
You're a cute kitty.
You like it.
Oh.
Oh god.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes, like, basically.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
That's so good.
Yeah.
Yes, it is.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes, uh-huh, yes.
Yeah, but fuck me with your job.
Uh-huh.
Oh, that's a wrong chair.
Oh, I can't.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Ah.
Mm.
Yes.
Ah.
What?
Oh, you're a big, big guy.
A big guy.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yes Yes
Yes
Oh my God
Fuck
You're so sexy
Look at that sexy.
Oh, my, my.
Oh, it's a nice car.
It's okay.
It's totally fine
Oh my God, oh my God.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my God.
Oh my god.
I don't know.
Six.
Oh, God.
Oh my god.
You're so nice.
Yes.
So sexy.
You're so nice.
You like that mouth?
Yeah I love it.
I love it.
Awe, yeah.
Oh my God.
I love you.
So good.
Oh.
Ooh.
Love you.
I love you.
I love you, God.
Oh my god, I see what she's always raving about.
It's so nice in my mouth.
You want to fuck me?
Let me just taste it all.
Yeah, please.
Oh, please get it.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
No.
Okay.
I don't have any more pussy.
No, I don't.
Can I accept my destiny and walk through your pussy with my face closed?
Oh, yeah.
I love a man who eats pussy.
Oh, God.
I don't know if you can see it, but I have a lot of hair on my face.
I have a lot of hair on my face.
Oh, my God, that feels, that feels so fucking good.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Fuck you.
Totally hit me a little bit.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
You like how I fuck that cock?
I love that shit.
Yes.
Oh my God.
No.
I want you to sit on my lap.
Please.
Please. Oh my God.
I'm so fucking...
I'm just like that.
I'm gonna cry.
Oh, come on.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Oh, touch me.
Oh, my.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, it's so bad.
Oh, you're so bad.
Oh.
Yes.
No.
Don't say that.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yes, I'll be in there for you.
Oh.
Oh, my.
Yes!
Oh
If you say shit like that, you mother fucker.
Oh yes, slap yourself.
Oh my god.
Someone's excited.
You're driving me crazy.
Let me just taste it on my own.
Yes, yes, please.
Oh my god.
You're incredible.
You're so hard.
Oh, look at all this.
Oh, fuck you.
Too much?
I love you.
Just come right back to me.
No more?
No more, thanks.
Let's get out of here.
Yes.
Oh, you keep fucking me.
Yes!
Yes, please. Yes.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck me, please.
Please.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, that dick is so good.
Oh, God, it's so good.
Oh.
You're fucking sucking my dick.
You fucking pussy.
Oh my god!
I'll be laying right next to you.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
I'm beside you.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I'm dreaming you're crying.
You want me to fuck you back, yeah?
You don't want me to fuck you back.
Oh, shit.
It's just like that.
You don't want me to fuck you back.
Yeah. Oh, God.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, God, yes, yes!
Oh, oh, oh, you're so, oh my God, please don't, please don't.
Wow, baby, wow, baby.
It's okay.
Oh, man.
Oh, my God.
This is crazy.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
That's so good.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my gosh, yes!
Peter, give me the stick.
Oh, God, yes.
The stick, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, Peter.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God, yes.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Give me my bat.
Just like that.
Right here.
Right there.
Perfect.
Right here.
Just like that.
Oh my body.
Oh my-
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck it.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mmm.
Yes.
Oh, fuck. Yes.
Oh.
Ohhhh!
Oh s**t!
No!
Oh, I'm gonna put you on the top of my head over here.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Put me down.
Oh my dear.
Oh my goodness gracious.
Oh.
Oh god.
Oh yes.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Oh boy.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm all right.
Shh.
No, I'll get it.
Yes.
I want you to shut me up.
Okay.
Yeah.
Can I come over and cut your tits?
You want to come over and cut my tits?
Yeah, I want you to come over
and cut my tits.
My pretty tits.
Yes.
Fuck yes.
Oh God.
Yes.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna help you tie it up.
Yeah.
Can you do it?
Oh fuck.
Just like that.
Show me your clothes.
Show me.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Oh fuck yes.
Oh my god.
Yes, baby. Yes, look at this.
Yes.
Oh my God, look at it.
You came home lovingly.
Oh my God.
You better get cleaned up.
You definitely gotta meet my wife for dinner.
Oh my God, yes.
Um, yeah, okay, yeah.
I have to shower.
Uh-huh.
If we're gonna see her.
Yeah.
At mom's work.
Okay.
Just in case we wanna do it again.
It was very nice to meet you, Pete.