Hmm.
I love cookies.
I love when you make cookies.
Oh yea.
You know what?
I think I'm going to give you a little bit.
Oh my gosh.
You just reminded me, my stepmom is so annoying.
She just bitches about everything.
I can't take it.
Don't worry about her.
Oh, stop!
She's not that bad. I'm sure she's not that bad.
Come on. You're exaggerating.
Oh, yeah?
I'm trying to make cookies.
You're such a whore dog.
I'm not doing anything.
Yeah, okay.
I absolutely adore your body.
What can I do?
Oh
Yeah
really you're being ridiculous
your girlfriend you need to put her in check how about that
next time you guys mess with my kitchen
That's so funny!
Shut up. You should just stop talking.
And like, start home.
Okay.
Yeah, you should stop talking.
I didn't say a word. I mean...
Sorry, but like...
You should spank her.
She's your girlfriend. You need to pay her a check.
Spank me?
I'm not gonna spank her in front of you.
Do it. Do it or you can leave.
What the hell?
You guys are hilarious. I'm not kidding myself.
Punished
Yeah, oh
Yeah
This will teach you guys to mess with my house.
I'm not cleaning these up.
You're cleaning everything.
I'm gonna make you one of those.
Stop it.
Stupid Adam and Cookies, man.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Ah!
Oh, my gosh.
Slut.
Are you guys in the same kitchen?
Oh, my gosh!
Ah!
OK, OK, OK.
Oh, my gosh.
Ah, shit.
Oh my gosh, oh fuck, no fuck, oh yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, you like that, you like that punishment?
Yeah, I mean, what the fuck do you want me to do?
It's so good, oh, you call this a punishment?
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm,
I know I'm so messy I like your step mom more now
oh yeah she's cool
oh my gosh
Oh yeah, you're gonna spank me?
I'm gonna fuck your boyfriend as punishment.
Wait, you're gonna fuck my boyfriend?
What the fuck?
Okay, thanks.
You like them?
Yeah, that's great.
He likes it.
I mean, whatever you want.
You're pretty fuckin' hot.
Your boobs are so cute.
Oh my gosh.
Gosh, this is what they look like. They're fuckin' cute.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh gosh.
Look, you know my real mom.
I'm excited.
Start the scene with a little smile.
Yeah.
Take it off.
Stop talking.
hair.
It's a lot.
eeeeeeh
mmmm
mmmmm
flowers
that's just so hot
oh my god
ahhh yes yes
yes
I really wanted cookies, but our love is dead, so.
You're going to watch me suck your boyfriend's cock now?
Okay.
You're gonna watch me suck your boyfriend's cock now?
That's pretty intense for the first time with your stepmom.
Really?
You better enjoy that.
Watch me.
I'm watching you.
You like getting a stick in your mouth?
Wow, she's good at this.
Okay.
Wasn't she a joy to do it with her?
Oh, my arm is so red.
Okay, so now we have to stop talking.
I don't know what to do.
I thought it was the other way.
I was like, oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
and
it
the
and
Yeah, I love it, it's great.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
You're in my house, you do what I say.
Oh my god, your steak is so good, are you going to give me a cookie?
Oh yeah, you want a cookie?
This is flour, I have to eat it.
Uh huh, I told you to clean it.
Oh my god!
Fuck!
So good, bye.
Oh my gosh.
Does he fuck you guys?
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Are you always this annoying when he fucks you?
Yes.
Probably.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, you look cute.
You little fuck.
Yes.
Yes, buzzy.
You look good to my face.
Oh my god.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, yeah, I like the band-aid.
Oh, it's right under you.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Yes, make her.
Oh, fuck, that's so hot.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
You're so sensitive.
Yeah, I can see you.
Oh my gosh.
It's so good.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Me neither.
Get the fuck in.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Fuck.
Ah.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Okay, it's your turn, honey.
Oh, it's my turn.
Yes.
How do I get it?
How do you want me to eat?
Like this?
This too?
Oh yeah, stick it in my face!
Yes!
Really?
Come on!
Oh, bud!
Oh my god, yes, yes.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck me.
Oh, the cock is so fucking good.
Good, good, good.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my God!
Yes, I love you, I love you!
Yes, I love you!
Oh, I love you, I love you!
I love you so much!
Oh, my gosh!
It's okay, come on.
I hope you have a mind.
You're so dirty.
You're the dirty one.
You got your flower, you had your cookies.
You're a nice doofy doofy.
I'm so sorry.
This is the worst punishment ever.
Stop it.
Just shut up.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
Don't rub that too close.
Kick it.
Kick that calf.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Easy.
That one was a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You guys look so cute.
Yeah.
Touch my foot.
Oh.
Oh, you guys.
You look pretty.
Hey.
Oh.
Got a little messy.
Oh, bye.
Ah.
Oh.
Oh my god, oh my god, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god.
Are you going to come?
Oh, you fucked it so good.
Oh my god, are you going to come?
Oh my god, yes.
Yeah, make her come, make her come.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, Buddy!
Oh my god, oh shhh!
Oh my god!
Come, come, come on.
Oh my god, oh my god!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, shit!
You wanna make more friends?
What is it?
Let's make more friends.
You want to? Oh, God.
You wanna make more friends?
Oh, you're terrible.
Oh my god, you're such a...
Oh, what are you doing?
Come here.
Hey, you're such a slut.
Oh, you're such a slut.
You're the only best thing ever.
Huh?
Come on, I want the car.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my gosh.
Yes.
Oh my gosh!
Yes!
Oh!
Funky!
Yes yes yes yes!
He's so good!
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Yes!
It's so deep yes!
Oh Funky he's so good!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh Funky!
Oh my god yes!
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh, yes.
Oh
It's just
Oh, fuck, oh my God, yes.
Oh my gosh.
Just a second.
Oh, me.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
How are you?
It's all right.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I can't even talk.
Yeah, I can't talk.
No, I'm fine.
It's just a teeny mess.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know what to do.
Take your knife.
Mm-hmm.
Here.
Feet.
All of them are beautiful.
Oh, they're beautiful...
Really...
Nice...
Very...
Oh,
beautiful...
Oh...
Wow...
What a beautiful family.
Yes...
Yeah.
Yeah...
All of them...
Look at that, I'm having so much fun here.
I know.
I love this.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna hold back, I'm gonna hold back to this.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Oh, you're all messy.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah.
You get dirty too.
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
Oh.
You're like a pussy.
Oh my God. Yes.
Yes.
Oh shit.
Oh my God.
Oh Jesus.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
It's a fucking Jesus.
It's so fucking huge.
That ass is out of his head.
Fuck him. Fuck him.
Oh!
Ow.
Oh, fuck.
Mm.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, hey, guys.
Balance on my cock.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Yeah, I am good.
Oh, yeah, balance on my cock.
Oh, yeah.
Work that cock.
muah muah muah.
oh my god yes!
yeah with this fucking costume oh yeah!
oh my god yeah!
muah muah muah
oh my god
yeah
so wet
muah muah
oh my god
yeah
oh fuck
oh my god
yeah worth that ass, worth that ass
I don't want you to come again.
Oh, you guys are so good.
I just don't want you to come again.
I know.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, work that cough.
Fuck, work that cough.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
Taste it, taste it.
Oh my God.
I don't want to go back to the cops.
Write it, write it, write it.
Thank you.
Okay.
It's so fucking important.
Oh my God.
Fuck yes.
Come on miss.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
Oh, shit.
Thank you.
Oh, God.
Just like that.
Oh, shit.
ah
oh
oh yeah
oh my god
oh
ah
oh yeah
ya
yeah
you are making me butts all
Oh. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Told you she's better than cookies.
Yeah.
Way better than cookies.
Oh, fuck.
Ah.
Oh my god.
Yeah, it's nice and slow.
Yeah, it's just enough.
So sexy.
That's good to the floor.
Let's get to the floor.
One more.
Second coffee.
Yeah.
Oh.
oh
yeah
uh
oh
mm
Mmm, I want some coffee.
Sure.
Mmm.
Yeah, she's so generous.
Yeah, she's so nice.
She's so fucking nice.
Oh, fuck.
Mmm.
Oh.
Yes.
Okay.
Really?
Get those pussies up to you.
Yeah.
In the air, like this?
I don't know why he's never done this with me.
Oh.
Oh my god!
Yes, yes, yes!
Give me all that coffee.
Yeah, give me all that coffee.
Yeah, yeah. Yes, yes.
Here we go.
Oh, fun.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, man.
So messy.
Oh, my gosh.
More mess.
Yeah! Yeah! Fuck it, my face!
Yeah, baby!
You want to mess up your face?
Yeah!
Come over here.
Huh?
Oh, you want to mess up?
You want to mess it up?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Oh
Shit
Keep crossing for the cookies!
That was the worst punishment I've ever gotten in my life.
Yeah, you still have to clean the kitchen though.
I don't know about that.
Clean the kitchen.