Gross. Seriously?
Get over him, dude.
What, is my little bro upset he doesn't have his own girlfriend?
Your own girlfriend?
Uh, I mean, I'd say so, yeah.
Yeah, I hate to break it to you, bro, but she's everybody's girlfriend.
Hey, what the fuck?
Yeah, man, yeah, that's for real.
Bye, man.
You'll see him soon enough.
That was intense.
intense.
Yeah, he can be a little headstrong sometimes,
but he's my little bro, so I'll be all of them.
Yeah.
You know what, I'm gonna go check on him.
What?
Are you ready for round two already?
Um, relax.
I'm not here to fight.
In fact, I actually wanted to apologize.
And how do you plan on doing that?
Well.
Angela, you coming back?
Uh, yeah babe, just a second.
I'll just have to wait to find out.
Well, how's it going in there?
Oh, um, well, I think he's just going to need a little bit more time to cool off.
Well, where were we?
Okay.
Mmm.
Oh.
Oh
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Yeah.
Why does that feel good?
Oh fuck.
Let me chill around that titty.
Oh fuck baby, you took me on so much.
I was feeling that fucking hot cock between them.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Shut up.
No hands.
Oh, fuck you.
Come back here.
I want you to fuck my face.
Yeah.
Let's see, let's just bounce around here.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Well, um, I'm going to go freshen up a little bit and, um, I'm going to go check on him
I'm too.
Come here.
Whoa, whoa, um.
Hey, why do you look so surprised?
I didn't think, um.
Don't just look like such a little bitch.
I want your cock.
What is that on your face?
What, where?
Right there.
What?
Oh.
Oh, that's just mayonnaise.
I don't know sugar tits
Looks like condiment
You are dirty little slut aren't you
Yeah dirty little sluts do what do they do let me put in whatever hole I want
oh my god
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yeah.
I fucking love it.
Eat that pussy, too.
I want you to go all the way from my clit up my crack.
All the way from that clit up my pussy into my asshole.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, that feels so good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, don't even bounce that off of your face.
Just keep that tongue out.
Yeah.
Fuck, it's so good.
Yes, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm
Oh, fuck, yeah, oh, that's so good, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm gonna use that, oh, fuck,
Oh f**k! Yes!
Oh god! Yeah, I'm washing my f**king arse
You can get deeper than that
Stick that tongue in deep
Yes!
Oh f**k!
Yeah, tongue f**ked my arse
Oh s**t! Yes, yes, yes!
Fuck. Oh my god. Fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I keep going. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Oh shit. Fuck. Don't stop. Oh yeah. Look at that. Fuck. Oh fuck. Oh shit. Fuck. Oh my god. Yeah.
Yeah, mmm, let me taste that, Duke.
Yeah, let me fucking taste that.
Holy fuck.
Nice and hot, okay?
Holy shit.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
You're such a dirty little slut.
Look at you go.
Fuck.
Grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr, grr.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
Oh my god, you're so much better than your brother.
Shit.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
He may be older, but he'll know what he's done.
I don't know where the fuck you learned how to do that but I am so fucking happy that you did
oh my god
I'm fucking crazy with that song yeah
Oh my god, oh fuck, stick your fingers inside me too, oh my god, fuck, yeah, oh my god,
Take that off, take that off, yes, mmm, mmm, oh my god baby, fuck, yes, yeah, oh, oh, fuck,
Fuck, you know I want that dick.
You know I fucking want that dick.
Yeah, tease me with it, baby.
Yes.
You're like a dead fucking pussy.
Oh, God.
I love the way you fucking tease that clip.
Just the tip.
Yeah, tease me with it.
Fuck.
Holy shit, it's so big.
Oh, God, yes.
Shit! Fuck! Oh my god!
Fuck!
Oh my god, that fucking cock fills me up so good!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Holy shit! Fuck!
Oh, it's so fucking big, god damn it, baby.
It's just a fucking tiny little thing.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to make a fucking hole like that all over that dick.
Yeah.
Those big fucking titties.
Oh, my god.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, my god, baby.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, my.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Don't come, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
I don't want that fucking cock in my house.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Holy shit.
Oh my god that fucking cock shit is so big.
Oh fuck baby.
Yes.
Oh shit.
shit oh my god yeah oh my god baby
oh shit oh my god holy shit oh you're so fucking good with that oh my god oh shit yeah oh my god
Oh my god, that sounds so fucking good, it feels so fucking good, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh
Oh, yes, baby, fuck, yeah, don't you dare fucking stop, don't you dare fucking stop,
yes, yes, take my fucking ass, take it, oh, shit, yes, yes, yes, take my slutty little
ass, fuck, yes, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, let me get the fuck, yes, fuck, let me take the
Yeah, it's fine. Let me taste my fucking arsehole too.
Right off that dick.
Oh, you like that fucking thing in your nose when you suck that dick?
Mm-hmm. It's so fucking good, baby. Everything you do smells so good.
Oh yeah, back in my house.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, holy shit baby, fuck, yeah, oh my god, I feel so fucking
good, shit, holy shit, oh my god, are you running out of steam baby, oh my god, oh my
I know you're running out of fucking steam, I know you've got more in you, I know you've got fucking more in you, give it to me, fuck, oh my god, you, those are my fucking holidays baby, yeah, yeah, yeah, mmm, fuck, oh shit, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, like that made me fucking cum, yes, fuck, yes, give it to me, oh my god, don't you fucking, so, yes, do it, do it, do it,
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, do
Oh my god, even your fingers in my eyes feel so fucking good.
Holy shit.
You want to get really fucking dirty?
Fuck yeah.
Come with me.
Sit down.
Let me scoot down that way.
Yeah, I'm stripping in that ass, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, this is gonna fucking tease you with that ass, right at the tip like that, oh, fuck, oh, yeah, slide all the way down that tip, oh, my God, yeah, oh, shit, yeah,
Oh my god, it feels so tight.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god.
Yeah, it feels so tight.
Yeah, you like it when I fucking bounce my ass in your cup like that?
Yes, fuck.
Oh fuck, I feel so good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's like I'm in this big fucking shit.
Oh my god, baby, fuck, you're so deep in that ass.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
You're a dirty little fucking cunt.
Yeah.
Oh god, yes.
Yeah, it's right there.
Yeah, you want me to fucking slap you?
Yeah.
Yes.
I feel like I didn't want to.
Yeah.
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yeah, I got to say that.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh my god!
Yes, yes, yes.
Fucking pussy and clit grinding up on me.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
It's the fucking clit.
Oh my god.
Yeah like that. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Yes yes yes. Oh shit. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh yeah let me taste it. Oh fuck yeah. Oh fuck yeah.
mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
I got balls deep in the nose
that's why you love it
you better take every inch
yeah
oh yeah
fuck
yeah
oh my god fuck fuck fuck
yes
oh
oh so good
fuck fuck fuck
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
I'm gonna squeeze you right between these two, yeah.
Oh my God, yeah, why you play with that ass?
Holy shit, that felt so good, baby.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God, baby.
Yeah, your fingers are just as good
as your fucking tongue and your cock.
Holy shit.
Oh yeah, I want you to fucking bend me over.
I want you to take me back in there and bend me over.
Yeah.
I just want you to bend you over and fuck me over the tub.
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to do the fucking good at everything.
Oh my god.
Fuck, baby.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, baby.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Fuck, yeah, yeah, oh shit, oh my god, it's so fucking deep, yes, oh, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh yeah, let me fucking go, let me go, let me go, yes, yes, yes, holy shit, fuck, fuck,
Oh my god, it's so fucking big, shit, oh fuck you, oh shit, oh fuck you, oh fuck you, oh
Oh
My god, yes fuck
Fuck, yeah, yeah, oh god, oh fuck, okay, I'm gonna fucking like, yes, oh shit, oh my god, that's so fucking good, oh shit, fuck, oh fuck, oh my god, yes, yeah, yeah,
Oh, so fucking good, yeah.
Oh, shit, baby, fuck.
Oh my God, fuck, yes.
Oh, so fucking good like that, yeah.
Oh, so fucking cheap and little.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes.
Mm, I'm excited, that little fucking click.
Oh my god, fuck, that's so good, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it,
I can't fucking feel it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, give it to me, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, baby, give me that fucking cum all over your face, yeah, yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Shit, you're fucking incredible.
She's a dirty little slut.
What the fuck?
Sorry bro, I told you she was a slut.