give you your special gift I have a special delivery from Santa but I'm
panties.
Don't you love the way it shows off my curves?
And what do you think of these boots?
I knew you would love it.
You want to see these tits so badly, don't you?
You like the way they jiggle and bounce?
I love making them bounce for you.
I like teasing you with them.
Don't you want to come over here?
Would you have some fun with me?
I want you to come over here and unwrap me.
Do you like it when I tease you?
Think about all the naughty things you want to do to me.
I'm going to put my little hood back on.
I think I've teased you long enough.
I think you deserve to see these.
Want to see the other one?
I like what this does to you.
I like how hard it gets you.
Why don't you just slide your cock in between them?
Fuck these big natural tits.
You've got so horny feet.
I think it's time for you to see your gift.
It's kind of a gift for both of us.
I want you right in between there.
No hands.
Just fuck my big tits.
Oh, that feels so good.
I'm going to twist them.
Ooh.
Stays right in there.
There's somewhere else I'd like you to be.
Slide your cock inside my pussy.
Oh god, that feels so good.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, that feels so good.
Oh.
Yes, like that.
Oh, you're getting my pussy so close.
Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
oh my god fuck you're gonna make me come like that oh yes oh my god fuck
oh yes
merry christmas baby