You know, I can't believe it.
It's really coming together, isn't it?
Oh my God, honey.
All our hard work, it's just...
I'm so proud of you.
Just think, tomorrow people are actually gonna be here.
We could actually get reviewed.
This is a dream.
Ah, did someone say dream? I used to dream, you know.
Excuse me, who are you?
Ah, building inspector. I've been tasked with inspecting this shithole.
Oh great, the city, they said you're going to...
They're the city, say a lot of things like that.
I'm going to give it to you straight.
This place is an absolute dump, not even close to code.
What? Really?
What?
You know, the septic tank is back top.
The wiring, have you seen this?
Looks like the wiring's been done by monkeys.
They wouldn't understand building codes, right?
But Jack's put his whole life savings into this.
The contractor... Yeah, it was a crook.
Look, they're all crooks, all of them.
Look, I'm sorry to break it, but this place is a shithole.
It's just not up to par.
Really?
Well, honey, do something.
Um, listen, the electrical, I can handle that.
And I can drain the septic system,
and that's not a problem.
You know what, let me go and start taking care of that,
honey, and you just deal with the inspector, OK?
Okay.
So, uh, Mr...
Name's, uh, Kieran.
What can I do for you?
Uh, well, Kieran, I was hoping maybe you could, uh,
run through some of the other issues with me?
Look, I see the twinkle in your eye, but this place,
three to four months minimum before it opens up.
No, that's not possible. We have reservations.
There must be something that we can do.
Miss?
What?
Did you know it took us seven years in jail for trying to bribe a building inspector?
Who said anything about a bribe?
I just thought that maybe we could come to a mutually beneficial arrangement.
Jesus!
What the f***?
Oh, God.
Oh, Annie?
Oh, um, hey.
I gotta run to the hardware store real quick and pick up some supplies.
Oh, uh, okay.
Okay. Um, yeah, well, I'll just, uh, keep, uh, checking the pipes with Kieran. Isn't that right?
Yeah, yeah. A lot of work to do here, mate. A lot of work to do.
Okay, well, I'll be right back, then.
Okay.
Shh. Hold it.
Oh, my. Yeah, that's not...
Pretty much. That's it, mate.
That's it.
Oh, shit, shit.
Look at that.
Oh, that's good.
Shit.
Look at that.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
This.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Oh my god, that's a big fucking dent.
Do that, do that, do that, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's
it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
Do that, do that, do that. That's it. That's nice.
Man, I fucked his big tits.
Yeah.
Put it back in there.
Oh, no. Put it in there.
You'll spit on them and fuck them too.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, I fucked his big tits.
Mmm.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh yeah, you know I'll do anything to make sure my restaurant closes for safety, at least
that you have.
I hope you have a first aid kit.
I'll look into it.
Oh my god, I know you fucking did it.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Just keep it there.
Keep it there.
Oh, yes.
Oh shit, oh my god, fuck, yes, yes, oh my god, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, this is so good, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, yes, oh my god, this is so fucking good, it's like, oh my god, fuck, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh shit, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god that's fucking juicy.
Ah, sit down, fucking sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down,
sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down,
sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down,
Oh shit, fuck, oh my god, fuck, oh shit, yeah, oh, I'm tasting both of those ones.
Oh, my God.
I just took that fucking dick all the way down my throat and made me choke on it.
And I want you to take every one of my fucking holes.
Yeah.
Yeah, like that daddy fucking asshole.
Alright.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Yeah, oh shit, oh my god, oh my god, fuck, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, shit, yes.
Spread it again.
And as you spread it, push it back in.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, yes.
God!
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Nice, nice, nice.
Good.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my fucking head.
Stay, stay.
Breathe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck, oh, yes, oh my god, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh shit, yeah,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Yes.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Holy shit! Oh my god!
Oh fuck!
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah, let me heat that up.
Get all that. Get it from there.
You know?
Yeah.
Oh, God. Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
In my arms.
Yeah.
Yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, oh, my God, holy fuck, oh, my God, oh, fuck, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh my god, I can feel it, yes, oh my god, yes, I feel it, I feel it, I feel it, I feel
It's so good. Yeah. Oh, like that. Fuck.
I hear what you do to me. I hear what you do to me. I hear what you do to me. Yes, please.
Oh, you're going to make me cum so hard. You're going to make me cum so hard.
Oh, shit. Yes. Oh, fuck. Yes. Yes. Yes. Keep going. Keep going. Go, go, go.
You can go now.
Yes!
That's it. Keep going.
Keep trying.
It's okay. Keep going.
Keep going.
Keep rolling it out.
Yes! Holy fuck!
Yeah, you see my fucking pussy moving in and out, holy fuck, yeah, yeah, holy shit, oh my gosh, you fucking do, oh my god, yes, oh shit, yeah, oh my god, I got these fucking huge cells right up in my face like this, yeah, oh fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
oh yeah oh shit yes oh fuck that's so good yes yes yes yes yes yes yes holy fuck oh my god
yes yes do it do it do it do it hold me there like that yes yes yes yes yes
Shhh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
I want to fucking work it, I want to fucking work it, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, oh, oh my god, fuck, oh, oh, yes, so good, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah,
Yeah, look what you're doing.
Oh my god, you're opening that up so wide.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Yes, yes, do it, do it, do it, do it.
Fuck.
Oh, that's so good.
Oh my god, fuck, yes, oh shit, yeah, yeah, oh my god, yeah, my ears fucking come like
that, yeah, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, oh.
Oh, yeah, fill up my pussy, too. Fill up my pussy, too.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah. Oh, fuck.
Yeah. This is fucking good.
This is fucking good. Fuck. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, keep your arse up like that.
Keep your fucking arms up like that.
Oh my god.
Bring it forward.
Come here.
Keep your arms up.
Oh yeah.
Come, come, come.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Oh yeah.
Can you understand how much you fucking stretch it?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
Put your fingers in your cunt.
Put your fingers in.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, I can feel it.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Stay there.
Huh?
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Oh, my god.
Fuck.
Oh, that's so good.
Oh, fuck.
That's so fucking beautiful.
Yes.
That's so beautiful.
No, no, no, no.
Oh my god, stay, stay down, come this way, stay down, come this way, come this way, come
Come, come, come. That's it.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Oh.
Oh, my shit. Come, come, come, come.
Turn around.
Turn. Turn, turn, turn.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God. Fuck.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, holy shit, yeah, oh my god, yeah, yeah, that feels so fucking good, shit, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god, fuck.
Oh, fuck, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yeah, that feels so fucking good. Yeah. Yeah. Oh my god. Yes. Yes
Oh my god, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
He gave me all that fucking cum.
He does!
Oh!
Oh my god!
Shit!
Oh, bless you.
Oh my god, it tastes so good Honey, there's no contract, everything's
done What the fuck?
You know, we're all done here, everything is looking great
Wait, I can't, Andrew, I can't believe you.
Um, so does that mean we pass the inspection?
You know what, we all have dreams,
and you made a lonely building
inspect if dreams come true.
Oh, thank you so much.
All right.
Whew.