hundred percent down for not a lot of experience but you did do you worked
yeah all right I can't remember what else is on that list but I was
they'll bruise really easily.
Cause I know that was one of the conditions of us.
like a week before Christmas and you bruise really easy.
Thank you. That's really awesome
Gags jaw pain will play this. Yeah, so I
So I once yeah, I've used ones before that like even after 10 minutes
Yeah.
Um, and everything else is kind of this, this, um, humiliation.
psychological domination.
to me and kind of fuck with me like that.
Right.
So, humiliation might be used in that, but I don't...
So, and it kind of depends.
I don't give a fuck what you say to me.
You can say whatever you want.
I don't care.
And we referred to her as just a paycheck.
And it broke her heart.
I doubt that will happen.
I just was curious about.
Well, we're going to take our time.
We're going to build up to it.
So know that we're going to start with me kind of feeling you out.
I like that.
Good.
I've spent 10 minutes.
way that you know it really resonates with them I think what you do is
beautiful just aesthetically it's beautiful so I guess it's it's not just
And we'll talk to you afterwards.
Yep.
Tell your parents bye.
Bye.
I'm so excited, I'm just like, I'm sweating.
First,
I'm gonna put in this.
Sensitive.
Start with not so mean.
Okay.
Yeah, that's not too bad, right?
No, it's nice.
Now you're awake.
Yeah.
Place me. Turn all the way around.
Stop right there.
Oh
We're going to let that drool come out as much as it wants.
We're not going to fight it.
Oh
Nothing zero
On a one to ten, what was that on your pussy?
Um, um, seven.
Good. That's what I thought too.
Just making sure we get a good read, an accurate read on little squeals.
So if I turn it up a little bit.
Have you ever actually had someone put these on your feet before?
Never.
Never?
You feel like your feet are well taken care of down here too.
So, I can't, you know what, I don't know.
I quit guessing a long time ago because I've done this before
and girls squeal and scream and there's other girls that giggle.
What do you think it's going to feel like?
I think it's going to feel good.
You think so?
Would that be the symbol or the sign you're making?
It feels good?
If that's the case, I bet there's a lot of confused people
I need to pull any of that stuff out of the bucket.
That's the sensitive.
Surprisingly, this right here,
I'm not gonna pull as hard,
because that's just a sting.
It almost hurts your feelings.
Stop it!
It feels horrible.
It does.
You know what it feels horrible about?
Cries.
That was right.
You know what hurts worse than just one of these?
Two.
like, well, where's the air going to come from?
I look scary in there, doesn't I?
Oh my god.
Yes, you!
Oh my god. Yes.
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Awww
Oh my god I'm so close
So close to
Shit
Fuck
Oh fuck can I cum?
Fuck fuck fuck
Oh shit
Oh my god
I'm so close
Fuck
Fuck!
Don't choke yourself.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh fuck.
Such a polite woman.
Let's do this.
Is it sensitive right now?
Yeah.
Really sensitive?
Oh.
How good you are being a slut.
Oh, that's all the way down.
You trying to become my new favorite?
You're doing a good job, I can tell you that.
Thank you, sir.
Yes.
Let's see.
Tougher than I thought.
Now, this way, where I'm gonna show you pain.
I've never been known to lie about this.
I'm gonna show you the pain
you never even thought existed before.
Oh, God.
There's no God.
It's just you and me.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, oh, shit, fuck.
Fuck!
And you think that was bad, that's just the warm up.
Oh god!
Take a breath, you ready?
Yes.
This is the one that I like the most.
Ready? Yes. Say please.
Yes please sir.
We don't have you walking around A.V.N. with a fucking limp.
You're getting used to this.
Say please.
Please, sir.
Did I lie to you?
No, sir.
started
i bet you are fun to fuck aren't you there it goes
There it is, right there.
I like it right there.
Thank you, sir.
Try it again.
There it is.
You can feel it right there.
Ah!
Oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, fuck, oh, thank you so, fuck, oh, oh, fuck.
Look down here, slut, look down here, there we go.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, thank you so much.
Oh my god.
Oh yes.
Oh, can I come, sir?
Come.
Keep coming.
We're not finished yet.
Oh no!
I don't know what, little girl.
Little pussy had too much?
Yes.
Oh my god, what is that?
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Hi, Angela.
Hi.
How are you feeling?
Really good.
So, we just wrapped up your hogtie.
Your first.
Yes.
Major, we didn't talk about this in the beginning.
Um, so I guess this would be your technical first big bondage scene.
Yes.
Um, it seems successful.
What'd you think?
Yeah, I think so.
I don't know.
You tell me.
I fucking thought it was hot as hell.
Thanks.
I had fun.
This is not what we're shooting today.
I would've really liked you to use your real penis.
I don't know if I'm allowed to say that.
That would've been great.
It's okay to say that.
Yeah.
Bring the dildo back over.
with the anticipation that I was fearful
and I thought that I would just,
but I kind of feel like crying now though.
So like with all the adrenaline,
so it's not, crying isn't necessarily about pain or,
or even fear or anticipation, it's just a release.
And so like now I'm like, I feel like I've got so much.
Well, all the endorphins are going and stuff.
So yeah, it's kind of like, and that's it.
And we talk about this a lot with,
especially bondage models, like that's like their thing.
And they're like, oh sure, I'll go do the porn,
this stuff you know the endorphins everything so you've got like all kind
just like, fuck, you know what?
I'm okay.
Everything's a little better now that it was.
It's not a sign of weakness.
It's just a sign of like releasing.
Just release.
It feels like you're releasing toxins, you know, like negative energies.
Exactly.
God, it was just that easy, right?
Yeah.
I have to do a lot of crying, but I can clean my whole body out.
So anyway, before we get too deep into that stuff.
So we, like I said, we had two suspensions, which is kind of uncommon.
if I felt it coming or like tried to catch you.
And then we had the first one where it was kind of
to get to know you, but it was very,
and like I said, from the time I walked in,
like you very much, and it's super hot,
but like you sexualized it.
Like I think there's a little dirty girl,
dirtier girl inside that just got kind of
woke up a little bit.
I have this weird thing where I can sexualize anything
though, it's kind of, I don't know.
I can sexualize a table, I can sexualize a chair.
life is like this sexual moment.
So, but that was not something I had to try and sexualize.
That was just sexy.
Right.
It was hot.
But you're sexy.
Thanks.
Yeah.
That's why all the girls fall in love with you.
I learned today.
Now you know.
I'd already been told by everyone like, I'm just.
You're going to love him so much.
Yeah.
tip of that cane and tap girls on the cervix with it before.
So it just depends like you hated me all of a sudden.
So we put it again.
It depends.
up a little.
Um, what was your favorite part?
Oh gosh.
Okay.