pussy gets so wet thinking about you, rubbing that cock for me, do it.
up to that head, squeeze it tight for me.
out onto you.
Yeah, you wanna see my big tits bounce, don't you?
You wanna imagine you're taking me from the heart,
grabbing onto my hips, swinging those big tits.
Yeah, do it.
Grab onto me hard.
Dig your fingers into my flesh.
And I feel those balls slapping against my clit while you fuck me.
What you do to those big tits?
Those big soft natural tits bouncing while you slam into me.
Yeah, like grind that pussy back onto you.
I'm gonna bounce that ass on your face
and just stick that tongue out and I'll ride it.
Fuck, you know what you do to me.
You drive me crazy.
The way that you touch me.
The way that you lick me.
The way that you fuck me.
I'm gonna sit on your face and jiggle my asshole over it.
Shoot a lick from my clit all the way to my asshole.
I just ride that face.
Grab onto those cheeks.
I like it when I twerk on your face.
But you know I want that dick back inside me.
Don't you want to feel those warm pussy lips around your shaft?
Want me to ride you, huh?
Should I lay down and get on top of you
and just ride you till I comb that big dick
all the way up inside me and that clit rubbing right on you.
And look up at me and see these big tits bouncing while I ride you.
Does that make you want to come?
Hearing those big tits, hearing them collapse, they ride.
Yeah, I'm gonna fucking grind that clit onto you until I come.
I'm gonna use your body.
Come on you.
Yes.
Oh my god, fuck.
Come here and lick up my juices.
Good boy.
Keep eating that pussy.
I'll do that stuff until I come
Oh, fuck
Oh, yes
Yeah, oh my god
Fuck
Yes, yeah
Oh, yeah
Keep looking
Oh, fuck
Oh my god, you're gonna make me come
Oh
Oh, fuck
Fuck.