with 200 gallons of gas, I mean...
No, those aren't the numbers.
Oh, my God. This is so frustrating.
Well, um, I may have an idea,
just to sort of, um, put your head back in the game.
What's that, babe?
Get a little bit excited.
Oh, shit.
That'll definitely do it.
Hey, kids, what are you doing?
Oh, my God.
Just some studying going on.
Yeah, just studying for my pilot's license, you know?
Trying to get it.
Helping him out.
Hey, sweetie, did your mom leave any leftovers?
I don't think so.
Probably have to get more.
Well, beers, well, maybe something to drink.
Oh my god.
Alright, well Bondi, I'm just getting this Brewski here.
Alright sir, good to see you.
Bye.
Oh my god.
Let me see him.
Let me see the car please.
Please.
I want to see him.
Let me see him.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's the biggest stick I've ever seen.
Oh my god, it's enormous.
Oh, it's like a, like a G8 or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
There you go.
Can I suck it?
Of course babe, come on.
I love you so much.
Oh my god, yeah, it's right there.
Oh yeah, it's just right there.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, yeah, it's right there.
Oh my god, right there.
Oh fuck.
Holy shit.
That is so fucking good.
Oh, you fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's so fucking big.
Oh, fuck.
It's huge.
Come on, get up.
That's my little guy.
Look at him.
He doesn't eat anything.
He don't eat anything.
You have to stop doing that.
Fuck.
I'm not doing that.
I know.
I can't do that.
You can do it.
That's good.
I can do it.
Sit in my lap.
Okay.
You need to stand up.
I can't do that.
Sit in my lap.
Okay.
I can't do it.
Just sit down.
All right, sit down.
Sit in my lap.
Come on.
Okay.
I'm not doing that.
Oh, my god.
Okay.
Sit in my lap.
Come on.
Oh my God.
Give me those titties.
Give me those titties right there.
Give me my titties.
No, give me those titties right there.
Yeah.
You want them like that?
Stop.
No, look at me.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Hey, you like that?
You like that?
You like my mouth on that big cock?
Yeah.
Hey, kids.
Oh, it's just you.
Hey, what's up, buddy?
Oh, I'm still hungry.
What can I eat?
Well, when in doubt,
have another one.
Yo, where's my daughter?
She actually went to the bathroom.
The guest bath, the one over there?
Yes, buddy.
Listen, tell her I need to talk to her.
She's got to come see me in my room.
I'm watching my shows. I might fall asleep before she gets there.
But I need to talk to her about something, alright?
Yeah, definitely, sir.
Alright, you let her know.
Alright, buddy.
Holy shit.
Shut up.
It's a crazy, f*****g s**t.
Really f*****g?
Yeah, it's s**t.
Can you suck on that big dick?
There you go.
Oh my God, put those titties back on it.
Put those titties back on it.
Yeah, there you go.
It's a f*****g big titty.
It's a big cock.
It's flapping, yeah.
It should move a bit, yeah.
There you go, yeah.
Can you get my pilot's license?
Uh-huh.
You're going to be up there in the cockpit, sucking me up.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
It's so fucking good.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna go to the desk,
get it all comfortable over there.
Okay, that's it.
You got like 30 minutes.
Okay.
Yes.
I can't believe you're a fucking asshole.
This is so fucking weird.
Oh my god, I asked.
Oh, shut up.
Like that? You didn't like that?
You didn't like that?
No?
Oh my gosh, don't make me a fucking god.
Oh, you're the fucking stupidest guy ever.
You're the one who shooed me out.
Oh my god, I need to pass your test.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, there we go.
There we go.
Oh yeah, right there.
Right in the fucking cut.
Right in the fucking cut, ah.
She's not ready.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
You you you
you're killing me now.
You're killing me now.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh my god.
You're here.
Oh.
No.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh.
Mmm.
Fuck.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck!
It's over. It's over.
Oh my god.
Oh.
All right.
I'm sorry.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh god.
Give me that.
Damn.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
Please give me a sign!
I'm going to give up!
I don't know what to do...
Oh shit...
Oh no!
Yes...
Oh...
Jesus!
Jesus, you do this!
I don't know what to...
I don't know what to do!
Oh!
Oh my God.
Get up.
Fuck us.
Oh my God.
I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck.
Mm-hmm, yes.
Oh, God.
I'm gonna kill you.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
There you go.
OK.
What the fuck?
Give me a pussy.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Oh.
Yes.
Mm.
Oh, fuck yes.
Fuck.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, it's so good.
Oh, this is so fucking good.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, thank you, thank you so much.
Come on, be fine.
Yes.
Honey.
Jeez.
Oh fuck, yes, yes, yes, you're fine, yes.
Oh my god, yes I am!
Oh fuck, yes I am!
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
This is so good!
Oh fuck!
Oh fuck, yes!
Fuck!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh, shit, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh my god.
Oh, you're so fucking genius, I mean, god, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, oh, shit.
Mm.
Oh, you're so cute.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, make me fucking sick.
That's what you're talking about.
Oh.
Yeah.
Make me.
Fuck.
Yeah.
I'm so excited.
Oh my god.
You're going to like this.
Oh, shh.
Yes.
Oh my fucking god.
This is so fucking good.
I just want to fucking come in.
And you want to come in a little closer.
I'm not done yet.
I want to have a more fucking, more of that feeling.
Oh, shh.
Oh.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh!
Oh, fuck you!
You!
Oh!
Oh my God, I can't see you!
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Oh my God, you took so good!
Fuck!
Oh!
Oh, yes!
Oh, fuck, get away there.
You little damn punch.
You stink, you little punch.
Oh, shit, oh, sick, ow, fuck.
Oh, fu-
oh my god
oh
I'm gonna hang you up.
Get over here.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
And please make me come back!
Please make me come to you!
Please make me come with you!
Oh!
Oh! Fuck you!
Oh my God!
I'm gonna fucking come to you, I'm so...
Oh!
Oh! Fuck you!
Yeah.
Pinkies?
Oh, here.
Yeah.
Here.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Shh.
Oh.
Yes!
Kill me, fucking yes!
Oh, oh, oh, shit!
Oh, oh, yes, yeah, I think.
I think I'm gonna forget this evil spirit.
Oh, oh, yes, oh my god, yes!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, shit!
Oh, god.
Oh, no.
You're so bad.
Oh, god.
Oh, no.
Oh, fuck.
No.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh
Oh, you can keep dancing.
You can keep dancing.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, I can't.
I can't feel my pussy.
Yes.
Oh, I can't.
Oh my god, it's so hot.
Oh my god, that was so good.
I should clean up before my dad wakes up.
Bangbros.com