You
Hey, how are you?
I can't believe you're here.
Yep, I'm here.
In the flesh.
Can I get you anything?
Um, I'm okay.
Wow.
You look amazing.
Thank you.
So sexy.
How are you?
I'm so excited right now.
I can't believe you're actually here.
What was your name again?
I'm sorry, I'm Ryan.
Ryan, that's a sexy name.
Oh.
I'm Ryan.
What do you do, Brian?
Oh, nothing near as fun as you.
Yeah, that's pretty true.
Numbers.
Oh, you're a numbers guy.
Numbers, yeah.
That's cool.
Are you, like a, what do you do, like a data analyst or something?
You could say that.
Like a math teacher or something?
I thought about doing a professor thing, but...
Ooh, that's hot.
I'm also just good at number crunching.
Ooh, where are you from?
Uh, from Colorado.
Yeah.
Oh, thanks. So you like my movies?
I do.
Yeah, do you have a favorite?
No, because you're so good in all of them.
Oh, thank you.
It's so fun.
Thank you for doing that.
I'd probably get into trouble if I wasn't a porn star
with all the sex that I would wanna have.
So this is like a more productive way
of channeling my slutty insides, you know?
Oh my.
Yeah.
I say silly things.
Wow, no, they're good, they're good.
That's, it's so good, this is.
Wow.
Do you like my dress?
I do, the dress is amazing.
It's pretty, right?
Oh, yes, you have a lot of words.
I changed my hair.
It looks great.
Thank you.
I just want to sit on your lap.
You're just so cute.
You remind me of my old math professor.
I have an idea for a little role play
that we could do sometime, if you're interested.
You could be my professor, and I could
I used to be like the naughty student.
Uh huh.
Just like not really getting that A quite yet.
I like that.
Yeah.
That's...
I was kidding.
And you could teach me a thing or two about numbers.
And I could do something for you in return.
You'll figure it out.
Yeah, you're fun.
You better be naughty.
You're naughty, I can tell.
Oh, you're married.
Yeah.
That makes it even harder.
Do you have like a...
Your gift?
Yes, yes, I do.
I set it in the bathroom in the bedroom that we did house.
I can feel your cock getting harder and harder.
That's all you.
Oh.
I think you're getting raised out of something.
I want you to pre-cum.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
I can't see.
Oh, Mr. Ryan.
I'll be right back. I brought something a little sexy to try on for you.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
Hopefully you'll like it.
I think I'm gonna like any of it.
All right, I'll be right out.
For sure, but we're right there.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Okay
Okay, now, this little number
Jesus.
I don't know.
Wow.
Hi, Professor.
That is...
Uh huh.
Is it nice?
That is so nice.
Do you like my outfit, Professor?
Uh huh.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Wow.
Uh huh.
It's quite the change of school uniform.
Isn't it?
Wow.
I'm just very immature for my age.
Very sexy.
Incredible.
I've been a very bad girl, Professor, a very bad girl.
Something tells me it's going to be even worse.
I just can't focus.
I need you to teach me and punish me and dominate me.
Oh, someone's rock hard already.
Listen.
Am I a good girl professor?
You're getting there.
I bet you want to see mine, don't you?
I get to see my own natural tits, professor.
Wow.
Making a good case.
I'm feeling dizzy
Oh, yeah, pet my little kitty.
Yeah, pet my little kitty. Make it purr.
It's so warm.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Did you know how big my clit is?
I have seen it once or twice.
It brings me so much pleasure.
Oh, yes, professor, yes, you're playing my little pussy, professor.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, you're trying to be so funny.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck, that's so good.
Can I taste that cock of yours?
Can I taste it?
I think you better.
Oh my god.
Oh, so hot.
You can spank me with this later.
Oh, it's so pretty.
Oh, wow.
Fuck.
Look at these big butts.
Someone needs to drain them.
My wet mouth can drain your big balls.
Oh my god.
Oh you dirty girl.
Dirty girl.
That's...
So...
Oh...
Fuck, that's good.
How long have you been wanting to fuck these tits?
It's been years.
That's okay?
Okay, that's right.
Look into the eyes.
It's so hot.
Oh.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh.
It's so hot.
Look into my fucking eyes.
Oh.
Oh, it's so hot.
I'm going to choke on it.
Do you want me to choke on it?
Just a little bit.
Yes.
Oh!
Oh
Yeah, this is only for my best fans.
Get you up out of here.
You can keep those.
Oh, professor.
Oh my god.
Oh, yes. Oh my goodness.
It's like that. Oh my god, yeah.
Oh, Ian, oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God, you're like that big lid of mine, you're...
Oh, my God, my tongue.
Oh.
God.
Oh, Ian.
Oh, fuck you.
I'm going to go on the floor.
Not so fast!
there she goes.
go ahead, do it!
go ahead.
monster monster Oh Xynn!
Yes.
Oh my God.
it really is for you.
Yeah.
I know why you're so sad.
Because you've been doing so well.
But now you're sad because you're too busy.
You can't take care of yourself.
It is so sad.
True.
Yeah.
It is.
So sad.
I know.
Yeah.
It is so sad.
It is.
Is this what you want?
I just want to sleep with you.
Mommy.
Oh, fuck.
Do you want to read to me, Professor?
Actually, I want you to read me this.
Okay.
Whatever you say, Professor.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, yes.
It's so good.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh.
You did it all for me.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, you like that?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, spank me, Ryan.
Just a little.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
You're so...
Shhh!
Mommy, they're freaking like this!
They're freakin' like this!
Oh my God!
They're freaking like this!
Ahh!
Oh!
Do it!
Ohh, yes, oh my God!
Ahh, yes, Ryan!
Ryan!
Fuck yes!
Fuck that pussy!
Fuck you.
Fuck you so hard.
He was staring at my tits when I raped you.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, my God, yes. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's so good.
It's my fucking stomach.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh yes.
Ready?
Yes.
All right.
Mmm, it tastes so good.
Oh, wow.
Oh
Oh my god.
Oh my god, right there.
Oh shhhhhhh.
Yes.
Oh my god.
My little boy.
It's so good.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Yes. Please.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god!
Yes professor!
Don't stop!
Oh my god!
Oh my god yes!
Oh fuck! We're fucking coming professor!
Oh!
Oh fuck!
Oh shit!
Oh!
Oh, fuck, dude, it's fucking good.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck.
I hate these tests, don't you?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh my God.
Okay.
oh
fuck yeah
oh oh
oh
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh my god.
Yes.
Yes, I can give you that thing.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh yes.
Oh fuck yes.
Yes.
Yes, yes, oh yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes, like that.
There.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god, yes, right there.
Yes, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, that's it.
You're so fucking good.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh my god, you're my fucking school.
There's a fucking dick inside of me, yes!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God!
Fight me all night, please!
Please!
Oh, my God!
That fucking dick is so good!
It's so good!
It's so fucking good!
Oh, my God!
That dick is so good!
Oh, shit!
It's so fucking good!
Oh, fuck!
It's so good!
It's so good. It's so fucking good.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
It's so fucking good. Yes.
Oh my god. Yes.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck, right there.
Right there, please.
Such a good person.
Shit.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Please don't stop!
I can't get away!
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
Yes!
That is great!
I have to take that shit.
I get an A for best of my life.
I'm getting a bad fucking sweat.
I'm getting an A.
This is so I get an A.
This is so I fucking get an A.
Oh shit.
Oh my God.
Just hang on.
Help me.
Pussies.
Pussies are wet.
Oh my god.
Shit.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Shit.
Oh my god.
Oh my.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
I'm so fresh.
Let's keep going.
Thank you.
Oh shit.
Oh my god!
You sick little stinker.
Oh fuck!
Oh my god!
You fucking licked my penis!
You!
Give me this cup.
I want to taste the cup.
Let me out of here.
Please, please, please.
Oh my god, Sammy.
I remember this.
I know you're there.
I know where that is.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Shit.
Oh my god, everything is so wet.
Oh fuck, you fucked me in the tits professor.
Yes.
Don't hold back.
I've been such a bad girl.
I've been such a fucking naughty little slut.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, mm, ah.
Yep, my big pungent tits.
Yep, fuckin' pound my fat fuckin' tits.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, you like my fuckin' juicy tits.
Yes, fuckin' covered in sweat
and cum and fuckin' spit
and shit.
Yes. Oh, my
gunny, it's so good.
It's so good, I just wanna squeeze that cum
in my big tits.
Squeeze the fuckin' cum in my big tits.
You wouldn't sleep right now, you make my fucking tits...
Oh!
Tuh!
Yes!
Yes, oh my bloody...
You fuck my fucking huge tits!
Yeah, be a good fan and cum from my tits, yes!
Oh my god, it's so fucking hot!
Yes!
Oh, I know you fucking want to!
I know you fucking been thinking about cumming on my tits forever!
Yes!
I know you can see fucking cum all over my fucking tits, yes!
Oh my god, I feel so good.
Hi.
What should I do with it, Professor?
I think you need to play with it a little.
Oh, fuck.
That's a good girl.
Fuck.
Some looks all over my tits.
It's a good look for you.
Even when that neck was little.
I'm a little messy.
Just gonna use the bathroom.
Of course.
Okay.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Okay.
Oops.
Hi.
Oh.
I did snag you.
Thank you.
Here's something for you.
Shoes.
You got to throw on the other side of the bed.
Well, I should probably be going.
Gotcha.
I will definitely be calling again.
Yeah, please do.
Maybe next time I'll call.
Bye.
Maybe next time I can stay over and I can take a bubble bath or something.
I like those words.
I think it's a possibility.
Yeah.
Well, thank you.
Sure.
Bye.