I'm gonna have a little kinky like that.
My pussy's so warm.
Oh, I want to cock inside it so bad.
I want it to fucking slide from my clit to my asshole.
Oh my god.
with it too, and tease me while you slap my foot?
Come on, fuck, yeah, make me your little whore.
Make me your dirty little sex slot, yeah, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah, dress me up in lingerie,
and walk away with me like a little doll.
Mm, oh, fuck, yeah, mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck, yeah, daddy.
Yes, daddy, fuck, I want Tyler more.
Oh, God, yes.
Ah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my gosh.
I'm not done yet.
Oh my god, yes! Daddy, yes, make me cum, please!
Oh my god, I'm going to fucking go on the rails.
Is it pretty?
Do you like my pussy?
My clutch is swollen.
I'm a little bit sick.
Swan, my pussy's throbbing for you.
Bye, Daddy.