You
Do you like how I jiggle these teddies?
Oh my god.
Oh, it feels so good.
I just wanna jiggle them.
Oh, you feel so good.
I just want to jiggle.
Yeah, you like these titties, don't you?
You like big, jiggling titties.
Who doesn't?
When I was younger, they used to make fun of me
for my big, giant titties.
the other hand, I just want to call someone and tell them to come over and
and fuck my little pussy.
They're such a big source of pleasure for me.
And so I let boys come over and fuck them.
Oh yeah.
You Cherry Pimps fans like big titties, don't you?
Yeah, you boys have good taste.
Here, the pimp's for you.
Do you want to see these titties?
Are you boys ready for that?
I don't think you are.
The only thing better than big titties is big slippery titties.
Okay, I'll show you one.
I can't put them in my mouth, they're that big.
I wish you were here to kiss it for me.
Give me a little kiss.
Maybe a little bite.
Ooh.
That's really good.
Mm-hmm.
Just a little bit of that going in.
the guy's moan behind it.
My tits aren't the only wet things on this bed, you know.
My pussy's pretty wet too.
It's like a magical pussy I've been told.
I'm a horny girl. I don't know if you've noticed that about me.
That's because of my pink clit. My cute little pink clit.
really sweaty.
to have a clit this big, in my defense.
Oh, fuck.
Little asshole.
Loosens up when I play with my clit a little.
Oh.
Fuck, yeah, it's all so wet and warm.
Oh my god, yes.
Just a little bit.
Oh my god.
Oh my god...
Oh...
Fuck...
Yes...
Oh shit...
I can't stop...
Oh my god...
Yes...
Oh...
Fuck...
Oh...shit...shit...shit...
I'm not even done...
I want more. I need more.
Oh yeah, put your cock right there.
I really hope you've enjoyed watching me
Watching me play with my big tits.
Oh my god, I could do this all day.
You're still here?
Okay, go away. Bye!