Fucking piece of shit phone.
Hello?
Are you still on hold?
Did you turn your cell phone on and off?
feeling frisky baby I listen I would love to and you look gorgeous but I'm
What do you mean, this is not tech support?
Are you fucking...
Sorry, are you serious?
Yes, I'll hold again.
Put me back on hold.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
How long for?
What, no one's on the other end right now.
I know, but if they come, I'm gonna, you know...
What?
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh, you're terrible.
Maybe you could just like, pay a little bit more attention to me.
Not so much attention to social media and your phone.
What do you need your phone for when you got me in front of you?
You're right, but this is about principles right now.
Principles?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I don't know.
I see your principles slipping away.
Just like that.
Stop.
Just let me suck it.
Okay, what if they come online?
Well, so what?
You can just be quiet.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Really?
You're more interested in being on hold?
Oh my god.
Oh, get comfortable, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Oh my god, yes.
Yeah, come on, don't you have to stop, promise?
Mm-hmm, I don't promise.
Mm-hmm, I'm sure you can handle it.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, baby.
Oh, my fucking God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah, she plays big fuckin' tits around it.
Keep suckin', keep suckin'.
Keep suckin'.
Oh, fuck yes.
Hi, yes, yes, yes.
I have a question about my phone.
No, no, no, I'm good.
yes my phone's not opening no sorry there's no so my phone's not opening I
don't know what to do
Yes?
Oh you gotta call back here and hold it in.
What?
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Yes.
Fuck.
Do you feel like that?
Yes.
Fuck.
Yes!
Can you help me?
Let me turn around.
Fuck, baby.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
I feel so fucking good.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh my god, baby, you know how much your fucking cup drives me crazy.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, tie them up.
Tie these titties up.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, shit, baby.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, put it back in there, fuck that pussy.
Yeah, make me fucking cum on it.
Yes, yes, yeah, like that, fuck.
Yes, oh shit, yes.
Oh my God, you're gonna make me cum.
Yes, yes, yes, oh, yeah, you're still on hold.
Fuck, oh, yeah, yeah, pussy.
Oh shit, yes, yes, yes, like that, oh my.
Yes, yeah, we can still hold.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, my God, that music sucks.
You listen to it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, look at this fucking pussy.
You don't even feel so fucking good at my pussy.
Shit.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, take this clothes off.
Let me check.
I was still good.
Fuck, baby.
Yes.
Come on, give me that dick.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God.
Yes. Yes. Yes. I want you to take me. Yes.
Oh, fuck. Yes. Oh, my God. Yes, baby. Fuck.
Yes, use my little pussy. Use my little pussy.
Fuck. Fuck.
Yes, baby. Oh my god. Oh my god
I'm gonna have to stay right there?
Yeah.
Fucking wait, my cock is up here.
Oh, fuck.
Here, let me have a second.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh, fuck.
Oh, yes, baby, fuck, you know I love that.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, yes, yes, take me.
Take me, take me, take me, fuck.
Fuck!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah, but let me look at you.
Stay right there.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Yes.
it, fuck, yes, oh fuck, yes, baby, baby, fuck.
God, your coke is so fucking hot, I love it.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it's fucking hot.
Oh, good girl.
Oh, you're such a good fucking girl.
Oh, yes.
I love seeing that.
Oh.
Shit
Oh my god, fuck yes. Oh my god. Oh shit
Oh shit that looks so good
Yes.
Baby, yes!
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my god, this is all right. I'll hold
Oh, yes, fuck me. Fuck it out of me.
I don't fucking know.
Yes, use it.
Oh, fuck, baby, yes.
It's going to make me fucking cry.
Yes, I want to make the cook.
I want to make the cook.
Yes, yes, yes.
Look at that.
Yes.
Is that your phone ringing?
Oh, my God.
Hello?
It works.
It's been working this whole time?
It's been working this whole fucking time.
Oh, fuck me.
No, not you, not you.
Hey, buddy, what's up?
Oh, man, you don't even know.