Good morning, Ramon.
I have something... I have an issue.
What? An issue?
Yes, I don't know how you are going to like this, but I quit.
What?
I need more pressure and I think I'm not going further in this position that I have in the company.
It's just way too much for me.
Listen, Ramon, I know I've put a lot of pressure on you
and I know we've been working a lot in preparation for this shareholders' meeting,
but today is not the day to quit.
I need you to deliver the new policy initiatives.
That's exactly the issue.
You only care about work, about work, about work.
We have a life, too.
I don't even have...
Listen, Ramon, I'm sorry that I've been working you so hard.
I understand I get it maybe maybe we could just get through today through
this meeting and then we can talk about you taking some time off or or taking a
different position in the company I don't think we have anything to talk
about really listen why don't I send you my address you can come over and we'll
just talk about it please I know your address okay I'll be there in time
Thank you, Ramon.
Here you are.
Thank you, Ramon. I really appreciate you coming.
Now listen, nobody can deliver these new policy initiatives like you can.
I think we can have a really successful meeting.
I see you didn't hear anything about conversation before.
Listen, Ramon, I know you've been under a lot of pressure
and I feel like you know if you just deliver the main policy initiatives I
can I can I can do this part and you know and then we can talk about you
taking a break in the future everything is work work work work for you and right
now and I am in a moment that I need to travel that I need to find my soul I
mean I need to find who I am because anything I do it doesn't have sense
anymore. Listen, Ramon, I love that about you. I love your free spirit. I love your
creative mind. But this soul searching can't... can't it wait till tomorrow? All the
decisions I have done are final. I'm here just because I respect you, Angela.
So, I don't think there is much more to say.
Yes?
It's not just about the work.
I need you with me.
I need you by my side.
Not just at work.
Ramon, I need you.
Oh my god, please, please, please, I need you, please, please, oh my god, oh my god,
oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
Oh, yes. I've been thinking about your hands on me for so long.
Yes.
Please.
I'm gonna feel your skin on me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, please.
Please.
Let's go to the other one.
My hands.
Oh, my God.
Wait, I'll just do this one.
Yes, please.
Please, please.
I'm gonna help you with that thing, Jess.
Oh, my God.
Yes, maybe.
Yeah, please, get it off.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes, you got that.
Oh, yes, please.
You used it.
Yes, you called in for me.
I have to.
Mm, God.
You're so fucking good.
I feel so good for you.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God, yes, fuck.
Yeah, let me bounce those tits out.
Oh, fuck.
Look at that.
Oh, you're gonna...
Yes, put it back there.
Yes.
Beautiful.
Oh, fuck.
I can't do this.
Yeah, yeah, it's going to be...
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, baby, fuck.
I love it.
Oh, you really want me, eh?
You really want to kill me, eh?
Yes, yes.
Do you know I do?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
What the f**king c**k just happened?
Oh f**k.
I don't expect to get my pussy please.
No, it's okay.
It will be okay tomorrow.
Come on.
Oh f**k.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
I love to fuck that mouse, you fool.
Yes.
That's beautiful.
That's fucking good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
mm-hmm
oh
just like that
oh fuck
fuck
so good with those bubbles
on it
mm-hmm
oh my god
oh
fuck me
you want that cock?
Yes, please.
Oh fuck! Oh my god!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Oh my god! Yes!
Oh my god!
Yes! Fuck! Fuck! Yes!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
Come on, come on.
Yes.
Yes, you want to use that cock.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Come on.
I'm fucking going to punch you.
Yes.
Mm.
Yes, give it to me.
Right there.
I feel you, mommy.
Beautiful.
Mm-hmm.
There you go.
Come on, give it to me.
Put it back.
Give it to me.
The pussy is so fucking wet.
Show me that. Show me that pussy.
Oh god.
Fuck. Fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, stick it in my eyes.
Please.
In my eyes, in my eyes, in my eyes.
Please, please, please.
Yes, yes.
Oh, they're so good.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh
Oh shit, yes
Oh my goodness
Feels so fucking good. Oh my god. You have no idea how much I fucking need this
Yeah, yeah, just like that.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes.
Yeah, you have both of them.
Yes, yes, please let me come like this.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
Oh my god, yes, yes, oh my god, it looks so good going on that pussy, yes, oh fuck, yes, oh my god, yes, yes, oh, it looks so good, it looks even better, yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck,
Oh, my God, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Give it to me.
Give it to me like that.
Fuck.
Come on.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, that's it.
Fuck.
Come on.
It's going deep there.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Ah.
Fuck.
There it is, there it is, there it is.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes, keep coming.
Keep coming like that.
Oh, fuck.
Keep coming like that, fuck.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yes, baby, yes, fucking beautiful.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes, go here, go here, it's the fucking car, there's your car, oh fuck, oh fuck, oh yeah,
Oh, it tastes so good.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, fucking me.
Yeah, I love that juice.
Yes.
I love you.
I just want to tease you like that, oh my god, oh my god, I feel so good, oh my god,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yeah, oh, good, yeah, fucking great, oh, you want to fucking take it, fucking take it, oh, fuck, oh, my God, oh, my God, remember, oh, yes, yes, oh, it's so good, yeah, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, yeah, oh, yeah, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Put your hands on me, put your hands on me, everywhere.
All over me, all over me.
Yes.
Yes, please.
Please.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That little pussy.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck
Yes, please, I want you to fuck me.
Hold it.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
Like that. Like that. I'm gonna fucking cum like that.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Give it to her.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
We have some fucking luck.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck yes, take me.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
Yes!
Oh my God!
Fucking good pussy!
You really feel fucking amazing!
Yes!
Are you there?
Oh my God!
He's just salivating right now!
Yes!
Please!
yes yes there yes there oh my god oh you're wet i love you
so good
oh here oh yeah get it to me like that oh oh oh my god that is so good yeah
Oh, my God.
Oh, baby.
Here, here.
Oh, fuck.
I need you, I need you, I need you
I need you
Oh fuck
Do you want me to taste it?
Yes you can taste it
Oh my god fuck
Oh fuck
You smell so good
I'm just gonna get my face
Please give me that fucking cup again
Oh yeah
Fuck
Oh shit
Oh fuck
Oh my god
It's so fucking big
God damn it
oh yeah
oh fuck yes
oh yeah please take it please take it yes i love being fucked by you i
I love being fucked by you, I love it.
Oh, mommy, yes.
Shh, shh, shh.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I like it when you take control.
Oh.
Yeah.
Show me who's really boss.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, it's fucking deep, I love it.
I love how deep it goes.
Oh, yes, fuck.
Okay?
Oh my god, yes, please.
Please, I don't want to fuck with you, please.
Yes, right, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes.
Come on, come on, give it to me.
Oh, god, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, oh my god.
Come back, come back. Where'd you go?
Fuck.
Oh.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, God. Oh, yes.
I like the way my ass shakes when I bounce on that dick.
I love them.
There, there, there, there, there.
Oh, fuck, yes!
Yes! Oh my god! Fuck!
Oh baby, you're fucking good!
Oh my god!
You're fucking crazy! Yes, yes, yes!
Oh yes!
Please, I fucking could!
Yes, play with that pussy.
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes!
Right there, right there, right there!
They're right there, they're right there, fuck, fuck!
I'm gonna come.
Come on, come on, come on, give it to me.
Yes.
Oh my God, I'm feeling you.
Yes, give me that pussy.
I got that pussy, girl, I need it.
Oh, that's why we like you to come.
Yes.
Oh, God, yeah, I wanna see you, I wanna see you.
Let me see you, let me see you, let me see you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, holy shit, fuck, oh yeah, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, fuck, oh
Oh, my God, yes, hug me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I feel it. I feel it. I feel it.
I feel it. I feel it.
I feel it.
Let's wait a little longer.
Please, make me come again first.
Make me come again first, please.
Give it to me.
Fuck. Fuck.
Yes, right there.
Yes, right there. Come on, give it to me.
Fuck. Fuck.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, deep like that, fuck yes, yes baby, yes, oh my god, come on, come on,
give it to me, I'm gonna fucking go and survive, I'm gonna fucking go and survive, give me
Me too, me too, me too, fuck!
Yes, baby.
Oh, there, there, there, there, there.
Oh, yes.
Come on, baby.
Yes.
Yes, man.
Fuck.
I'm not supposed to say you have luck.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah, please, please, please don't want you to cum for me now.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God, stop it.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, right there.
Fuck.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God, so much fucking cum.
Oh, my God.
I really lost track.
Fuck.
Beautiful fuck.
Put my face into it.
That's beautiful.
What time is the meeting?
I knew you'd come around.
Okay.
I need to shower first.
You do.