Okay, I have one question for you, and it's going to decide your fate.
What color are my eyes?
Um, brown?
Green.
I knew it.
Why is it that you never look in my eyes?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Your boobs are so big, I can't stop staring at them.
Oh, my boobs are so big and so perfect.
You just can't help yourself?
Mm-mm.
Well, I can't help but want to punish you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Come on.
Let me see that butt.
Your fate's been decided.
Mm-mm.
So you like girls with big tits.
Do you like girls with big dicks?
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna destroy this little ass.
Oh.
Mm.
Moans of pleasure or moans of pain?
That feels pretty good.
Mm.
Oh.
Let's give you both.
Mm.
lube on the cob.
Making that big fucking dick so easy
Stop fucking whinging.
Oh, look at that.
Yeah.
Back that ass up.
Come on, fuck my dick.
Back it up, back it up, back it up.
That's right.
Fuck yourself with this dick.
Yeah, you're doing all the work for me.
Come on, just slow down.
Fucking take it.
Oh, that's slow.
Oh, yeah.
Come here and taste your fucking ox juice.
Come here and clean it all up with your tongue.
Suck it all up.
Come on.
All the way down.
Keep toward that dick.
You can do better than that.
Keep that fucking throat open.
tell me how much you love that cock
look up at me
look into my fucking eyes
what color are my eyes
that's right what color are my fucking eyes
that's right my eyes are fucking blue
yeah and get all that good fucking spit for me
oh yeah
put it all over that asshole
come on again
I'm in distress, oh my god, oh!
Yes.
There we go, keep that sucking up.
Come on, better than that.
Back it up onto me.
Come on, do it, do it, do it, do it, come on.
You make so much fucking noise.
Come here, let me fill that fucking mouth up with this dick.
Come here.
Lick up every last drop of your ass juice.
Such a dirty fucking whore.
there we go put those legs back ha ha nice and exposed for me oh thank you
I think you missed your...
Nice and easy.
If you don't shut up, I'm going to have to put something in that mouth.
Oh, it's so slippery with all your ass juices.
Oh, God, nothing shuts you up.
Yeah, you fucking like that, you little slug, huh?
What color are my eyes?
Your eyes are blue!
Your eyes are blue! I want them bad!
I'm sorry!
You know what color my eyes are?
The same color
as your balls!
Blue balls!
Blue balls, huh?
You got blue balls in my blue eyes?
Did you just touch me with your feet?
I'm sorry! Did you just touch me with your fucking feet?
I'm sorry!
This is what happens when you touch me with your fucking feet
Don't touch me with your feet
Don't ever touch me with your feet again
I'm sorry
Keep your fucking feet up
Oh
Look into my motherfucking eyes.
What color are they?
They're blue, it says.
They're blue eyes.
They're blue.
Beautiful blue.
Oh, such a little bitch.
I haven't even begun to destroy your aunts yet.
Oh, fuck.
Throw his fucking feet away.
Yes, yes, take it.
You want to look in my fucking eyes! You want to look at my face!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Don't you dare fucking look away!
Don't you fucking dare!
Did you just look at my fucking tits?
No! I'm fine!
Yeah, you like it, don't you, being a little odd-slut?
Yeah, she's admitting to me.
Let me do whatever the fuck I want to your body.
That little fucking man-pussy.
Get that nice and deep in there.
Oh, look at what you can take, huh?
What are you fucking complaining about, huh?
What are you sorry for, huh?
I'm sorry for looking at my fucking tits.
What color are my eyes?
They're blue.
Oh, my God.
I'll fucking teach you
look at that
asshole opened up
for me
don't you look at these perfect boobs
don't you fucking dare
you ready to really get destroyed
no oh that's too bad i'm gonna flip over right now did your foot just
oh i'm sorry did your foot just touch my fucking boob
oh sorry why did i tell you
I didn't want to touch you again, I'm sorry.
Flip over.
On your fucking stomach.
Hurry up.
Look at you.
Soaking wet from all that sweat.
Did it stress you out, huh?
Having to look at a woman's eyes
What you prefer dehumanizing women
Over this body
It is not going to tickle.
Didn't I tell you?
It doesn't tickle.
No, that doesn't tickle at all, does it?
What colour are my eyes?
Oh
We're going back it up onto that cup
I told you I was going to fuck you hard.
Did you think I was fucking kidding?
Did you think I was fucking kidding, you little bitch?
You think us chicks just joke around, huh?
You think that you can just stare at our tits, dehumanize us,
And we're just going to sit there and fucking take it, huh?
Is that what you think?
Is that what you fucking think?
Now you're just going to fucking get away with it?
No.
Fucking deep.
What?
Yeah, it is so fucking deep.
So fucking deep.
Oh, you should be looking deep in my fucking eyes.
Hmm?
Yeah, as deep as you should be looking into my fucking eyes.
What do you say?
Come here, come here, come here, come here.
Oh!
Yes.
I'm going to look deep into her fucking eyes.
Destroy that little fucking eye.
Oh, man.
Come on, fuck it back.
Come on.
Fuck it.
You're making my big fucking tits bounce while you fuck it.
I don't have to do anything.
Come on.
Come on, I shouldn't have to do all the work.
I don't want you to destroy your own ass for me.
Do it, come on!
Now come around here and taste your own fucking ass.
Come here.
Fucking taste it.
to come back up and breathe, one more time, one more time.
So what did you learn today?
To look women in the eyes when I talk to them.
That's right.
I want you to stay here and think about it.