Come closer, crawl to me in these big, perfect breaths.
You can't help but stare at them, can you?
You're addicted to big, natural tits.
Go ahead.
Stare into them.
Stare into my deep cleavage.
So big.
They're hypnotizing, aren't they?
You can't help but stare.
Deep into that cleavage, makes you so hard.
Watch them sway.
You can't look away.
You are completely under my control, hypnotized by my perfect breaths.
You try to look away and you can't.
That's right, I've got you now, completely under my spell.
hypnotized.
Go on, keep staring.
Feel how hard your cock is getting with every second that goes by.
Getting harder and harder until it hurts.
purple, it's starting to throb.
My tits control your cock.
They control your mind.
They control all of you.
Just accept it.
Give in to the power of my boobs.
of your dick.
You're completely powerless to my charms.
Completely powerless to these perfect breaths.
Say it, completely powerless to these perfect breaths.
even handle it.
Oh, look at that.
Deep cleavage control.
I dare you to look away.
I know that you can't.
there. Grab on to that cock of yours right at the base near the balls and
control your orgasm
You are hypnotized by these tits.
Say it, repeat it.
you close to the brink and just leave you there.
Stroke faster for these tits, faster for me, faster, keep going.
You're going to come for me after I count down.
Are you ready?
I know your balls are fucking full for me.
I know you're ready to come for these big tits.
So fucking close, aren't you?
Two.
Oh, it's killing you, isn't it?
So torturous being so close to coming.
See what these big fucking tits do to you.
See how much they control you.
Are you ready?
One.
Come for me.
Drain those balls.
Show me just how much these tits control you.
Jerk out every. Last. Drop.
Look what these tits did.
Look at that mess.
You were powerless.
To these tits.
There was nothing that you could do to stop it.
and pathetic. You can't control yourself because of these.
And that's all you get.