Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody, does it better.
Are they covered?
Okay, keep them covered, okay?
And don't uncover them yet, okay?
Okay, go.
gave you a little one-on-one bachelor party what do you think of that
Yeah, you want them, don't you?
Yeah.
Not yet.
First, I want to show you something.
I want to show you just how badly I want you.
I love being your wife. You're the best husband
husband ever. You know that?
You make my pussy so wet. My pants are soaking wet for you.
Is this what you want?
Look at this baby.
Look at your wife's wet pussy.
How chubby it is. Do you like it?
I want to give this to you.
Is that what you want?
You sweet, wet pussy.
Leave your hands there.
Yes, but first, I want to taste this hard cock.
Oh, I love this hard cock.
It's such a good call to me.
Yeah.
Yes, you sacrificed so much by not having a bachelor party.
It's only fair you get one now.
It's so hard already.
Do you want my mouth on it?
Do you?
Oh yeah, I'm gonna put my mouth on it.
Oh, someone's eager.
Okay.
Oh, you like my tits, baby?
You like your wife's big, natural tits?
Consider me your personal stripper for the evening.
Oh, I want this, and you're going to give it to me.
Give it to me, give it to me, yes.
Oh my gosh.
I really like being your little stripper.
Mmm.
Ah.
Okay.
Mmm.
Ugh.
You have a slutty little wife, honey.
Oh my god, I'm so glad I married this cock.
Yes.
I will forever lick your balls.
mmm
am I doing it right?
I think this is how the pros do it.
Do you believe that honey?
I love you.
Oh, is this what you want?
Anything my baby wants?
Yes.
Not too fast.
Does that look good?
Do you like that?
Make your wife's big tits all over that cock, yeah?
Wrapped around tightly on that big hard rod?
Yes, yes.
Can you handle it? Can you handle it? Yes.
I'm married to it, not you.
Oh, it disappeared.
Mmm.
Argh.
Mm.
Mmm.
Oh, yes.
Yes, it made sense.
Yes.
Mmm.
Do it.
Oh, baby.
Yes.
Ah.
Mmmm.
Mmm.
What are you?
Mmm
Ah!
One
Mmm
Mmm.
Cough. Cough.
Alright.
You turned on yet?
Wait till you see what I have in store next.
I'm staying right there.
Mmm.
Yes! Yes!
Oh!
Hmm!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Hmm! Hmm!
Oh!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Pull my hair! Pull my hair!
So little! Yes!
Oh!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Oh, you drive me crazy with your cock, baby, yes.
Yes, this is what you like.
Right there.
Oh, fuck.
Smack me.
Yes.
Ah, ah, ah!
Oh my God, baby, yes!
You speak!
Oh, ooh, ooh, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Fuck, yes.
Ooh.
Yes.
You guys like that?
Oh yeah.
Touch my butt.
Oh baby, please just a little.
Oh.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, daddy.
like that?
oh
oh my god
yes
oh
ok
mm
Taste this.
Taste my pussy up here, gorgeous cock.
Ah.
Ooh.
Mm.
Oh
Oh God.
Oh.
Oh and you want some more?
Yeah.
Some more of this cock and morsels.
Mm.
Oh God.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Ah.
Ah. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Ah.
Ah. Oh my god.
Incredible! Yes!
Oh, yeah!
Yes, baby! Yes, baby!
Yes!
Come here, baby.
Come with me.
Oh, we wanna ride that car.
Oh, yes!
Yes!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh
Go for it, go for it.
Oh, yeah.
He's serious!
He's dancing!
Is this what you want?
Oh Holy God!
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
Tap it for me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
It's so hot, it's so hot.
Oh yes, yes, baby.
Oh yes, yes, just like that, just like that.
Oh God, that's so good, baby, yes.
This is why I married you.
Keep going, keep going.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, you're so hard for me, you're so hard for me, yes.
Oh
Oh my God, you're so good at that.
Oh, that's incredible, baby.
You have to do it for me.
You're gonna stand, stand, yeah.
Nice long struts, mm-hmm.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh my god. Oh, that's so good.
Oh. Oh. Oh, fuck.
Oh, baby, that's so good.
I know what we should do, baby.
I want you to bend me over.
Will you bend me over? Please.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
You're gonna bend me over like that, baby, yes I will.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, fuck, it's so good.
Oh, yeah, you like that?
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, shit, yes.
yes
oh god its so good
just like that
oh
yes
Please, yes.
Oh!
Ah!
Oh, oh, yes.
Oh, you adore it don't you?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Do it.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh
You're so deep, baby.
Yes.
Oh.
Finish.
Ah.
Yes.
Please.
Oh, keep going.
Yes.
Ah.
Oh my god, yes!
Yes, don't stop!
Oh, don't stop, please!
Fuck me, yes, fuck me!
Oh my god, baby, yes!
Oh my god!
Yes, yes, yes!
Manhandle me like that baby, yes!
I love it when you do that!
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
Yes!
Yes, baby.
Oh yeah!
Oh yes!
Oh, oh my God, yes.
Come on, fuck me, come on, fuck me, please.
Oh, yes, give me, give me, oh my god, yes.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Mm, I like that.
Oh my god, yes.
Mm, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh my god, yes, right there.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, fuck, yes, yes.
Oh, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Mm, mm, mm, mm.
Oh yeah, breathe, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Oh shit.
Oh.
Yes.
Keep going.
Harder, harder.
Oh.
Mm.
Yes, yes, yes.
My face.
Oh yes.
Oh.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, yes, oh!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh shit, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, oh, oh!
Yes!
Oh my god, I'm so good!
Oh, oh!
Dang!
Oh, yes oh!
Oh my god, yes!
Yeah!
Yes!
Oh my god.
Oh, pound it, baby!
Yes!
Pound it!
Oh my god!
Oh, oh!
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit, yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, yes, baby, oh, my God.
You're gonna make me cum, baby, don't stop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shit.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God, I'm coming, baby.
Don't stop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Mm.
You're a villain.
Oh, fuck, yes, fuck, yes.
Fuck you, and don't stop.
Oh yeah, yeah, fuck that pussy baby, fuck that pussy!
Yeah, fuck that pussy!
I want you to come for me, baby!
I want you to come for me, please!
Give me the cum, baby!
Please, I want you to come for me,
Come for me baby, please!
Please, please, I want you to come for me.
Yes, yes, yes, come on, give it to me baby!
Oh my god, please baby, please, I want it so bad!
Oh, I want it so bad, baby, just come.
Ahhh.
with. Let's go get some dinner or something. Some champagne.
Naughty America. Nobody. Nobody. Nobody. Does it better.