Hi, my name's Justin. I'm here to give you a deep tissue massage.
Great. Hi Justin. You can come sit up down here.
Oh, of course. Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, I've been really needing this massage.
Thanks for coming at such short notice.
Yeah, yeah. Of course.
Absolute pleasure to meet you.
So, do you want to just sit up down?
Yeah, yeah. Of course I will.
You want to sit up here?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, just get your big laptop, I mean your big, is that your table?
Yeah, it's my big table.
Oh, I love a big table.
Yeah, it's so important.
Yeah. Oh, it's nice and red.
It's burgundy, it's exotic.
Oh, it's like a wine.
Oh, wow.
doing.
Are you okay?
Do you need help?
Your ears seem to be creaking.
Okay.
All right.
Do you need, oh, wow, you're really, yeah.
Perfect.
We're all set up.
So, uh, yeah, let me get you some towels real fast.
Okay, great.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah, just there.
Perfect.
Here, you can get changed on this one. Let me just put this here.
It's fine.
You sure you don't need a towel?
Oh, no.
I'm fine. I do want a deep tissue
massage today, so, uh,
I'm kind of expecting you to get
into all
Of course, of course. Oh my god.
Oh yeah, that's great.
That's okay.
I don't mean to stagger you.
Here we go. Let's put this towel on.
Come on up. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, which way would you like me?
Stop on.
Just like this?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, there it is.
What, uh, do you want, uh, coconut or baby oil?
Well, I don't want a yeast infection, so I'll take the coconut.
Oh, okay.
Hey, um, is that organic and gluten free?
Of course, nothing but the best for you.
Oh, thanks.
Is it vegan?
You know it.
Okay.
Okay, oh, yes, excuse me?
Oh, no, no, I'm, you know, of course, just needed to work.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, I'm glad that I could help you out with your rent.
Oh, yes, of course, thank you.
Yeah, must be expensive buying all those vegan,
organic, gluten-free jars of coconut oil.
You know, I just like to spoil my...
Oh yeah, get it nice and deep. That's how I like it.
Well, you know, this does feel great, but my problem is more in my glutes.
Your glutes?
Yeah, my glutes, my hip abductors.
So yeah, you just want to get deep.
Yeah, of course, of course.
How was that?
Oh, yeah, that feels really good.
Exactly what you need.
Oh, yeah.
Plus all the big dicks I take.
What?
Oh, sorry. Inside words.
Oh, I love that you're not afraid to really get in there.
Oh, afraid?
I've been dreaming about this thing my whole life.
When the agency told me
you were the best at deep tissue
I know exactly what they meant now.
You know, I just want to make sure I get all of it.
You know, I wouldn't want you to exclude any part of my body. Yeah
They got a bed bath or a bed shower
They didn't even wash the most important part
Oh my goodness.
Yeah.
That feels so good.
Oh, whoops, the towel fell off.
Oh well.
Okay, let me just make that easier for you to get into.
That doesn't make you feel uncomfortable, does it?
No.
Oh, I take it.
You definitely need this massage.
Okay.
Yeah, it's true.
Let me go get something else real fast.
Of course.
This is my premium stuff.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
That feels so good,
dripping down.
Oh, yeah.
Make it easier if I flipped over so you can
get,
you know, at a different angle.
Oh, sure, sure.
Maybe.
Let's see what we've got over here.
Yeah, I have a lot of
tension in my pecs as well, just
so you know. Oh, in your pecs, of course.
Yeah.
You must have been really lifting.
I mean, I've just been bouncing around everywhere.
It just really takes
it out on me.
Are there some bench presses or two?
I mean, not really. The heaviest thing I lift is probably balls, but yeah.
Well, I mean, these are pretty secure.
I mean, well, yeah. I have a strong back.
Well, that's degrading. Let's give it a nice, lovely massage.
Thank you. I appreciate that. Strictly professional.
Of course. Does this look unprofessional?
Oh no.
Of course.
This is just really deep tissue massage.
Yeah.
Really deep.
Mmm.
Is that good? You're cock-a-rock-a. Come here and give it to me.
Teddy, drop them right into your face.
Hey, have you heard of that new technique? It's like...
Oh, of course, of course.
Have you tried that on anyone?
I've not tried it yet, but I mean...
I don't know.
Simply retards.
I'm so happy that I've got you, Justin.
Yeah, I'm so glad that the agency recommended you.
and comfortable.
Oh, yes, of course.
Yeah.
I'm going to sit up more.
You can get behind me and maybe...
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
This friend is like all of us.
That would...
I think...
Yeah.
Oh, of course.
Does it?
Yeah.
Jeez.
I read about that on the internet.
That's where I get all of my information.
Deep tongue massage, huh?
Yeah.
I hear that you can massage other things too.
Your tongue, like genitals and stuff.
Are you talking about the clitoris?
I am.
Yeah.
Not everybody knows where it is.
It's kind of a mysterious muscle.
it might not even be a muscle to be honest but whatever it is it's very
I think I might be able to show you where it's at.
OK, well, yeah, let's.
Just open up right over here.
God, yeah.
Oh, you found it.
I think I did.
How's your massage coming?
Oh, yeah, you're really getting deep into that tissue.
Of course.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, keep going, keep going, keep going.
and then let's, no, maybe we should.
Let's get one.
Yeah, let's try that one.
Which one?
I'll try my way first.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Okay, I'll let you handle it.
You're the professional.
Of course.
But then after you're away, I wanna like,
I wanna feel the, yeah, the deep tissue massage
down the throat.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
As long as you're cool with that.
Speaking of, how does that massage?
Yeah, I don't know why anyone ever uses their hand.
That's what I feel.
This is so much better.
Oh, it's ugly.
Oh my god, they're so slippery.
Yes, they are.
Mmm.
Massage those big tits.
Yeah, this is strictly worth it.
Yeah.
This is nothing but professional.
Of course you gotta help those lips.
There's no better massage than this.
Justin, I really want to try my way now.
Oh yeah, of course. Let's try that.
Yeah, thanks.
I feel so fucking good.
good.
I have a confession to make.
What?
I mean, I really do need a massage.
I mean, my muscles are sore, but I really just wanted to get fucked.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
If you could, yeah.
What's up?
I'd really just like you to.
I mean, you know what?
Just, um, just fuck me for a bit right now.
Of course.
Yeah.
Just do that
Let me bounce that fucking ass.
Yes.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna fucking cum all over that dick.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Give it to me. Yes. Yes.
Oh my god.
Fuck. Yes.
Mmm.
Oh yeah, let me taste
myself with that fucking dick.
Mmm.
You know what? Put your leg up here. I don't want to get deep in there.
Yeah. Oh yeah. That's what I like. A guy who's game.
Now get up on that fucking table. I don't want to suck that dick.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna play with this full skin right here.
Stick my fucking tongue in it.
Now who's giving a massage?
I won't lick my tongue, my hands, my fucking tits.
My big, natural tits around your cock.
Tease you with them at the side.
Don't they feel so fucking good around your hot dick?
Fuck yes.
Squeeze them tight.
Squeeze it.
mmm oh fuck you're getting my pussy so wet
do it again
do it?
use it on my clit
oh fuck
yes
oh my god
so good
Mmm, this is exactly what I wanted.
I bet you wanna see those big tits bounce, don't you?
You already know, yeah.
Yeah, like that.
Fuck.
Oh my god, your dick is so fucking big, I love it.
Oh my shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You feel good
Just tease you with that pussy for a little bit
Good, yeah, so fucking good
Fuck, fuck, fuck
Fuck. Oh my god. Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, that little pussy's so fucking close to cumming again.
Oh my god.
Fuck. I was like teasing myself like that.
Edging myself on your dick.
Mind if I use your dick and make myself fucking cum on it?
Oh no, use away.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck
Steve, I love it.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes.
Oh my God, it's such a big fucking dick.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, I love being able to watch it in and out like that.
Watching it fuck me.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Mm.
Yes.
Yeah, it's so fucking good.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Bangbros.com.
It's all right.
Holy shit, it's so fucking good.
God dang it.
Oh, I am.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, fuck that.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Yes, like that, like that, like that.
Fuck, fuck.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
I want that dick back in me.
Yes, please.
Oh, yes.
God, you have such a fucking good coat.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Fuck me like that. Yes
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes, fuck, fuck, fuck, yes.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, yes.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Just fucking balls slapping against my hip.
Yeah, it's so fucking heavy for me.
Filled with calm, huh?
Yeah, you got a nice big lip for me.
Yeah.
Work it up for me, work it up for me.
Yes, work it up for me.
Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
But I wasn't paid yet.
Oh.
That's okay.
See? I told you it was a music video.
That's exactly how it's gonna roll.
But if you don't know, now you know.
I fucking tit so I can have sex.
Okay, see that's fucking perfect there, yeah, look at that shit, huh, see?
I haven't even swallowed it yet.
That was sexy.
But how can people see more of you on the interwebs?
Where do they go?
There are so many places.
I don't believe you, tell me.
out.
Oh, okay.
No, you can go, I mean, you can go to .
That's the hub of all things internet.
Oh, you can follow me on
Ah, okay, gotcha.
And of course, this amazing scene for
like, you know, rad, so it was ridiculous.