at the house?
It is huge.
It's like the biggest thing I've ever seen in my life.
It was like, I was like, oh my god, how do girls even like handle that?
You know what I mean?
And like that has to hurt or something, you know what I mean?
But anyways, I'm just getting home, so let me call you back later, okay?
Goodnight.
What's that sound?
Oh my God!
What?
Oh wait, I'm late.
Ugh, what are you doing?
Hey, uh, what are you...
Tasha, I didn't know you were going to be home so early.
Sorry.
No!
I didn't...
It's okay.
Yeah.
No, I'm sorry.
It's totally not a big deal, you're just taking a nap.
I mean, like, it's a big deal, but...
I mean, it's totally okay.
It happens all the time, I'm sure.
Yeah, well, no, no, but...
It happens lately.
Yeah, I know.
You're so big.
so big.
Like, I think your boxers are too small.
What?
But nothing...
Oh!
Um...
I mean, no, no, I like it.
I mean...
Okay.
I like...
Like...
I mean, it's so big.
Um...
Can I suck it?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, that's enormous.
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
Woah.
Oh my god.
I mean, I think I can like...
Oh my god, it's so fucking big.
Fuck.
Fuck, it's so big.
Okay.
I feel like I can do that
all day
oh yeah
mmm
yeah
ahh
mmm yeah
yeah
I wonder if I... oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Do that again.
Suck those balls.
Oh yeah.
Look at those balls.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, it's so fucking big.
Oh my god, just do that a little bit.
I just wanted to do that for some reason.
Fuck!
It's so big and important.
Oh, that's so good.
Do it again.
Oh my God, oh my God, it's so big!
It's so fucking big!
Oh, what the fuck?
It's so fucking...
Oh my God!
Oh my God, it's so big!
Oh!
My big tits are in the big cock.
You came up with a challenge?
Yeah?
Fuck.
Oh my God.
Yeah, that's got to be a big one.
Yeah, that's when you get that, like that.
Wow.
Yeah, oh, wait, let me, let me, allow me.
Yeah.
Yeah, like that.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
For me?
Thank you so much.
oh my god oh shit
shit
fucking cool
do it, do it, do it
fuck yeah
oh my god
it's so fucking big
cool
oh my god
Take this shit, and I'll kill you.
Get the hell out of here.
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh my god, it's Tito, yes!
Oh, fuck, you took him fucking away with me, oh my god.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, spread that.
Yeah, look how good that is.
Yeah, so wet.
Hmm?
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
That is so fucking hot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck, yes, yes, come on, please, please, please.
in the cock, you know?
You're creaming like that, right?
Oh, yeah.
So fucking good.
Wow.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yeah.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Yeah.
There's so much of it.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
You get that cock.
Get that.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm going to have to find a second thing to do, honey.
This has got to come off.
Let me take this.
Take it off of me.
I don't need this anymore.
Is this for sure?
You just want to stare at my butt a little bit?
Oh yeah, won't you, Jekyll?
Oh, you have pretty eyes.
Oh, I'm not sneezing.
I'm not.
Oh my God, that's what I even wanted.
Yes, I'm going to sit down.
Oh my God, yes!
Oh, oh.
Oh my God.
Oh my goodness, that's the biggest thing I've ever had.
Just, oh, oh my God.
It's so fucking big, yes.
Oh my fucking God.
Yes, oh my fucking Jesus, oh my God.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh my God.
Oh my God, I'm going to die.
This is the biggest thing I've ever had!
Shit!
Oh my god, it's so fucking big!
Oh my fucking god!
Oh my god!
Ah!
Shit! Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Oh!
Woah!
Oh my god!
Please, please show yourself.
Yes, show yourself, yes!
Oh my God!
Oh please God, that's it, stop!
Oh my gosh, you can see me!
You can see me!
Ooooooooo.
Ooooohhh!
Oh my God.
Oh.
Oh, come on, he's crying.
Oh, you're so hot.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Is this what you want too?
I want to give you my big tits.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, shit, that fills me up.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my...
Oh,
fuck, yes!
oh, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh,
it's so fucking big.
Oh,
oh, oh,
Oh, fuck!
Oh, do it, do it, do it, do it.
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck! Oh my god!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh, it's so fucking big!
Oh shit, oh my god, ew, ew, ew, oh my god, it's so good.
Fuck.
Oh my god, it's so fucking big.
It's so fucking big.
Fucking big.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Please, please, please, I feel so good.
I feel so good, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh my God.
What?
I'm gonna get on my back so you can fuck me.
You can fuck the shit out of me.
Please, please will you fuck me on my back?
Oh my God.
Oh
Oh my god!
Dingo, you're gonna make me cum!
Fuck! I'm fucking cumming ya!
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Fuck!
Ah!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Oh my god, Ewan!
Oh, fuck.
You like my big swollen clit?
You like that?
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh my God, yes Yes, yes, yes
Yeah!
Oh my God, that's so big
Fuck!
Oh my God, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh my God, ooh, I'm gonna get a cut
What? What happened?
Nothing.
Oh my god, it's so big.
I should probably shower before Andrew gets home.
Bangbros.com