God damn it! Where is she?
What is this, some kind of power move?
Sean, relax. Everything's going to be fine.
I should have had her sign her prenup.
It just felt so cold at the time.
But now, I'm fucking screwed.
Listen, my fees are high for a reason, okay?
No matter what your ex-wife throws at us, consider your assets safe, okay?
Look, Xander, with all due respect, you don't understand.
I've never failed a client, okay?
I don't plan on failing my client today, all right?
My track record is huge, all right?
You're dealing with the best of the best here, okay?
Don't worry about it.
Oh, shit.
I'm Sean. Xander's a- um, Xander?
Charmed, I'm sure.
Hello, Sean.
Angela.
Happy to see me?
Come on, Angela.
What the fuck are you doing?
Well, Sean, today's a very important meeting,
and I think it's important to be...
transparent.
I'm sure you agree, Xander.
Yeah.
Transparency is, uh...
it's key to, um...
any...
Well, I'm sorry, I didn't know that you were Angela White.
Oh, so you're a fan.
Oh, I wouldn't, yeah, yeah.
Right, let's get started, shall we?
Okay.
Miss White, should we be expecting your attorney any time soon?
Oh, no. I'll be representing myself today.
Yeah, yes, so what might my files have indicated that uh
The reason for the dissolution of this marriage is due to
irreconcilable differences
correct
Sean thought it would be fun to be with a woman in the adult industry
but I guess it was a little too much for him to handle.
See, Sean doesn't like to admit this,
but he's the jealous type,
and I don't plan on retiring anytime soon.
So here we are.
I'm not jealous.
It's just, it's just a lot, okay?
It's a lot.
Have you two, have you guys thought about
about the division of assets and all?
I mean, listen, what's your end game
with this divorce, Ms. White?
Well.
You are not getting the car or the house
over my dead fucking body.
Sean, I don't want your cars or your house.
In fact, I don't want anything monetarily.
I make my own money.
You don't want anything.
Yeah, you get to keep everything.
That's nuts. There's nothing out of this that you want.
Well, there is one little thing.
And the good thing is, we can take care of it right now.
Okay.
I want to suck your attorney's cock.
Here we go.
And I want you to film it.
rethink my demands
If you're gonna get anything better than this, you should consider it.
Fine. I'll do it.
Yes.
Sick box.
Five minutes, max, and that's it.
No, no, no. Use my phone.
We can use this for legal
purposes.
Yes, really.
I'm so glad that we could come to an arrangement, Sean.
I bet you are.
Oh my god.
God. Fuck. Your cock is so much bigger than my husband's.
I hate to see this.
Damn. Holy shit.
God, that is a nice big dick.
A nice big settlement.
My big fucking tits are on the tooth.
Holy shit.
Oh yeah.
Damn that feels so fucking good.
Big natural tits wrapped around your cuffs.
Yes, yes, my bouncy big tits are on fire.
Oh, yes, get them both in, yes, it's so fucking hot.
Oh, fuck you.
Get them all like that.
Oh, fuck.
Do you see the tits jiggling as I suck his dick?
Fuck, dude.
Oh, boy.
Let's get this.
Mmm.
Let me ask you something.
He has been here.
Five minutes.
Fuck this.
It was not even five minutes.
Xander, I'll see you outside.
Make sure it's safe though.
Fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
I deserve it after all this shhhtttttttttttt
Should I have been through with my husband?
Yes.
Husband?
Oh my god, fuck.
Yeah.
Holy shit, yes.
Yes.
You're a fucking pussy.
Oh my god, you fuck me so much better than my husband.
Yes.
Holy fuck.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes, please.
Look at me when you're done.
Look at me.
Yes.
Ah, yes, I feel it.
I feel your fucking pussy coming out.
Oh, fuck!
Yes.
Yes, you pushed me out.
Oh, yeah.
You fucking pushed me out.
I'm sorry.
I keep doing it.
Open it up.
Spread it out.
Down on that dick like that.
Yeah.
Fuck!
Yeah!
Oh, so fucking...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, fuck this guy!
So fucking...
Oh
Oh my god, oh yes, holy shit, yeah, yeah
Oh my god that cock is so fucking big damn it.
Oh fuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
I fucking tease you.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, baby, fuck.
Oh, my God, you're so much better than my husband.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, just leave that for me.
Just keep fucking riding it.
Oh, God, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God, just leave that for me.
Oh, my God.
Fucking hold on.
I can go to bed with these big fucking titties.
Yeah, just like this.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Stop.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes.
Yeah, pull me up.
Pull me up.
Yeah.
That's nice.
Do you want to fucking face?
Yes.
yes, yes, yes, oh my god, my husband never fucked me like this.
Yes, baby, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, I feel like this was fair me too. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Good for Sean, right?
Of course, that's what I'm here for.
Oh, sorry. I guess I'll...
No, no, it's fine. Yeah, okay, great.
Thank you so much.
No worries.
I'll just get my things and I'll...
Yeah, it's all there.
Well, thanks again.
You got it, alright.
Yeah.
Fuck, Angelo. Was that really necessary?
Well, hope on the bright side.
At least you get to keep your precious car.
And I hope you're happy.
Hey, yeah, man. It's another case closed. We knocked it out.
Fuck. Well done, bud.
Just get the fuck out of here.
All right.
I'll get the law.
Okay.