of ozone.
I am, they're hard.
I imagine they would be.
I like it.
Yeah, they're wonderful.
Thank you.
At what age did those start to form?
Eleven.
Wow.
Yeah, I tend to get lost in blowjobs, it's like a meditative experience.
So that's some useful information I feel.
I get lost in malls.
You get lost in malls?
Yeah, that's what I do.
That's because your brain's in your dick while I'm sucking it.
Giving you a spiritual experience.
Yes.
Only I'm so fortunate.
So you've been doing this for a while now?
Yeah, I started 12 years ago.
Wow.
Oh shit.
Does that put you in the milk category now?
No.
I think it does.
Sometimes for some people.
I still do custom videos as a school girl though.
Well.
And I still call men daddy all the time so
I don't know what I am.
Does it bother you to be classified as a MILF now?
Cause you know you gotta classify everybody as something.
I don't know cause MILFs are really fucking hot.
They're like pretty much perfect looking
but I still like calling men daddy so
I don't know.
No.
It's really a conundrum you found yourself in.
They have something. Alright, what is your game plan today, young lady?
Is that good?
That's good.
Yeah.
Ready to go.
Let's do it.
Okay.
You want to see these?
You want to see what's about to devour your cock?
Okay.
Oh, where'd it go? It's disappeared already.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah, you like those big warm tits?
Oh, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Mm, these big bones.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm.
You like my fucking wet mouth all over the car, yeah?
You like it sloppy?
You're like a fucking sloppy slob.
What about some of this?
You like some of this?
Yeah.
You like big fat tits bouncing on my cock?
You know, just like big fat tits bouncing on the fucking clock.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it goes on for you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Do you like that?
Yes, you like big blood around your dick?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh
Itchy, itchy...
Itchy, yeah.
Oh
It's still over the fucking clock, don't be fucking through.
Oh my god.
Mother.
Oh.
I'm going to kill you!
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, here we go.
Ooh.
Oh, yeah.
I'm about to eat.
I can't believe I'm about to do this.
Oh, yeah.
Ah, ah.
Ah.
I can't breathe.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to eat you.
Oh my god, give it to me, give it to me, please, I want that fucking gun.
Ah, fuck.
Mmm.