Hi.
Come on in.
Hey, I'm Ricky.
My name's Jack.
Nice to meet you.
Ricky, here's the deal.
stop.
You can do something about it?
Yeah, definitely.
That's what I'm here for.
All right, cool.
She might be in and out of the bathroom soon.
Just let her know you're there.
Okie dokie.
Thank you.
Oh my god!
Hi!
Hello.
Are you the plumber?
Yes, I'm just here to fix the pipe.
Oh yeah, so there's a
leak in that
big black
pipe
under there.
Yeah, I'm just gonna...
Go ahead.
So, you fix pipes
often?
Oh, um, yes, uh, sorry.
Oh, do you need me to?
If you can, thank you so much. Appreciate it.
Oh yeah, no, I've been doing it for like six years.
So, if I was doing that, I'm sure I'd get wet a lot, you know what I mean?
Like dealing with so many pipes and the water.
Do you, do you lay the pipe?
Um, if need be.
Okay, cool. Good to know.
little bit of trouble reaching my back, you know, to, to clean it.
Are you talking to me?
Yeah, could you, could you come here and, uh, just help me?
Are you, is that, is that okay?
Did you, you want a light?
Oh no, I mean, I need the assistance.
Okay.
It's greatly appreciated.
Oh yeah, plumbers really know how to handle water.
Yeah.
It's your specialty.
What happens when your jeans get wet?
Do you have to take them off?
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't, I, did I hear that?
Yeah.
a little bit.
I'm, I'm terribly sorry.
It's fine, it's fine.
obviously, you know, it's a hazard and you could get wet.
Yeah, that's actually a good idea.
Yeah, your jeans need to dry.
That way it's not weird if I'm wet.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Good luck.
Oh, you want me to help?
Get my shirt.
Oh my god.
I see you brought your own
big black pipe.
Do you think maybe it has a leak?
Maybe some pressure
I don't know, just...
If you wanted to look...
and opinion.
Holy shit.
Oh, sorry.
I was just like, this is how I assess situations, is with my mouth.
It's just a thing.
I have like more senses in my mouth than in my eyes.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Oh.
Ah, this really is a very large pipe.
You're cleaning it really well.
Thank you. Yeah.
I mean, I've had a little bit of experience with this kind of going.
Yeah.
I don't like it.
Oh my god it's so good, I love it.
Oh please, yeah.
I don't even know what I'm supposed to do.
Pussy?
Oh my god.
Feels so good.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, that feels so fucking good.
Oh god.
Yeah, this is me.
Holy shit.
Oh.
Well, it's up against me, come on, like that.
Fuck, holy shit.
Oh yeah, put it back in there, put it back in there.
Mm, fuck, yeah, yeah.
Oh god.
Oh my god! Fuck!
Every time I get fucking close, he wants to push you right out.
Oh shit!
Oh fuck!
Steve, oh my god!
Shit! Yes!
Yes!
Yes.
Yeah, it's fun.
Getting high.
Oh, fuck yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Dig in.
Oh, fuck yes.
Yeah
Oh shit
Come on
Mmm
What the fuck
Yes
Oh there is some
Oh my god
Fuck I love that
Oh
Oh fuck
Yeah
Oh shit
It's so fucking good, you know when I fucking bounce on it?
Yeah
Oh, fuck
Oh, good
Oh, shit, that's good
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, shit
Oh, my God
Oh my god, it's so f***ing big, I love it
Yeah, yeah, oh my god, oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh f**k baby f**k me d**k mother f**ker
Mother f**ker
Oh my god
Yeah
I feel so f**king great
Oh my god
Yes
Oh god
oh shit that is fucking good yes yeah
oh my god
oh my god like that like that shit shit
i'm kidding bangbros.com
It's just that this isn't the most comfy place to have sex.
We'll make it work.
Yeah.
But the most uncomfortable place you've ever had sex on a set is what?
Oh.
For me it was a stainless steel table, kitchen table.
table.
You know what I mean?
So it was like...
Probably making a lot of noise too.
And not comfortable on your knees.
So that was the most uncomfortable place.
Rocks.
Yeah. I don't know. Rocks aren't great, especially if there's bugs.