I'll be right there.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh, I'm so excited.
Thank you so much for coming.
Would you mind bringing them up for me though?
I just did my nails and I don't wanna ruin them.
I just painted them.
Yeah, no problem.
Thank you so much.
Just up here.
No problem.
I'm so excited to see them.
I'm so glad they arrived.
I need them for an event tonight
and I wasn't sure that they'd arrive in time.
No problem.
Great, they look amazing.
Well, I guess I'll see you later.
you mind maybe helping me put them on, if it's not too much trouble?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
I really appreciate your help.
oh they're such a pretty color wow that's so beautiful
Yeah.
Thanks.
I love the straps.
Oh, that's nice.
Wow, I think they look great.
What do you think?
They look incredible.
I think they go with this dress perfectly.
I'm definitely going to keep them.
They're gorgeous.
I'm glad you like them.
I love them.
I'm definitely going to send a special note
to your store manager for
being so wonderful and getting these
to me on time
thank you so much
I guess I'll get out of here
well before you go
would you mind taking them off for me as well
because obviously
I still don't want to ruin my nails
is that ok?
yeah sure
and I wouldn't want to get nail polish on the shoes
it is not a problem
thank you so much for all your help
I really appreciate it
It is not a problem.
Oh, you have very soft hands.
You really, really do have beautiful feet.
Oh, thank you.
Well, it's nice to have lovely sandals to showcase them.
I'm sure they work good in anything.
Hmm. Oh, you like feet, don't you?
Uh, yeah.
Ya
Must be interesting delivering shoes
It definitely makes the job a little better
Ya
Seeing all those pretty feet
So what do you like about feet?
Cute little toes
Beautiful soles
The way they smell
Like the way they taste
Ya
Your lips and tongue feel so good.
And I want you to wash up my feet. Oh wow, it feels so good.
the first career I've had suck my toes either.
I love the way you make out with my feet.
That drives me crazy.
Mmm, I do like beet.
Mmm, excellent.
I bet you'd love to have my toes wrapped around your cock, wouldn't you?
Mmm.
Oh, god, yeah.
Oh, it feels so good between my toes.
Mmm.
mmmmm
ahh
oh my god
this is so soft
fuck
oh my god
yes
ahh
mmm
yeah
oh my god
ahh
God damn, you're so good.
Oh my God, fuck.
Pshhhh
Ohhhh
Hmmmm
What package do you have for me?
Pie
Mmmmm
Fuck yes
That is so nice
Mmmmm
God that's so nice
I just want to massage it with my feet and my toes
Wrap it around
Get those toes nice and wide
I feel so nice on my sensitive toes.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I don't know.
oh my god
fuck it feels so good
yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, God, it feels so fucking good,
Oh my god, it feels so good, god damn it.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, your tongue is so fucking good.
Oh god damn it, fuck.
I'm gonna put my feet right there.
yeah
shit
yes
yes yes
oh my god
it's so fucking deep like that
yeah
oh
let me get those
heels under the balls like that
yeah
Oh God, he has to keep playing with my pussy like that.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Oh.
yes
fuck
oh my god
that felt so fucking good
yeah
oh
yes
god damn it
fuck
oh
oh god damn
yes yes yes
yes yes
yes
oh
fuck
fuck fuck
fuck yes like that oh my god
fuck
He just pushes his hair right out and he gets close like that.
He just chews the head like that.
Oh
Oh my god, fuck.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, fuck, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
I want to feel your hug come on my toes.
Yes, please, please, please.
I want to feel your hug.
Yes, please, yes, please, come on.
I bet you've got a nice big load for me.
I'm going to feel that hot come.
I'm going to feel it dripping between my toes and down my shoulders.
Yes, please give it to me.
Oh, my God, it's so hot.
Yes.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, yeah, give me every last drop.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, it's so nice and warm between my toes.
I want to lick it up.
That's two.
I don't want to waste a drop.
Tastes so good
Mmm