Shannara, the sexy night elf, needs your help to find the orcs.
back.
she's come to you to recruit you to her team
you didn't hear anything I said after sexy night elf did you
promise me you'll at least hear her out
after you finish fucking her
That's why I've asked you here.
I need you to join us in an assault on Warsong Gulch.
Okay, he didn't see us.
I've heard you're the most powerful warrior in all of Azeroth.
I've also heard some other good things about you.
Some very good things about you.
Very powerful things about you.
Oh wow, that's quite a piece of equipment you've got here.
it could definitely serve us in battle
Mmm
Lovely rod you have here
That is exciting
This is the moment I have been waiting for
Here
Let me get this for you
How about this, will this convince you to join our fight?
Oh yeah, it's convinced many other warriors.
Oh, that's amazing!
Mmm...
Yes, yes...
A warrior such as yourself
shouldn't get any less than this!
Mmm...
Mmm, yeah...
Oh my gosh...
Oh, yes.
Oh
What you like
Oh my lord, yes
It's really quite a sore
I'm not quite sure I should let you fuck me yet though.
Maybe we should see how you do in battle first.
I do want to show you something though.
Would you like to see it?
I would love to show you what you do to me.
Oh, this is what you do to me.
Yes.
Put this please.
Oh yes.
Show me why all the rumors are true, warrior.
Come on.
Put your sword inside me.
I want you to stab me, warrior.
Do it.
Oh.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, yes!
Oh, oh, oh, yes!
Mm-hmm!
Mm, yeah!
Oh!
Oh, yes!
Oh, Warrior!
Oh, me!
Yes, the rumors are true, Warrior!
Oh, yes!
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
Oh, you stabbed me, stabbed me with that big sword, yes.
Oh God, it hurts so good, Worry.
Oh.
Yes.
Very deserving of this pussy, Worry.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, have your way with it.
Yes.
Have your way with it.
Oh.
Mm.
Stay, stay put, warrior.
Stay put.
Let me do it.
Stay.
Oh, you eager little warrior.
You're very eager, aren't you?
Yes, mm-hmm, that's why you're the best.
Uh-huh, just wait there while I ride that sword.
Yes, oh, oh my God, yes, uh-huh, oh, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, yeah.
Yeah, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Mm.
Yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Ow.
Oh, yes.
Mm.
Yes, please fuck me.
Please fuck me.
Yes.
Please fuck me. Yes! Yes!
Ah!
Oh! Yes!
Oh!
Oh god yes!
Oh fuck!
Oh god!
Yes! Please keep going!
Oh my god it's so good!
It's so amazing!
Oh!
Oh yes!
Oh
Thank God, oh, yes
Yes, oh
Last thing we need is a dragon right now. Don't you think?
Oh yes, oh yes.
Oh God, yes.
Oh God.
Yes, oh yes.
Oh, mm-hmm, yes.
You like that more, right here?
Yes, oh God, yes.
Oh
Please, oh, yes, yes, warrior, uh-huh, keep going, yes.
Oh my goodness, warrior, oh, mm-hmm, uh-huh, uh-huh,
oh, yes, uh-huh, oh, warrior, yes.
Oh, no, please don't stop, please don't stop,
oh, yes, here, go nice and slow, mm, yes, mm, uh-huh, yes.
oh yes, oh yes, just like that, just like that, just like that, uh huh,
Mm, yes, please, yes, oh, it's so good.
Oh, oh, you, oh.
Oh, yes, uh-huh, just like that, yes.
Mm, uh-huh, oh, you, oh, right here, please.
Oh, that's so amazing, it's so amazing, yes, yes.
Oh my god, yes, Mario, please keep going, yes.
Oh my god, oh
Yeah, oh yes
Yes, oh, oh, it's so amazing, yes, uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah.
Don't you stop, don't you stop.
Get your finger out of there.
Don't you stop, uh-huh, uh-huh, yes, uh-huh, yeah, oh.
You're so good, oh, oh, yes, unleash that rage, please.
Please, warrior, please, yes, uh-huh, yes, yes, uh-huh.
Use that on me, warrior, yeah, um, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God, oh, God, mm-hmm, mm.
Oh, yes, spank it, warrior, spank it, mm-hmm.
Yeah
I don't want to be here.
Mmm.
Oh my.
So good.
Ah.
Oh my.
Oh
You ready for more you want some more elvish pussy
So amazing, oh
So powerful inside
Oh
Oh, yes, oh, yes, warrior, oh my god, yes, mm-hmm, yes.
You like that, don't you, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Oh, yes, oh, oh, mm-hmm, yes, yes, warrior, yes, oh, oh.
Oh
Oh, yes, prepare for battle, yeah, just like that.
Oh, you show me how powerful and strong you are.
Oh, yes, you're doing such a good job, yes, oh, yes.
Oh, you're such a worthy warrior, uh-huh.
Oh, my God, it's amazing.
oh
Oh, God.
Mmm.
Oh.
Please keep going.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
It's so good.
Mmm.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Mmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Ah.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Please.
Oh , yes, oh my God.
Wow.
Ohhh, oh.
F **** it is so good.
Oh my God.
Mmmmm.
Oh
Put that big sword back in my pussy warrior
Yes, you stab me with your sword warrior, yes, oh
Oh, yes, just like oh, you're so good at that
Uh-huh, yes, yes, mm-hmm, yes, ooh, give it back to me.
Yes, yes, oh my god, it's so powerful.
Oh, you're ticket's so powerful, warrior.
Oh, the big, huge sword is so strong inside me, yes.
Yes, warrior, oh my god, oh, oh, please, yes.
Ah, yes.
Oh, yes.
Please, uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Oh, fuck.
Mm-hmm.
So good.
Ah, yes.
Do you like that?
Do you like that, Mario?
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
oh my god
oh god
oh
oh my god
you just keep
stabbing me with that big sword
please don't stab me with that big sword
yes
oh
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh my goodness, yes.
Oh, oh.
You're so good at that word.
So powerful.
Oh my word.
I had no idea how powerful your sword would be.
Oh god, yes.
Uh huh.
Yes.
You like, yes.
yes spread those little slutty elf legs
yes oh god yeah uh-huh strip me with that sword please please yes
Mm-hmm, yeah, happy, ooh, ooh, build up that rage, warrior.
Do what you need to do, yes.
Oh, oh, oh my goodness, oh.
Yeah, uh-huh, uh-huh, warrior, that's good, that's good.
Just like that, just like that, that's so good, yes.
Yes!
Ah!
Mmm!
Mm!
Ah!
Yes, baby!
Yes!
Ah!
Mmm!
Oh, yes!
Mm!
Mmm!
Warrior!
Mm!
Oh, this is so amazing!
Oh, that sword!
I can't get enough of that sword, warrior!
Oh, my god!
Oh!
Oh, it's incredible!
Mm-hmm!
Oh
Tap me with that sword, yes, please.
Please tap me with that sword.
Oh my goodness, yes.
Oh, uh-huh, yeah, oh.
Mm-hmm, yeah, mm-hmm, yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Save some for the fight, yeah, oh yeah.
Tap it on my pussy, yes, tap it, uh-huh, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yes, yes, oh yes.
Oh, oh, mm.
Oh, oh, oh, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, mm.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, warrior, warrior.
Give it to me, warrior.
I know what you want to give me.
Unleash your rage, warrior.
You should love me.
Yes, warrior, yes.
Please, please, warrior.
I want it.
I want it, warrior.
I'm so glad you're on our team.
Yeah, we just need to find a healer.