You
We need to keep it moist.
We know how to cook the pork.
How about girls?
I thought we were going to be girls here.
I thought you came over here for meat.
I did come over for meat.
Okay, well we got chicken.
We got jalapeno peppers.
We got kebab.
We got chicken.
You know what would be better?
We got beef.
I think...
That doesn't make any sense.
Yeah
Her mouth is watering from the meat which meat
I don't think you ever invited any other girl.
Serious
It's real sweaty, you need to take them shorts off.
It's a nice ass crew back here.
I could put a beer right here.
We have all afternoon, gentlemen.
We got some work.
We don't need work to do.
We don't need those for that type of work.
Wait, wait, wait. One more game, one more game.
Now we got some buns to go with
the meat over there on the grill.
You know what I wonder?
Can we see her titties from the back?
Between your legs. Between your legs. Can you see them titties shaking?
Yeah, I have really big tits.
I know. We know it.
As if we didn't know that already.
They're 34DD.
34DD. We gonna eat all day, guys. We gonna eat all day.
Shut up.
They're raw meat.
No.
Hang on. Hang on. So what do you think about it?
I don't burn them titties.
Is that okay?
It's more meat for me, you know
Hey guys the meats almost done
You guys I think the meats done
I think we can go this way
I'm going to bring it forward for you
hold on, hold on
go inside the office
yes, I'm going to go
go ahead
thanks for inviting me, Shemeka
of course, I just knew you would enjoy it
yea, all the meat
all the meat
all the available meat
yea, I really like all the meat
it's so good
it's a very large selection of meat
good appetite?
yea
yes
come on in, baby
we got you
yea
I love a feast
how about this?
I'm going to get some of this
who's eating meat?
We got you.
I'm going to get the door for you real quick.
Okay, go ahead.
You guys are hungry too, right?
Yeah?
You guys want to have a little appetizer fun?
Oh, you want to have a little nap?
We all in it now?
We all in it together now?
I'm going to have them throw out boxes and keep opening them up.
Or, let's get her open both of them.
I'm going to throw out boxes and keep opening them up.
Oh my God, look at that big head.
She looked like she had quite the appetite.
Look at those titties, fellas, left to right.
Oh, shit.
Get up and touch those titties, everybody.
You ever see titties like that all summer?
Bring it back.
You need to take your hand to the floor.
Grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab.
Barbecue and stroke.
There you go.
You are a tit in the barbecue, sweetheart.
You are dead in the barbeque, sweetheart, and it's dick in your mouth.
Real rock sausage.
Real cricket!
Oh, my gosh.
That was so lame.
Who was it?
That's the other dick.
I'm going to give you one more before I get up out of here.
I'm going to gag you one more time, I'm going to...
I'm going to...
I'm going to smash it.
Oh my God!
Double jack!
Double jack! About to get the jack!
You're about to get the double jack!
Oh, look at that.
Back and forth.
Oh!
Oh my God!
You're so hot!
Right down your throat there.
Sorry!
Be gentle, just gentle.
You're blowing, queen!
Spit, he's got the worst.
Come back this way, come back this way, you got that wet stroke.
You got that spit going?
Okay, okay.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's a lava mouth, it's a lava mouth.
It's a lava mouth.
Slow stroke, slow stroke, it's nice and romantic.
Romantic with that dirty look.
Yeah, suck and stroke. Suck and stroke, baby.
Suck and stroke, baby.
Suck and stroke, baby. Oh, shit, yeah.
Don't fall back. Don't fall back.
You got another one.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
Put your hands down.
Oh, there you go.
So what do you think about barbeque so far?
I like it.
You like it?
You are attending a barbeque.
Oh my God, it's a big cut here!
Oh, thank you, Lord!
Pretty on there.
Let me get that big cut one more time.
Real slow, we're going to do it slow.
All the way down.
There you go, girl.
One more time, nice and slow.
There you go.
Very nice, very nice.
It's all fucked me.
Get out of my house.
Get out of my fucking house.
Hang on.
Nobody's fucking nobody until she says what, gentlemen?
Please.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, please.
Yes, please.
Please.
Please give me this black meat.
I need a watch.
Please give it to me.
Give it to me.
Do it, do it, do it, oh my god, oh my god, yes!
Come back on that, too.
Oh my god, look at this big fucking dick, yes!
Yeah, take it, take it, come on, take it, yeah!
You are tending this dick bar of dicks!
Dig your ass out!
I don't like long distances.
No, no, no.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Look at you.
You want to sit on my dick.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh.
I can hear you baby.
I can hear you.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
That looked good.
Then what?
Yeah.
Look in the mirror.
Put that shit in the mirror.
Taste that pussy.
Come taste your pussy.
Oh shit you about to attend this barbecue and this dicks for you
Oh my god, yes! Yes! Oh, it's so good! Oh my god, yes!
Oh, fuck, yes, I love it!
Mark, please, please, please, please!
It's so good!
Put a stick in your mouth, put a stick in your mouth.
Here you go, here you go.
Yeah, boy!
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck!
tag out
another tag in
get that ass in the air
oh shit
there we go
oh
oh my god
how do you feel
oh my god I'm so fucking good
yes
oh my god
give me that black knee please
yes
take it bitch
Get up.
Get up, son.
Get up, bitch.
Get up.
Come on.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes.
Sit down.
Yeah.
That's it.
There we go.
Yeah.
Take your places.
Sit down.
Sit.
Yeah.
Give it to me.
Yes.
More.
Mm.
So good.
Yeah.
Mm.
Swing.
Oh.
She's not too good.
Yeah.
Oh my god, this is so good.
Get that back to me.
Get it back to me.
Give me that fucking, give me that fucking dick.
Give me that, give me that black fucking dick.
Give me that.
Oh, shit.
We can taste the stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Look at those fucking eyes, man.
Yes.
That tongue, those eyes.
You're going to get your eye out.
You're going to tear it.
Fuck that bitch.
Fuck her up.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Jump that bitch.
Oh, my God.
I choked that bitch, I choked her!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Please, please, please don't kill me.
Snap her, little bitch. Snap her, little bitch.
Next.
You boys are crazy.
That's what you came here for.
Come here, bitch.
This pussy is for barbecue.
First.
You need something to eat, man?
I left.
Jerk.
Come on, come on, Natasha, that pussy is nice.
Yes, give it to me, oh my God.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Come on, all the way, all the way.
That pussy is nice.
All the way, all the way.
No wonder they call you nice.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Nice, baby.
Oh my God.
Nice pussy.
Oh, deep in your mouth.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, look how deep, look how deep it's in your mouth.
Look how deep it's in your mouth.
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah!
Oh yes!
Perfect!
Oh!
Oh fuck, yes!
Yes!
Oh yes!
Hold it close!
Oh my God!
Ah!
Switch!
Oh man!
Oh let me take that for you.
You want to see it?
Oh!
Open your eyes up there for me baby.
Fuck yes!
Oh my god it's so fucking big!
Yeah it is.
I love it!
Take it away!
She's talking too much!
AHHHH!
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh my god it's so big!
Oh my god.
It's so big!
So, we're going to see if your back was hurt.
Arch that back.
Arch that.
Motherfucker.
Oh, fuck you.
Let that ass.
Oh, God.
Jump in.
Come up to me.
Get out of there.
It's so fucking wet right now.
Oh my god, it's so fucking big, I love it.
Yeah, I want you guys to cover me with cups.
You know I deserve it!
There you go.
Down the throat.
Oh, I'm such a good girl.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck you.
This is fine.
Wait, give me that mouth hand, actually.
Use that hand.
Oh, shit.
Give me that mouth.
What did I just say?
Oh
Give me that
What?
Is that what she was asking for?
Rock, rock, rock, rock.
Oh, yeah.
It's the off-bouncy water.
I think you're turning red.
Ah.
No.
Oh.
What are you guys going to do now?
Oh, my.
Come on.
Get it on your face.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Please, give me some.
Please.
I've been such a good girl.
Oh.
I'm gonna eat you, baby.
I want to eat your fucking face.
Oh!
Oh, baby.
You're my baby.
Baby.
Oh!
Oh, you motherfucking fuck, baby.
Oh, yeah.
I said you're gonna remember that shit later.
Oh!
I still want more.
Say please.
May I please have some more?
I'll take more than you will, baby, you know that?
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Keep him till he's bouncy.
There we go.
Pretend to barbecue.
You're about to get shot, girl.
You better catch that.
You deserve the sauce.
Yeah, I deserve the sauce.
Please.
I deserve the sauce.
Give her the sauce.
Give it to me, please.
I wanted something bad.
Oh
Yeah
BOO!
Dammit.
Right?
I'm completely happy.
It'll be alright.
Just like this.
Like that.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, I can feel it coming.
I can feel it coming and I fucking want it.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Please, yeah?
Oh!
It's breathing!
Oh no!
Oh!
He's more tense!
Oh my God!
Oh!
It's breathing!
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
What's that all?
It's not your fault.
Not your fault.
Can I have it please?
I want it.
Please, I want it, please.
Please, please, please.
Make yourself come.
Sound off of that cup!
Please! Yes!
Yes! Oh my God!
Sound off of that cup!
Keep bouncing.
Drip!
Turn to the front.
all over my fucking slot face
I
Hold on, Mitch! Hold on!
That's the one!
There it is!
Take that with you when you leave.
There you go.
Put that in the box.
Oh, thank you.
The meat's done.
Oh, is it?
My meat is done, too!
Apparently.
I'm out of here.
Let's go.
She took all my meat.
Oh my gosh.
I'm so sleepy.
Thank you.
I'm tired.
Hi.
I need that butt, man.
Thanks for the meat, guys.
Thank you.
Excellent.
Scratch.