Did you say fuck your cousin or you wanted to fuck your cousin?
I did!
Girl or guy?
Guy.
Hi.
Get the fuck out you little slut.
I'm a slut right?
See it hasn't even been a minute and you're already turning me on.
I made the right choice obviously.
You have great boobs.
I'm loving how hot it is in here.
I know right. You're going to get sweaty.
It makes your skin feel so slick and moist.
Moist?
Yeah.
You have a great tan.
Do I? Do you like that?
Yeah.
You're a little beach babe.
I grew up in the 80's and I like tan.
Do you want to share it with me?
You deserve it, you know that?
I know.
You're such a little slut.
I can't help being a slut, can you?
No, I'm not.
No, you can't.
I don't really want to.
You're just a slut.
I know.
I'm just a fucking whore.
I'm not fucking sorry.
Oh, look at these tits.
I'm not a whore.
Look at these tits.
Yeah, you have these big fucking tits.
Yeah.
Did they turn you on?
Mia pinch him harder, Mia pinch him harder
Mia make him scream, make him scream
Yes oh fuck fuck yes
Oh fuck
Mia Mia these beautiful
faces
Let me show you guys my titties
Oh my god
Oh
Oh fuck
Oh Mia yes
I can't wait for you to do these nails.
On your neck?
Yeah.
Do you want to bite it?
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
That's beautiful.
So, I'm just going to put you on my neck, too.
Put your face right there.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, look at that pretty tongue.
Oh, that fucking nipple.
Yeah.
Look at me. What are you fucking doing to me?
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Let me see this ass.
I just want to look at it.
It's so fucking pretty.
Look at this butt.
Oh, it's so hard.
Oh, you pretty little pussy.
Oh, yeah, are you a bad girl, Chrissy?
Isn't that pretty naughty, too?
Yeah.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh.
It turns me on.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh my god.
Do you guys want to see this?
Oh.
Oh, look at that.
You want to put your paws in here?
Nice tight, deep hole.
Uh-huh.
Mm.
Ah, your cheeks are looking good.
I'm gonna take this right here.
Look at you.
Oh, let me just spread this a little bit.
Yeah, look at that.
Aw.
Aw, look at your cheeks.
Ah, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, we know what you like in there.
Yeah.
Yeah, you look so good.
Oh my God.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Ah.
Oh, it feels too good.
It feels so good.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna put it on my foot.
Oh my God!
It's perfect.
You wanna taste?
I think I ate it all.
Maybe some more for you.
Creamy pussy.
Yeah.
I want it. It sits all over mine.
It's okay.
Let's get really messy.
Yeah.
I know.
Oh yeah, that's better.
That's good.
Can you clean up my pussy for me?
Look how you begged.
I cannot.
I'm so sorry.
You teased me.
I'm going to get teased right back.
Play with me.
I'm going to be your little toy.
You are my little toy.
It's okay.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, are you teasing me?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
You play with my slutty pussy.
Such a slutty pussy.
Yes, oh my god, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah, like the fucking clit, yes.
Oh my god, yes, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, shit, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, it's so wet.
Yes, yes.
Oh my god, just look at my fucking big clit, baby, please.
Please don't fucking stop. Please don't stop.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
It's so fucking wet.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Don't stop. Don't fucking stop.
You're fucking crying and making me fucking cry.
Yes!
Oh.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Get him out of there.
You just close them up.
OK.
Yes.
Can you do me a favor and sit back down?
Oh my God.
You get all of it, don't you?
She wants to get all of it.
Oh, I don't mind if I do, right girl?
Yeah.
You're so pretty.
You're my mommy.
Oh my, you really know how to do that.
It's so good.
Fuck you. I was like a pussy. Don't you go sucking pussy.
Oh my god.
Stick your tongue out.
I'm gonna rub my face
Do you hear my voice?
I'm coming!
Oh, lick up all the juices.
Oh, yeah, lick it up.
Oh, do a good job.
Stay right there.
Oh my god.
It's delicious.
Yeah.
That can be arranged.
I just love these.
Maybe we should have sex on the beach.
I like that.
Until someone comes.
Yeah.
We should have sex on the beach, until someone catches us.
Maybe I'll just fall inside your swimsuit.
Maybe I'll just make you calm.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Aw.
You like that?
Yeah.
Aw.
Oh, good.
Here, let me get you out of here.
Oh, my God.
Is it that bad?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's good.
Yeah, like this?
Yeah.
It's hot.
Come here.
It's so warm.
It's so shiny.
It's so slippery.
Yes.
It's a nice tight coat.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, it's clenching up on me.
Yes.
I'll give you a massage as well.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh, how fast.
Fuck you.
Fuck yes.
Oh!
Oh, thank you.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, that hurts.
Yeah.
That hurts.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
Oh.
You might have to taste this, because I want to have dinner.
Taste it for me?
Mm.
Oh.
It's too beautiful?
Mm.
You're so admirable.
Oh.
I'm sorry
i'm sorry
fuck
oh fuck
Oh, my God, yes.
Fuck yeah, oh my God.
Yes, yes.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh yes, yes.
That big ass, yeah.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh shit, yes, yes!
Fuck yes!
I think I need a napkin.
It's like a hundred degrees in here. I love it.
I know. I'm sick.
Let's see.
Oh, it's your turn to lay back.
Oh yeah, that's him right there.
Oh, yeah, you wish you were me right now.
I wish they were.
Oh my God, that's so good.
Oh God, that's good suction.
I feel real good sucking on the head of your cock.
Oh my God, it's a powerful suction.
Oh, you are a pleaser, girl.
You are a keeper.
Smells good, too.
Maybe I'll just tie you up and keep you in my room.
You and your guy friends can have your way with me.
You and your girlfriends, too.
I don't want to fuck you.
Yeah, I'm a total old neighborhood.
Oh, you're all messy.
Thank you for coming to fuck me today.
She sounds so innocent, doesn't she?
But she's not!
That's all for fun.
It's my pleasure.
And thanks for watching you guys.
Bye guys.