She's going to be split open.
Right? You see what I'm saying?
Yeah, I think I'm going to have to masturbate at work.
Hang on a sec, I think my annoying coworker is in my office.
Let me just call you right back.
Excuse me?
Yes, yes.
Were you just staring at my tits?
No, I was just helping, you know, clean the office.
I don't know.
You have a big black cock?
Yeah.
Maybe, um, I mean, maybe you should show it to me.
If I show you my dick, will you show me your tits?
nobody does that oh my god holy fuck what wow okay that's that's that's
that's definitely what I'm into oh okay oh you don't mind
Oh yeah, you should. You should just take it off.
Holy fuck.
I'm so fucking big.
You are serious.
Holy shit.
This is as long as my forearm.
Shit.
Damn, you just let me suck the back of your throat like that.
Oh.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Wow.
Holy fuck.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
Oh, keep that all in there.
I'm gonna stir it up in here.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh yeah, yeah, I think she does that just here.
You know what, maybe we should make you more comfortable too.
Really?
Yeah, should we go over to the couch?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, let's go.
There you go.
No fucking hands.
You can just bounce these big fucking tits around.
Yeah.
You're too fucking sexy.
I've been watching you a long time.
Not spying.
Watching.
I'm not spying.
Oh, really?
You want to squeeze in too?
I'm nice and fucking tired.
You can't squeeze in.
Here.
Oh, fuck.
Look at that.
She looks cute.
Fuck off.
I'm so happy you're such a nice big dick for me.
What the fuck is going on with you?
Oh shit.
I'm gonna sit on that face of yours.
Yeah, dude.
Oh fuck, look at that.
Oh, this is so fucking good.
Oh, fuck.
I should have just these big fucking tits.
Mmm.
Oh, fuck, it's so big.
Mm-hmm.
Titties.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck!
Oh my god guys!
Oh yes! Look at their fucking tongues!
You've been so mean!
Oh my god! Look at them!
That's you!
Yeah!
Oh
God, you're going to make that pussy cum.
You better get your...
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna fucking cum all of that dick.
Okay, let me tease it.
Mmm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, you.
Yeah.
Oh my god, baby, fuck.
There it is, there it is.
Yes, you, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh shit.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, take it.
Take it.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
You don't want to taste my fucking ass with your dick?
Oh, fuck.
I think the bus will be really proud of us.
It's so fucking nice.
Fuck, it's as big as my head.
Let me hit it from the high too.
Which would you like first?
Fuck.
Oh my god. Wow.
Oh, fuck. Yeah.
Yes. God, baby, you stretch that all so good. Oh my god. Fuck.
Oh, yeah. Let me fucking bounce that up.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, fuck! Oh my god!
Oh god, baby! Fuck, it's so good!
Oh my god!
Yeah, I'm going to do another last half.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God, you stretched it out so good.
oh my god
oh let me taste that
Oh my god, that looks so fucking good, too.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, that feels so fucking good.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
That's true.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, that cup feels so good. I can feel it in my ass.
I want you to fill it up.
Yeah.
I want you to go back to my pussy
and then into my ass again.
Oh God, I could frog like you do.
Yes, please, into that little pussy.
Oh, fuck, yeah, I want all of my holes used by you today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna put your chicks right on there.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, and stick it right back in that ass.
Oh my God, fuck, yes, yes, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, fuck.
It's so fucking deep, Jesus Christ!
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Shit!
Fuck!
That food!
That's what I wanted!
Yes, yes!
You fucking
motherfucker!
I hate you right now, JESUS CHRIST!
Fuck!
Oh fuck, you're gonna fucking kill me with that dick.
Shit.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, baby.
I feel so f***ing dead.
Thank you.
Yes, how do you think?
Oh, that's so f***ing amazing.
I don't even want to f*** these baby titties.
You don't want to f*** them?
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, right between those big tits.
Yeah, my cock feels so good between these big natural titties.
Oh my god, yes, I love that sound.
You don't think we were too loud, right?
No one noticed it in the office.
Nobody came in, so we're good.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, so I'm going to finish that Bang Bros update.
Bangbros.com
I'm sorry, say that again?
Don't come, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, we still need a little more footage, right?
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry, I thought I...
going through the motions, you know what I mean?
You know, just like, you know what I mean?
But, because you're my bro, it's okay,
you know what I mean?
You can totally fucking, you know,
make up for it by you guys, like, you know,
doing some sort of like, you know,
thing in the bathroom, you know, off camera.
Because I heard that, you know,
she likes that kind of stuff, you know what I mean?
After like, she gets, you know,
cum on her face and she's like, totally into that stuff.
And then my, my, my wrist.
It was like, present, present.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, I didn't mean to touch me.
Yeah, I didn't want to, don't mind me.
Wait, wait, don't touch him right now.
The scene's over.
We're not paying for that.