Angela, come in.
I'm glad you could make it.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Come have a seat.
So, did you have any trouble finding the place?
Not at all.
Good.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Could I offer you something to drink?
Nothing for now.
Thank you.
All right.
Well, thank you for inviting me here today.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Well, thank you for coming.
Of course.
How do you like the place?
It's very nice.
Good.
So, what are you in town for?
I'm actually on a little business meeting with my company.
Oh, okay. What does your company do?
Nothing really exciting.
I just work for this tech company.
We make some different apps and stuff like that.
Cool.
Yeah, so how long have you been out here for?
I've been out here for two years.
Okay.
Yeah.
Is it what you thought it was going to be like?
Good.
Yeah, I'm enjoying myself a lot shooting a lot. Oh, it's wonderful
So, um, have you?
Done anything like this before?
Not on this level. I've had a couple massages and
I've never met up with someone on your level before. This is something I've always kind of fantasized about
The porn star
well thank you I mean you are my favorite yeah so you like my scenes you
like what I do like everything about you yeah the prettiest eyes I've ever seen
thank you and your smile is just like it's from ear to ear well I must say you
You have beautiful eyes as well.
Oh, thank you.
I guess it takes one to know one.
So have you always been this good looking?
Well, beauty is subjective.
For sure.
I'm glad you like what you see.
I do.
And what about what you like in terms of sex?
and obviously you've seen my scene so you know what I do but I have range so what kind of
experience would you like today I would like for you to make me feel like you are falling
in love with me that would be my pleasure good so what do you like hmm how can I please you
there are so many ways you can please me but you know today is about you but if you feel
like pleasing me I'm sure you have many ways well it makes me happy to make you happy
what a man well before we make each other happy I know you wanted to pay
extra for bareback I did now my safety and your safety are of highest priority
so did you get tested like I did you'd like to see I would love to see I will
will show you my test as well. Perfect. Thank you so much. You're welcome. Let me just get
mine up. There you go. Feel free to zoom in. Awesome. Excellent. So how does this work?
Well, since you asked for the lingerie package, I'm going to try on a few sexy outfits for
for you. Give you a little show. We'll get you all
worked up before I start to fall
madly and deeply in love with you. I like the sound of that.
And there's one last thing I have to take care of
before we begin. What's that?
Did you leave what I asked you to in the bathroom?
I did. Well, let me get that out of the way
so that then we can get this party started.
Sounds good to me.
I will be right back.
You're gonna be a fun one.
What do you think?
I think that's my favorite color ever.
Matches your blue eyes.
Yes it does.
I see what's going on now.
Did you find what I left for you?
I did, thank you, that's perfect.
Good.
So, I also have another outfit that I can try on for you.
But, why don't you take a seat
and I'll give you a better look at this outfit.
I don't like it, I love it.
Do you like the way it squeezes my breasts together?
Oh, it's amazing.
Well, you did ask for a tease, didn't you?
You're very good at it, too.
So would you like me to put on the other outfit for you?
I would love that.
I'm going to tease you by making you wait to see my breasts.
It's fine. I've been waiting my whole life.
You have such a pretty tan.
Thank you.
That's lovely.
Very feminine pink.
Heels or no heels?
No heels.
You got it.
You ready to finally see them?
A little bit.
Sit on your hands.
Ah, yes ma'am.
You can't get the T's lingerie package without getting T's.
Oh, shit.
The best tits I've ever seen.
Not yet.
I can't get over how beautiful you are.
Thank you.
I bet you taste even better than you look.
You'll find out.
Good.
That looks pretty good.
Oh you definitely pull it off so what is it about watching a woman get dressed in
lingerie it turns you on so much I like the spiritual connection I feel from
from anticipation.
Mmm.
You sound like a man
who likes the chase.
I think I do.
Mmm.
You sound like a man
who both
likes
to get what he wants
but also
kind of doesn't.
You kind of
I like to wait, be denied, hmm.
How do you know me so well?
I'm pretty good at reading people.
Stay.
I'm speechless.
I know what you're thinking.
What am I thinking?
You really, really want me right now.
I do.
But you also really, really want me to continue to not let you have it.
Maybe for a little bit.
Just a little bit.
Maybe just a little bit.
Kind of makes the torture of waiting okay, knowing that you're going to get it at some point.
Well, I'm all about the journey and not the destination.
Oh, good man.
so what do you think of the way this bra holds my tits up it looks lovely but I
think it's gonna look even better if you put on what I got you you got me some
I'm good, you wanna see?
Of course.
I'll sit right there.
Me?
Right here.
Well, thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Oh, you're a man of taste.
Yes, I am.
So the robe was a good choice.
You like it?
I love it.
Good.
It's beautiful.
Oh, classy.
Oh, I see.
Now I see.
You like stockings, huh?
I knew you were going to be a fun one.
Okay.
I'll take one last look at this lingerie.
How it caresses my curves.
So you can compare it
with the beautiful lingerie you bought me.
Maybe... you'd like to help me out of this?
Oh, I would.
Maybe... you'd like to pull my straps down?
Oh, going straight? Wow.
You like that?
Very nice.
Thank you.
Mmm.
Do you like the way I taste?
Keep that in your mouth.
Suck on it.
Suck out my juices.
How do I taste?
Not bad.
You're naughty. You taste great.
Do I taste sweet?
I didn't get enough taste. I'm gonna have to.
Suck your tongue out.
So what do you think of this bra?
I see you know my size. I think it's a perfect fit.
I really like this.
Good, you can keep it. A little memento
of you. Well thank you. I guess you
know the trick. You gotta put the garters on first.
Oh, is that the trick? Otherwise how are you supposed to
take the panties off after? I don't know, that's a good question. Oh, this is an interesting pair.
Okay, let's see. You solved the mystery. It's cute.
I want the best one.
Why? You already spent big on your package. I guess that says a lot about you and your
Tech company.
Well, you're definitely worth every penny.
Thank you.
What do you think?
I think you are one in a zillion.
Like the way it frames my arms?
Oh my god, I love it.
This is the trick.
You put the panties on first.
So when the stockings are on,
go with them.
Surprised you didn't know that one, playboy.
Any man who likes a robe loves a good tease.
But I saved the best till last.
Did you?
I did.
Tell me more.
I'm gonna need you to help me with my stockings.
Oh, is that so?
I think you were hoping I would need a hand.
Maybe too.
so do you know how to put these on a woman you want to teach me I will slowly
finger the pantyhose like this bringing the toe up to meet the opening you place
And simply roll. Would you like to try?
I would. So let me get this straight. You finger it first.
That's right.
And you get to the bottom and you slide it all the way.
Mm-hmm.
And...
Oh, you're a fast learner.
Mm-hmm.
Now does this clamp?
It does.
How does that work?
Take this like that, place it onto here.
So you see that little mouth?
Place it onto here.
This is a thick one.
Might not be the last time you say that tonight.
Oh, really?
Uh-huh.
Okay, Playboy.
You want to try that side?
Yeah, let me see if I got this right.
Alright. So you slide the thick side in the hole, and you slide it, just like that.
Well done.
Thank you.
Is this distracting you? So what do you think?
I think I got it.
And the question is, with such pretty lingerie, do you leave it on, or do you take it off?
I think we should take it off
Already?
I do
I think part of you wants me to ignore you
Yeah, I think you're enjoying this torture a little bit
I think you enjoy me getting this close to you
you almost having me and then me taking it away.
Such a well behaved boy too.
So are you married?
No.
So I can kiss you?
Yeah.
May I kiss you?
Please.
I have another surprise in store for me, huh?
Holy fuck.
Just what you deserve.
You're thick.
Your tits.
They're a good match.
I think your tits on your chest are about the same size in proportions as my cock on my waist.
You could be right.
So how many times have you jacked this thick cock watching my movies?
Countless.
watching me on my knees stroking and sucking wishing you were sitting right where you are
my god stroke it for me while i take this off whatever you say
Oh, you didn't do a very good job at these, did you?
You need more practice
Nice try, though
My god, this lips
Wrap these big tits around that butt
Is that okay?
Make it dance for me
Looks so good
Move it off
Nice and wet for these tits
Oh you like that
Yeah
Just having my hands running like that
Oh I love that sound
Doesn't that feel good?
Just massage that cock with these big tits
Make these tits nice and shiny for you
oh my god your eyes are so fucking gorgeous
i love the way you look at me
such a beautiful body you have too
oh god
oh my god
God, yes, yes, yes, oh, yeah, oh, that's fucking good, yeah, keep going like that, oh, yeah, yeah, oh, thanks, fuck, fuck, yeah, just like that, oh,
Fuck!
Oh my god, yes, please please please
mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
I'm going to tease my pussy with that glove, that's right, just tease it, just like a tease
right now, just like that, I'm going to chuck it right there, teasing my clit like that,
slow baby
oh
yes
fuck
it's so thick
god damn it
fuck
yeah
oh
Oh shit, oh, oh, fuck, fuck, oh man, I feel fucking good, bear in that pussy, bear in that pussy,
Yeah, do it, do it, do it, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yes, yes, oh my
Oh my god, it looks so fucking good going to that pussy like that.
There you go. There you go. There you go.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yes.
Yes! Fuck!
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh my god. Fuck.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God. Yes. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Oh, shit. Yes. Oh, my God. Fuck. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, oh my god, please, oh my god, oh fuck, yes, yes, just like that, just like
Oh my god, oh my god
God, it feels so fucking good inside me, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, take me, take me, take me, take me, take me, yes, yes, yes, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, it's so fucking good,
Yes, yeah, do it, do it, do it, yeah, fuck, it's so quick, I don't know, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, oh, fuck, oh, my God, yes, fuck, yes, yes, yes, keep going like that, oh, you're
You're gonna make me fucking cum on that poke.
Oh fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Just like that, fuck, oh no.
Oh fuck, oh fuck.
I knew you would be a fun one
I can't do this
It's beautiful
Let's see how it's going to stir up this cock
Yeah
Oh fuck
I'm going to get on top of that cock
Yeah
Oh jeez
Please, that pussy.
Holy fuck.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna sit all the way down on that cock.
It falls deep inside that pussy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yes, yes, yes, oh fuck, yeah, yeah, make me take all of that coke, make me take all of
it, every last inch of it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh fuck, yes, yes, yes, yeah, yeah,
Yeah, yeah, yes, give it to me, holy fuck, oh my god, yes, yes, fuck, oh, yes, yes, oh,
oh, oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, I love that feeling. It holds deep inside me.
Something so deep inside that pussy.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yes. Oh, fuck.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, fuck. Yes.
Give it to me. Give it to me. Give it to me. Fuck. Yeah.
Yes!
Fuck!
Oh my god!
She is a heaven!
Fuck!
Yes!
Yeah.
Did you just get close, did you?
There you go.
I'm gonna come, yeah.
I'm gonna get you full time.
Can I lick you?
Yeah, suck it there.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh, it's throbbing.
So sexy.
My cockles throbbing inside my pussy is so close to coming inside me, babe.
I haven't sucked on those balls yet.
Oh my god.
Oh, I love the taste of your pre-cum.
Fuck.
It's so nice and sweet.
You can get back on.
Yeah, I can get back on.
Yeah, are you sure?
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, oh, fuck, yes, yes, there we go, there we go, oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, yes, oh, I feel
so fucking good inside my pussy, like, yeah, yeah, you can just lay back and enjoy, yeah,
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You deserve this. You deserve to just relax and enjoy. Yeah. Oh, fuck. Yes. Yes. Oh, fuck. Yes. Yes.
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
oh my god yeah yeah yeah yeah oh i feel you throbbing huh you're getting close to
you okay
fucking come back
I got my neck cut, I fucking got my neck cut
Oh fuck
Yes
I love how purple it gets
So fucking beautiful
Oh fuck, yes, yes, pull that butt back inside me, oh fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, I'm gonna come just like that.
I'm gonna come just like that, I'm gonna come just like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh!
ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
I know you look so sexy when you fuck that beautiful body, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh god damn it, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh god, yeah, you feel so good, you can tell, you feel like that, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah, it's all looking, yeah, good fucking view right there, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Oh my god, yeah, yeah, oh, you're driving me fucking crazy, Jesse, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mmm, yeah, this is so fucking good, yeah, oh my, yeah, oh my god, look at that fucking
booger, look at that fucking booger, yeah, yeah, oh my god, it looks so good, fuck, yeah,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Hmm, tentacles are fucking animals, aren't they?
I'm gonna fucking come at you, you little bunny.
Fucking animal, fucking animal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
That fucking beast.
Yeah, yeah.
Get your fucking head off the floor.
Yeah.
Oh, come fuck these, Ted.
Come here.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Oh
Oh, next time you're back in town, you're going to be teased and miss me until then.
Me too.
Good.
We have more to explore.
Well, I'm going to freshen up.
Okay.
Have a quick shower.
Take your time.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I think that's your shirt.
Oh, I might need that.
Well, thank you for an incredible evening.
I had a really good time.
I had a good time too.
Good.
I'll be thinking about you.
How about I get to see you again soon?
You will.
Let me know when you're back in town.
Okay.
And have a good meeting with your company.
I'll have the best meeting ever.
Mmmmm