you to do.
Yes, Mistress.
reflection in them deep-throated show me how far you can take it down
Good buddy boy.
Lay down.
Stick out that tongue.
Let me see how far I can stick that down your throat.
Mmm.
Go on, suck it like a big dick.
Show me how you would suck a big cock.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Yeah, get it all slobbery.
I see it wet.
Mmm.
This other one too, see if you can take both down your throat.
Stop whimpering.
Come on.
Take it all the way down your throat.
How's that little cut?
Oh, you're such a little sook.
Keep licking.
Do you think they're shiny enough yet?
I don't think so.
I think you're going to do a much better job of it.
right into every little crevice.
Do it.
I'm gonna rub it all over your fucking face.
Put that extra weight on there.
I don't think you're trying hard enough.
What do you say to your mistress?
Thank you, mistress.
Do you want more?
Yes, mistress.
So how do you think you should get more?
Can I please talk to my mistress?
Can I please?
I didn't claim this half yet, mistress.
You really like being a dirty little dog, don't you?
Licking up that dirty boot.
All the dirt and shit and piss that I walk on.
Wicking it all up.
Dirty little fucking slave.
Yeah.
Keep going.
What about this other boot?
Any bits that you've missed?
Right there.
So you better get working.
Alright, get on your hands and knees so you can get a better angle.
Hands and knees.
Down.
Stick that tongue out.
Yeah.
Oh, he's so funny.
All right, time's up.
How do you think you did?
You look shiny.
Not bad, but I think the bottom of the boots need more work.
Sit over there.
Come on, show me how you take both of them again.
Good boy.
They better be fucking spotless by the time you're finished.
I love watching you degrade yourself like this.
Thank you, mistress.
Get into every little crevice.
Yes.
Use that fucking tongue.
than that.
And the other one, all the way down that throat.
Are you finished?
You think so?
I think so.
You better be sure.
there's not one fucking mark on there.
Okay.
Look at these streaks. Look here. Look there. Look there.
My reflection is completely fucking warped.
Do you think I should have to look at myself like that?
I'm sorry. My spit's not clean enough.
Why isn't your spit clean? Is that because you're a dirty boy?
You're a dirty little fucking dog, aren't you?
Yes, mistress.
Fucking hands.
And he's right there.
What are you?
I'm a dirty dog.
That's right.
What are you?
I'm a dirty dog, mistress.
You're a dirty fucking dog.
Out your back.
That's better.
What are you?
I'm a dirty dog, mistress.
I'm a really dirty dog.
Bad spit.
I'm sorry. I made your shoes dirty.
I tried...
Get out of here.
That's another week in chastity for you.
you