I'm hiding a whole bunch of stuff from you guys.
I don't want to write this.
Oh, they've all seen it. I'm a little bit of the internet.
Hi, Hussein. They look better every day, so.
Oh, it's been so long.
Do you guys want to see my outfit?
It's cute, right?
Oh, what about my shoes?
Cute, right?
Fuck your shoes.
I'm like, oh shit, I'm going to break it.
Oh yeah.
It's okay.
It can take a week.
Oh yeah?
I know.
I practiced a bit.
Oh, thanks, Luke.
Yeah, I'm your cherry.
Natasha, cherry of the month.
Nice.
Cherry of the month.
Your newest cherry of the month.
Yeah.
Your freshest cherry.
Cherry of the month. Nice.
Cherry of the month.
Your newest cherry of the month.
Yeah.
Your freshest cherry.
Your juiciest cherry.
Oh, don't show them.
I'm not gonna show them.
Here, I got you.
Yes.
Your squishiest cherry.
Don't fucking do it.
You're going to get me in trouble, Sam.
Sam wants to get us all in trouble.
Um, I think they're velour, Hussein.
I'm not the best person to ask fashion questions to.
I just know they're soft and they're pretty and they're shiny.
So I bought them.
Pretty much.
Yeah. Anything shiny is pretty much like my best friend.
Like oil, for example, or spit, or wet genitals.
So you'll just have to join the gold show.
Join the gold show.
Everybody's doing it.
be submissive.
But I can be dominant, too.
Thanks, Luke.
Yeah, I really like red.
It's my favorite color.
Is it?
Yeah.
Oh, well, lucky for us, we're on a red couch.
Yep.
Shooting for a while on cam.
But I'm still sweet like one.
Yes, this show is going to be fucking awesome.
I can't wait for all the dirty stuff to start.
I'm going to show you guys my holes and how wet and shiny they are.
Oh, you want to speak in French?
Yes, we can do that if you want.
We can say things together, you and me.
He doesn't speak French, and neither do you, but I do.
So I can say what I want.
I was thinking more like French kiss.
Yeah, that too.
Aww, Sam wants a fresh kiss.
Poor little Sam.
You can spank me.
I've probably done something wrong with me.
You haven't told me twice.
Yeah, make my ass match my panties, fucking do it.
Make your ass look like a cherry.
I make my ass look like a cherry.
Oh, that hurts, daddy.
Oh, yes.
Oh, wow.
Oh, shit.
Can you give a J-Y countdown during the show?
I need to glaze those big jugs badly.
Maybe.
Because my mind will be on other things.
Yeah, always remind me of anything, because I'm going to forget.
Once I'm having sex, it's like, phew, nothing to do.
Can I dominate you, Sam?
No.
Please.
Natasha, I'm happy.
Natasha, leave Sam.
He said I can't dominate him, I think that's bullshit.
Oh shit, are we ditched already?
I wanna dominate somebody.
We can dominate each other.
Look at my big ol' butt.
I just gotta look at you.
Look at you.
Nice and red.
I think I know where I want to go.
In my soul?
In your soul?
I see your soul in your tits.
I think so.
I think that's why everybody always stares at me.
You guys ready to start this thing?
Let's do it.
So cute.
I don't know, Donnie, what do you think my shoes smell like?
Do you guys dare me to lick the bottom of my shoes?
I have a very strong immune system.
All the nasty shit I've done all my life.
What's with the strangers and shit?
Oh, I wish you guys were all here to fuck me on this floor.
You guys want to see it?
You guys want to see my dance?
You guys wanna see my tits?
My big fucking tits.
My big, fat, famous tits.
Oh my gosh.
They're so big.
I love it.
I've had them since I was 11.
Do you like them?
They're so cute.
Do you want one?
Yeah.
I haven't since I was 11.
Do you like them?
They're so big.
They make cocks disappear.
I bet you want to put your cock in between my tits, don't you?
I would like that very much.
rob everybody's lobes one by one, like the nice girl that I am.
Oh, you're so messy.
Oh, fuck.
Ow.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I like a little pain with my pleasure.
You like that big ass, guys?
Yeah?
That big ass and that little ass hole?
Is this what you want?
Yes.
I like my holes nice and wet.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, shit.
oh
what to do now?
shh
oh
Oh my god.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck you.
You fuck this fucking slutty pussy baby.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
I think this slutty pussy needs a good toy, what do you guys say?
Oh, there it is.
That's the one we're fucking there.
Oh, fuck, yes. Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna fucking cum, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh
I need some dick in my life.
I need a lot of dick in my life.
You need any assistance with that?
No.
Let's check here.
Maybe that should come with my ticket for haircuts, right?
Oh, give me that, please.
Oh.
in this video I will be sharing a cup of coffee
and a video on what food I eat
and why I do it
I hope you enjoy watching!
I'll see you guys soon!
I love you!
Bye!
Oh
You guys are gross!
Yes.
You want to fuck my tits Sam?
Fuck my tits Sam, fucking fuck my tits Sam.
yes...
you're big and squishy there
wet and slippery there
please fuck my tits
oh my god please fuck my fucking tits
yes
That's perfect for fuck.
Thank you.
Oh, fuck.
I have to bend my knees.
I'm gonna bend my knees.
I'm scared.
Ouch!
Ow!
Fuck!
Okay.
I can't get some more.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Oh my God, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, yes!
Yeah, right back, yeah.
Waste of time.
Oh, fuck.
Dirty girl, I almost forgot the condom.
Oh fuck.
Oh
Oh, fuck.
Yes, swing, swing.
Swing, swing, swing.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Fuck you.
Okay.
Like this?
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh shit, yes.
Yeah, fuck, hold on, that pussy's here.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh my god, yes, fuck that pussy, please.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh my god, yes.
This is only good, yes.
Oh my god, give me the tape.
So good.
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
Oh yes, just like that.
Give me the tape.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Do you want to sleep again?
Do you want to sleep?
Oh
You guys want to see how much I really love this
Fuck me, Sam. Please.
Fuck me, yes.
Yes.
Tits. Tits.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, yes. Make me fucking
tits bounce, Sam, please. Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Fuck me, please.
Oh, shit. It's so fucking
good. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, oh fuck, oh fuck, yes, ah, oh my god, yes,
put me down please, yes, so good, ah, ah, ah, fuck, yes.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, shit, that's, oh my god,
oh fuck, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
Oh, God.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh my god yes.
Oh, fuck yes!
Give me the fucking six!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my god!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh, my god, right there!
Right fucking there!
Shit, yes!
Oh, fuck me so fucking good!
Please, please!
Oh my god, oh shit, yes, oh, oh fuck, oh fuck.
Oh my god, what do you want to do, what do you want to do?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'll carry you.
No.
Okay.
There you go.
I can't see.
I can't see, Tina.
What if I write you?
Get on the floor.
He's not waving.
He's the camera.
Fuck yeah.
Oh, my god, oh, is this good, Sam?
Do you like this, Sam?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god.
Fucking.
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, my god, that fucking day!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my fucking tits bounce, yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my god, this freaking day!
Oh, my god, oh, my god, my fucking tits bounce!
You know you guys fucking like that?
You like watching my tits bounce?
You only fuck this big fucking cock?
Oh my god, yes.
Oh fuck, yes.
Yeah, you like that shit?
Yeah? Oh my god, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Last year.
You like this thing?
It's the best.
Mm-hmm
Oh yeah, I want you to fucking come in my mouth if you're ready.
I'm not done yet though, so you better have a second load waiting for me.
Oh fuck.
I want you to come in my mouth.
Fuck!
Look at these big fucking balls.
You like that?
Fuck.
Oh, sorry, I forgot about you guys.
Yeah, Justin wants a J-O, right?
Should I do it?
Okay, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it for Justin.
Yeah.
Alright, I'm gonna count down from ten, Justin,
and then you're gonna come in my mouth, okay?
Alright.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three...
One...
Come in my fucking mouth. Fucking do it.
Come in my fucking mouth.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Bon...
Alors on fait quoi, maman?
Tu veux me baiser en doggie?
Oh yeah, fuck me in doggie.
Yes.
Comme ça.
Ça vous va comme ça?
Oui?
S'il-te-plaît, s'il-te-plaît, baisse-moi, please.
Fuck me, please.
S'il-te-plaît.
S'il-te-plaît, baisse-moi.
please fuck my little French cunt.
like a French fucking whore.
Baise-moi comme une salope, s'il te plaît.
Oui, baise-moi.
Oh putain, baise ma chatte.
Oh, piss my shot into pieces.
Oh, you don't.
Oh, oh, bitch.
That's my shot.
Don't fuck me, please.
You.
Fuck me, please.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, fuck me, please.
You fucking low-posy.
Piss my bitch, shit, piss my bitch, shit into pieces.
She just pissed my bitch, shit, into pieces.
Oh my god, it's so good!
Please, continue!
Don't fucking stop!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, please, don't fucking stop!
Don't stop!
Oh fuck!
Oh fuck, don't stop please!
Oh fuck, don't stop!
Don't fucking stop!
King Panda, where are you fucking going?
Yes!
Ah, yeah, you like my horny fuck up, I like it.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, I make my eyes roll
in the back of my fucking head, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, yes, fucking, fucking, oh my God, yes.
Oh, my God, yes!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, my God, yes, oh!
Can you give me that dick, please?
Can you give me that fucking dick?
Please, that fucking dick.
What, what am I doing, Sam?
Kids won't fit in this chair.
Okay, I'm on my back, I can't do this.
Ow.
Oh
Shit oh shit
Oh, shit.
Play with my globes, Justin.
They are pretty good.
And they help get around.
Oh, shit.
Please, please, please.
I feel... I look pussy, Sam, and I feel so fucking good.
I feel so fucking good. I hate this fucking condom.
I wish I could rip it off so you could cut off my fucking twat.
Ah, ah, fuck. Oh my god, yes. Treat me like a little slut, Sam.
Treat me like a little slut, Sam.
Ah, fuck.
Man, you fucking like my fucking twat.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, it's so easy.
Yeah, you wanna fuck him again?
Like this, or something?
How should we do it?
Get into this position now.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I can't read upside down.
Yep, I can do it.
Slap my face down.
I can do it.
Yes.
You're fucking perfect for fucking me.
meant to come fuck my tits and come all over them.
Come on.
Oh, yes.
You know I've been a whore for such a long time.
Legally 12 years, but you know.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god.
Oh, shit.
I'll come like this if I can.
Maybe I will.
Sounds like a good spot to come.
I need blood in my brain.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to say.
Oh, fuck.
What's up, Sam?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, bye.
What should we do next, guys?
You guys direct the show.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, can I shove my tits in your face?
Oh, fuck, yeah, oh, can I shove my tits in your face?
Yes, come see me, yes.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
See what you two boys have almost done?
What do you wanna do?
I'm going to do it to your face.
You do it to my face.
Let's see.
Is there a pillow?
Here we go.
Like this?
Yeah.
Nice pillows.
It's pretty.
Like this?
Yeah.
Is this good?
It's fine.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
this is fucking sick, yes, oh fuck, oh shit, fuck, yeah, like this, yeah.
Like this?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Don't stop, sit.
Oh, fucking don't.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yes.
Okay, you're doing all right there.
Oh my god, I can't do it.
Come here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my, oh my god.
Come here, let's just go.
I want to do all the positions before time runs out.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God, it's so fucking good.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Yes.
Fuck me.
Oh, fuck me, yes.
Yes, fuck me, please.
Fuck me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, fuck me.
Oh, fuck me, please.
Oh, shit.
Yes, guys.
I want you all to fuck me.
Please, please, please.
Oh, fuck.
What?
Doggy.
Okay.
Like this?
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Yes, yes, oh, my God.
Oh my god, oh my god, yes!
Shit, no!
Oh fucking god, please, please, it's over.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my God, it's so good.
Can you see I'm covering my fucking tits in gum, oh my god.
Oh my god.
So much gum on my tits.
Do I look good?
Yeah, I think so too.
Fuck.
What to do with this mess?
What to do?
Wow, you guys really like my tits.
You guys want to do a countdown?
Let's do it in French.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Oh, God, I'm such a messy little French whore.
Oh, my God.
Come on, my big tits, Luke.
This is a happy kitty.
Oh, my big fucking butt.
Oh my god.
Come on my face, Bichon.
Yes, is that what you want, Bichon?
Bichon.
I want you to come for me, Mo.
Come on for me, Mo.
Oh.
Mmm.
You guys want to look at my pussy one more time?
I want you all to come right here.
Right in there.
Oh, cover my big tits, Luke, yes.
And come on my feet, Hussain.
Everybody, come on something.
Mm.
Yes.
Yeah, come on my fucking tits.
And come on my feet.
And come on my fucking holes.
My wet fucking holes.
Come on, my pretty whore face.
Oh, yeah.
I want to come right there.
Oh, it's so shiny.
Oops.
Oh, fuck.
Three seconds of fun.
Oh, well.
I'm Natasha Nice, that's Sam Schock.
Caught red-handed.
Or something like that.
Thanks guys, I'm going to do one final countdown.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Yes.