He left this morning because he said I wasn't sexual enough, but the truth is I just wasn't
that sexual with him.
He was a brute, a big louse of a man, not a gentle bone in his body.
Not that I wanted it gentle, but a little nuance would have been nice.
he never quite understood the fantasy. He'd call me a whore, but not his whore. He could
never quite grasp the ownership part, which is really all I wanted, to feel owned by a man,
if only for one night. In front of his friends, he'd say, get in here slut, and then laugh too
too loud at his own stupid joke, the tinge of cruelty ringing in my ears for hours.
In the bedroom, though, he was a mouse. We'd lay side by side like schoolgirls,
hands barely touching. Night after night, we'd lay there while he shivered with trepidation,
and I cursed him under my breath for making me feel the way he did.
I always wondered if his hesitation was because he couldn't get it hard
he said he wanted a girl who knew what she was doing and so he left because he thought I didn't
know but I've always known he just didn't deserve to be shown and now that he's gone
I'm free to be with whomever I want I can give it to everyone or no one I can
be this one's little slut or that one's special whore I can let him own me and
tomorrow own myself again
I'm yours, I'm yours, I'm yours, I'm yours, I'm yours, I'm yours, I'm yours, I'm yours,
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, please, please, please, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Look what you did to me, look what you did to me, you're driving me crazy, you're driving me crazy.
Oh, I just want to be able to see you.
I want to imagine you in my sleep.
You, you, you.
So cool.
That's so sweet.
I want to kiss you.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Fuck.
Yes, baby.
Oh, my god.
Yes. You're so fucking good. Everything that you ask of me, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. It's all yours. It's all yours. Yes. Yes. I'll do everything that you ask of me. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, you own it, you own it, it's yours, it's yours, oh, yes, yes, yes, oh, my God, you feel amazing, yes, oh, fuck me, yes, yes, yes, oh, God, yes, incredible,
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
I'm going to wash it now.
Come on.
No, no, no.
Yes.
Yes, please.
Please, please.
Thank you.
Yes, please.
Right there.
Make me calm.
Mommy, please, please, please, please.
Oh, please, may I come, please?
Please, may I come, please, please, please?
Oh, my God.
Tell me when, please.
Give me permission.
Please give me permission.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do it, do it, do it.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Ah, ah, ah, oh my God, I love you, I'm a slave to your desires, yes, yes, yes, ah, oh, yes, I love it, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yeah
Oh, fuck
Yes, please use me
Use me
I'm just a slave for you, please
Yes, please
Fuck
Oh yeah, yes
Yes
Yes, I love you, you're so good, oh my god, thank you, thank you, yes, yes, please, please, please, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh fuck, oh my god, I love it, yes, I'm completely yours, I'm
completely yours, oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Oh, fuck, yes, fuck, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Come here. Come here. Come fucking here.
I'm gonna do everything I want.
Yes.
These tits are yours too.
Wherever you are.
I don't want you to take it.
Yeah.
Yeah, mmm.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
Little smudge.
Yes.
Oh my God.
I love you so much.
I'm so open for you.
Oh my God.
I love you so much.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, let me see, holy fuck, oh my god, fuck, oh my god, that's incredible, oh my god, that was so good, yes, yes, please, yes, again, yes, yes, oh my god, I can see, I can see you owning my asshole like that,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh
What you doing?
Just take me
And send me
Yes
I just wanna make you feel so good
Tell me all the ways
That I can make you feel good
Yes
yes yes oh yes oh my god oh my god
oh my god yeah keep going just like that just like that just oh
Please, may I come?
Please, can I come?
Yes, yes, yes, ha, ha.
Yes, just like that, just like that, yes, ha.
Thank you, sir, thank you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
It's so fucking good, it feels really fucking good.
Let me see.
I'm gonna taste my ass.
Fuck yes.
Fuck yes, baby girl.
Oh, fuck yes, baby.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuck, yes, come here.
Woo!
Yes.
Look at this.
Oh.
My God.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you fucking love it?
I fucking love everything that you give me.
So good.
Yes.
I'm your fucking servant.
I'm your fucking whore.
Your slut.
Yes, yes, yes.
Whatever you need.
Just use me.
Look at this.
Just show me this.
Show me this.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Right there, right there, right there.
Oh, my God, what the fuck did you do to me, please?
Stay right there.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God, my God, my God, my God.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Fuck, yes.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Whoa.
Whoa! Whoa!
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh, boy.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Oh, my God.
I want to leave
every one of my fucking holes.
Every one of my holes. Yes, yes, yes, please. I don't want to feel used by you.
I don't want to feel used by you. Yes, and please put it in my pussy, please.
Please, every hole I want you to use. Every hole, every hole.
Please put it back in my ass. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I don't want to taste my ass off your teeth. I don't want to taste it off.
I'm gonna taste, yeah, mmm, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm gonna fucking taste, I'm gonna taste my own.
Whoa, whoa, give me your boobs, give me your boobs.
Yes, please, fuck me, dude.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes
they say your experience marks you like a stain on raw wood forever altered but that was the point
wasn't it i wanted to be made different to be forever changed and transformed
to have a life worth living written across my skin