You
Hey
Miss Natasha Nice. Been waiting for you for a long, long time.
Really? A really long time?
Yeah.
You must be backed up.
My God. How big are your teeth?
Um, they're like 34 double Ds.
All natural?
Yeah. You like that sort of thing?
My God, I might want to put something between those right here.
That would be awesome
They would like that a lot
What do you want to do today with me?
I want to play with your car
Oh, you want to play with my car?
Are you going to be a good girl?
I have a really wet mouth
My throat just won't stop producing saliva
Can I see that sexy ass?
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Do you like getting spanked?
I do.
You can spank it harder.
Oh yeah?
So sexy right now.
I'm going to tap my ass with that thing.
Mm-hmm.
Remember I'm going to put this cock in your pretty mouth
Oh yeah, you want that?
Yeah
Oh yes
Let me see what we have here
A nice pretty pussy
Do you want to come down on your knees for me?
Get comfy.
Okay.
Look, we're moving together.
Give me your tongue out, oh yeah
How many cocks did you suck in your life?
I don't know, a thousand?
Twelve hundred?
Wow
So we make this 1,201
Yes
Oh, it's such a nice cock
Mmm
mmm
nice and soft like that
yes
I like it
mmm
Open them up, nice and wide for me, I don't want to...
Help!
Do I see tears of joy?
Yes!
They're building.
Yeah.
yeah
yeah spit on that cock, spit on that cock, jerk it
like this? yeah
Yeah, they put fish in that cup.
Oh my god, it's so hard.
It's so fucking pretty.
Let me put it back in my mouth.
Yeah.
Show me those eyes.
oh yeah look at that
oh
what about down here what a good little corn slob
those balls
mmm
Should we get those fucking titties out?
Yeah.
Huh?
Let's do it.
Do you like it?
Oh, yeah.
Like a soccer player.
Yeah.
Put the cock between your teeth.
Fuck my cock with your big teeth.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah.
Nice and slow.
Oh.
Just like that.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Slow.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh, I need the big dick to disappear.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, you're gonna be all right.
Yes.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna rub that fucking thing.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my.
Fuck, yeah.
Put a big hand on me.
I'm feeling pretty fucking filthy now.
Yes.
You see how hard you got on me?
Yes, oh, my God.
I'm going to use your pretty face right now.
Ah, you're good.
You're doing good girl.
Oh yes.
So fucking pretty.
Yeah.
Mmm.
I suck that cock, don't I? Good.
Put a buck in your tits.
Like this?
Yeah.
Oh my god, it's so silky smooth.
That's so hot.
Yes.
Yeah, like that.
Oh yes.
Yes.
Fuck me.
Fuck your fat tits, please.
Yes.
Oh my god, yes.
My big titties, please.
Yes.
Fuck me.
Please, please, yes, yes, yes, fuck my tits, yeah.
Oh, it's so hard.
Oh my God, oh, your dick's so fucking hard
in between my legs.
Ah, get over here.
Stay right there, baby.
Okay.
I'm gonna put it back in there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're good, you're good, baby.
Yes, you're good.
Fuck them, yes, please.
Please fuck my tits, please fuck my tits, yes!
Yes, fuck my tits, yeah.
Oh yeah, fucking peck my fat tits, yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Yes, yes!
Oh, I love those big tits.
Shh.
Suck on those balls. Suck on those fucking balls.
Nice. Nice. Stay Natasha. Nice.
Very nice. Very nice.
Oh, my.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Come here, turn around.
Sit on the fucking carpet.
Sit over here?
Yeah, and put your head back.
Come down a little bit.
I'm gonna fuck that pretty face.
Come on, come down a little bit.
Oh my God.
Hold tight. Hold tight.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Fuck!
You like it when someone cucks like that?
Yes!
Look at your fucking pretty face.
Come here.
Yes.
Do what?
Jump in there.
Is this what you want?
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Down here?
Mmm.
Oh, yeah, like that.
Yeah, like that.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Fucking sucker.
I'm gonna open my eyes.
Careful with the teeth.
Your hand, your hand.
ahhhhhh
mmmmm
you're so pretty
such a pretty face
mmmmm
ok
nice and slow
Oh, careful with those teeths.
Mm-hmm.
Come on there.
Jerking your fish.
Take it out from the water.
Oh, oh, god.
Look at this jerking.
Yeah
Mm
Yes
Sounds so sexy
Sounds so slippery
And so wet
oh yes
oh yeah
You like sipping coke, huh?
I don't like these I don't like these
Here's your end.
Huh?
Jerk.
Jerk with your hands.
Oh, my.
Oh, it seems bloody hell.
Aw, look at that pretty fucking dick.
All right.
Oh, no.
Oh, fuck.
It's a bitch.
Oh
I want to fuck your tits again.
Do I?
Yeah?
Oh yeah, I was thinking that.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I'm okay.
Yeah.
You like that?
You like my big tits bouncing on that fucking thing?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, it's so fucking hot.
Oh my god, you're so sleepy.
Yes, yes, fuck.
That's so hot.
Fuck, that big fucking hard cock in between my tits, yes.
Oh my god, yes.
You fuck my slutty tits.
Oh, fuck.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah?
Uh-huh. Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Let me touch it.
Let me fucking touch it.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah?
You don't like that?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, fuck you.
Are you ready for my cum?
Yeah, I want it.
I want your fucking cum, please.
Where do you want my cum?
I want it on my tits.
I want it all over my tits.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Please give me your cum.
Please give me your cum all over my tits.
Oh, fuck.
Please, please, please, please.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, give it to me, please.
Please give it to me.
Oh my god, please give it to me.
Please, please, please, please, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Look, you're too nice.
aahhh
mmm
nice shower
aahhh
look at that
mmm
aahhh
well thank you beautiful
till next time
mmm