I can't wait to see what her tits look like when they're full of milk.
Does she have a bush?
Or is it shaved?
I really can't tell.
I think it's shaved.
You should zoom in.
Can you zoom in?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look at those tits.
Oh my god.
Don't cover them up.
Why is she sleeping in clothes anyway?
That outfit looked great on her though.
Nice and tight.
It's hot. I would just rather her to be sleeping naked.
Let's see.
Do I have to change this camera angle a little?
She turns the lights off.
Wait until you see what happens next.
What happens?
She's twitching herself.
You're gonna like this part. It gets better and better.
She's horny.
Look at that.
Isn't that good?
Yeah.
It's hot. I just want her to take the panties off.
Can you make it brighter? It's hard to see.
Oh, that's as bright as it goes.
I love your security cameras.
Me too.
She's doing all ready.
Wow.
She was really morning. That was fast.
That's hot.
What do you think she was fantasizing about?
Women.
Does this happen often?
No more than once a week. It's perfectly normal.
We gave her a sedative too, so it's very relaxing.
Is that good for the baby?
Her being relaxed there is good for the baby in the long run.
We don't want her injuring herself.
now so I was a little concerned about that we just want this birthing team
Right? To be strong and connected. Do it for me.
For my little sugar plum.
Okay. We should just say yes so we don't upset Elsa.
Yeah, stop being selfish. Okay.
This is for the baby.
For the baby, of course.
I feel really bad for Elsa.
it was...
So, have you ever had thoughts about women?
Yes. I just like looking at them.
You never acted on your thoughts?
So, I just look.
Well, it was a little forward.
Yeah.
I didn't...
This whole thing has been really weird.
Yeah.
I've never told her that I've never been with a woman.
I've kind of led her to believe that I like women.
Just so I could get the job as her midwife
because that was the requirement that they needed a lesbian midwife.
Well do you always want to just
just lead her to believe that or
would you be interested in
And, you know, I'm making it so you don't have to lie to her.
I don't know.
So you don't know.
I'd like to explore you a little bit.
You know, it's pretty amazing to be in bed with such a beautiful woman.
that and try something new down here on your skin.
So beautiful.
It's okay.
Yes.
Oh, it smells so good.
Excuse me.
It's beautiful.
Such a beautiful little pussy.
Oh my god.
My hands got tingly.
Wow, does it touch the skin?
Your skin is so soft.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
This is so good.
Yes, please.
I'm gonna make those panties wet and I'm gonna wipe them later.
And I'm gonna stuff them in my mouth.
And I'm gonna lift it after this.
Yes, come to me.
It's so hard to hear you scream.
Oh, fuck!
It smells so good, it's food, I want to eat it.
Fuck.
Why didn't you put it on there?
I know, I want to feel it for real.
I can't.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Cheese.
Oh
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
oh my god.
Go on your skins.
Holy fuck.
Imagine.
I feel so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes. Yes, do that.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh
Yeah.
Oh my god, I just love feeling nuggets when I eat that.
I want your skin on my skin.
Turn over.
Oh, wow.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Can you touch me?
Fuck, yes.
Oh.
Yes.
Fuck.
Please.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Yes, that's so good. Fuck. Yeah
That's amazing
You know, make my fingers fall asleep.
Yeah, give me that tight pussy.
Oh my God.
You, yes.
Tight, wet, slippery, I was like.
I don't know, but I actually was really on my neck, too.
I'm like, you know, I can't understand a word you said,
but it was hot.
Oh my God, I love making it calm.
because he's so swollen
Oh
Oh, that's amazing.
Oh, wow.
Oh, look at that fucking clip.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Oh, yes, brother.
Yeah.
Holy.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, go ahead, go ahead.
I want to be like Elsa. We should make lots of babies together.
Well, I'm already going to be lactating soon.
Then it won't be hard to get you pregnant.
Should I get the turkey bacon?
Oh, yes.
I want to fill up one of those sporting penises and fuck you with it.
I think we can do it better than that.
I'm going to fill it up with color, get you pregnant badly.