Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody, does it better.
Oh, hey honey.
Hey.
Um, Lucas, do you want to wait for me in the living room?
Um, I just have to put this up now.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Um, hey honey, remember that guy Lucas we talked about?
to go through with that.
Do you remember how we talked about that?
today he was like staring at my tits like so much and it kind of made me
i like really want to it's so hot that it turns you on
Yeah, should I do it
I'm gonna do it
Uh, i'll be right here. Yeah, you just wait right there
Okay. Oh my god. I love you so much for agreeing to this. This is so hot
i'm like kind of nervous but
Oh my god, this is so hot.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Stay right here.
Okay.
Hey.
I wonder what he's doing down there.
He's probably stroking that big cock.
Thinking about my tits.
Oh, I'm so excited.
But I'm kind of nervous too.
I'm just so glad you're here to watch us.
It kind of reassures me.
I love the fact that you want to watch me fuck another guy.
It's so hot.
God, it drives you crazy, doesn't it?
I think that was tough.
I think I'm going to wear it like this.
Right?
Can't wait to see his face.
Oh my god.
I hope he likes these.
It's cute, right?
your way with me in it.
guys at the yoga studio just a thought
do you like the fishnet? I felt like it was extra slutty
do you like your little slutty wife don't you?
you love being your little slutty wife
I'm gonna be such a fucking whore with him.
I'm gonna slobber all over that big cock.
I'm gonna cum on it too.
But don't worry, I'll save a lot for you.
I'm gonna put on my shoes.
call him up and just like be doing something sexy I kind of like that
better. The second one. Okay, I'm ready. Oh, my hair's all fucked up.
You fat pussy. Okay, I'm ready. Can you call them up?
expect anything and I'll be here I mean
Oh, it's so hot in here.
Hey.
Hi.
Oh.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You like my outfit?
Why don't you sit over here?
Okay.
You like it?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, you like my outfit?
Why don't you sit over here?
You like it?
It's a little bit shorter than that yoga outfit.
This is everything you hoped for, baby.
Squeeze, squeeze my ass, yeah.
Oh yeah, put your face in it.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I saw this hard on in class today.
I almost fucked you right then and there.
You want me to suck it, baby?
Oh my god, do you love how hard his cock is?
Just thinking about putting it in my mouth.
Are you still gonna love me after he's done using me?
should I suck it?
oh my god
mmm
ahh
you like that
is it good
You're so pretty.
Yeah.
Oh, you like these big titties?
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
You ever have a real tits wrapped around that hard cotton before?
It's nice and soft.
I like your tits.
around his cock baby?
Oh you think I'm going too fast for him?
Oh my god.
Should I suck his balls now?
Will you still kiss me if I suck his balls?
Does that drive you crazy?
Give it to me.
night
home
mmhmm
ah
mm
oh
ah
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, it went all the way down my throat.
Oh, he wants to eat it, babe.
You're strong.
Oh, yes.
Oh, lick it, please.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
Lick it all. Lick everything.
Yes.
Oh, my.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, yes. Choke that cock for me, baby.
Yes, choke that cock while you eat your wife's pussy.
Mmm, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Keep eating that pussy.
Yes!
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah, just like that.
Oh, my God, your mouth is so wet.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
yes yes yes yes
ahh
oh my god
oh
oh god
just like that
yes
ahh
oh my god
Oh yeah, you want to put your fingers down?
Yes!
Oh yes!
Oh my god, you're so good at that.
Oh
oh my god yes oh shit oh oh oh my god dude he's fucking me so good oh shit
Oh fuck!
Oh my gosh!
Oh fuck yes baby!
There he is!
Oh my god!
Oh god it feels so great!
It feels so great!
Fuck!
Oh fucking great!
No, you leave me alone!
Oh my god!
I'm fed up since a second ago!
I'm sorry to be in that class.
Fuck yes!
It was Messi up with that big clock!
Oh fuck!
Baby he's kicking my butt, I'm so sorry!
Oh my god!
He's kinky baby
Oh my god it feels so good
Oh shit
Oh my pussy's so wet
Oh my god
Yeah
Oh shit no keep going
Baby I wanna come again
Oh my god
Come over here
Get over here
Oh shit.
I got to talk.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck it.
Please keep going.
Oh my god.
It feels so good.
Oh.
Oh god.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Don't let it come again, babe. I'm gonna fucking kill you, babe.
Oh, fuck you! Oh my god, yes!
Oh shit! Oh shit!
Yes! Yes!
Oh, fuck! Oh my god, yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh! Oh, fuck!
Oh, shit!
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck you!
Oh my god. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh my god. So deep. So much deeper.
You want me on top? You want me on top?
You want to taste that pussy? Yeah.
Yes, spank it harder. Not bad, girl. Spank it harder.
Oh
I mean right in the fucking pretty cock.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Yes.
Like that?
You like that?
Oh, fuck.
You just spanked ya?
Yes
You like my big ass?
It's so fucking nice.
Yeah?
Oh, it's so firm.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, right there.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes. Oh my god.
Yes. You.
Yeah, you like that?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's okay.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's all set.
Oh my god. Oh shit. Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
You stay right there. Stay right there.
I want my husband to stare at my big tits.
Give me that big fucking cock.
Oh fuck.
Oh, yes. You like it, baby?
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, you like watching me
bounce in this big coffee
and rub my clit
and my wedding ring on it?
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, yes. Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
You...
Oh...
Yes...
Ah...
Oh, fuck...
You...
Fuck you...
Ah, this is shit...
Shit...
Oh, fuck...
Yes...
Oh, this is great...
Oh, thank you...
Yes...
Oh my god!
Oh my God!
Fuck!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh shit!
Oh no!
Give it to me!
Does a stranger's cock look good going in my mouth, honey?
Do you like the way it locks in my mouth?
Oh, that's a good one.
Get back on it a little bit.
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh my goodness!
Okay, good.
Juicy!
Oh my god! Oh fuck! Oh my god, yes!
Oh, oh fuck! Oh my god!
Oh, oh my... oh shit!
Oh yeah, you like that? I'll bend over.
I'm so fucking excited.
I think he wants to bend me over, baby.
Can I lie down?
Can you bend me over, like, right here?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, look, all those fucking juices.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, give it to me.
You're gonna give it to me?
So juicy.
Don't stop.
Oh, god, yes.
Oh, he's so good.
He's so good, yes.
Oh, thank you so much for letting me fucking bury.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god.
He was so deep.
Oh, fuck.
Not yet?
Just like that?
Oh my god, we've been titty slapped together.
Why you fuck me?
Why?
Oh god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fucks.
Oh my...
Oh.
Oh, just like yours do, baby.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God, yes, just like that, Lucas.
Oh, you're putting me so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yeah, just like that.
Yeah, oh, my God, yeah.
Mmm, yeah.
I mean, just like that, yeah.
So let me clip those big balls.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Both. Uh-huh.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
You fucking pussy.
Please. Oh, my God.
Oh.
Mmm.
You want a little more?
Oh, my God.
Yeah
Give it to your wife
Yes, yes, he's giving it to his slutty wife so good.
Oh, shit, he's really pounding that juicy cock, baby.
Oh, you are, yes.
Yeah, I know you are.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, I want to watch you play with your hard cock, baby.
Oh, yes, play with me, baby.
Okay.
Play with your hard cock while you pound your wife's juicy cock.
Give it to me, baby.
Give it to me like this.
I found this juicy cunt.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, yes, found that juicy fucking cunt, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah, just like that, yeah, watch it, watch it.
Oh, yeah, mm-hmm, mm, yeah, oh my, yeah?
You wanna feel my tits again?
Oh, yeah, mm, like this, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm,
you wanna feel my fucking tits?
He wants to feel my tits again, babe.
Should we let him?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Come here.
Give me that cookie.
Yeah.
Oh my god, yeah.
I feel just as good as when I passed you.
Yeah, you're gonna make me fucking cum.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, baby, I'm gonna make him cum.
Oh fuck, I think he's gonna cum.
Do you want him to cum on my tits?
Like you do?
Or in my mouth?
Oh my god.
Or both.
Yes.
It's going to come all over my chest.
I'm going to get some in my mouth.
Would you like that?
Yes.
Oh, you can't fuck these fucking things.
Oh.
It's gonna come all over my tits.
I'm gonna get some in my mouth.
Would you like that?
Oh, you can't fuck these fucking things up.
Oh.
Oh, yes!
Oh, fuck, it came all over my tits.
Oh, shit.
Oh, do you like that baby?
It came all over my tits and in my mouth, too.
Tastes so good.
Oh, should I leave it?
Do you want to fuck me with this cum on my tits?
It'll be fun.
Make me really look like your totally slutty wife.
You just fuck me with cum on my tits.
You know you want to.
Or should I lick it off?
Oh my god, that was so much fun.
That was such a good idea.
I can't wait to do it again.
Oh my god.
Naughty America.
Nobody.
Does it better.
you