Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.
Hey Tony, hey, thank you so much for coming.
No problem.
I'm such a great assistant.
I'll do everything for you guys.
Oh, thank you.
Where's this computer at?
Um, let me show you, it's over here.
Okay, cool.
Alright, cool.
Stopped working completely?
Okay, was it running slow before that?
Yeah.
Okay, let me check it out.
Check out some of that.
It's making noises and stuff.
How long have you had this?
I don't know, like eight years or something.
Oh, wow, okay.
Do you know what the problem might be?
What?
Oh, um...
Oh, uh...
Whoa.
But don't, don't we look good in our photos?
Yeah, I probably shouldn't be looking at these.
Well, no, it's okay. I mean, you're our family friend, Tony.
You can see whatever we have in here.
Actually, he would probably like it. We're pretty open like that.
He's very proud to have a wife with such, like, natural assets.
Oh my gosh.
Rogers here, and we will I'll do this
Open family, okay, what's Rogers is yours and
What's mine is yours and all that good stuff I?
I just want you to feel relaxed and I want this to be comfortable for you.
We're very open.
We share everything.
I think I have a way for you to relax.
I think I can maybe be of some assistance.
You're a friend. This is what friends do.
Mmhmm
You like my tits?
I do
Ya? You wanna see them?
They're all natural
Look at this nice stiff cough.
Someone's nice and stiff already.
Oh, shit...
Um, yeah, how does that feel good?
Your friend's wife's mouth on your big heart cock
Such a pretty dick
Mmm
yes
I know
I
I'd love to.
See, you stare at my tits.
All of my husband's friends stare at my tits.
Oh, shit.
They fucked each and every one of them, except for you.
Fucked Jerry?
Yes.
Oh, yeah, fuck me some.
Fuck you the best.
Yeah, yeah, fuck me the best ones.
Oh, my God, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God, yeah, it's been me over 20 years.
Oh, yeah, fuck your friend's wife.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God, it's so good.
So good.
Oh yeah, Bella, please.
Bella, please.
Tony, please.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, yeah, get that.
Come to me.
Just like that.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, rub my ass.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Ah, yes.
Oh my god, Tony.
Oh my god.
Did you fuck Kevin too?
Oh my god, a million times.
Oh fuck, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck, I fucked him all over the house.
Oh shit.
And I called Roger, and he listened to it.
Oh my god, I'm really open.
He just loves it. I'm such a little slut for him.
I fuck all his friends.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck me. Fuck me, Tony.
Oh, God.
Yeah, you like that?
You like me, Tony?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
That's so creepy.
Please don't stop playing with my club.
Will you fuck me like that, please?
Oh my god, you're going to make me cum.
Fuck!
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Spank it, Tony.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
I'm going to take this off.
Yes, Tony, yes.
Oh yes, Tony, yes.
Oh shit, yes.
Oh my god, yeah.
Yeah, you like that?
You like that?
Yes, yes.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh my god, so fucking...
Yes, thank you so much.
Yes, yes, yes.
you're so cute
oh shit
oh
oh fuck
oh my god
hm
oh yes
yes
oh
oh so cute
oh my god, yes, yes!
Ahh!
God, shh yes!
Ahh, ahh.
Yeah, yeah you like that?
You gonna take that fucking push?
Oh my god, yes!
Shh!
Oh!
Yes, yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh fuck, oh.
So fucking good, oh my god.
Oh my god, this is so good.
Oh fuck, yes.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god.
yes
oh yeah
oh yes
oh
oh fuck
oh, yeah, you like that
oh shi-
oh yeah, you like that big ass
yeah
oh yes
oh my god
oh fuck
tell me yes
for that big ass
oh you fucking pussy
oh my god
oh
Oh my god!
No! No! No!
No!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
I think it's so good.
Oh, it feels so fucking good.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, like that meaty ass falling off your cock?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh春
Yes yes yes
Oh my god
Oh shit
Yes yes
Oh my god yes
Oh fuck yes yes yes
Yes yes yes yes
Oh my god oh my god
Oh fuck
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Yes. Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, give me that ticket, please.
Please, please, please.
Baby, come on, just give me some peace, I'll be gentle.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, this is so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God.
Fuck.
Oh my God, it's so good.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, do that, do that, yes.
Yeah, you like that, yeah, yes.
Yeah, correct, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Fuck.
Mm.
Oh yeah.
Fuck.
Yes.
Fuck, fuck.
Yeah, you like that.
Oh God, that looks so bad.
You're having so much pain.
Oh, fuck. Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, but the pussy, please.
Right there.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God, oh, right there, it's me, yes.
Oh, fuck that pussy.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck.
Oh my God, yes, oh, fuck me, please.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God, this is so good.
Oh my god, it's so fucking good.
Oh, oh yeah.
Yeah, don't stop.
Give me that dick.
Give me that fucking dick.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, you like that pussy?
Yeah, you like your first wife's pussy?
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, that dick feels so good.
It feels so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, just say it.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, just stop.
Oh, just stop, baby.
Yeah.
That's all.
Yeah, kiss me.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh
shhh
oh god
so good
yes
oh my god
oh
fuck
oh my god
oh fuck
right in there
oh my god
oh
yes
oh my god
oh
oh fuck
oh shit
oh
oh fuck
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God. Yeah, keep fucking me, Tony.
Tony, can you fuck with me, please?
Fuck me, Tony.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, you fuck the shit out of me, Tony.
I want you to come all over my face and my tits, Tony.
Oh yeah, oh, is that what you want?
Is that what you want?
You wanna come all over my face and my tits, Tony?
Please, please, I want it so bad.
Oh God, I want your cum, Tony.
I want your cum.
I want your cum all over my face and my tits.
I want it.
Come on, you gotta give it to me.
I fucking want that gum, please give me your gum,
give me one, it's so bad.
Ah.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
That was really bad.
Ah.
Wow, it's fucking sensitive.
Mm.
Oh, don't touch that.
Is it fucking sensitive?
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, yes, you covered my tits with your gum.
That's exactly what I wanted.
It's so hot, Tony.
Are you sure Roger's going to be okay with this?
He's totally going to be fine with it.
Don't worry, I fuck all his friends all the time.
Alright, I just feel like I should probably get my stuff in.
That's okay.
Okay?
Naughty America.
Nobody.
Does it better.
Bye for now.