So, you call yourself a porn addict, huh?
tits. But it's not just my tits, is it?
hole of yours, fill that void, that gaping hole inside you.
Makes you feel a little bit better about life to come for me, doesn't it?
But then there's some kind of sadness knowing that you can never have me.
So here we are again.
self-control, especially when you're around these.
yours growing.
Go on, make yourself feel better.
shaft to the head of your cock.
Stroke it for these perfect natural tits.
Every day, for me.
Keep stroking.
But don't you dare fucking come.
Not without my permission.
Did you miss this little pussy?
My perfect pink pussy.
You think I'm going to masturbate?
You think I'm going to touch this pussy for you?
Absolutely not.
Why would I masturbate to you?
The thought of you makes me sick.
Jerk faster now for me.
I want you to get close to the edge.
Jerk that special way that you jerk when you need to come really quickly.
you know like when you're in the bathroom at the office in that tiny
Keep stroking.
I didn't tell you to stop.
Oh, you're going to beg me now?
You want to come so bad?
Oh, Mistress Angela, it hurts now, though.
It's throbbing.
All this pre-cum is dripping down your shaft.
You want to come so badly, don't you?
Keep stroking, but don't you dare fucking come.
Keep going.
All the strain and the struggle, you're right on that edge.
You're ready to come for these big natural tits.
All right, I'll count you down.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2.
You're so fucking dumb.
through it.
Don't you dare fucking come.
Slap your cock.
Slap it.
you'll never have a woman like me.
Just another reason you're stuck behind that screen.
Knock, knock.
Oh, you poor pathetic little loser.
Bye now, fucker.