see. Now I must warn you, there might still be some swelling so don't be
alarmed if... Can I just take the damn bandages off? As you wish.
I can already tell.
Chop, chop with these bandages, I want to see.
Okay, ready to see?
Yeah, yes, yes, yes.
I've been waiting six months for this.
Just take them off, take them off.
Come right here.
Okay.
I look just like her.
Her?
I mean, I look exactly how I imagined I was gonna look.
So you're satisfied?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, very satisfied.
He'll never be able to know the difference.
Ding.
Hi, honey.
Natasha?
Yeah, who else would it be?
I, um...
Are you just gonna stand there?
Are you gonna give me a kiss and let me in?
Of course.
Let's do it.
I don't know what it is,
But something seems slightly different about you.
Oh.
Now why did you go and do that?
You look so beautiful the way you are.
You don't think I look more beautiful now?
Oh, no, no, no.
I didn't say that.
Well, a lady who never tells.
Have a seat.
Okay.
So, what do you want to do today?
I was thinking the same exact thing.
Good.
It's exactly like I pictured it.
What was that?
What's gotten into you today?
This is the best blowjob you've ever given me.
This is the best blowjob I've ever had.
Yes.
No, no, no.
Excuse me.
What?
Who are you and what the hell are you doing in my house?
Dr. Plastique, what are you doing here?
Dr. Plastique?
Kimber, I knew I'd find you here, you evil bitch.
Kimber?
Okay, obviously this woman has lost her mind and you should call the cops.
Not so fast.
Natasha?
But that's impossible. You should be dead.
Dead.
Dead?
Surprised to see me, Kimber?
Kimber?
Now I'm really fucking confused.
Honey, this is Kimber.
We have been rivals since college.
She's always been jealous of me.
I have no idea what she's talking about.
Kimber hired some like rent-a-hit man to kill me,
but I paid him double to find out who hired him.
You fucking bitch.
Wait, what?
I found out that she was planning
on getting plastic surgery so she could steal my face
and steal you, so I got my friend Dr. Plastique involved
and we set up this whole thing together.
Then why let me go through with the surgery?
So I could catch you red-handed, you treacherous slut.
I want you to know forever
that I foiled your plan right here.
Oh, Jesus.
Charles!
Charles, are you okay?
Charles, get off of him!
Charles, baby!
Baby, are you okay?
No, Charlie, no!
No, Charlie!
Oh, my God!
Oh, honey!
Thank God you're okay!
Oh!
I'm so happy you're okay!
Get out of this, you fucking bitch!
As crazy as it sounds,
I think this happened for a reason.
I don't understand. What are you trying to say?
Look, the vision was clear.
If I can't have you both, then I can't have either of you.
You want me to share you?
With the woman who tried to kill me?
Listen, I'm sorry babe, but this is the way it is.
I'm with it.
I'll show you how to suck a fucking cock.
Move over, I want some.
Gimme.
You're such a bitch, Kimber.
Ugh.
At least fucking do it, Rice.
You're gonna do it.
Grr, grr, grr, grr.
Yeah.
No breathing.
Yeah, like that, you little fucking slut.
Yeah, you stupid bitch.
Mm.
Very nice, ladies, very nice.
Here, you can have the balls.
Hey!
Mad?
Let's see how long else it can suck in.
Yes!
What?
Oh my God...
That's enough..
Go on, go on.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, can you suck it now?
Come on.
I don't think they realize that she sucks my cock.
Why don't you ladies get acquainted?
I'm going to take my clothes off.
Get acquainted?
I don't know this stupid bitch.
I don't fucking know you.
Come on.
Mommy?
Mommy!
Mommy.
Please, come this way.
Relax, relax, play nice, all right?
We're gonna find out who gets the dick first.
Who wants to get the dick first?
Well, I'm the real Natasha, so I think,
but I'm a manufactured Natasha and I look better.
I'm thinking of a number.
That's the stupidest thing ever.
I'm thinking of a number between,
hey, hey, hey, control yourself.
I'm thinking of a number between one and three.
Seven!
Two!
Really?
Yeah!
Seven!
Obviously you win.
Ha!
You're stupid.
At least I'm pretty.
Because you look like me.
Oh my God!
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
This is going to suck.
Put your big dick in there.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh.
That's fine, you can get my big ass in your face.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
You take the shot.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll kill you!
Mommy, how?
I ... I ...
I'll kill you!
Mom, I ...
She's my pussy.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Yes, she's my fucking pussy.
You know it's a slut.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you like me?
You like my pussy as much as you like my face?
Yes.
Oh, I love it, bitch.
Oh, my God.
Hi..
I'm gonna get you back..
Put that thing away..
Beautiful ex..
ooh fuck yes..
Such a beautiful ex..
Oh my god, your man's fucking real fucking good.
Oh my god, you're so stupid.
Oh my god, yeah.
Yeah, you're a fucking little stupid whore, yeah.
Oh my god, it's so hot.
You're watching him bend you over like the little fucking slut you are.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh shit, yeah.
He's a fucking pussy.
Yeah.
Shut up and eat my pussy.
Oh my god, yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
Come on.
I love you.
Spank that fat ass then, baby.
Spank that fat ass.
Yeah, hurt her, hurt her.
She's a bad girl.
Aren't you a bad girl?
Yeah, you're a bad girl.
She's a bad girl.
Yeah, she is.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God, yes.
No.
My God.
Oh, my God, yes.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, there's more.
Please, baby.
Oh, okay.
Okay, guys.
Please, baby.
Yes, you're fine.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you're a good boy.
Give me a kiss.
Mwah.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, you like that big fucking dick?
Yeah, that dick's mine.
That dick's mine.
Yeah.
Oh, I love it.
Fucking take it.
Shut up, Anita.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
He's so funny.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, you fucking whore.
Oh, fucking whore.
Oh.
HMM.
Ah, yeah, you fucking whore.
Oh, yes.
Hm mm.
Mhm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I get it.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I know what you did.
Oh, lucky fucking whore.
Oh, yes, woman.
Boom.
Oh, you haven't gone to bed yet.
Oh, yeah, go deep, my boy.
Oh, yeah, that's a great boy, Cush.
You're a good boy.
You're a good boy, Cush.
Yeah, yeah.
You're a fucking asshole.
You, slow cow.
Oh, Bugs.
Oh, man.
You're such a little asshole.
You want me to change to look like mine?
Oh, man.
Oh, Bugs.
Oh, my God.
It's like you're doing a little half
while you're doing a little more.
Yeah.
All right, ladies, all right.
Give me a doggie stack.
The only way I can tell the two of you apart
is by your buttocks.
I'm going on top.
Let's get a good look here.
I mean, it's cute, but I mean, it's not like.
Oh, wow.
I don't know.
There's certainly a difference, but that's
That's the way I'm going to have to tell you two apart, for sure.
It's so funny.
Let's try.
Oh, oh my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, shit, yes.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck me, please, fuck me, please, please, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, oh my God.
Straighten your back.
Straighten your back!
Woo!
Oh my god!
Girl, girl!
This is the worst.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, God.
Fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Fuck, oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Yes.
Let me get these fucking wet.
Yes, I'm done.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh shit, oh.
Take it, go ahead and take it, yes?
Baguette, Baguette.
No.
Yes.
I don't know if that's gentle, but I'm going to have to do it again.
a bitch.
Suck my cock!
Gentle!
Just like that, just like that.
Just like that.
Good girls.
Yes, these are good girls.
Yes, you are.
That's good.
She's coming off that cup.
Slap her.
Keep her in place.
Keep her in fucking place.
You better be a good girl.
Yeah, you'll be.
You are.
Oh, my God, yes!
Oh, fuck, you're hurting me!
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Fuck, yes!
Oh, fuck, what did you do to me?
Oh!
Fuck!
Yes!
Oh!
Oh my God!
Fuck these motherfuckers!
Oh shit, oh shit.
Yeah, oh fuck.
Oh shit!
Oh my God.
Oh shit.
Oh my God!
Holy God, fuck this.
Oh my God.
Oh shit.
Fucking fat, give me that.
you're so damn cute!
Oh my god.
Oh!
Ah!
Oh, shit!
You see me there all of a sudden?
Oh!
Ah!
You see me there!
Oh!
Oh, shit!
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
What do you see?
Yeah, make it stop.
I can't hear you.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
No.
Give me a kiss.
Oh my God!
Oh my God.
Oh my God you suck!
Oh, my God, look at his fucking ass.
That's a nice baby.
Do you like when I lick it?
Can I get a big finger in the head, Dad?
Ohhh!
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Shh.
Mm-hmm.
Ah!
Come on.
Ow, my hands.
Oh my god.
Yes, fuck yes.
Yes, because of my fucking pussy.
Oh fuck yes.
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Do you want me to put your ass on?
Yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you're gonna die.
Oh!
Oh, oh.
Yes, I'm gonna die.
My face?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Oh, oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's so good to see you.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God, fuck.
Oh fuck, oh my God.
I'll take that crutch.
Oh my God, oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God.
Ah!
Oh, my God!
I've got to get up.
You're gonna be okay.
That's it.
Just breathe.
Woo.
That asshole's so inviting, he's sucking me in.
I'm sorry.
I'll smack you with that fucking jig.
Ah, fuck yes!
Fuck yes, fuck yes!
Oh, fuck yes!
Ah, fuck yes!
Oh, no, no!
Oh, no, oh, fuck yes, oh fuck yes!
Oh, fuck yes, oh fuck yes!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh, that's so funny.
Oh, fuck, I'm going to eat you shit.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Oh, shit, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah,
yeah.
Oh!
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
Oh mum,
yeah,
yeah.
Oh is it tickling back in you a little bit?
Yeah?
Oh fuck.
Oh yeah,
yeah, let's just be strong.
Do your best to scream.
Yes, mum.
Fuck!
Oh, God!
Fuck that asshole, buddy.
Oh, fuck, God.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, God.
Yes, I'm gonna fucking climb that.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck, Ian.
I'm going to go fuck you.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Hi, you're back.
Nice to see you.
All right.
Come back.
Are you here?
There's your pie.
How you doing?
Mmm, good.
Oh, fuck, oh, my god,
oh, yeah, oh, my god.
Yeah, oh, give me that ticket.
Oh, my god, yeah, enjoy that, buddy.
Enjoy this.
Oh, fuck, oh, yeah, yeah.
Fucking take that buddy, take that pussy chance.
Take that pussy kiss, yes, oh, my God, oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God. Oh, my Jesus.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes, oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, you're so beautiful.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yes, oh, yes, yes, oh shit, oh my god, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh shit, oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes.
No.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I feel you.
Yes.
Oh, yes!
I feel you.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, yes, please don't fucking stop.
Oh, my God, that's too fucking good.
Yes, yes. Oh, my God, you're making me fucking come.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck that.
Ahh.
Ugh.
Uh.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Uh.
Ugh.
Ah.
I'm gonna surf this.
Ow, ow, ah.
Ha.
Hah.
Hah, hah.
Ha.
Ah.
Oh.
Ah!
Oh, yes!
Yes, oh yes!
Go down, yes!
Oh, yes!
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Oh, yes.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Oh, my God.
Everything's gone.
Oh, you're so beautiful.
You're almost delirious.
I can't.
I'm done.
Oh, my God.
My God.
I'm ready for some pussy ladies.
Yeah, you want some pussy?
Who wants to go to a ride?
Oh fuck, yeah, yeah.
Oh fucking fuck.
Oh yeah, that was that big one.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
I'm going to be a pussy.
Oh my god ...
You're fucking dead.
I'm not fucking dead.
You're ...
Oh my god ...
Yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck ...
Yes.
This is a nice feeling.
Ah!
Oh fuck.
Oh, oh oh oh shit.
Oh yeah.
Fuck yes, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Oh my.
Come on, sweetheart.
Okay.
You've got it.
You've got it so much.
There we go.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, that was so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck, yes!
You're fucking boring.
Let me show you how to really please a cock.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, you listen.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, yes.
Come here, come here.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, oh, fuck, yes.
You're like a fucking genius.
Fucking dead genius.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, yes.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God, yes.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck, it feels so fucking good.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh yeah, this is how you write a fucking card.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh my God.
See, he likes it.
Oh, oh fuck.
Shit, yes.
Oh my God, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God, it's a fucking card.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Lay on my pussy, you little slut.
Lay on my pussy.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Yes, oh, my God.
Yeah, you think you could do better, you little slut?
Yeah.
I don't think you can.
Okay, show me, you little cunt.
Show me.
Come on.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
Ah!
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Jesus.
Ah.
There you go.
You're a nice little puppy.
Yes.
Yeah.
All right, let's see.
Oh.
Yeah.
Come on.
Just a moment.
Oh.
I'll make me, I'll make me, I'll make me, I'll make me.
I'll make me, I'll make me, I'll make me.
Yeah, come on, come on.
Oh, yeah.
Make yourself comfortable.
Look at that big toe.
Oh!
Bigger.
Come on.
I gotta write this fucking down.
Yeah?
Hey, hey.
Hey.
I gotta write this.
I gotta write this down.
Ahh.
Please.
Oh my God.
Fucking yeah.
It's so fucking funny.
Oh my God.
Oh.
It's so fucking funny.
Boogie.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Oh my God!
Oh, fuck.
Get underneath.
Oh.
Hey, I'll put on our faces.
Please, come on our faces.
Please, please, please.
Give me more than my face.
Please, give me more.
Give me more.
Oh.
Here we go.
Oh my God....
Oh...
holy fuck.
Oh my God.
It's a mess.
Oh my God, this is so...
Honey it's me.
Ian, I forgot my keys!