So, Natasha.
Hi.
What's up?
So, Natasha.
Hi.
What's up?
What's going on?
Not much.
Chilling.
What are you getting ready to do today?
Uh, let's see.
way.
I'm going to fuck him next.
So you're ready for your third scene?
Fuck yeah.
end of the day.
I'm like, I don't know what I'm doing.
I don't know what I'm doing.
So you're ready for your third scene?
Yeah. Good day.
Have you worked with Rob before?
Mm-hmm a couple times. He did my first gangbang, my first IR gangbang.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Do you have any like memorable sexual moments with him?
Um
I think we were taking a break or something
So yeah, that's when I was like, I like Rob Piper. I
Well fuck raw, let's get out of here. I'm kidding. Actually, let's all go.
No, they haven't fallen yet.
God, please give me big boobs.
And then I got big boobs.
My guy friend and I were about to go out to lunch
and I was wearing a really low-cut sweater
and I was like, is this too offensive?
And he was like, fuck it, just do it.
And I was like, no, but what about old people?
So I'm definitely a slut,
but I don't like to offend people out in public.
Alright, awesome.
Do you have anything else you want to say
where you jump into the scene?
No.
No?
No, thanks for the interview.
Yeah, well thanks for being here.
You're so hot.
Why don't you take those titties out one time?
All right.
You guys want to see my tits?
Not that you haven't already, but...
You are so fucking hot.
Thank you.
They're really cute, huh?
my slutty little pussy.
That's what you guys wanna see, isn't it?
That's what you guys want to see, isn't it?
You want to see my wet mouth surround his big cock?
You want to watch my big titties jiggle while he fucks me from behind?
This is how I'm gonna fuck him.
This is how I'm gonna ride his big cock.
Mm.
I really want something shiny.
Yes, yes, yes
You should try it
Mhmm
有沒有
You should try it
OK, yes, yes, yes
Mhmm
OK
Stick with some more
I can't, I can't, I can't
No, no, no, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope
Okay.
Holy shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, it's so long.
Is that too sloppy?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
Now I am between my palms.
Oh yeah?
Yes, please.
Yeah.
Yes.
Just like that.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Just like that.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
I will kill youane!
I will shoot you!
Oh, you're just a fucking pussy ass.
Oh my god, that wet fucking tongue.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yes.
Mm, oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, you have all those fat lips with that mouth, yes.
Oh my god, oh my god.
and then I tickle him.
Yeah.
Oh, that fucking tongue, that pretty, pink tongue.
Yes, oh my fucking white, slimy pussy.
Yes, oh my god.
Oh, oh my god.
Mm, mm.
Yes, yes.
He's a sweet one.
Fuck, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my, yeah.
Oh, God...
You're the toughest.
You're the stinkiest.
Oh, fuck.
He's can't breathe.
He's going to kill me.
He's going to, he's going to kill me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, oh, shit.
Oh, he's going to kill me.
Oh, fuck.
That's gonna be sick, oh, my God.
Oh my God!
Oh fuck, that's such a big dick!
Oh my God, yes!
Hahahahaha
Fuck, yes!
Mmmmm, yes!
Oh my God, yes!
Oh shhhhh...
Oh fuck!
Oh my God, this dick, yes!
Mmmmm!
Oh fuck yes!
Oh, oh yeah!
Mmmmm, yes!
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh yay.
My God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, comforting.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
I want this fucking money.
God.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, yes.
Okay, go ahead.
Yeah
uh...
louise
well
from
mo from
no
uh...
well
moon
really bad, really bad, really bad, well.
Oh man.
Get your hands behind your back.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, my ears...
Oh, shit!
Oh, my mouth feel so fucking good.
Oh...
Oh, shit, Jess.
Oh, my...
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, mommy's hands, this is crazy.
Wow.
Mmm.
Oh, fuck me.
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you fuck.
Let me do it.
Oh, wow.
Just piercing like this.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Give it to me, please.
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Uh huh.
Good job.
Yes.
Uh huh.
Mm.
Wow.
You're really good at this.
Oh my God, yes!
Oh fuck, yes!
Oh my god! Yes!
Oh fucking yes!
Fuck! Oh my god!
Oh fuck!
Oh yes!
Fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck. Oh, bloody hell.
Oh, shit. Yes, spank that ass.
Spank that ass. Yes.
Oh, fuck you.
I want a big fucking dick.
Oh my god.
Ha ha ha.
Oh shit.
I do.
I like it as far as I can go.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
I want a big old big ass butt.
Would you like that?
Yes.
Ha ha.
Ha fuck.
I need to be fucking with you.
You have to be serious.
You don't want me to see you.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck, crazy, 5,56, yeah, yes, oh, oh, oh, fuck.
Yeah, only you and me, you're all for me, fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
Oh my God, oh shit, yes, fuck you, please, oh my God, yes.
Oh, fuck you, fuck that bitch, oh, oh, mm, mm, mm,
yes, just like that, just like that.
Oh
Oh my god, it's actually gonna be me coming in, fuck.
Oh shit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, yeah, pull that fucking push.
Come on, come on, yeah, yeah, I want this.
Oh shit, oh my god.
Oh fuck.
oh my god yes
yes
oh fuck
oh my god
yes
so good
oh fuck
oh my
oh my god
oh yes
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, I'm gonna fucking come again.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, shit.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, what the fucking pussy, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, shit.
Oh.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my, oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh shit, oh my god, yes.
oh my god yes
oh yes
yeah
oh my god
oh
what is this
Oh my god.
Oh good.
Yes!
Fuck yeah!
Fuck yes!
Yes!
Fuck, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck yes.
Yes, yes.
Yes!
Oh, shit.
Oh, stay right there.
Don't move.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Oh, thank God.
Fuck yes.
Oh.
Oh, it's fine.