I've been awake for days, 96 hours straight
Yeah, you like what you see?
Take it all in
This is my, my state
This is a rapture now
I have been captured now
By something holy
I've been awake for days
96 hours straight
This is a rapture now
I have been captured now
I'm hardly breathing
And my body is bleeding
But I see deep in me
Because I know that I'm a
Congratulations on the job
Thanks
Come on
Really?
Let me know you did this
Are you alright?
Let me guess
You fucked him, didn't you?
So what if I did?
It's all part of the game, isn't it?
Sex is art
And all that bullshit
Yeah, I like it.
I fucked you.
Because I liked you.
Cut the fucking shit.
Okay?
You fucked only me because you wanted to control me.
And I was in control.
Or was I?
Yes, Dennis.
You were in control.
And you should be fucking ashamed of yourself.
Please, declare.
Sorry, I just needed a second.
Of course. They call the time you need. Go have a seat.
Your club is spectacular. I've never seen anything like it.
I'm glad you like it. I'm looking forward to seeing these pictures.
I'm going to do the other eye, so it should be, so it should be.
Yeah, it's all good.
It's all good.
Oh
Oh, my God.
That's so good.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes.
I'm gonna let this cock inside you.
You don't want it inside you.
Yeah, yes I do.
Oh my god, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck.
I'm gonna let you.
I love how that's going to sound.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
give it to me.
Oh, fuck, dude.
Come on.
Try that.
Oh, he has to get back in there.
Yeah.
Oh, you're fucking digging me.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
It's so fucking gross.
Yes. Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Fuck! Oh my god, this was incredible!
I'm so fucking proud!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yes!
Yes! That's it!
Oh my god!
I've never felt anything so fucking good!
Yeah!
I'm so sorry!
Yeah, shh!
Yeah, give it to me!
Oh my god, I'm gonna cum so fucking hard like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
What is that baby, what is that?
Oh fuck yes, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Come on, come on.
I'm finally f***ing fraught
Just for me
And transported just for me
Yeah
This is for me
This is what I f***ing need
This is what I've always f***ing needed
This is what I've always needed
God, Tom! You feel so good!
You know you're one of those fucking...
Like that! Fuck! Fuck! Oh my god! Fuck!
Come on! Come on!
Yes! Give me two laps! Oh, fuck!
Yes! Give me two laps just like that!
Mm-hmm!
Oh, fuck!
Oh my god!
Pull your leg.
Yes, baby, yes.
Yes, my love.
Oh, honey. Yes.
Welcome, love. Welcome, love.
Come on. You have a beautiful child.
How did you do? How did you do?
Are you crying?
Do you want one more?
Yes, I want one more.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, I wish I could suck my ass.
shhh
mmm
come on, come on
no, no, no, no, please, please, please
oh, that's so f***ing good
yes, give your love like this
oh, like that is amazing
oh my god
we know what you like
oh, thank you
oh, yes
Oh
Fuck yes, I feel you
Yes, keep coming
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yeah, it's my mother's love, it's cool.
Oh, yeah?
My fucking love.
Oh, man.
I love it
you want me to fuck your ass too?
we're gonna share that fuck
yes
mhm
you see
there you go
yes please
use me
yes
oh my god i fucking love it
yes you do
yes yes yes
yes
come on
oh yes yes
Oh
Go fucking
Let me see how you fight, let me see how you fight
Yeah, which hell do you go to?
Yes, yes, right there
Oh my god, yes, oh god
Oh baby
Gee Dennis, you're really fucking me better than you've ever fucked me.
Nothing like a little bit of competition, huh?
Nothing like a little competition.
Yes, you're right.
Please suck it, doctor.
Yes, baby.
Right there. Right there. Right there.
You got it. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, fuck!
Yes!
Oh, my God.
Yes.
oh my goodness, oh my goodness.
oh you have so many uses you have so many fucking uses
How can I fucking pussy an ass if I've been fucking missing?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, good.
Yes, you know I fucking do.
Fuck.
Oh, no, let him get inside the house.
oh there we go
god i'm so full
that's what i fucking need
so fucking incredible
yeah yeah
oh my god
oh fuck
fuck dennis if only we had done this
I think you were too fucking scared.
Me too, it's so fucking hot
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh God, fuck, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
Don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
Oh, fuck, yes
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes
Oh, fuck, yes, just like them
Oh my god, I can see it going in all my fucking holes like that.
There we go.
Oh, that's so fucking good.
That's so fucking incredible.
Yes.
Don't fucking stop.
Oh my god.
Yes, come again, come again
Oh, fuck
Yes
Come on, meet with us
Right there, right there, right there, right there
Oh my god, fuck, fuck, fuck
Yes
Oh, fuck
I want your fucking cum, I want both of your fucking cums
Don't let me put my face in shit.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Come here.
Give me that fucking towel.
Oh, fuck.
Nice seeing you again, Denise. No hard feelings about the job, right?
No hard feelings, no, forget it. It's just business.
Exactly. I'm gonna give you both a little time, okay?
Chelsea, I'll see you out there.
So, what does it mean for us?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
I mean, we're done, Dennis. I'm done.
You're done? You know what?
No, we are never done, never.
There is no way anymore.
I'm done.