I'm just glad to have you back here again.
Yeah, thank you.
Well, anyways, enough of the niceties.
Yeah.
I have to ask.
What's up?
Have you ever had, like, a guy in there?
What do you mean a guy?
We have plenty of guys going in there.
there?
Yeah.
For real?
Of course.
Oh my god, that's crazy.
What do you think?
We build these things and the tensions of, like, come on.
with it.
I mean...
Come on.
I mean, it's really cool.
I think it's a great idea.
You should charge extra for it, really.
Well, you know, that's why we don't put quarter machines in there anymore.
on over there.
Okay.
Alright.
You just let me get it for free.
black-on-blondes that one's pretty pretty numerous right the cockled
Cuckold Sessions.
Yeah, Cuckold Sessions.
And, um, oh, we got, uh, where is it?
Oh, right here.
We got, uh, black meat, white feet.
Black meat, white feet.
I like it.
Yeah, definitely.
Oh, my God, that's her foot in her hand.
Oh, I did not see that.
Yeah, no.
Holy shit.
Definitely a thing.
Yeah.
Is he?
Yeah, he's previewing something.
He's previewing something?
Do you think he's going to preview over here?
Oh yeah, I think so.
You think so?
Maybe as soon as he hears your voice.
Yeah? Does he look like this, though?
Probably, I'd say.
Last time I called, yeah, he's probably still in there.
Do you think maybe you could put this on for me?
Yeah, hell yeah. I'll definitely work on it.
I'll rent more when I get out.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I just go right in there?
Yeah, definitely. Just go right in there.
Alright.
Alright, thanks. I'll be waiting.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Mm.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I am sorry.
Oh my godness.
Oh my...
Oh my goodness.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, it's so cold.
Oh my god, it's so good.
I have to do something.
Oh my god, this is so good.
Is that good?
Oh my god, look at these little balls.
I have a surprise for you, too.
Just stay right there, Mr. Big Cock.
You're pretty well endowed, too.
You need like big tits around that big cock.
Oh, fuck. God, that dick is so hard.
Yes, it's so fucking hard.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Fuck it.
Oh my god, it's so fucking big and hard.
Smooth?
Yeah.
Yeah, do you like that?
I have a really big clit.
It's too bad you can't see it.
Oh fuck.
Yeah, it's too bad you can't see my big clit.
It's all swollen.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Do you want to maybe, um...
I want you to feel it a little bit better.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God, yes.
Oh fuck, yes. Oh fuck. Oh my god.
One second again.
How do you like that?
Take it down with the rocks.
Oh, yes.
That fucking pink fucking black cock is so fucking hot.
There he is.
Yeah.
Yeah, you want some of my pussy?
Oh, that's so bad.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, it's so hard.
Oh, yeah, you want this?
You want this, Mr. Strangecock?
Yes, Mr. Big Black Strangecock.
You wanna poke this little thing, too?
Oh, fuck, let's get that right.
Fucking dying white pussy.
That's strange, dying white pussy, yes.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh my god, it's so good
Yes, oh
Fuck yes, yes
Uh-huh. Oh, that dick is so good.
Oh, I love that big, strange cock.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God.
What a fucking slut.
Yes. Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, my God.
Oh. Oh, fuck.
Uh-huh. Oh, shit.
That dick is so good.
Oh, my God. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Fuck, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. You like that pussy?
You like that pussy? Oh, my God.
That shit's gonna make me fucking cum.
Oh my god, yes!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, it's so good!
Oh!
Did you hear it?
You wanna come?
Oh my god, it's so good!
Oh, yes!
Oh fuck, my pussy tastes so good off that cock.
Oh, what's that stranger?
You wanna come?
You can do whatever you want, Mr. Strength Cock.
You're gonna come on my tits.
You're gonna come on my huge, all-natural white tits.
Oh my god. Yes.
Oh yeah, look at this big, hard cock.
I think he loves strange black cock.
Oh my god, he is.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I want your cum all over my white tits.
Please. Please. Please.
Please, please, please, Mr. Stranger.
Please, Mr. Strange Black Cock.
Please, please, yes.
Oh, come on, yeah, come all over my big tits.
Come all over my big tits, please.
Oh, yeah.
Like this.
Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God, yes.
Yeah, yeah, do it.
Uh-huh.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yeah, come. Come all over my big tit.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Where? Where, please?
Oh, shit.
Do you have any more for me?
What?
No.
They didn't hear us.
Oh, fuck.
I want to keep it. Oh my god. Wow. That was a big load, mister.
This is my first time having this
I'm a huge fan of her
I can't wait to see her
I've never seen her in person
but I'm excited to see her
Perfect
I can't wait to see her
I always wanted to try this
I've never seen her in person
I'm super excited
So, how'd it go in there?
Oh, uh, you know, it went great.
entire time it was just really good really yeah all you did was watch it
It's so funny, you think it's, no, um, okay, I have to go, bye.
Bye.
Ah, jeez, I hope he enjoyed it.