So, how was college?
I mean, same old, same old. I have so much homework all the time.
Well, have you partied with any cute boys?
I'm so much into older men.
I mean, I can see why. That's why you married your stepdad.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, we have good taste in men, then.
Yeah, we do. Probably.
Probably.
So, mom, how often do you let dad have sex?
Like, as you get older, do you guys not have as much sex?
He's a fucking horndog.
We all fuck three times a day or more, and he will still watch porn.
Oh, my God, that's a little ridiculous.
It's fucking gross.
It is.
It's a little funny, too.
Fucking God, again?
Like, no, no, you can't, no.
Teen porn on Xvideos.
But you're such a fucking pervert!
I'm sorry, babe, you weren't here. I thought I had the house to myself.
No! You can't do that!
I'm sorry!
So, you like watching teen porn?
Don't all guys?
I mean, it's kind of hot when you watch it, though.
Really?
Do you want to see them?
Yeah. Don't tell your mother.
Why would I tell her?
Aren't they pretty?
They're so nice.
You can touch them if you want.
And you won't say anything?
I kind of have a thing for older girls.
You don't have to be so gentle.
cock in college and make all the boys like me.
Daddy, can you help me with that?
I think I can.
Oh, God.
Remember.
Yes, he was with me.
A handful of...
I feel so good.
That's so nice, Daddy.
Thank you.
I bet you have.
You pervert.
I bet you got a nice juicy pussy waiting for me too, don't you?
Oh my God, you're so funny.
Yeah, you are, Daddy.
Yeah.
Oh, yes. Oh my god, you'll taste it.
You're a dirty little fucking slut, just like your mother.
Oh my god, I thought you'd never ask.
You're making me so nervous.
I'm gonna see you.
Oh yeah, spank me, spank me.
Oh my God, Daddy.
You're so naughty.
Yes.
Yeah.
How's it be over there?
make me messy
make me a sloppy bitch
do you like that little teen pussy?
the little 19 year old pussy
so tight just for you
squeeze it, squeeze it tight
bite down, bite down
oh my god
You don't need those anymore Yes, don't they look pretty against my bright
red pussy?
Yes, yes, don't tease Ah yeah, show me all those skills that you
have
yeah showing those beautiful eyes oh my fucking god
yeah oh that's so hot oh yes
I'm just gonna feel even better.
You're making me so worried.
Oh my God, yes, this is why I need an ointment in my life.
Yeah, you can take care of me just the way I want.
Just the way I need.
And you know exactly what you're doing.
Yeah, spit all over it.
Yeah, it's so fucking hot.
Um, yeah.
Oh, that's so nice.
Oh my God.
Yeah, it's yours, Daddy.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, show me.
It's yours.
Show me this pussy belongs to you.
Yeah, I'm going to prove it to you.
You're going to use me.
Yeah, see?
Yeah.
I can tell you're getting excited.
Am I making you horny, Daddy?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Oh, such a teaser.
Oh, fuck.
Man, it's just for you.
Pussy.
You can use it.
Use it, use it.
That's right, use it.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Come here, let me kiss you, let me taste my pussy on your lips.
Yes.
My pussy tastes so good.
God, that's so hot.
I love watching as your cocks like this fucking tight teenage pussy.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Help me!
Help!
So much spit, it's, oh my god, it's everywhere.
It's such a mess, I gotta...
Knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock.
Okay
Oh, shit, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have my legs stretched for you, yeah?
Yeah, I'm using...
Oh, I want to watch.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit, forget it.
Oh, okay.
I'm just enjoying myself too much.
Oh, I can't help it.
I feel excited.
I don't want to hurt you, Daddy.
Oh, that's it, just like your mother, also.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Squeeze them hard.
Separate them. That's it.
That's good.
Oh my God.
Daddy, Daddy.
Yeah, suck on these titties.
Suck on these titties.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck it.
Put that back in.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh.
I wanna be a good little condom stirrer
Fuck, fuck, fuck
Yeah, pile drive me, baby
Yeah, daddy
That's hot
mmm yes, yes, yes, mmm yeah, oh, that puts you clean, look at me,
What do you mean when I fucked you?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
oh
oh my god
my leg is shaky
yeah
yeah you do you wanna come all over me
you get down on your knees when i tell you to
whatever you want
you got this
pretty face you're gonna come all over
yeah
just imagine you wanna come all over
my fucking beautiful face
all this makeup just for you
Yeah, my hair done just for you, are you going to run it for me?
Squeeze that pussy tight, I'll let you know.
Yeah, tell me.
Squeeze it tight.
Here we go, here we go, to your knees.
Thank you.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, tastes so fucking good.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Oh, such a slut, just like your mother.
So did I do as good as those girls on the X videos, Daddy?
All those horny teen girls?
Way better.
Oh, good.
You should give me more lessons in the future, too.
We should get you on the X-Videos.
Sounds good to me.
Bamber.com