Teksting av Nicolai Winther
What do you want to see today, huh?
You want to see me suck a big cock?
Fuck.
No.
You wanna see me suck a monster cock?
Take it in all my holes?
Mmm.
It's what I want.
I wanna be taken.
Fuck.
Mmm.
No.
I love when you touch me.
Oh my god.
You're so fucking sexy.
Yes.
Oh god, that is so fucking amazing.
Shit.
Oh my god.
Damn.
I can't even fucking breathe
I'm trying to push it down my throat
It's fucking good.
It's so fucking good.
My god.
Mmh, fuck!
Fucking shit.
God damn.
Oh my god.
Fuck!
What are you trying to make out with your cock?
Oh my fucking god
So fucking incredible
Yes please
Come and get me baby
God I don't know whether to look at you
or that cock
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Fuck.
God damn it.
I get so much more energy
Oh fuck yes
My god baby
Get comfortable
Oh my god
Look at this
God damn
Yes
No, we go no, I really got him now I really got him look at that
Heavy dick down with those balls
And that is fucking heavy.
That is heavy.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, when I hit it, it hit me in the face with a damn.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
That is a heavy fucking dick.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Let me get this ball.
Yeah, you keep trying to escape, but I'm not letting you go anywhere.
Yes.
Yes! Pull him right down.
Fuck yeah.
Let me get that asshole too.
Let me get that asshole.
Jesus.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, you hit me in the head with that cock.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh, shit.
Oh, man.
Amazing.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, let me get those balls again.
Fuck.
Yeah, come to me.
Come to me.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
So sexy.
It's all for you.
Yes.
Take these off, too.
Oh, my God.
I want you to take all of me today.
With pleasure.
God damn it.
Is it ready for my pussy?
It is.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
You're gonna stretch my holes right out.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Tease that clit.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Oh.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, that feels crazy.
It's incredible.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, yes.
Fuck.
God damn.
Oh my god, trying to get that fucking cock inside me.
Yeah
Oh yeah
I'm gonna fucking bounce
Yes, take me, take me, take me
Yes
Take me, take me
Oh fuck
Oh god, baby
Fuck
Yeah
Yes
God
God damn it!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh my god! Yes!
Yes!
Don't fuck with me!
That's it, you.
Fuck! Fuck!
Oh my god!
Fuck!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Fuck! Yes, please, Jeff!
Fuck!
Jeff!
Yes! Yes!
God damn it!
Jeff, please.
Oh, fuck, look at me fucking cum on your cum.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, give it to me, give it to me.
I'm gonna fucking cum like that.
Keep going, keep going.
Oh, my God.
Come over here and fuck me, come over here.
Get behind you baby.
Oh you wanna go behind?
Just fucking right there.
Yeah.
Yeah you're gonna go for that asshole.
You're going for it.
Oh god.
You're gonna go nice and easy on me.
Nice and easy.
Stretch that out so long.
Oh my god.
Holy fuck.
Oh, it's so damn big.
Oh my god.
It's fucking crazy.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Yeah, baby.
And I love the way it snakes into my arsehole like that.
Fuck!
God damn it!
Oh my god!
Fucking amazing.
Every fucking day.
Oh my god!
Fucking amazing.
Fuck!
Shit.
It's insane.
Oh my god.
It's fucking, fucking, I don't know.
I hate that fucking thing in my arsehole.
Oh my god, just you, just you.
You're the biggest fucking thing that's ever been done.
Oh my god.
Oh, I want to taste that cock straight from my asshole.
Straight from my asshole.
God damn it.
Oh my god, my asshole tastes so good on your cock.
Oh my god, I love eating my asshole off your cock.
Yeah, I want it back inside that hole, too.
Yeah, you want to put it back in it.
I do.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Why?
Oh, God.
God damn it, that is fucking perfect.
Wow, you really stretched that hole out.
Look at how much of my dick you take.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god, baby, fuck.
Oh my god, really, really, oh my god.
Fuck, I can't believe it.
I'm gonna keep it in and roll over right on your side, baby.
Right on your side.
Jesus fucking God.
I'm a dick drunk so fucking quickly.
Holy fuck.
I can't believe it.
Nothing feels like it.
Oh my God.
It made me crazy.
God damn it.
It's fucking crazy.
Wow.
Oh my God.
I can't believe I'm taking that much of your coke.
I want it.
Oh my god.
You're fucking incredible.
Yeah, that fucking
big monster cow
back inside me. Back again.
Yeah. He wants to go back
Oh my god, you're giving me fucking tins and needles, yeah.
Yes, yes, baby.
Oh shit, you're giving me fucking shit.
Holy fuck.
Oh yeah, now I can see it.
You can see it going in and out, huh?
Yeah, I see it, I see it, I see it.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh my god, fuck.
It's so big.
Oh my god, I can't believe I can even take that much of it.
Oh my god.
Fuck, damn it.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh my god.
Oh my god, baby, fuck.
Fuck yeah.
God damn.
Oh shit.
Fuck, it's so good.
Oh god, oh god, oh god, oh fuck, oh fuck, oh fuck, oh fuck.
Oh god.
God damn.
I'M GONNA GO HOME!
SHIT!
AH!
I'm here!
Oh my god, I'm so fucking hot!
Holy fuck!
Oh my god!
Fuck!
I'm so fucking hot!
Oh yeah, one more!
One more!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, fuck!
Oh shit!
Oh my god!
I'm obsessed
I'm obsessed with your cock
Oh my god
It's so good
God damn it
Yeah
Yes please
Yeah right in the nose
That's what you like, isn't it?
That's what I like.
You like that.
I fucking love it.
Oh god, yes.
I'm gonna jerk it off right inside that also.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Right there.
Right fucking there.
Open me up so good.
Yes.
Oh god, that's so deep.
Oh, it's so deep.
Oh my god, it's so fucking deep.
I love that feeling in your back.
Yeah.
Oh.
Ah.
Shit.
Here, you rest. Yeah, you just rest there.
I'm just going to massage that cock with my asshole.
Just grind on it like that.
Oh my god, I feel your hot beating so fast.
I feel it out of my hands. I even feel it in your cock.
I feel that hot beat in your cock. It's throbbing inside my asshole.
I'm so fucking good.
Oh, God damn it.
It's incredible.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
My God.
My fucking God.
You're so good.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, you got everything.
You got everything.
Oh, my God.
You got a big fucking dick deep in my elbow.
Oh my god, let me taste my hot sauce.
Oh my god.
Here, let me have one more.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I can control it with those balls.
Yeah, make you fuck me.
Make that big fucking cup fuck me.
Oh my god, I can tell how far I've taken it by where it's all juicy.
God damn it.
You haven't fucked these big tits yet.
And now you want those big fucking titties.
Come here.
I'm going to put your fucking eyes on my face like this.
There we go.
Now I can have those big fucking tears around it.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god.
Oh, shit.
Shit! Fuck!
Fuck! Yes!
Oh shit!
God, it looks so fucking good between those two.
Yeah, it does.
Yeah, you wanna fuck them? Let me fuck them.
Fuck them. Fuck them like that.
Yeah, I love when you take advantage of me.
Yeah. My whole body.
Big dick, big dick.
Shit!
Fuck!
Fuck, that's groovy!
Wow!
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
I know I'm gonna do it again.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yes.
I love it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah, way to go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Jesus Christ.
Damn it.
Oh, shit.
Every last drop.
Squeeze it all out.
God, good boy.
Fuck yeah.
Get my tongue in that eye.
Just dig the rest out.
Yes.
Shit.
Oh, damn it.
What an amazing gift.
You're incredible.