How do I look?
Perfect, as always.
Aren't you a charmer?
Learned from the best.
Keep that charm on full force.
Everything needs to go perfectly.
I got this. Who grizzes the space?
Oh, um, hello Selena.
Hello Bridget. You remember my son, Ray?
Yes, of course.
Hello Bridget.
Oh, that's, that's very sweet of you, but I'm fine, really.
If you want to be alone, we completely understand.
But being alone can get lonely, so...
If you need anything, anything at all, you know where to find us.
Wait, um, would you two like to come in for some tea?
the rest of the house it's just lovely you have exquisite taste
How long have you lived in the neighborhood, Bridget?
Uh, I'd say about three years now.
Yeah, we visited the area and we just fell in love.
I can see why.
We love it too.
Clean and quiet.
And the people, well, they're just...
delightful company.
I completely understand what you're going through.
My husband passed away as well.
Ray's father.
It's hard to talk about, but I...
Oh, I'm very sorry.
Thank you.
It's been years, but luckily I've had Ray
to take care of me.
Wow.
It's just lovely.
Do you have anyone to take care of you during this trying time?
Um, well I don't really have any family, so no.
No, I guess I don't.
Well, if there's anything you need, anything at all,
I'm here for you.
Ray is so caring. He's always been so attentive.
I just know that a woman's needs are very important,
especially during a trying time like this.
Wow, is this for Duchi?
It looks very expensive.
Oh, no, Arnold's and I, we got it in South America.
Apparently it's worth $150,000.
Nice.
Oh, you're not seeing anyone? A handsome guy like yourself?
No, I'm not. Completely single.
Ray is very choosy.
What can I say? I have a very specific taste.
taste. If Rhea's got his eye on you, you know you're something special.
I should leave you two alone?
Oh, I, uh, no, no, of course not.
I'm just teasing.
Uh, look, I am, I have a lot to do
with, like, the arrangements and everything.
Maybe I should just, um...
Let me get that for you.
You have a lot on your mind.
I'll just clean these and we'll be out of your hair.
Okay, sure.
Look, I'm sorry about my mom.
She can be a little overbearing,
but she means well.
No, it's all right.
She's very sweet.
I just want you to know that I meant what I said back there.
About what?
About your needs.
I can make you feel so much more than just sadness.
Don't you want to feel something more than just sadness?
I can make you feel...
so good.
Nothing messy, nothing complicated.
Just good.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
oh my goodness, it hurts so bad
Oh, yeah.
Oh
I love you guys so much, and I hope you're having a great day!
oh my god, it's so hot
Oh, I can't see it.
Mine.
I don't want to do it.
It's painful.
Yeah.
Really?
okay
oh my god
oh yeah
oh my god that is so good
stay right there
like this
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh yeah.
Is this really what you came for?
Isn't this really what you came for?
Oh, fuck yeah.
You know, we really shouldn't be doing this right here, right now.
Yes, we should.
What if your mother catches us?
It's okay.
I cannot believe it.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I can't go in there.
I can't.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's been so long.
I've just had one of my intense thoughts lately.
I can't.
Oh my god.
Oh yes
Oh, yes, you are, yes, you are.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, it's such a pretty young cup.
Oh, it feels so good.
Yeah.
Are you sure she won't care?
Okay.
She takes forever cleaning.
I got something.
Oh
Just a little bit, just a little bit faster, just a little bit faster.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, oh, God.
Oh god
Oh goodness
It's so tickly
It's like my face
Oh god
Oh yes, really get your face in there
Please get your face in there
Oh
Oh, please keep going.
Yes.
No.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
I have an abscess.
Oh, dude.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, please give me that.
Oh yes, oh that's what I need.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, please.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck you so much.
Oh God.
Oh, God.
Oh my God.
I missed you.
You were good.
Oh my God.
Fuck.
Oh my god, yes!
Yes! Oh my god, he made it so bad! He escaped!
Oh god, Rick!
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Okay, please!
Oh my god.
Yes!
Oh, fuck you to my...
Yes.
Please.
Oh, shit.
It's OK.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
I really need a sober.
OK.
Oh.
Shh.
Oh, fuck.
OK.
Mm.
Yeah.
OK.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
oh yes
oh my god
oh fuck
oh fuck yes
Oh my god, I need it. That's so bad.
Yes.
Oh, my stomach.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, oh.
I'm gonna get you.
Yes.
Right?
Oh, sit down.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Stay right there.
oh yes
mmhmm
ok
beautiful
this is
oh yes
mmm
mm
Oh my god, yeah.
Wow, that's so good.
Yeah.
Stand up.
Just stay right here, okay?
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Yes! Yes. Yes, yes, yes ...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes!
Dad...
Kollege,
Kolekie,
Kol...
Yes...
Wohn...
Oh my god,
boldness...
baldness...
Beautiful,
Yeah...
Oh yes...
Oh wow,
Ooh yes...
Ah yes...
Ah.
Ah,
Ah yeah...
I'm going to cry...
Oh
Yes, speak! Speak, my ass! Speak, my ass!
Oh yes, oh yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh yes.
Mm.
Ah, ah, ah.
Oh yes.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
All right.
Mm.
Oh fuck.
Yes, yes.
Mm.
Ah.
Oh
Oh my god, it's getting me so deep.
Ah, yes.
Ah.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Ah, shit.
Oh.
Oh, god, yes.
Yes.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Ah.
Oh my god.
Oh god, I'm so bad.
Oh fucking...
Oh
Oh my god yes.
I can't breathe.
Oh my god, I want you to let me over now, okay?
Fuck.
Jim.
Move.
Fuck.
Oh.
Yes.
Move.
Oh.
Okay.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God.
Move.
Oh.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh.
sign
oh
oh my god
oh yes
oh
yes
oh god just like that
oh
oh my god
Oh God!
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Please, please give it to me, please!
Please, please!
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh yes.
Yes.
I fucking love you.
I love you.
Oh yes.
Yes.
Oh god yes.
Oh.
Oh fuck yes.
ahhhhhhhhhh
ahhh
ahh ahh
ahh ahhh
ohhh
ahh
ahh oh my god
yes yes
oh oh oh my god yes oh fuck
oh fuck yes
oh
Oh shit! Oh my god, yes!
Oh my god, get down there and eat it.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, mm-hmm, yeah.
Oh, fuck this.
Yeah, oh, fuck you.
Oh, Sammy.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Oh my god, yes!
Mm!
Mm, oh yes!
Oh fuck.
Oh my!
I can't fight.
Oh my God, you're so-
Mmm.
Oh my God.
Oh yeah.
Oh...
Oh my God.
Oh, oh, oh yes.
I just keep looking, you just look at me.
I mean, you know it's so bad.
I know it's so bad.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh fuck.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh god.
Oh fuck yeah.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god yes, yes, oh yes.
There it is.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Mm.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh yes!
Yes!
Oh my god.
Alright...
So you're traumatized.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Fuck you.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, this one I need.
I need it so bad.
Yes.
Fuck you.
I got you.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck, yes!
Yes, yes, oh my God!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Yes, oh!
Oh, fuck yeah!
Oh my god, yes! Yes, oh my god!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh my God! Oh my God that tickles so good!
Oh that tickles so good!
Oh it feels so freaking good! Yes!
Oh I'm crying!
Oh, oh kiss!
Kiss!
Oh god.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh god, yes.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh, my God.
Oh my god yes, oh fuck yes!
Oh yeah!
Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh fuck yes!
Fuck you come for me, please, please!
All right then.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, oh, fuck yes!
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Morning.
You took the teacup?
You said I wanted one, didn't I?
I think it has class.
Better not be all you took.
You told me.
How do I look?
So sexy, Mom.
Thank you.
You