I check my rearview mirror, and there's a golf cart and some guy.
I'm furious at this point.
I'm ready to give some gaffer a piece of my mind.
So I jump out and stomp towards him, and who is it?
Alex Baldwin.
Oh my god.
Can you believe that?
Needless to say, he was speechless.
He'd been texting his dog sitter and just hadn't been paying attention.
But he was so sweet and apologetic about the whole thing.
Well, I would have hoped he would have been.
He was only working alongside the lead of the movie for six months.
I'm surprised he didn't bow down and beg for mercy.
Wait, okay, tell me you took him up on that offer.
I told him that if we win Best Picture this year, I'll think about it.
No, stop. He did send flowers the next day though.
You never told me that.
Oh honey, it was nothing. Just a friendly gesture between co-stars.
If you insist.
But if he wants to take you out, he has to go through me first.
But really, I cannot believe these stories. They're so crazy.
Yeah, I am unbelievably envious.
Mm-hmm. Same here.
I can't believe that you almost gave up and went back home
before you'd signed with an agency, too.
And before you met me.
Oh, I cannot believe it. It would have been such a waste.
Yeah.
A waste?
Oh, Jocelyn, no, not a waste like that.
You know what I mean, okay?
Okay, you would have been forced to be normal.
And you said it yourself,
no one from your hometown ever leaves.
They just stay there.
You're right.
You're right, I'd be in the suburbs changing diapers
and dragging myself to kids' soccer matches.
Don't forget weekend trips to Safeco Supermarket
and Catfish Roundup.
You're right, you're right.
Goddamn vultures.
Is that surprising?
The consequences of fame.
Now, where were we?
It's so good to see you.
We'll see you next week.
Drive safely.
We'll drive.
Okay.
Bye!
Oh!
Someone's feeling playful.
Oh, it was so torturous waiting for them to leave.
I just want you all to myself.
You can have me.
Jocelyn, are you gearing up for award season?
Jocelyn, come on, come on and talk to us.
Miss Blue, how was the catwalk in Berlin?
Just for the record, I'm glad you decided to stay.
I would have never met such a brilliant, exceptional, beautiful woman.
And I know we had a small hiccup last year, but...
That hiccup... you mean the affair?
I'm just saying, I think it made us stronger, and...
I just...
I don't know what I'd do without you in my life.
I love you.
I love you too.
I love these
Gorgeous
You're so handsome
Excuse me, let's get this right
You're fast
you look so beautiful tonight
you just love your eyes
everything
take these off
comfortable
Oh my god.
I'm so proud of you.
How did I get so lucky?
We love you.
I don't know.
Oh, you're such a devious god.
Don't act like you don't love me.
I do, I love you.
You're just too good at it.
I like to drive you crazy.
You do a fantastic job.
You planned this.
I would never.
Then why are you wearing this lingerie?
I just might wear it around my house once.
Sure.
I don't know.
How do they resist?
Now I'm going to keep teasing you.
No.
Is it mine?
It is on your eyes.
You promise this time?
I promise.
I went to the moon completely, and the moon is just you.
Oh, my God.
God, I love watching you cry.
Oh, man, it's so wrong that you can make me do that.
God, what is this?
It's so beautiful
You're going to tease me right back huh, I guess I deserve it.
I don't want to do this.
Yeah.
Oh my god, your lips.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, you're so good.
Yes
Oh
Oh, my God.
I want to feel all of your skin.
I'm a little smothered in here.
I'm smothered in here.
I love you all the time.
I swear your hands are magical.
I love your skin.
I love it when you talk like that.
God, you smell so good.
Oh my God, your body is so good.
Oh my God.
I feel like I need to use my body.
Oh, man.
Look at me.
I'm so lucky.
Yes, yes.
So close.
I swear you are pure bliss.
I don't know what to do with you.
What?
Oh, just that you're the sexiest woman I've ever seen.
Shut up.
That's not true.
You are.
I'm not that superstar.
I like you.
I'm so lucky.
I love you.
Hello? How did you get in here? Who are you?
Hello, Jocelyn.
What is this? What's going on? Who are you?
where you would be now, if you had stayed.
None of that matters anymore.
It's in the past, I can't change any of it.
I am where I am, that's that.
But what if it wasn't?
What if I told you?
Give you the power of choice?
Don't you miss your family, Jocelyn?
You haven't spoken to your parents since the day you left.
They're getting so old.
But I could give you that time back.
What if I go back and I'm still miserable?
Can I come back?
You're looking a gift horse in the mouth.
I am offering you an opportunity that many people would kill for.
you'll start your new life
Baby, come back to bed
I'm coming