I miss nice
And how do you like it?
I love it.
Mm-hmm.
Great.
Sit down.
Um, water?
Please.
Thank you.
Beautiful place you got here.
Oh, thanks.
So, tell me about yourself.
Why do you think you'd be a good tutor for my son?
Well, I'm great with guys and they seem to take a liking to me.
I know how to make things make sense.
Great!
Well, my son has a lot of trouble focusing.
Is he?
Mm-hmm.
So, the tutor I'm looking for has to be a bit unconventional.
You know, someone to help him get his mind back on track.
I don't really follow you.
You know, just someone to help get it out of the system.
Wait, you want me to fuck your son?
Mm-hmm.
But I have to make sure you're up for it first.
I'm not sure.
Hey.
No problem.
You can leave.
But wait, I'm a good tutor.
No, I'm sure you are.
Bye.
Look.
Look, I promise, I can show you I can do a good job, okay?
You're so pretty
boys.
Oh
Um
um
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Yeah,
mm,
yeah,
I'm taking you to your mother.
No, no no.
Really.
No, no.
Don't make me laugh.
Oh, I thought you were telling me that.
Really?
Yeah.
You really think that?
You think you tell?
Yeah.
I don't.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
No.
No, you don't.
Ah.
Don't make me laugh.
No, you don't.
I want to stand up.
Oh my god.
Yeah?
The boys listen to you, do they?
I wonder why.
mmm
sit down for me
what size are your tits?
30, 60, oh my god. Yeah, you make a great tutor
Oh, I miss you so well.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, you're so big.
Yeah, you know what you do to boys, you little slut.
I think you know exactly what you did to them.
Oh my god.
They're so big.
Look at your big titties.
You like them, don't you?
You like turning boys on with them, don't you?
I bet you do. That's the only reason you're a tutor, isn't it?
So you can get some dick.
Take this off for me.
Yeah, yeah, now sit back down.
Do you know how to eat pussy?
Mm-hmm.
Show me.
Put your little mouth full of that meaty pussy.
Oh
oh yes
umm
um umm
yes
ummm
umm
uh
spit on it
yes again
I'm gonna rub it all over my pussy lips.
Get messy.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh my god, yes.
Keep going.
Oh my god, yes, keep going.
Mm-hmm
Stand up I want to bend you over
You really enjoyed this.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Oh no.
Oh, yeah.
That's a tight push.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah, you like it.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Ew...
Ah!
Ah...
It's cold here.
You can tell the boys are fucking out.
It's cold.
Oh my God.
No.
oh
Come on.
Come on, that's all you little slut.
You know I want you.
Come on.
Yeah.
Oh.
Come here.
I bet you want to sit on that.
Oh
Yeah.
Uh, mm.
Uh.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Mm.
Oh.
Yeah.
Mm.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
I'm going to try to get you something to drink.
here.
Ah!
I don't know.
MOANING
I'm sick.
Get on the floor.
I have one last thing I want to show you.
I'm going to get you out of here, okay?
Oh
I don't want you to go.
Oh my god.
I think you could probably take very good care of my son
So, did I get the job?
You bet your sweet ass you did.