Is relentless
The more I get
the more I want
Are they ready for me? Yes, and I'll stop nothing to get what I want
You know, I've worked up quite an appetite.
I bet you boys are hungry too.
You may have noticed I haven't served any food.
But I have a full meal for you, right here.
So who's hungry?
going to devour each and every one of you get the champagne ready
Shall we toast to that?
Let's toast to it.
Yay, for the lady.
Thank you.
Everyone fill your glass.
Up there, you want to cool it off a little?
Oh yeah, look at that.
Put something down, Steve. Put something more down.
Right into the glass.
You guys ready to do this cheers?
Shall we toast?
To my dark side.
To the beautiful Angela White.
Dark side.
Now who's ready for a meal?
Everyone put their hands on me.
Oh my god, you're all so fucking delicious.
Yes, it's so good.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Put your fingers back inside there.
No, put them back in that pussy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rub my clit.
Oh my god, that's so fucking good.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck. Yeah, make me come on those fingers.
Yes, fuck.
Oh, fuck. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't fucking stop.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
You're gonna choke me, choke me, choke me.
Fuck, yeah, I'm gonna fucking choke.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
You're gonna fuckin' talk for minutes, huh?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, my God.
So fuckin' hot.
Look at all these hot dicks for me.
Oh, fuck.
Go around the tables.
Yeah, you fucking come.
Yeah, you fucking come!
Fuck yes!
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm.
Mmm. Fuck yes.
Maybe she can put two at the same time, huh?
Can you put two at the same time?
Yes, please.
Next dick.
Oh, my God.
Then I fucking help out. Hold my fucking hand back while I suck a dick.
You're gonna stick that fucking dick in me? Fuck yeah!
Look at this, there we go, baby, yeah.
Ooh, and this, to be honest, that's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look at this, yeah.
Get that shit going.
There you go.
Ooh.
Ooh, yeah.
There you go.
Just like that.
Don't you stop. Don't you stop, baby.
Come on. Right there.
There we go.
Take this. Take this.
Take it. Take it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, it's so fucking good in my house like that
Oh yeah, my back, my back.
Get that shit right there, girl.
Oh fuck, yeah, it's so fucking good.
It's fucking good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh, fuck you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Hey!
Yeah, he's gonna take that fucking off!
Huh?
He's gonna take that fucking off!
Just like that?
Yeah!
What's the mean, alright?
Oh my god!
Fuck!
Yeah!
So fucking good!
Right there!
yeah, yeah, oh my god, fuck, I'm so filled, so filled.
Yeah, that's what I fucking mean when I want to be full.
That's what I mean.
You got a lot more.
Get that shit.
Chocolate? Vanilla.
Get that shit. Get that shit, girlfriend. Get that shit.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what we're talking about.
Oh, open that one.
Open that one.
Here we go.
Oh, just like that.
Open that one.
Oh, my God. It's so fucking good, man.
It's so fucking good.
Oh, God, you're going to make me fucking cum so hard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, give that shit to him!
Yes!
That's what I'm talking about.
Right there, baby.
Oh, God, yeah, that's fucking good, baby.
Yeah, that's fucking good.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Get that cat in the car.
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
Almost.
Get that, too. Get that, too.
Oh, shit.
Right there.
Get that shit.
Ooh, hey.
Let's go.
Let's go. Here we go.
Here we go.
Ooh, wow.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Those latex fucking gloves on those people.
Just like that.
Like those latex gloves on your fucking cunt.
There you go.
Get that shit.
Fucking cunt.
Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Keep going, keep going, keep going.
Get it, get it.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get it.
There you go.
Yes, yes, yes, c'mon.
F**k yes.
F**k yes, take it, get it.
One by one, one.
F**k yes.
It ain't stuck.
There you go, we ain't stuck.
F**k yes.
Get it.
Take it.
F**k yes.
Take it. Take it.
There you go, monster. There you go.
Hit that shit.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
Don't let it go. Don't let it go.
Right there.
Uh huh.
Oh yeah.
Oh. Give it.
Give it. Come on.
Oh yeah.
There we go.
Yeah.
Take that fucking pussy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Fuck me.
Fuck that little pussy.
You see?
There it is.
Come on, come on.
Show me, show me.
Give it to me.
Give me that fucking dick.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Here we go.
All righty.
Look at that.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, good looking.
Yeah.
Show me.
Show me the spot.
There you go.
Right there.
Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Fuck.
One by one.
One.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh
Oh, fuck, yeah, yeah.
Fuck, yeah.
Come on.
Let him get it.
Yeah, fuck.
There we go.
Come on.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
There we go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
Right there.
Just like that.
Yes.
Go.
Yeah.
Yeah, here we go, don't play with it, let her get it.
Yeah!
So look at this, look at this, look at this.
Oh my god.
Look at this.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's so good.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Come on.
Yeah.
Work that.
Work that out.
That's it?
Mm-hmm.
Fuck! You keep fucking giving it to me like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, just like that.
Oh, yeah, let me stick this here.
I feel you. I feel you through my fucking pussy.
I'm so fucking going through it.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Yes!
Oh, my God.
Let me put it back in.
Pussy.
Oh, yeah, I fucking love it when my own feels like that.
They're fucking feeling like that.
My fucking pussy and all is getting stretched out so good.
Yes.
Just like that.
Yeah, keep going, keep going.
Keep going, keep going, keep fucking going.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here you go.
Oh, my God, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
baby.
Yes!
That's what you call it.
Look at that.
What?
You know what?
Yeah, back and fucking pull.
Stick that fucking dildo.
Oh my god.
Let me go watch.
Come here, come here. Yes, yes, stay like that.
Here we go, here we go.
Fuck you.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I fucking love that. I fucking, fucking felt like that.
I fucking love it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wow, I fucking love it! I fucking love it!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck this!
Get that shit!
There we go!
Fucking watch it just like that.
Watch it. Hit that shit.
Have a get it.
Have a get it. Have a get it.
Oh, fuck you.
Just like that.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Here, here.
Fuck, yes.
Here we go. Here, here.
One, fucking one.
Do you think he's fucking with us?
He's fucking with the shit?
He's fucking with you?
Here we go. Come on.
Get on back in there.
Take that shit.
Fuck yes.
Fuck yeah.
There you go. There you go.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Very good. Very good.
Yes!
There you go.
Come with me, Angela.
Don't fall. Don't fall.
And you're going to put your fucking hands on me and all of you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it goes down so you can look up back closer.
Oh, there.
Good fish.
Whoa.
That's what we talk about.
Ah, yes, green.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
Second wall.
Make your way around.
Oh, yeah.
There you go.
Fuck your face.
Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let me fuck your face.
oh, that's what I'm talking about, that's what I'm talking about.
Hey, look at that face.
Yeah, just jerk it, just jerk it.
Yeah, I'm fucking lying.
It's on my face.
It's on your fucking face.
Open your mouth wide, open it wide.
Put more than one, more than one.
Fuck, it's so good.
Give me a fucking kiss.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Give me a kiss.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I fucking love it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my God.
Oh shit.
I'm gonna fucking put it in, I'm gonna put you through.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh my God, fuck, yeah, yeah, oh my God, fuck it through.
Open your fucking mouth, open your fucking mouth.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes.
Oh my God, fuck, all this fucking dicks
What the fuck are you doing?
Mama!
There you go, there you go.
Fuck, yes!
There you go, suck it in.
Drink that shit!
Oh my god, fuck!
I'm so fucking filled with cock!
Oh yeah, fuck!
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh wow
I want you all to fucking take turns.
I want you all to fucking take turns in my homesteading.
There you go.
Yeah.
That pussy's so good.
I like that fucking pussy.
Yeah.
There you go.
There you take it.
Yeah, next fucking gig.
Yeah, everyone take fucking time.
Yeah.
Everyone fucking take time.
Oh, my goodness.
Fucking Christmas.
Yeah.
Cocktails are fucking good.
Fuck.
It's so big in that pussy.
Holy shit.
I fucking love it.
It's so fucking sexy.
Fucking take that hole.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, fuck.
Yeah, take it. Take it.
Take it. Fucking take it.
Take that fucking pussy. That's your fucking pussy.
That's your fucking hole.
That's your hole.
Back it up. Back it up.
Next fucking cock for me
I like Whitney Tick Tock
I'll figure it out for you.
That's it.
Yeah.
Fuck yes.
Right there.
Fuck yeah.
All right.
There you go. Don't stop there.
Yeah. Look at that. Look at that.
Yeah, yeah.
Who is next?
Yeah.
Yeah
Yeah, make sure you fucking show me
Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god!
There you go.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck. He's strong.
He's strong.
Come on. Get that shit.
Get it.
Come on. Give it to me.
Yeah, just like that, just like that, just like that, just like that.
Oh, fuck you, man.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Christ.
I'm going to fucking die.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, shit.
Fuck you.
Come on.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
Come on. Yeah.
Oh, my God. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go, baby.
Yeah.
Come on.
Get down.
Go down.
Jump, jump.
Again.
Yeah.
Come on.
Oh, shit.
Don't do it.
Here we go, here we go.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god, yes!
Get out of the room, get out of the room.
Look at that big fucking tissue.
Here we go, here we go.
There you go.
Wow.
Oh shit.
Just like that.
There you go. Yes, yes, get it.
Take it out.
Take that out.
Just like that.
Right there.
Go.
Back.
Fuck yeah!
Yes!
Give it a go.
Next part.
Woo!
Yeah.
Yeah, come on.
Come on.
Hold it down.
There you go.
You got it?
Come on.
Don't stop.
Get down.
Yeah.
Get up.
Get down.
Come on.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's time for me to get on that fucking tube.
Yeah, let's go.
Yeah, take a seat, my lady.
Fuck, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, put it in that fucking pussy.
Put it in that fucking pussy.
Yeah, slide it in.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, how many guys behind you?
How many guys behind you?
Oh, my God, three fucking guys.
Three fucking guys.
I see some coming.
Oh my god, oh my god
Oh my god, that fucking three dicks inside me
Holy shit
Oh fuck
Oh my god, fuck
Fuck, fuck, fuck
Oh my god
That's it!
All the way! All the way!
All the way up!
Oh, fuck! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh my God!
There we go!
Fuck!
Holy shit!
Yes! I'm proud of you!
Yeah, man. Come on. Take it, take it!
There you go. Yeah!
There we go. Ooh, yeah.
Come on.
Show me your eyes, show me your eyes.
Show me your eyes. Uh-huh.
Let us see it. Let us see it.
Get down there. Get down there.
Whoo! That's what we're talking about.
One more? That's what we're talking about.
One fucking round. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fucking round. Let's go. Let's go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's go.
Nothing can stop us. Nothing can stop us.
There you go. There you go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, take me, take me, all my fucking old heels.
Yeah, look at that.
ah
oh
oh yes
ah
here we go
all the way
there you go
come on
Oh
Yeah, I love being able to see those fucking cuts in my house like that
And a perfect fucking view
A perfect fucking view of those fucking
Yeah, I love seeing them going
I fucking love it
I love it
I love watching them
I love watching them fucking pounding me
I mean, I love those fucking holes
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, fuck, fuck
Yeah, yeah, you like fucking watching it?
You like fucking watching me take those fucking dupes?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You fucking like watching it, don't you?
You like watching those fucking dupes take my holes?
Stretching my balls, watching all these guys use me
Taking every thought I need
Yeah, I fucking love it
Yeah, yeah
Get those fucking cuffs ready
I want you, I want you to fucking get them fucking ready for me
Use my fucking, oh my god, fuck yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I am so fucking close to coming in and out of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I fucking love it.
Yeah, yeah, jerk those fucking cunts.
I don't want you to fucking get off watching me
get fucked like this.
Jerk those fucking dicks.
Yeah, stroke them for me.
Stroke those fucking chumps.
Yeah, it's a lot hard.
It's a lot hard.
Just imagine taking these fucking holds.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, God, you're gonna leave me so close like that.
Perfect.
Got a nice big load for me too.
Fuck yeah.
I love that fucking cum.
I want all of it.
Cover me.
Yeah.
That fucking looks awesome.
I love all those fucking loads.
Oh shit.
Oh, yeah, give me every fucking drop.
Oh, shit.
Oh, Nick, get all these other ones, baby.
Yeah.
Get them, get them.
Come on.
I'm shoving up there.
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, yeah.
Yeah, just rub my balls just right there.
That's perfect.
I'm going to come on your face.
Oh, you're coming.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah, fuck, everywhere.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
Look at all that fucking cum.
That was a nice big fucking...
Yes, I do.
I want a fucking second one.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I love you cum so fucking much.
You get so fucking horny.
Oh, my God, yeah, shut it down.
Oh, let's eat it all.
Oh, you're so last.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, yeah.
I know there's some more for me.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, yeah, give it to me.
Come on, my baby.
Oh, yeah, I'll never eat.
Fuck, don't I look all pretty covered in cum?
Glistening?
I think it's when I look my prettiest.
You still stroking that fucking cock?
I know you got a big fucking load for me, don't you?
Those balls are so fucking filled with cum.
Oh yeah, give it to me.
Mm-hmm, shower me in it
Shower me in that fucking cum
Oh, yeah, so fucking good
Mm, fuck
Oh, yeah
Mm-hmm
Oh, my God
But we're gonna save the best for last, aren't we?
Because you and me, we gotta cum too, don't we?
He's striking that fucking cock at home
And a nice big fucking load
On those balls
Should we use
This cum to make me cum
I think we should
And then you're gonna
Cum all over my fucking face
Aren't you
Yeah you are
I'm gonna rub that little fucking pussy
I use all this cum as a lube
Look at that
face, do it, oh my god, fuck, so fucking good.
Get me covered in all that fucking jizz.
Yeah, you like that?
You're a fucking like that?
Yeah, you want to wash this cum off my face?
Come on, Marcus.
We know you got those magic fingers.
Up here.
I'm so fucking slippery with all that fucking cum.
Yeah, shower me.
Oh, fuck, yeah, fuck, that's fucking good, now you've seen my dark side.
I'm sorry it had to end this way but you said you wanted to see my dog