Co-operate.
Hey!
Hey, you two, save it for the scene.
Save it for the scene and put some life jackets on
and chop you out here.
And don't drink!
What the fuck?
Who are these guys anyway?
Fucking amateurs.
Tastemade.
City bar security.
Yeah, I'm so rich.
Yeah, keep it coming.
All that money and luxury.
Is it not?
I'm so tough as a bitch.
All right, girls, come on.
That's enough.
Bring me my first mate.
Okay.
I love money.
Oh.
Ahoy.
Uh, hi, sir, ma'am.
Ahoy there, mate.
Yeah.
Come.
Okay.
Hmm. Let's see. What have we got in here?
Seems like we might have a lot of semen.
Well, um...
I love semen.
Do you?
Yeah, I really do.
I think that, uh...
Oh. I should take a closer look at this.
Hmm. Oh, yeah. It appears...
It appears to be quite a submarine.
Yeah. I don't know about a...
But first, you need to drop anchor.
Well, if that's the case, we've all been told to
avoid buoys, but...
have some oil right here hidden behind this cushion
Aye aye, Captain.
Oh my god.
I didn't know submarines grew.
Well, if you play with them right, I guess, right?
Good, yeah. They are quite buoyant.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Especially in water.
Flotation devices.
I'll never drown.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, cover them.
Fuck, yeah.
You guys feel much better now?
I love this.
Oh, yes. Drop anchor.
Whoa! Holy
Holy fuck, we have a big one.
Oh shit.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And a fucking death ramp.
Where are you going fast?
Oh, we're going to need a bigger boat.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, goddammit.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yeah, I love how you do that.
Mm, oh, you're fucking slipping out all my money.
Mm, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, God, yeah, yeah.
Fuck, it feels so good.
Yes, I love it when it fucking feels so good, pussy.
Mm, mm, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah.
Fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, good, fuck, yes, yes, take it, take it, take it,
take it, take it, yes, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Would you fucking take me, would you fucking take me?
Yes, yes, oh, God, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, God damn it.
Yes, you used me like that.
Fuck, yeah, there they are.
I'm fucking...
Oh, fuck!
Give me that fucking oil.
Yeah.
Have a minute.
Fuck you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
look at that huge
fucking cock
yeah you're gonna
Just wave, look at that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh god, that's good.
Oh fuck, that's so good, my asshole.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh god, yes, yes, yes.
Mm, fuck, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, mm, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck,
Fuck, fuck, fuck, ah, ah, ah, it's so fucking good.
It's so fucking good.
Yeah, I wanna fucking, yeah, do it.
I don't want you to go wherever you want,
inside that fucking house, inside that fucking pussy,
straight from that house to my mouth.
You don't have to worry about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, wherever you want me.
Oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, ah, ah, ah, ah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, let me fucking come on that dick dick.
Fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck, fuck, yeah, yeah.
Let me taste it straight from my ass.
Fuck, yes.
No, my ass.
oh my god yes yes yes
yes oh it's so fucking good
I don't fucking cum with your cock in my asshole like that.
Yeah, I don't fucking cum like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, play with that little pussy.
Yeah, yeah, ha, ha, ha, yeah, put that cock back in my pussy.
Yeah, put it in my fucking pussy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, I love the way you use all of my fucking holes.
Yes, yes, yes, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, ha, oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'll put it back in that asshole, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, oh, God damn it, yes, yes, yes.
Ha, ha, ha, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's fucking good, oh, that's fucking good.
You don't like that tight asshole wrapped around that cock?
Yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, ha, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes.
What oh god your cock is so fucking good
Yeah, yeah do it do it do it take it take that little asshole
Yeah. Fuck yeah. Get your grip, sailor.
Fucking sealings.
Yeah. Oh, fuck. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh my god.
of going in and out of that, holy shit, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, keep me there, oh fuck, oh god, yes, yes, yes.
I love the motion of your ocean.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, fuck my tits.
Oh, no.
Yeah, you want that little piece of you, yeah?
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, good, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
oh my god you're so naughty cool very
Oh, very naughty call.
Mm, mm, fuck, yeah.
Mm, my god, your content's so good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, mm, fuck, yeah, yeah.
Even without the semen, the ship still functions, you know?
It's fucking great.
That ship never sinks.
Mm, mm, mm, fuck, mm, mm, oh, that's a lot of semen.
Mm, fuck.
Yes, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
I want you to fuck those big tits.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, so impressive.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
That's so fucking good.
I love it when you fuck those tits and come out of the room.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Cut! That was beautiful, guys.
Where's my phone? Can I pick up some water already?
Somebody get her some water.
I mean, I guess my phone's not really a priority.
That's what I'm talking about. No wonder down under.
That was a good day.
Such a good day.
The life, the life, the life.
Just throw it, just throw it, just throw it, just throw it.
Woo!
Yeah, we had a perfect day.
Well, I mean, it was great.
Took you like a champ, like a champ.
If I could have changed just one little thing,
I would have liked to have rode the jet pack.
Xander, definitely next time.
We got you covered.
No, it's cool.
Definitely have to try it.
Yeah, but it's a jetpack.
Guys, guys, guys, I just got a really important message. Hold on, hold on.
Who is it?
Oh, shit.
Look.
It's the prince that didn't give us money.
Shh.
Okay, let's see, let's see.
Oh my god.
What the hell is that?
Look.
Charlie, where you going?
No!
No what?
What?
Where's he going?
Ricky!
Walk the empty beach in the sun Watch the tide roll in