The film school...
Today, at least this week...
Oh no, I can't deal with these Americans anymore.
I'll see you at the office.
I've had it up to here with these Americans.
What are you doing? You have a photoshoot today?
Oh, I have to check my schedule.
Your schedule?
been on the payroll for 15 years.
Oui?
Ah mais non!
On ne peut plus attendre!
Qu'est-ce que tu racontes?
Non!
Je quitte!
I need my phone.
Asshole.
So, Tommy, I've been having trouble finding the contracts.
We've been moving stuff around, so they may have been misplaced.
Oh, no worries. We'll look together.
You look lovely, by the way.
Oh, thank you.
You doing okay?
You seem a little off. Are you a little frustrated?
Uh, I'm just a little bit overwhelmed.
Well, completely out of it would be more accurate.
Okay, um, so let's go have a seat then.
Okay.
Would you like a water?
A vodka soda would be amazing.
If there's any vodka in this house.
No, because Francois believes there's gluten in it.
Oh, a Diet Coke then? Unless there's gluten in that too?
That I could do. Coming up.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I was just thinking about when you would order those vodka sodas.
You ordered so many during the New Year's Eve party our freshman year.
I love vodka sodas. I drink them all the time.
I always make sure my manager...
Whoa, wait. Joint? Manager? Who are you and what did you do with Joss?
Are you happy with how things turned out where you ended up?
I guess I did, too.
You know, I always thought I'd be an actress.
But who knows what I'd be missing out on here
if I'd gone down that route.
You could have done it.
I think out of everybody in our group,
I really felt you were the one that could have done it.
I mean, yeah, sure, everyone picked their safer thing,
the manager right before you left you said you're gonna remember my face
It was so cool.
Do you remember why I never ended up going to LA?
Um, yeah. It was Francois.
I mean, you and I planned on going to LA after we graduated.
and I mean we were gonna go out there together and but things were you and
Francois got more serious and right when your student loan was approved he
All three of us.
No.
His business started to get bigger
and he wouldn't have budged.
You know, honestly, I'm surprised
you don't remember any of this.
You and him almost split up because of it.
Oh, I see.
Hey, the last time you saw me,
did I seem happy?
Until this morning, I was living a completely different life.
was woken up by an intruder I went out to confront them and
it seems like I never really found my calling yeah you and I both I always
so afraid of losing you or having a chance or something with you.
Um, you know what? I shouldn't have said that.
What are you talking about?
From the day I met you, I knew you were different.
I always had a little crush on you when we were working together.
do it again we both could ah come on that's crazy
crazy. Your house is here, Francois. Your whole life is here.
keeping me in this town. Just like all those years ago.
if you went out there but I'm pretty sure my time I missed my chance Joss
Is there anything? Just tell me. Just say it.
I feel so familiar.
I got it.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, God.
I don't think anyone's worshipped me like this.
How did you know?
You've talked about it.
Of course I have.
after you had one or two many
so weird like i feel like i've known you for so long even though
Technically, I just think it's so weird.
I feel really good with you.
What if what you said changes?
What do you mean?
Say if one morning you wake up and someone else is there.
I would never make that decision again.
I want to see where this leads, you and I.
Like it was supposed to be.
This feels so right.
Oh
Hmm
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh my God, I'm sweating.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Sorry.
Oh my god.
Do you like that?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I can't wait to go on your body.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Ready?
Okay.
Yeah.
Mmm
Yeah
Oh, wow
You're a messy one aren't you?
Well, I haven't played with one of these for a while.
I have a Dolph Rhoad headlight on the left.
So it's fun.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
Are you putting it all in your mouth?
Are you trying to put it all in your mouth?
I'm trying.
Let me help.
Oh.
You stayed in for a second.
Oh my god it's so deep like that.
It's incredible.
Oh my god.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck.
You're feeling it.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes, please.
You're right.
Don't!
Yes!
Oh, my God.
Yeah, oh, my God.
Oh
I don't know, it's always weird.
I know it's gonna take forever to pack all this stuff.
Nope.
I'm only taking the essentials.
I'll put this in the closet.
Thank you.
Ah!