My name is Dr. White.
We have an appointment.
I see that you're here.
Physical exam.
Is that correct?
I have your file right here.
Today's date.
Prescription medications.
Describe your diet.
It's chocolate
Rehational drug use
Sexual activity
Any STDs
When was the last time you were tested?
We can resolve that
Any questions for me?
Oh, absolutely. Your wife is welcome to stay during your examination.
Okay.
Step over to the examination table in the hospital gown.
I'll give you some privacy.
I don't know why if I see
Would you mind?
You're very muscular
given your less than perfect diet
Everything looks great
your skin signs are normal
now I'm going to just relax and breathe
that your body reacts when I touch it
I need to do a taste test
nice and wet
I don't know.
he seems to enjoy this technique
technique
oh really?
I do
I think it's time
there's no need
see I told you
just take a deep breath
So easy
It feels great
See
It doesn't hurt at all
It actually feels
That was it
Your prostate exam done
But you'd like more wouldn't you
Your body's scared at first
But we have a need to do today
So you better
Before it feels good
Tease it against my clip
but I want it inside me
it feels so good
it feels so good when it's deep
against your chest
to see them bouncing
cock is deep inside
it's so good
now you feel the grind?
push myself all the way down
you can grind that clean
it's really, really lucky
lay me down
and fuck me
I like that sound
that's so good
yeah
you
oh fuck
inside me
you
oh fuck
you feel incredible
it looks so
good guys
I love to see like that
I feel like your cock's stroked inside
Is that pussy jerking off your cock?
Squeezing tight around your shaft
I love when your balls steam like that
Yes, I want you to use my pussy
Oh good, yes
just stroke your shaft inside it
yeah
oh I feel you getting hotter
you're getting closer on you
every stroke
yes
don't stop
I need to test your comb too
I need that semen
That's fine
Yes
I want you to use that pussy
until you cum all over it
Yes, chuck that cock off inside me
You're so deep inside that pussy
Yes, yes, yes
I'm going to make you feel full up
I look so good guys
Oh fuck yeah
Oh my god you're going to be so fucking close to complete that
Yeah, yeah
Oh god you're going to make me go
Oh my god, f**k
Yes, please, please
Oh f**k
Oh yeah, I want that
I feel you're so close
to my pussy clenching down on that cock and she glues
do you feel me coming like that?
yeah
fuck you
fuck
like that
yeah
oh that's so fucking hot
my god it feels so good
it's so warm on my pussy
oh my god
look at all that cum
oh yeah
so virile
let me do the taste test
oh wow
you are a
it's your physical examination
next week
to give you your results
you need to schedule
a