the mere sight of me is making a cock throb with fucking blood just up and
down you're pathetic hmm I want you to take out your cock
Up and down.
Now you wanna see my pussy?
It's just how the goddess likes it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Stop.
Give my pussy a second.
Just look at it.
Look at how beautiful this pussy is.
It's all mine.
good slave now lick that pussy again
yes yes right there right there
up and down up and down
yes
yes right there
fuck
yes the mistress loves it
yes you're such a good fucking whore
thank you mistress
Stick your finger in my pussy.
Just one.
Kiss the mistress.
Thank you.
Oh, yes.
Oh, that's my pussy.
All right.
That's it.
That's enough.
You can't touch it, but I can.
And I want you to fucking think about my pussy
every time you touch your cock.
My pussy owns your fucking cock.
No other pussies, just this one.
I'm getting my pussy wet for you.
Now I want you to just stroke your cock.
Stroke your cock while you look at this tight little pussy.
Stroke it, stroke it harder.
you get right to the edge but then I don't let you come hmm just like I'm
want you to put your hand back on your cock and then the other one oh your
Your clock's too small for that, I forgot.
Okay, just one hand.
Now stroke it.
Stroke it slow, stroke it nice.
Let me see.
I'm gonna give you another view to look at.
This is just how the goddess likes it.
Stick your tongue in my ass.
Just like that.
Fuck.
Such a dirty little whore.
Love it.
You love to lick my fucking dirty asshole.
Yes, you do.
Yes, you do, you dirty little slut.
That's why I keep you around.
Because you're so good.
Up and down.
Long strokes, long strokes from my pussy
all the way up to my asshole.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Good little slave.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, it feels so good.
I'm training you so well,
you good little fucking bitch.
Oh, yes, more, more, more, more, more, more!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, good fucking slut.
Ah, eat my ass. Eat my ass like breakfast.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ah, fuck yes.
Oh, you dirty fucking whore.
Ah, yes, just there.
Right there. Right there.
How does it taste?
So good.
Mm-hmm.
Nice and clean with your tongue.
Right there, right there, right there, right there.
Oh, it's so good.
You know what? You're good for one fucking thing and that's eating ass.
You are so good at that.
Oh, yes.
Let me ride your face with my asshole.
Yeah, that's so good
You like when I smother your face with my ass
Right there, right there, right there
You can't even fucking breathe
My ass is giving you fucking life
And that's just how you like it
That's why you're my favorite
Thank you, mistress
Now get on your back
So I can sit on your face
Right there
Like a good little boy
With your balls all fucking stretched
In my humbler
Look how hard that makes your cock
All fucking hard
When you can't even touch me
Your dick can't even get close to my pussy
But it's all fucking
Filled with blood
Spit on fucking cocks like that
But you love it
Now I get to ride your face
That's what you were made for.
Oh, fuck.
You're gonna make me fucking cum on your face.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Suck on those pussy lips.
Suck on them.
Good boy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah, now fucking just ride your fucking face right there.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my life.
Oh fuck.
Oh, lick that fucking tight pussy.
Lick it, lick it, lick it.
Oh, yes.
Oh, good boy.
Good boy.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Just like that.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you made the goddess come like a good slave.
Are you ready to come?
It's not your turn yet.
Oh, please.
No, no.
I need to cum a few more times before it's your turn.
If I give you a turn.
So just keeping a good little boy for me.
And making my pussy and ass cum.
And then maybe, just maybe, I'll touch your cock.
push that fucking cock through the hole
You're welcome.
Let's tie those balls out of the way so I can use that dick.
Like when I fucking stroke this cock.
Thank you.
Get it nice and wet.
Fucking stroke that cock.
I want to take you to the fucking edge,
but you can't come quite yet.
Up and down, up and down your fucking cock.
Do you wish you could see this?
Oh, yes.
Oh, it looks pretty nice.
Look how fucking hard your cock gets with my thumb in your asshole.
Look at that pre-cum fucking just dripping off your fucking cock.
I got you pretty close, but I'm not going to let you come yet.
I'm going to let you almost taste my pussy, but not quite.
So I could feel the heat from my pussy.
Come on, fucking take your ass off.
Oh yes.
Oh, fuck.
Take it, take it, take it.
Oh, look at the fucking hot cum.
It just wants the fucking cum.
Yes, yes.
Oh, but that's all you get.
Oh yeah, I'm gonna fucking stroke your face.
Oh yes, I'm gonna fucking take it.
I want you to fucking cum. Not quite yet, but I want you to fucking get
so filled with cum. Make these balls so full with cum.
Oh you fucking lag.
I'm gonna fucking make you cum.
I'm not quite yet.
This fucking cock in this asshole's mind.
Oh, yes, you fucking love it.
You fucking love it.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Fucking dirty cock.
Oh, this fucking cock.
Oh, yes.
I'd like to have both my fucking hands around it.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fucking stroking your cock with both of my hands.
Look at those fucking red balls.
Oh, so fucking red.
Take that fucking cock.
Fucking milk your fucking fat cock.
Oh, yes.
You want to come yes, please
Oh
Fucking
Look at that, look at your fucking pre-cum dripping,
look at it, fuck, oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Look at this fucking dog.
Please, please, please.
You just gotta tease your little balls with them,
they're so fucking red with blood filled with them.
I'm so
My life for massaging this fucking hard cock.
It's hard just for my hands.
Oh, it's so fucking hard.
This is my mistress fucking cock.
Whose cock is this?
This is, this is my god, it's this cock.
Yes, you're fucking right, it's my cock.
My cock is for my own pleasure and enjoyment and amusement.
Oh, yes.
I'm going to get it fucking wet.
Fucking jerk, you little cock.
Oh, fucking dickhead.
Oh, yes.
just tease it
just tease that fucking cock
just softly tease that
fucking cock
may it go faster
and harder and longer
yes please
I think I'd rather just tease it
up and down
fucking hard cock
is that what you fucking want
is this what you fucking want
this is what I fucking like
thank you
Oh, yes.
Oh, come over.
I fucking love watching the cum drip out of your fucking cock.
Oh, yes.
I like to fucking milk it out.
You see that drip right down.
All right.
Down.
Not that fucking cock.
Look at all this cum that you gave just for me.
Fucking dirty asshole of yours.
Look at it drop into that fucking asshole.
Oh, fucking take it down your ass right there.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it's going all the way.
You're a good boy
I want you to stroke your cock
And imagine you could put it in between my ass
Just imagine you could put it right here
And you're gonna get so fucking hard for my ass
Oh, I love it
up and down up and down up and down up and down just like that yes goddess
cock now go up and down but in a circular motion feel that twist on your
Just look.
Look at my body going up and down.
Oh, I know you wish you could have my pussy,
but I'll just have you come here every day
to see me and tell you exactly how to play.
Tell me how much you love
those fucking sweaty smelling sheets.
I fucking love these sweaty smelling sheets.
Yes. Good boy.
I'll be fair to the other one.
Goddess Blair just loves when you
fucking rub your face all over my dirty feet.
Good boy.
Now, take off my stockings.
I love when you
Can you fucking worship my body?
Dirty fucking feet, walking around all day, all over the fucking street.
Yes, you love him, you love him.
Lick the bottom of him, lick him, lick that dirty fucking soul.
Oh, good boy.
Ah, it feels so good.
Oh, so good.
Ah, yes, right in between those toes.
Oh, yes, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it.
Ah, you dirty fucking whore.
I love it.
Mmm, suck those toes.
Oh, yes.
Mmm, another one.
Mmm, good boy.
Oh, yes, yes.
Right in between them.
Oh, that feels so good, like licking my nice little pussy.
Oh, it's so nice.
Right in between.
Oh, suck on those toes.
Suck on that big toe.
Oh, yes, each one.
Oh, yes.
Right there.
Let's see, can you do both?
Can you put both in your mouth?
Let's see both big toes.
You're not gonna let it yell at you.
Not again.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I'm gonna pull this fucking cock
in these balls with my feet.
You like that?
Does it hurt you?
Oh, I fucking love it.
I own this cock.
I own it.
Even my fucking dirty feet own your little cock
in the cage.
it's filling the cage
put my foot back in your mouth
where it's supposed to be
yes just like that
oh yes
you fucking take it down well
oh
oh yes yes
suck that foot
oh
you're so fucking dirty
now the other one
Oh, yes.
I love when you fucking gag on my feet.
Let me spit in your mouth.
You good little slave.
How do they taste?
Oh, so good.
I love the control I have over you
with just the little bottoms of my feet
oh fuck the control over you
when I smack you to my fucking feet
you fucking good little slave
oh yes
you fucking good little boy
you're so good like him
Ah, yes, ah, suck it one more time, ah, good boy.
I'm gonna lick the bottom of my soles.
I'll lick those fucking dirty feet, ah, yes,
from your face all over them, ah, mm.
Ah, you're so fucking good at that.
You little fucking slut.
You look so pathetic, but I love it.
Now lick my ass.
Lick my ass and my feet.
Good fucking boy.
Suffocate on that fucking ass.
Suffocate on that ass.
Give it all to me.
Until your fucking last breath,
I want you to fucking lick my ass until you can't hold your breath anymore
Good boy
Uh-huh
Yes
Right there
Let me see
Take my fucking little dirty asshole too
Lick it clean, lick it clean, yes
with that dirty fucking hole clean yes oh it's so deep into my
fucking tight dirty asshole oh you're such a good slave
Wave nice and slow.
Uh-huh.
Back to my feet, back to my feet, back to my feet.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Uh-huh.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, yes, look from my feet to my asshole, yes.
Uh-huh.
Oh, so clean.
Mm, make your tongue all fucking dirty.
Yes.
Oh, so pathetic.
Oh, yes.
Does this look at your dick hard?
Oh, yeah.
You're making my pussy so wet just licking my asshole.
Oh, yes.
Oh, the mistress takes lots of pleasure in this.
Oh, fuck.
Suck my toes again.
Just like that.
Those two big toes fit them both in your fucking whore mouth.
Yes.
Do you know what your sole purpose in life is?
What, mistress?
To fucking lick this goddess clean.
And you do a real good job at it.
Thank you.
Keep going.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck.
right down your fucking whore throat
yes you're gonna fucking gag on my feet
take my foot like you're my fucking
nipples on it
yes I fucking love it
oh you're such a good little
slave good
fucking slave
look in between my toes
like right there
right in between my toes
yeah my fucking
good look
owie
Ah, fuck yes, I'm gonna dip him back in your mouth.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, you fucking take it.
Take both of his fucking toes, yes,
both of his feet right in your mouth as well.
Oh, oh, let you fucking suck on him.
Yes, good boy, good fucking boy.
Yes, yes, yes, you take it so fucking deep.
I love it.
Open your mouth.
Good boy.
You're such a good sleeper.
I like the way that tastes.
Awesome.
I don't know what I want to do with you now.
Let me think about this.
I have your cock in a cage because you're my little cuck hold I can do
Ready, maybe we can fucking stretch that out.
All right, let me see.
Oh, so deep.
I'm gonna take it out.
I'm gonna stick it in my mouth.
You like it like that?
Yes, mistress.
Fucking take my fat dick, tight with a glass.
I want you to fucking think about me
after you sit down this week
you sore little fucking asshole
yes goddess
what goddess?
Blair, fucking say my name right
yes goddess, Blair
good boy
take it in
fucking in your deep little ass
take it
you hard, getting hard from this fucking cock deep in your ass?
Yes, Ms. Blair.
You little little slut.
Oh, yes, you love it.
Take that big fat blue cock.
Give it to me.
Give me your fucking tight asshole.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Stop! You're enjoying this too much. What did I tell you?
You're not fucking me back right now. I'm fucking you.
I'm sorry.
Good.
I love it. I love taking your asshole from you.
Taking it because it's my little asshole. It's not your asshole.
It's my fucking asshole. It's my anal toy.
Yes, Miss Player.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
Oh, yes. Take it. Take it.
Take it.
Oh, fuck.
Let's take it deep, deep, deep in that fucking child's asshole.
Oh, I can feel it fucking stretching open from here.
I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it, I can feel it!
I like it.
I'm gonna be nice and keep it wet.
Tricky, tricky, tricky.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fucking tricky, tricky, tricky.
It's gonna be a fucking tough kick in your ass.
Oh
Now get on your back so I can fucking take your ass again
Look at that cock in the cage
Poor pathetic little thing
the goddess takes pleasure from fucking taking your little hole
You like to watch your eyes like fucking take your ass away.
Fucking give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me.
Give it to me.
Oh, stop.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, stop.
give it to me
yes yes yes
yes yes
look look
look
Oh, yeah.
Oh, the cousins.
Oh.
I'm going to put it back here.
It's just a little fucking hole.
Do you want to put it right here?
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Right just on the head.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, yes.
Take it, take it, take it.
Oh.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Look at this little fucking cage stick.
Oh
Now get on your fucking knees
Get on your fucking knees and doggy for me
Your ass open and ready. I'm waiting
Good fucking boy, good boy.
I'm gonna slap you with this cock just like you like it.
Just like you like it.
Oh, take this big fat cock in your ass.
Oh, yes, deep.
Oh, fuck it, take it, take it, take it, take it.
Oh, mm, I like to watch it slide
and then how does your cock just, oh.
Oh, mm.
Yes, you love me.
Oh, you just love the fucking quick control of your ass.
It's going to make you come fucking over and over again.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, back inside that tight little hole.
Oh, it goes so deep.
Oh
Slips right out of that loose asshole
Right
I'm taking a run, taking my big back, and coming around.
Fucking scratch my back.
I'm taking a horse.
I'm so deep.
Oh, fuck, oh, fuck.
Let's fucking take it, take it, take it, take it.
Oh, my God.
Kiss. Yes, Miss. Kiss.
Fucking gape for me. Fucking gape that asshole for me.
Let me see it. Oh, wow.
Right into your hole.
Wow, that's a fucking loose asshole.
Oh, look at this little pussy.
I know you want it, I know you want it, I know you want it.
Now grab your fucking cock.
Yes, just like that.
All right, now I want you to grind it up fast.
I want you to just fucking jerk it so fast, so fast,
so fast, so fast.
Now stop and just look at my nice tits.
Look at these tits.
just the sight of him is making you drip with pre-cum
amusing
it clean while you're licking your come think of licking this little sweet
and come back every day wanting more, more and more and more.