Thank you and rolling action
Angela
Your breasts have moved mountains and fed villages
So much more than I ever could have tried
Like
No, it wasn't you it wasn't your delivery it's just the script is really I don't really
Well, I mean, this isn't really what Bang Bros is known for.
Not normally, no.
Why?
What is the change of?
What happened?
They brought in some new, like, hot shot Hollywood producer, Colin something, to Bang Bros and,
you know, they're so worried about trying to stay relevant, so they're trying this new
script, you know, these, like, feature style.
You know what?
That's stupid.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but if it works, why change it?
Why change it?
I didn't write it.
The language is really, I don't know how, if you want to say relevant, maybe using the
word bosom isn't.
Wow.
This just gets worse.
Holy shnankies.
Why am I wearing this if they want some Shakespearean stuff?
Oh, no, that doesn't look so sexy.
Yeah, but it doesn't make sense.
This is like a slutty porno outfit.
It's not.
Well, it's the juxtaposition that they're going for.
The slutty porno outfit with the.
The contrast.
with this I mean so what who wrote this what's his name his name is Colin Colin
he's the new you know guy the new in-house producer for bang bros and so
they're now we're doing scripts every scene yeah I thought you were pretty
good at it man I thought you're pretty good yeah because I am a good actor and
she's a good actress so I think it's better to call me an actor though like I
I think that that's more gender neutral.
I think like actress, I don't know.
Whatever.
I don't know.
You guys, I mean, it's not like you're winning awards for your acting.
This is porn.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
What is the PA?
Do you need these, sir?
Here.
Oh, shit.
Those are your porn acting awards.
What was the last comment you made?
Never mind.
Those are lovely.
Here, take these back.
Yes, sir.
Appreciate it.
Who is that?
Okay.
It doesn't matter.
Angela?
Did I say something?
No, no, it's fine.
I mean, it's okay.
We don't work hard in this industry.
It's fine.
Our job doesn't matter, right?
Well, look, we're trying to change.
We're trying to adapt.
It's adapt or die, you know?
It's no, no, it's not.
There's all these clips.
All the girls have their Lonely Fans accounts.
They're flaking on shoots because they're making their own money.
Well, yeah, we can make more money on Lonely Fans.
Well, at least you showed up today, so I thank you for that.
What?
Do you know who this is?
show up and I always turn up nice so listen I do usually like to see the
script before I turn up on set especially something I did sorry I kind
of ambushed he just wrote it this morning so I don't know we know when
you just write those scripts come on come on listen i got into this industry
to you know this this is not the first time i've worked up a bang for script oh
colin it was you saw it i didn't do it oh and look wait wait wait this is gonna be my first
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
does. Yes. Titties, ass, fucking anal. Titties and ass. Piledriver, cream pies. Titties and
ass. Titties and ass. Titties and ass. Can we start or are we dancing? Okay, okay. I
have an idea. I have an idea. Okay. Ready? I'll be the director because I am. Motorboat
her action. That's really, that's unique. It's original. It's different. All right.
What should I do just you should receive the motorboating? I'm ready to receive. Should I take it today? Yes
I mean you didn't you didn't really tease the nipples in this outfit that will come
Wait a second. This is bang, bro. She has to like show all this off
Again they're trying to switch it up, but this is this if it works it look this is the hook for the trailer
Yeah, right. They need this. They need my tits bouncing. They need my house bouncing
saying they need the reveal ready oh please it's not even possible
yeah some of that a little bit of us oh hold on yeah yeah there it is now i see all right all
right tell me us jiggling come on can you do a little more self-ass jiggling tommy's flying in
tommy's flying in oh that's great yeah okay all right tommy it's time to shine yeah no i mean
oh oh yeah yeah shake it shake it when they said to adapt you gotta like arch it more arch it
really arch it oh that really hurts yeah you're telling me you're just bouncing yours how do you
how do you twerk it i mean how do you do that what do you mean like the the little yeah how
teach tom you gotta teach him that's just muscle control i have no idea like i don't know i just
do it i'm like move that butt cheek move i just my brain tells my butt to do things maybe you
You could motorboat her ass.
I think I would love to motorboat her ass.
Yeah, you gotta move those heels out of the way.
You gotta like, yeah.
So can you take the heels off or no?
Do they stay on?
They should stay on.
Okay, they stay on.
Excuse me.
I wanted to step on my feet.
I put this outfit on for a reason.
You're right, keep the heels on.
I can take it off, take them off soon.
Are you gonna put the heel on Tommy's butt?
I mean, it's a bit.
Sand down that heel for a second.
Yeah, yeah, it's a little.
Bring your ass out.
Okay.
Oh yeah. Oh fuck that feels good.
Tongue inside my asshole.
That's all the script needed to say is...
Tongue inside your asshole.
Do you like air in your ass? Do you like making noises from your butt?
I mean we could, no I see the director shaking his head, no we don't.
I mean you can make noises, he can make noises.
No, we don't, we don't, we don't, we don't, we don't do that, no.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yep, dude.
Tongue in the two hole, finger in the one hole.
Two fingers in the one hole or the two hole?
Oh, my God, so much going on.
Wow, there's a lot going on.
Fuck, yeah.
We could get that other guy back for the three hole.
That sounds so fucking hot, too.
My only complaint is that I can't see you, though.
Oh, yes, yes.
I like to look into your eyes as you bury your face in my asshole.
That's what I like.
I appreciate that.
I appreciate you.
Oh, fuck.
This is definitely staying relevant.
Yeah.
Look at that.
She has three holes.
Oh, three.
Show me the third one.
Her pee hole?
Oh, that's where that is.
That hole in her butthole?
My urethra.
Which one's the urethra?
Yeah.
That's it.
Right there.
Oh, a butthole.
It's like her second clit, kind of.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
Interesting.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's pretty, too.
It's cool.
She's pretty, though.
I like it.
Is it?
Yeah.
Is that shirt exactly?
Mm-hmm.
You've done this before, Tommy?
I hope so.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuck, he's really good at it, oh my god, yeah, fuck, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, fuck, yeah, yeah, brush your fucking teeth with it, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah,
Pussy lips. You grab that whole thing. Yeah, grab it.
Oh, fuck.
That's fat. I like it.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, like that.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, yes.
Fuck.
Two-hole it. Two-hole it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stroke my clit like that. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're not paying for DP, by the way.
I know, I know.
Oh, it's so fucking slippery.
Slippery, slippery, slippery, fucking so fucking slippery.
You want a handy?
Here, here, here.
Put your face in it when I...
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I don't fucking cum like that.
Holy shit.
Here, here, here.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, fuck, oh my god, oh my god, yeah, oh fuck, oh fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Oh my god, oh
That's so fucking pretty with that pussy pop
Oh my god
That one was wrong, you didn't know
You didn't know
You're so f***ing cute
You're so f***ing hot
I don't know what you f***ing do to me
You gotta get your cock out because I want to take these shoes off already
so I need to step on your fucking balls and fuck right now.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Mmm.
Oh, my fucking God.
Yeah.
Fuck these socks.
Buy socks.
We don't need socks.
Fuck those socks.
Oh, fuck.
Come this way a little bit, because then I can sit and play.
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
Fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Where are those fucking balls?
Right there.
Oh, my God.
Oh, this is what's this is this is adapting. This is called stay relevant. This is Hamlet.
Do your lines now. Do your fucking lines now.
Oh
Yes, oh yeah, that's the new one
Need to pull that full skin up
Fuck yeah, it's fucking hot.
Oh, spit on that fucking, yes.
Oh, let's pull it all the way up.
We don't want to hurt your dick.
Not yet, not yet.
We do that with my teeth later.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh.
I want to rip your foreskin all the way off.
Oh, yeah, spit on that.
Let's get that good spit.
Yeah, let's get that good spit.
Oh, I need to work some more.
I want to fuck every inch of your body, like the back of your fucking...
I want that.
I'm not coming.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm not coming there.
I want some of yours.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my fucking God.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
I'll let you do it.
You can hurt yourself on those fucking heels.
yeah yeah like that kick you in the fucking balls at the same time
oh lord yes
fuck fuck fuck let's make it all pretty too oh you're too good to me
you got a little crown look at that look at that so pretty yeah i'm gonna jerk you also
Let's get that foreskin up.
Fuck.
You fucking styled it.
Up there.
Look at that cock style.
Oh, dude.
Oh.
Ooh.
Oh, my God.
Diamonds are a cock's best friend.
Oh, I feel so fancy.
You are fancy.
Look at you.
I think I should use my mouth a little bit.
just a little bit okay just a time not too much not too much it is bang bro
cost extra you don't have the budget to juice or not I'm gonna take these off
and you can play with them yep here you can have this you can yay sniff my
My fucking feet.
Oh, a lot of people are going to be angry.
I don't want this to sink them.
Oh my God.
Sniffed your own?
Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
I'm bad like that.
Oh, look at all that fucking pre-cum.
I love when you fucking pre-cum.
You know what I really want to do?
Let's play with this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Relevant
Docking
Well, actually technically ducking should be with another penis, but I don't have one
Ow, what are you doing?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Can you put the balls in a hole?
Let me see.
Oh!
These balls want to slip out.
They want to fucking slip out.
Let me grab these balls.
Let me fucking grab them, they're mine, they're my balls, look at that little brain, this is the brain that you really think with, isn't it, this is the important brain, this is the important one, you need this brain, you wouldn't be a man without this brain, no you wouldn't, it hurts a little bit, doesn't it, it hurts a little bit, I kiss it better, thank you.
Are you okay dude?
Yeah, that felt so good.
I can't explain.
Oh, show your teeth on those fucking brains.
Show me those nipples.
Yeah.
Want to see my titties?
Those are big fucking titties.
Yeah, actually they're not big at all.
But they're still beautiful.
All tits are beautiful.
Trying to get them hard for you.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh
Jeez we're losing focus. Let's get back
I'm not done with this dick, I'm not fucking done with this dick, I'm gonna fucking bite
it all up and down.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Yes.
I love this.
I'm so happy with you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
guy's back bro it's coming in my eye i'm just i'm so sorry
speaking of eyes oh you got such a tiny little pee hole oh i'm sorry don't be sorry i'll try
harder don't be oh there it is wait no there it was
oh and if you don't like whoever's watching this too fucking bad oh yeah oh yeah fuck that
Look at that pinky hole, yeah.
Look at that.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, this is how we do it.
This is how we stay fucking relevant.
Oh, fuck.
Fingering dicks.
Let me get my tongue in there.
Oh, fuck.
There we go, look, it's disappearing now.
Fuck.
Did your pre come out?
Yes, please.
Oh, my God.
You're shaking like a
horned church.
Uh-huh.
Oh, fuck. That's so fucking
good.
Oh, my God.
I want to fucking scratch your cock.
Scratch it.
Yeah, bad cock.
Yeah, bad cock. Bad, bad, bad, bad.
Bad boy.
Boy, make it dance for me.
I'll slap it while you make it dance.
Make it dance.
Oh, it likes to stay up there.
Oh, just slap it.
Just slap it, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck.
You can take it.
You can do it.
A little bit more, a little bit more, a little bit more, a little more.
Okay, let's give it a break.
Now the balls.
Oh, oh, fuck.
We got it.
Yeah, I got it.
Fuck, yes.
Fuck, come here, come here, come here.
Don't be scared.
Don't be scared. I'm talking to your balls. Where do they go? There we go. There they are. There they are find them
You know what? My hands are all slippery. Oh
I got one. There we go. There there
Yeah, I was scared. I shouldn't have told it though
Slap it. Oh
Oh my god
Ah fuck
It'll be worse when it's wet. Oh fuck she's right
So much worth when it's worth.
I'll tell you
whatever you want.
There's the tit.
Should we do some titty fucking or something?
We're not there yet.
It's already been 27 minutes.
Okay, take your time.
Be here all day.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, yes, just one day, just, oh, oh, oh my god, oh, chew, chew, chew, chew, chew,
Chew.
Ugh.
I'm going to find it all the way down.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah, she's chewing.
Yeah.
She's definitely chewing.
Ugh.
Fuck.
Fuck, man.
I guess they want us to fuck.
But I also want to fuck.
Yeah.
Ugh.
What do you want?
Oh, fuck.
I mean, I don't know.
I want it in my butt, but I know they have to get one vag, one vag, don't you?
That's for broadcast.
Hold on, can we, can we, yeah, let's get it back.
Oh, wow.
You like that?
Yeah.
Oh, Angela, I can see you.
Oh, there you are.
Hey.
Oh, that's really annoying.
Now I don't get to look at Tommy, now I have to look at you.
Yeah.
But it looks okay.
I'm not very happy about that.
Well, it's not about how you feel, it's about how you look.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Really?
That just looks awesome.
Look at that. Yeah.
You should lose your hair.
Ah, fuck this.
You booked Angela White.
That means... Angela
anal. All anal.
All the time.
I can't see it though. Well, you know, let me
get it in once. Okay. It's been...
Hang on, let me... Here.
Here.
Well, sorry, I just need.
Oh, there you go, yeah.
You gotta like warm it up.
From self-anal fingering.
Stretch it out.
Right, JT?
Self-anal fingering's always encouraged.
Yeah, he's good at that.
Wait, I'll go this way, okay?
So then you can see it go in,
because if they don't see it go in,
then it could have been like CGI or something.
Exactly.
Oh, I saw that one go in.
You saw it go in, right?
Let's show you again, ready?
Yep, pull it out.
There's the butthole.
Yep, and then show it go in.
And then, boop.
In.
See how it like pops in right there?
I saw the moment, yeah, it just goes in.
Look, I see it in your butthole.
Oh, she's okay.
Oh, I see side boob.
Oh, side boob.
Oh, you see side boob like that?
Yes.
Oh, holy fuck.
Oh my fuck.
Fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Are you doing an up and over or should I come over?
Oh, you're doing that?
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
I can see her in there.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, there she is.
Oh, my God.
Hi, Angela.
Hi.
Jizzy Jaws.
Let me get back to the house like that.
Oh my God.
All right, all right.
Can I try the kind where I'm above, dude?
And you're like down?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, man.
Can I try it from here?
Yeah.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you want me to scoot this way?
Yeah, scoot, scoot, scoot.
Yeah, it might make it easier.
Do you need JT to get some pillows for you?
No.
Yes.
Hi.
How you doing?
He's still with us
Yes
There it is, there it is, they're in.
You see that?
I think so.
I see something.
Oh yeah, that was cool.
How'd you do that? Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, wow.
Ball's in.
Oh, yeah.
And...
Oh.
Oh my god. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, he's going for the pussy first.
He's going for the pussy and the balls and the...
Oh, the DP.
Yeah.
My head's not even here and I just feel like I can't figure it out.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, my God.
You're being DP'd by one guy.
I had to try.
I hope that's okay.
Good try.
Oh, it feels so good.
Everything that you do.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Yes, please. I fucking love that. Oh my god
yeah, yeah, so good, so good, so good, so good, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, oh fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Oh
I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.
I feel my asses open up after they cry.
My fucking ass is open.
She doesn't even want to open her eyes.
Oh, man.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
I shove your nose in my pussy while you put your fucking tongue in my ass.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Nice. Fuck that hole. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Lie to me. Lie to me. Lie to me. Make that noise bigger.
Oh my god, this is advanced. Oh, yeah
Oh, that's a new one.
That is a new one.
Oh.
Yes.
Wow.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, okay.
Wherever you want.
Yeah, you can go back and forth.
That might be fun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm, fuck, yeah.
JT, I'm so glad we did those floor lights.
Oh.
Yeah.
And this is...
If this doesn't win awards, I don't know what will.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Fuck.
Oh.
Back of my pussy, back of my pussy.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah!
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Wow.
Fuck.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Best day of my life?
That's a lie.
The best day of your life is when I licked your asshole.
I want to smell your pits.
You don't see what she wants to smell.
Oh, I see.
A different type of scene today.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh
Squeeze this fucking ball
Yeah
My god
Oh, my God, yes.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god,
fuck, I don't think I'm going to be able to learn, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, there
you are, Angela, yeah, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, I'm going to fucking come like
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go, oh fuck, oh, oh, oh fuck, oh my god, yes, come here, come here, yes, come here, oh my god, fuck yeah, just a little bit, just a little bit, yes, oh fuck, yes,
Oh, yeah
Yeah, let me get him money me
Yeah, yeah make you fuck me with that big
Yeah, yeah got you by the ball
Yeah, yeah, fuck, that's good, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, shit, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, if you start slowing down, I'm going to squeeze those fucking balls harder.
Yeah, I fucking promise.
Oh, you sure about that?
You sure about that?
Oh, that's fucking tight.
Yeah, you keep going.
There you go.
A little release.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Make you fuck, man.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's so fucking juicy.
Look at that juicy ass.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I love that.
Oh my god. Oh, yeah, I've never seen that. Oh, oh my god
Fuck I don't think I've tasted that cup straight from my asshole either you get that fucking cup covered in my ass juices
I'm gonna fucking deep in there. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, slow down. Let me get inside there. Yeah. Yeah. No fucking controlling you.
Why do we need to?
You're a puppet master.
Does this count as double anal?
Do I get more?
Sure.
Oh, shit.
Slow down so I can get the second.
Slow down.
There we go.
Why are you putting two?
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is going to be a jib.
Ah.
Fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pull him in.
Pull him.
Use his...
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
That was the back of my earring.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm going to find that later.
Okay.
He wasn't expecting that.
No.
Oh, yeah.
Just a little bit.
Oh, my God.
You're going to fucking love this if you just give it a chance.
Just give it a chance.
Oh, he's fingering my ass, too.
Oh my god, what's good for the goose is good for the gander. Hold on. Oh
Oh fuck
Fuck
Yes, yes, that's epic. Oh so good. Oh
Yes, look at that keep going Tommy putting work put in work
she's relentless she is relentless oh look at this oh my god oh angela angela look here this
is gonna be a gif this is gonna be a gif having hot flashes he's having hot flashes
wait let me bite your dick oh my god yes oh wait let me get under here
Let me see.
Fuck!
What is happening?
I hope they like this.
Who cares?
Angela likes it, that's what matters.
Yeah, that's what matters.
If Angela likes it, the fans like it.
Oh my God!
Fuck!
He likes it.
He likes it, yeah!
Yeah.
We don't need these.
Let's take this off.
This is like real serious girl business.
Here, his one.
JT, the awards guy, hands, hands.
Now I can get serious with that deep-throating.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh
Yeah
Finally do some titty fucking.
I've been waiting all day patiently.
All fucking day?
Yes, please.
All fucking day.
They told me if you don't get titty fucking, don't even bother turning in the footage.
Oh, my God.
So if you don't get titty fucking, you don't get paid.
Exactly.
Come here.
Bring your fucking dick to me.
Oh, you know what?
No, no, no.
Lay back.
I feel used.
You have been used.
Lay back here.
Bring it.
Bring it to me.
Put your butt up here.
Come on, baby
See then it makes it easy for us both
Yeah, he has leverage so I could not do anything if I want to seem like you can fuck but pop it through but also
So, I can do all the work so fucking easily because all I have to do is bounce.
This is genius.
This position is always weird.
You want my face?
Stylist.
Here we go.
Okay, there we go.
Look, no hands.
Oh my God.
Yeah, do that.
Do that.
Oh my God.
They're going to love that.
Yes.
Don't stop.
No hands.
It's a twister.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
yeah yes like that yeah it's just tall yeah let's go that hole's a little bit small i think it's a
little small but you know what we could oh you're just gonna force it no lube or anything fuck it
fuck my god dude you're white you're brave man brave he's brave it's gonna hurt but it's all
right oh yeah oh yeah just that bit just that bit oh yeah oh yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh we tried
That was good.
Oh, fuck.
Jesus Christ.
Genius.
Fucking genius.
Best way to titty fuck, right?
Yeah.
Really epic.
Your butt rubs all over me, too.
Oh, yeah.
If you had a titty.
Put it right in there.
Right in there.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck it.
Fuck it.
Who cares?
Fuck.
Oh my god!
Yeah, I need a fucking strap on right now
so I can fuck you like this.
Oh my god!
God damn, girl.
It feels so good for me just watching it feel
so good for you.
My pussy just gets so fucking wet
seeing you like that.
Just losing your fucking mind between these tits.
Fuck you.
You're making film history today.
So is he allowed to come like this?
Or is he allowed to fucking come all over my fucking tits like that?
He is allowed to come all over your tits, but first we still need you doggy style.
Well, I gotta fucking tick the boxes.
Oh yeah, we did that fun thing we did, remember?
We took some pictures earlier and you were doing some crazy stuff.
Yeah.
Gracious don't forget all the boxes. Oh
Wow, oh my god. Oh fuck. I don't know what to focus on it. Just there's so much going on
shake. Holy shit. Fuck, fuck, fuck. Yeah. Fuck, fuck, fuck. Fuck. Oh my God. Right down to the ear.
Oh, it's right in my pussy. That was great. Oh, right into the pussy. All right.
I'm going to give the pussy a little bit of love too. God damn. A little fucking love for my pussy.
Oh, I love it. Yes, please. Yes, ma'am. Oh, yes.
Fuck, fuck, yeah.
I'm gonna have those big fucking tits.
Ah, ah, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, fuck, yeah, I grind them.
Fuck.
Oh, just stroke the head.
Oh, fuck, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes.
Make me fucking come on that tree.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my legs.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
oh wow i see you inside snap i see you inside
all right oh yeah some water water some water bring me the water this is all part of the scene
this is all part of the scene yeah you know real people drink water yeah i'll hide the brand yes
hide the brand oh my god this is this is we we have made history yes 2020 is a new year
so maybe some dogging and a cum shot on the tits we'll go back to the basics for that
okay give the man a give the man a second
give the man a second give the dog give the chick a second yeah no what do you want to
talk about politics religion none of those none of those
ah fuck why don't you say the bang bang bang bus what was the question bang bus have you been
Have you been on the fucking bank every day? That's not true. I mean like
legit the original I've never bang but have you
Angela white has never been on the bank bus. I mean, I've fucked on plenty of buses
That your impersonation of an American
Yeah, do that thing yes do that thing
Oh, let's get rid of this hair. Yes. Yeah. Got it. Oh, yeah. Oh, fuck. It's real. Oh, it's real. It's really happening. It's really happening. Go back and forth. Back and forth. In my pussy and my butt. Yes, ma'am. Yes. Oh, fuck yeah. And then butt. And then pussy. Oh, yeah. Oh, my God. It's working. Pussy only. Oh, look at her ass. Oh, pop in and out. Oh, fuck. It's fucking magic.
Oh my god, it's so fucking deep, holy shit.
Oh yeah, rock that.
Oh, that's going to look good.
It's going to look good.
Look how he's stretching.
Bang bro.
Yeah.
Oh, you want me to hold it open?
One, two, snap.
You forgot the three.
One, two, three, snap.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Snapping.
I wish I could drink something out of that.
Yeah.
Thank you, get rid of that.
Hold on, you tried, but you failed.
Is it attached to her?
No, it's not.
I don't think so.
I think she would notice.
Yeah, it would hurt.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, sorry.
Don't be sorry.
Holy shit.
I'm gonna stick your toe, oh my god, sit back, no!
That was pretty cool.
I think I have become one with the couch, uh-huh.
She's become one with the couch?
Uh-huh, uh-huh, I am the couch.
Hey Tommy, what do you think about blowing a load?
Oh yeah, your balls are on my feet.
Fuck my feet.
Oh, can you call me feet and my face
What do you I don't know where I should go I want some here and then and tits and face
Fucking love calm on my feet so much like hard questions
I don't know, I don't know what's the best thing to do.
I think tits are great, feet are fine, and face is good.
Everyone's seen cum on my tits before, it's fine,
you don't have to do the same thing every time,
just give me what I want, I just want fucking cum
on my feet, is it so much to ask?
I will give that to you, by telling Tommy to give that to you.
Yeah, yeah, I want that fucking cum on my tits.
I feel that fucking hot jizz on my soles.
It's so fucking bad.
Yeah, yeah fucking give it to me that fucking word
Between my toes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Every last fucking drop
Yes
Yeah, oh my fucking feet
Oh
Oh my God.
Look at that.
You feel that?
Oh, fuck.
Do you know how fucking good it feels when the hot cum shoots on the soles of your feet?
My feet are so sensitive.
You have no fucking idea how good that feels.
I'm not fucking lying.
Great.
There's some on my tits, too, and on my, and on my body, right here.
there. Just taste it all. Loved it. Well, you can tell Cullen to go fuck himself. Well,
I'm going to get out of here. I'm going to go take a nap. Yeah. Right. I'll check. Yeah.
Yeah, great job everybody. Oh, yeah
Yes
Yes, it was really good. Yeah, I think throwing the script out was the right move
We think that way I mean the editor
There's no editing. I mean, it's just all it's at one hour of stuff. I don't think you should
touch
Yeah, please don't release it like this. It's exactly it's a masterpiece. Yeah
Yep.
Hey, thank you.
You're fuckin' amazing.
Oh.
This smells so good.
God.
Fuck.
All right, any final thoughts, Angela?
Oh yeah, did you save me a couple of pieces of that chocolate?
There is some chocolate left.
Good job.
Thank you.
Bye.