Charlie had spent the last year trying to prove that he didn't want love
or that love didn't exist.
And in the process, he'd hurt a lot of people, including himself.
But it was time for him to change that.
After thoroughly reviewing a few algorithms,
he realized that the best possible match for Elaine
was actually a pastor from a neighboring church.
church. He knew about Elaine's past with Jamie, and he loved her anyway.
other people find true love deserved to find it herself.
Do you have anything special planned?
Other than drinking a bottle of wine and watching bad rom-coms?
No. You?
I actually have dinner reservations.
Oh, how lovely! Who's the lucky girl?
Well, I thought it would be you.
Me?
but I never had courage to do so until now.
I... I don't think...
That's okay, I understand.
No, I was going to say, I don't think that was a question.
Hillary, would you?
Yes.
and turned out to be part of the 80% success rate.
I can't even remember the last time I brought somebody back to my place.
Well, then I consider myself lucky.
You kiss so well.
Me too.
I never thought we'd be doing this.
I like you.
I like you more.
Let me get you up.
It's been a while.
I can help you.
Help me?
I've always wondered what's under here.
Come on, this feels so good
You're so giving
Hmm
Yes.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Oh, fuck.
I love that you're so good at this.
I don't want you to do it like that
as you feel the throbbing heart in your mouth
and then you're talking
tease me first
Oh, my God.
Oh
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Suck.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yes, please.
I don't want to say it again.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
God, you feel so fucking gross.
Suck.
Mm, fuck.
Yes, please.
Please.
Oh
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh, yeah.
Shh.
You're so good.
You're amazing.
Happy Valentine's Day.
I told you a flower delivery business wasn't for you.
What are you talking about?
It's one o'clock.
The day's not even halfway done and you're already home.
Well, I had to deliver these.
Wow, this guy never misses a beat.
Birthday, New Year's Eve plans, Valentine's Day.
Why do you sound so annoyed?
Does that sound horrible?
No, not really.
I guess it just feels like he's just going through the motions.
I want somebody who does something because their heart's in it.
I left Kyle's bouquet in the car because...
Well, I hate that fucking prick.
You got me flowers?
Look, I've been awful the last few years.
And not just to the people at work, but to you.
Well, you were awful when we dated.
I wanted a chance.
What?
Look, I know you're a match with someone else.
but maybe we could be the non-match that somehow...
Still works out?
Yeah.
And when we were together, I was scared of everything.
But I'm not anymore.
And maybe it's too late to say this.
It's not.
I love you.
Finally, you fucking figured that out.
The moral to this story
is whether algorithms say you're a perfect match
or whether you don't seem like a match at all,
love will always find you when you're ready for it.
Happy Valentine's Day.