jump in go around the other side because that door's fucked
No, for this I can drive for free, you know. My books is like, no 50%
yeah this taxi could be quite expensive
um okay okay i think we can do it
oh my god i have just seen the mother load
tips have gone to my head
how about
you suck my dick
it was unexpected
you know
it was unexpected to have such a beautiful lady
in my car or my taxi
do you have a big cock
I don't know
I don't have a measuring
No, if you have a big cup, okay, I can suck it.
I think there's got to be one way to find that one out, isn't there?
So let's go find a nice little place, a nice place off the road,
and we can study that one, and I'll give you a whole taxi fare for free.
Okay, deal.
Wow, it's a very interesting day.
You're English is very good.
Yeah, I learned it in university and in school, so.
What was you studying, clock?
Sorry.
Sorry, no, what was you studying?
What I studied?
Yeah.
Economic international relationship.
We can make a nice little relations
in the back of my taxi, I'm saying.
Yeah, exactly.
It might get a little bit exciting as well.
Might get a bit steamy.
It seemed like a good gift from my parents.
You've got any sisters?
No, I'm alone.
You have your own child?
Yeah.
If I was your brother, it would be getting more special.
No, it's better that I don't have a brother.
Yeah, I know. I've been keeping you in the shower all the time.
It's not straight, it's completely not straight.
I'll be in the back there in a minute.
I will be testing them out.
Have you ever sucked dick before?
I'll just say, yeah, I've sucked but not a lot.
Do you like big dick?
Yeah, I like big dick.
because you're a guy yeah but some guys like it i definitely don't
let me just turn this off let me just jump in the back okay
My god! Have you seen these?
Hello, I'm Dave, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Josephine, can I just touch these for a minute?
You can try.
Oh, look at these.
Oh my god, fucking hell.
Can I just put my face between them?
yeah yeah oh oh you smell great oh god smash them in the face
oh they call that the motorboat
stand up come on come on sit on my lap sit on my lap baby
oh yeah look at these big knockers well what do you call them in ukraine
Now, you've done that before, haven't you?
Get them tits out as well.
Show me them tits.
Show me your boobs.
Show me these boobs.
Get them out.
You gotta watch them up and down.
Oh, put my cock between them.
Yeah, wait.
Yeah, go on.
Put it in there.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck it.
Yes.
You are lovely.
You too.
oh my god go back to sucking that dick please oh cock tits mouth
what's your favorite food what's your favorite food
food sausage yeah why not yeah
Two hands round it, two hands, yeah.
yeah show me more of that I love it when it's wet
Oh, I love it.
Lucky.
Help me take this off quickly.
Pull it right off.
Oh, come on.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my God, you're filth.
Fucking hell, man.
Oh, your eyes look amazing here.
Show me, show me, show me your tongue.
Show me your tongue.
Look at my eyes.
Do you fancy getting a little bit extra naughty?
Would you take them trousers off?
Show me the goods.
Oh my god.
I'm so excited to see something so beautiful.
Turn that round there and look at that.
How about you get on your knees here just a little bit.
oh yeah that was just come here baby put your head to the side
oh yeah it's so tight
oh my god
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yes.
Come on.
Is that good?
Yeah.
Wow.
So big.
Yeah.
Yes.
You said you got a big dick, didn't you?
Oh, yeah.
Are you good?
It's my first time
yeah oh yeah come and taste your pussy over here come and taste your pussy
man you're amazing i love ukraine never been there but amen
the gentleman should take a woman's shoes off shouldn't they
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Come on, make him clap.
Yeah, clap.
pyramid between your head
Oh yeah, look at that, look at that, look at that.
Yeah, I'm playing with them boobies, yeah.
So you do like big dick, don't you?
Yes, now for sure.
Oh, it's big enough for you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you're a lovely arse.
Oh, fuck.
you've got a really tight bottom as well look at that
that's very sexy
Yeah, go straight. There we go. Now go. There we go.
This is the best taxi ride you've ever had.
Yeah.
You're an animal.
You too.
oh yeah look at that go go for it go for it take this dick oh man a bum
Oh yeah, you do like big dick, don't you?
Yeah, come on, suck it.
There we go, wake it, wake it as well, yeah.
oh you're gonna make me come all over them tits yeah
oh yeah
the way, I need to swim.