I'm sorry it had to end this way, but you said you wanted to see my downside.
Don't worry, you're gonna love it.
You're coming with me.
I deserve this.
I'm gonna be my pay you back for all the joy you've given me.
You ready to be controlled by me?
Think you can handle it?
Then follow that ass.
You ready for me to do all sorts of nuts?
I'm gonna do bad things to you.
You're gonna fucking...
Fuck it.
Anything that I fucking want.
Oh, you want those tits already, huh?
Look what I found.
Look at this little bitch.
On a fucking leash.
He wants those tits.
Look at him.
Come, come get those fucking tits.
You want them or not?
You can't fucking have them.
What will you do for them, huh?
Anything?
Show me that top.
Stick it out all the way.
I really like having this power over this little bitch damn I get so excited
yeah you want these fucking tits yeah beg for them like a good little dog
oh my god
Oh my god.
Fucking smother you with these big natural tits.
Look at that.
Do you like that?
Do you like it?
Yes.
Put it right in your fucking mouth.
You want to suck as much in there as you can.
Yeah, I want you to fucking breathe.
Come here.
There's no fucking breathing for you.
Completely fucking smothered by those big titties.
I'll get you in the face with them.
Oh my god, please.
Oh my god.
What the fuck is this?
Fuck, get down with my fucking spit on your forehead.
Oh my god, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna fucking tie you up.
Look what I got up here.
Stand up.
Look against the door.
Oh my god, your cuck's so fucking hard, huh?
Oh, how the fuck did that happen?
I don't know, I guess you like being a little sub, bitch.
There we go.
Oh my god.
Try and get out, I want to make sure you're in.
Fuck.
Wait, this one, this one needs to be tied up.
Yeah.
You in?
Oh my god.
Damn.
Oh, I can't trickle.
Look at that fucking cuck.
Oh, I think you like it.
Oh, shit.
Look at that fucking cock.
He gets so hot being a little fucking bitch.
Fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Whose cock is that?
Is that mine?
That's your fucking cock.
That's right.
It's my fucking cock.
What are you going to do with my cock?
anything like shut you I'm gonna put this fucking doggy bone in his mouth
yeah I like having your fucking board every time
We put it in the wrong way, let's put it in the right way, I want you to be a pretty little
dog.
Oh wow.
Yes.
How's that?
Yeah?
Oh my god.
Yeah.
You look so fucking good.
Oh, we can go one tighter.
Oh.
You look fucking great.
Fantastic.
Oh.
Go straight inside.
Look at him squat.
Oh.
Jorgel's Jordan, big plump Jorgel. He's such a little fucking bitch.
I'm gonna cry here too.
I'm gonna tease that cock and balls.
Oh my god, I fucking love having you in this position.
Oh my god, even without touching your cock it stays so fucking hot.
Oh my god.
Oh
Should I bite it bite that fucking cup
I've got a whole bunch of other implements that I'm going to use on this body today.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, that was nice.
Oh, yeah.
What about these thighs?
These little white thighs, huh?
I think we should make them red, huh?
I think about all the times Jules has spanked me in a scene.
Payback.
Oh my God.
He takes it so well.
Oh, look at that.
Look at that hand print right there.
Can you see that?
Nice and tender there.
Oh, so red.
Oh, his cock is still fucking hard.
What does that say about Jules?
you don't want you to be able to see what's coming oh this is exactly you're
You're not going to tell him what's coming next, okay?
Damn. I was worried that this cup wouldn't stay hard, but it does.
No matter what we do to him.
Look at those handprints, goddamn.
What's coming next?
Oh, that was a nice noise. I like that.
Oh, yeah.
Should we put some on his balls, too?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Right there.
oh bitch I haven't even done it yet oh just the anticipation here we go here we go here we go
oh that wasn't so bad the anticipation was way worse
Oh, my God.
You have essentials like this.
Squirming like a little bitch.
Oh, my God.
How does that feel?
I spit all over your face.
I don't know, kiss me, huh, huh, you want to stick that tongue out, kiss me, oh, he can't, oh, he wants to though, stay right there, let's get him,
Oh
Fucking like that
oh it always hurts more when you take them off that's what people don't expect
oh oh oh fuck yeah oh should i tease him a little bit
oh just a little bit give you a treat after all that torture
I think that's enough, one more lick, gonna have some fun with that cock and these balls.
Oh
How's that feel you like that
What am I doing, indeed?
I'm having a blast, that's what I'm doing.
Oh my god.
Doesn't his cock look pretty?
Oh, that looks good.
Look at those balls.
Oh my god.
Oh my God.
She's so tired and red.
Oh, he's squirming now, but I haven't even started.
You want more?
Yes.
He doesn't even know, he's not sure, he's scared.
He's scared to ask if you want more.
Hey.
I like it, huh?
Oh!
Tied up. Fucked up.
You having fun?
Oh, God.
I'm having fun with you. I can tell you that.
I'm having so much fun with you.
Oh, you want those fucking tits?
You can't really get to them very well, can you?
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Look at those balls.
Oh, that's a lot, isn't it?
Oh
That's a lot I think he said you fuck
Bucco, is that what you say, you cootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-pootie-
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh yeah there's big tits down there yeah
you want my big tits pressed up against you
yeah yeah you heard him he wants my big tits pressed up against him
oh you didn't say with or without studs
oh yeah you're like feeling that fucking crop right on those balls
yeah
oh that wasn't a hard one
oh
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Yeah, that's right.
Choking on your own spit?
That was a nice one.
Pull these down so it whips around to your arse, I'll tell you.
Oh
Isn't this what you want?
What a little bitch.
Give him a little pleasure.
Make him cry.
Oh, God.
God, your cock is so filled with blood.
Look at this bull.
Oh, God.
Oh, look at that.
Mm-hmm.
You're damaging that cock.
You don't need it though, right?
You don't need this.
Do you need this?
Yes.
You need it?
Yes, I need it.
When do you next need to use it, huh?
I think you're going to be using it for a while.
Let's see what we've done.
Let's check out the damage.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Look, we bruised his cock.
Should I kiss it back off?
He's scared now.
With that blindfold on, hearing me talk about his bruised dick.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, yeah.
Now we fucked it up.
I told you I was going to fuck you up, Charles.
Didn't you believe me?
Oh, I think I was just gonna take it easy on you be nice to you. Oh
I mean now that I have you tied up, of course, I'm gonna take advantage of the situation. Oh
You do the same thing to me. Oh
Oh, God, yes, oh, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh yeah
and that cuckoo
oh yeah I got that fucking
cuckoo wet for these big tits
yeah fuck those big titties
bet that fills my
Nice, after having that fucking crop on that cock.
Oh, it feels so good.
Jiggle those big titties around it.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
Yeah, okay, now doesn't that feel nice, doesn't that feel nice, and I've got a fucking tooth.
Oh shit.
And whose cock is that?
Oh, it's your fault.
Yeah, it's my fucking fault.
Does that mean I get to do whatever I want with that?
Oh, yeah, please.
You know what I really fucking want?
What?
I want that fucking coke inside me.
Oh yeah, the food.
Yeah.
Oh, food.
I'm just going to rub that coke in my mouth like that.
oh my god you gotta feel so fucking good
yeah which hole should i put it in oh anyway anyway and it's going inside that ass
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Stretching out that tibial muscle.
Oh, yes.
Fuck.
Oh my god, that feels so fucking good inside my asshole.
Oh, my balls deep inside.
Yeah, yeah, fuck, yes, oh, good, yes, yeah, feels so fucking good in that asshole, yes, yeah, I'm making this fucking shit bounce, oh, yeah, yeah, fuck, yeah, yes, yeah, oh, my God, that's my favorite part.
My fucking dick.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Fuck yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's just like that fuck
Taste it us straight
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, don't you go in.
Oh, fuck.
Mmm, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my fucking god.
Yeah.
Yes, fuck.
Mmm.
I think I want to fucking take you to the bed.
I want you to fuck me just the way I want you to.
Yeah, still on this avenue.
You don't want this off, huh?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, you don't want it?
Yes.
I want you to fuck my ass.
See if you can find it with your tongue.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, he has escaped.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
Fuck yeah, I want you to service me.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
I want to push you all over my face.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, I still love the way you fucking dive right into my holes.
Yes.
So good at that.
Tongue fuck that asshole.
Yes, yeah.
Yes, get him deep in there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good boy.
Lick that asshole's throat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Mm, mm, fuck.
Oh, you're such a naughty boy.
I love that.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yes.
Mm.
Some of that pussy too.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Yes.
I don't want you to fuck all of my hoes.
Oh, yes.
That's my fucking dick.
I need that pussy so fucking bad.
Yes.
You deserve it after what you've been through.
Yeah, I think you deserve this at all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fucking take me.
Take me, take me.
Fuck, fuck.
This is so good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Look at your little bruised dick.
Look at that.
Yeah, I fucking love it. Oh my god, that looks so fucking good
Oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Oh, yes.
Mwah.
Yes.
Fuck.
Look at this.
Can I come take these fucking holes again?
Yeah.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh, that looks so good.
Yeah.
Yes.
use it. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Oh my god. You're a fucking monster. You fucking
earned it. You earned that little pussy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh god. Yeah. Keep fucking going.
Keep fucking going. I want you to make me come along. I do. Oh yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Don't stop.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Can you please put it back in your mouth?
Yes, please put it back in my asshole. I love it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, that's my pussy.
Get back in that tight little arsehole.
Yes, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, God damn it.
That feels incredible.
Yes.
It feels so good inside that arsehole.
So good stretching it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, fuck.
Thank you so much
Stroking off that
Use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it,
use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it,
use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it, use it,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Oh yeah, suck on these bolts.
Oh fuck.
Yeah, can I climb on board?
I'm back inside that asshole.
Oh shit.
Oh, fuck, yeah. Oh, it's so fucking tight. There we go. There we go, yeah.
Yeah, you like watching him fuck my little asshole like that? Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck! Oh my god, he's so fucking good in that asshole. Use it, use it, use it, use it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's it, that's it, come on, come on, make me fucking calm, make me fucking calm, make me fucking calm.
Oh my god, fuck!
Yes!
Oh, fuck!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't want to do this big fucking shit, John.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, stop, yeah, yeah, oh, yes, yes, yeah, yeah, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, like that, oh, fuck, oh, yes, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, fuck, oh, yes.
Yes, I don't know why you use that in love, so...
Yes, Jules.
Oh, God, stop.
Stop. Let me taste it.
Fuck.
Ooh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, look at those bruises right there on his fucking cubs.
Oh, what a shame.
Mm, we fucked him up.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Yeah, you want to get fucking smooth like that?
Oh, you're giving me a little pussy.
Yeah.
Mm, bounce that fucking ass.
Oh.
Ah.
Mm, mm, mm.
oh yeah please climb back up yes i want to feel you
oh fuck yes
oh fuck yes my god yeah oh fuck yes oh my god yeah yeah do it do it
give it to me yeah fuck that asshole oh yeah that feels so fucking good yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
show me how you use that fucking dick show me how you use that fucking dick it feels so
good inside that ass yeah yeah
Yeah, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, fuck, yeah, keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going, oh, shit, yes, oh, yeah, let me fucking write it, yeah, let me make this big fucking thing bounce, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, fucking give it to me, oh my god, yes, yeah, yeah, oh, no, yeah, she's a little sissy, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, oh, god, yes, that's good, yeah, yeah, yeah, take me, take me, take me, oh, fuck, Jules, yes, yes, yes, yeah, yeah, go, go, go for me, give it to me,
Give it to me.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't fucking stop.
Yeah, get back on top of that dick.
Yeah, yeah.
Get back on top of that dick.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, show me what you've got.
Show me what you've got.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, yeah, pound that little asshole.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Bowls deep inside that asshole like that.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, God damn.
Fuck, yeah.
Yeah.
Fucking grind that.
Sounds like that.
Fuck, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, oh, good, yes, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, my God, it feels so good in my mouth, so, oh, God, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, oh, yeah, yeah, use it, use it, uh-huh, oh, my God, yes, yeah, it feels fucking incredible, yes, yes, yes, oh, my God, yes,
Let me choose that little clip, like, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, god damn it, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
oh god yes yeah come on fuck me fuck me with my cock that's my fucking dick and i want you to
fuck me hard with it yeah that's fucking right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, he does big fucking tits, you know.
Yes, please suck your cock right now.
Uh-huh.
You don't want to fucking taste it.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
My asshole tastes so fucking good.
What do you fucking want, huh?
Yeah?
What do you fucking want?
Why don't you tell me if you want me to fucking kill you with those big fucking tits?
I bet the fucking cock wants to cum, doesn't it?
Yes.
Yeah, but you've got to fucking earn it.
How are you going to fucking earn it?
How are you going to fuck this ass some more?
Earn it?
oh my god fuck yeah yes take it yes yes oh fuck yeah that's what i fucking need
yeah yeah yeah yeah if you make me come really good I might let you come let's
Let's see that fucking gait.
Let's see what you fucking do.
Let's see what you do.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, let's see it.
What you do to that little asshole.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
You're going to make me fucking cum on that cut.
Make me f**king cum on the c**k
Yes, f**k
Yes, yes, yes
F**k me, f**k me, f**k me, f**k me
F**k, yeah, yeah, yeah
Keep going
Yes
Oh yeah, just like that
F**k, f**k, f**k, f**k, f**k, f**k
F**k, f**k, f**k
Yeah, right there, right there
Right there, right there, f**k
Oh
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, yeah, so fucking good, so fucking
good fucking comes so good with that cock do you think I should let him come
he deserved to come yeah I want to fucking taste that come fucking swallow
Swallow it up, mmm, yeah, I'm gonna fucking cum all in my mouth, mmm, I'm gonna swallow every last drop of it, yeah, you got a nice big load for me, yeah, mmm, fuck yeah, mmm, yeah, rub it in with that cock, fuck yeah, you gotta fucking use those titties, mmm, fuck yeah,
Fuck those big tits, yes, yes, oh, I feel good around your cock, I'm feeling that hot
dick, mm-hmm, oh, yes, stroke that cock between them, yeah, oh, it's so good, yeah, mm-hmm,
Yes, it's a perfect little face.
Yes.
Yeah, push it right in there.
Yeah, nice and tight in there.
Oh, God, it's screaming like a fucking cock.
Fuck.
Huge teeth.
Yeah, make that fucking cock disappear between these titties, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my
god, yeah, use those big tits, oh, that smells so good, yeah,
Let me see if I can catch you.
Sucking on those big tits?
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, we fucked.
Oh, shit.
Oh, thank you so much for letting me come home.
Oh, my God.
You are welcome.
Swallow it up.
Look at all that cum.
Oh, my God.
So much cum.
I saw it like squirting all up.
Oh, my God.
You deserve that after everything you took.
You are welcome.
Oh, sorry.
Mwah.