You
Hi everyone
Hello
up here
You know, Santa is so busy this time of year.
He barely has any time to peep Mrs. Claus company.
So I'm just here going through his list,
looking for a special little soul
to see who's been especially naughty this year
and maybe needs a little extra attention.
So let's see who has been naughty and who has been nice.
Okay, let's see here.
Who's been especially naughty?
Avery was nice. Very good, Avery.
Damien was nice. Very good, Damien.
Eric was also nice. Oh, you're so sweet, Eric, every year.
James was very nice.
dirty, rotten little soul you've been all year.
Hmm, Mrs. Claus likey a lot.
Hey, do you guys want to come with me
and see how Mrs. Claus gets down?
Let's go pay this dirty little pervert a surprise visit.
I believe it's bloody Christmas
Yeah? Oh, I know. Me and you, pal. It's always me and you.
Oh.
Hmm.
Ah.
Okay.
Hmm.
Hmm. Well.
Let's get it.
Mmm.
Oh.
Ah.
Mmm.
Here you go.
I don't know if I can do it, but I'm going to give it a try.
You're such a bad boy, you're a very naughty boy, Quentin.
Aren't you?
I'm a naughty boy.
Yes, you are.
You're very naughty.
You were naughty
all year.
I'm a naughty boy.
Who's a naughty boy?
Me.
Very, very
naughty boy.
You're just dreaming about sex right now.
Sex.
Yeah.
Such a bad boy.
Such a rotten little soul.
Aren't you?
Rotten soul.
Oh yes, you're the most rotten boy I've ever seen.
You've been bad.
I've heard it.
I saw it all year.
You look so bad.
I like that.
You've just been checking out girls' asses.
I've been staring at their tits all year long.
You've been very, very bad.
Very naughty indeed.
I love that.
I love my rotten little soles.
You are a rotten little sole.
Mama, you deserve to be toyed with.
You want to be Mrs. Claus' little toy this year?
I want to be Mrs. Claus.
I'm going to play with this hardcock all Christmas long.
And you, you're going to do whatever I say.
Aren't you?
Hi.
Hi, Hunter.
No, don't worry.
Just staring at me.
Oh, Mrs. Clausewijk.
Mrs. Clause-like, yes, she wants your bad boys.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, oh, yes, oh, yeah, oh, good boy, mm, oh, good, oh.
Oh, you impatient little soul.
Okay.
Oh, there you go.
Do what you do best.
You rotten little pervert.
Eat it.
Come here.
Are you Mrs. Claus' little cookie?
Yes.
Yes, I'm doing gluten-free cookies.
Oh, is that sweet?
Oh, yes.
Oh, goodness.
It's a good one.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, you put your tongue in there?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Wow.
Sniff my panties, Quentin.
What do you mean?
Do I look like a panty sniffer to you?
Do I?
Oh, yes.
You're such a bad boy.
I'm gonna make you a new one.
I love you, Cameron.
I love you.
Yes.
Yeah.
High-five.
Mm-hm.
Oh.
I've been naughty, too.
Oh, yes.
Mmm.
Oh, god, yes.
Oh, god.
I know you boys so good at that.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, Harry.
I mean, look at this.
Look at your face.
Oh, I suck at this.
I can't go on.
Mm-mm.
Oh.
Yes, that's good.
Mm-mm.
I'm
Yes.
Ah.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
You were so very good at that.
You're a bad boy.
I'm gonna try this.
This is mine, okay?
oh my god
this is so hard
oh god
yes
oh you
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Oh, oh, come on.
Oh, oh, wait.
Oh, oh, yes.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my gosh.
Yes.
Ow, ow.
Oh my God, yes.
Gee.
It's all right.
Yeah.
Ow.
Oh.
Oh, dude.
What's wrong?
Oh.
Oh God!
Oh fuck you!
Oh, fuck you
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Her head is here.
Here.
My head is upset.
What's he doing?
Oh.
Oh, God.
Push, push.
Ok, I'm going to go.
I'm going to go.
Oh my God
I can tell
Oh God.
You're gonna be alright.
You're gonna be okay.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, there we go, there we go!
Yes!
Oh, God!
Oh, God, you're so good!
Ahh, yes!
Oh, God, it's so wet!
Oh, God, you make me so, naughty boy.
You make me so, naughty boy.
No.
I don't.
Mm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Yeah, fuck me.
Mm.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh
Here we go.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Ooh.
Ah.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, guys.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh my.
I have a.
Back, back, back, back.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, oh, oh my god, yes.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh my.
Oh Fuck! Oh God! Oh my God!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Oh fuck!
Jesus please!
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Fuck!
Ah!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Oh God.
Yes.
Fuck, oh God.
Right there, oh my God.
Oh my God.
Yes, yes.
Fucking yes.
Oh God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh God.
Oh my God, you're ridiculous.
Oh my God, yes.
Yeah, hold on, hold on, hold on,
Mrs. Claus, please.
Oh my God, yeah.
Oh God, yes.
Oh.
Oh, it's time to jump on your cock.
Look at it.
Yeah.
Oh no, no, no.
Oh.
Shh.
Yes, yes, yes, oh my God, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Cutting her.
Awhh.
Oh, fuck yes.
Damn.
Open up, fucking come on.
Come on, fucking come on, open up.
That's gonna hurt.
Awhh.
Meowth, you like that?
My gosh.
Take these off of me.
I'll take these off.
Take it off.
It's a zipper.
Oh, it's a zipper? I see the zipper.
Good boy.
There we go.
Good job.
Now this one.
Mmm.
Oh, good boy.
Yes.
Come here.
I'm not.
You deserve it for all the pride.
Yes.
I love you.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Oh, holy Christ.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
God.
Oh, God, you're so good.
Oh, my God, you know, you're so good.
Oh, God.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Oh!
Taking control already?
Yes
Oh!
Oh, God.
Oh, yes baby.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
I love you so much, so much.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, yes.
oh fuck
oh my god
oh
oh fuck
oh fuck yes
oh
oh god
yes please oh my god
it's so fucking good
Oh
Sit down, sit down on the chair.
Oh, fuck yeah, that feels good.
Oh my god, that feels good.
Let's put my tape between his titties.
Yes!
Come here.
Right there.
Oh yes.
That's perfect.
Look at his tits.
Look at his fucking tits.
Fucking look at that.
Oh yeah, that's aesthetic.
Yeah.
Oh, such a good boy.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Yeah.
That's a good boy.
Can you pretend he winces?
For my big day.
Yeah.
My big merry days.
Mm-hmm.
oh my god just give me that cock give me that heart
please give me that oh oh god yes
Oh my god, yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh my god!
Yes!
Yes, yes.
Oh god!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Oh, God, yes!
Yes!
Oh!
Oh, yes!
Yes, baby!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Oh, my God, yes!
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yeah, just like that, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Ah.
Look.
Oh, yeah.
Can I smash that?
Yeah.
Smash it.
Oh, my God.
Ah.
Oh... Oh, God!
Oh... Oh, Jesus!
Oh!
Are you okay?
Oh, my God!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Mmm...
Be a good boy and spell now...
Yes. Oh, so hot. So nice.
Oh, God, yes, you look fucking great.
Oh, honey, ah.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Oh. Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck. Fuck, yeah.
Oh, God.
Yes. Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Please don't stab me again, Nico.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
oh...oh shit
oh my god
oh...oh...oh my god
oh...so cute
so cute
oh my god
oh
that's so fucking cute
oh fuck
oh boy
Yo, give me the f***ing thing, baby.
Give it to me, give it all over.
Put it all over my face, put it all over my face.
Put it all over my face.
Give me that egg.
You ready for this, baby?
Open your mouth, open your mouth.
Open your mouth, baby.
Here we go.
Oh, oh.
Oh, f*** me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Holy fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it tastes so sweet.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Have you been naughty?
Or nice?
Merry Christmas everyone!
Hey everyone!
I'm Natasha Nice.
have some of your fan questions that I'm going to answer for you today.
How does it feel to be the MILF of the month for December?
or is there another holiday that you celebrate in December? No I just
I was bored.
Can you name all of Santa's reindeer?
Donner, Vixen, Rudolph, Blitzen.
What's that, like 4 out of 12 or something?
That's all I've got, guys, sorry.
What else?
Snow or tropical Christmas, which do you prefer?
I actually tried to get out of Christmas this year
with my family.
I was gonna go to Hawaii and like surf or something,
but then I just decided it was the wrong thing to do
because it was Christmas.
So I want to try a tropical Christmas one day,
but they've all been San Fernando Valley Christmases.
So, no snow either, just sun.
Um, what was the best gift you ever received on Christmas?
Um, I got an Xbox when I was 17, that was pretty cool.
That's kind of it.
I'm not big on giving gifts, but I love buying gifts for people.
I spend so much money on Christmas time for people.
I just love buying presents for people.
If you could have one wish this Christmas, what would it be?
These are so cheesy, you guys.
What would it be?
I don't know.
super up like like really turned on because he didn't really know me that
me do it because I think he knew I was going to and then I just ended up