Naughty America. Nobody. Nobody. Nobody. Does it better.
I'm so sorry, I didn't mean to scare you. Um, hi, I'm Quentin.
Um, this was my, uh, my nan's house.
Yeah, yeah, of course. Hi, Quentin.
I know.
Wow.
It should be in her bedroom.
Paperwork.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
It's upstairs.
It's in her bedroom.
Okay.
Yeah.
So I came to collect that and look over that.
So, um.
Of course.
Um, would you like me to show you?
Oh, yeah.
If you can, that would be great.
Yeah, it's not a problem.
Thank you.
Yeah, sure.
Um.
Just.
i'll let you let you lead the way so here it is wow
Yeah, well.
All right, it's lucky here.
That's not right.
Is everything okay?
My name's not even on here.
It's left to a Natasha Nice.
Natasha?
I'm Natasha.
You're Natasha.
Are you, she left me the house?
Oh my God, no way!
Oh my God, that, I would, what?
She's a-
I'm not even related to her.
What?
Are you serious?
She's left you everything, I guess.
Oh, everything?
The backyard?
The house?
The property?
Oh, my God.
This is, like, so amazing.
Oh, yes.
I don't understand, but, I mean...
Oh.
She's left you everything.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Quentin.
I'm sorry.
I really had no idea she was going to leave me anything.
I'm just...
No, no, no.
I've been her caretaker for, like, so long.
It's okay.
I've not been here for two years.
I should have visited now.
No, she loves you.
I've been busy with my business and the kids.
Of course.
She knew that.
You've been here.
You've been here with her every day.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Here.
It's yours.
Thank you.
I'm so excited.
It's such a nice house.
Quinten, I feel like I know you. Yeah, of course.
I really do.
Well, my flight's in the morning, so I guess I could...
Oh, look, that's perfect.
I guess I could stay.
It's what Nana would have wanted.
Nana.
It's what she would have wanted.
Yeah.
It would be great to get to know you.
Yeah, I would love that.
I just...
I did so much, and I'm appreciative of everything that you did.
Yeah, and I loved your Nana.
I just...
Nana.
Yeah.
So, I mean, yeah, I could stay for a few hours, I think.
Yeah, you should stay for a few hours.
And catch up and hear stories and...
Oh, I can tell you so many stories about her.
Yeah.
Yeah, all the ones she told me about you.
That would be, I mean, wow, I would definitely like to get to know you.
Yeah.
Should be my guest.
A little bit more.
Oh my gosh, baby, you're so handsome.
Oh, come with me to the bed.
Dad, I'm gonna show you, come here, I'll get it for you.
Oh my God, look at those.
Yeah, I like those.
These are amazing, I like them.
So big.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
You're so talented.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
That's amazing.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh my god
Oh, this is so, this is so wrong, this is so wrong.
I know.
Oh my God.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh, this is too much.
Oh, God.
This is so wrong, but I just have to believe you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's so wrong.
Oh, yes, just like that.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, this is so good.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
You're waiting for me to see it?
Yes! Oh my God, yes!
God, it feels good, huh?
Oh my God, yes!
God, you feel so good, huh?
So good!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, yep.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, it feels so good.
Squeeze it out.
Oh, god.
It feels so good.
Yes! God, yes!
Oh my God!
Oh!
Yes!
Yes, baby!
Oh, God, yes!
Oh, fuck it!
Oh, God!
I want to ride your car.
You want to ride it?
Yes.
Just stay right there.
All right, let's go.
Hold on, you're all right.
Can I sit on this girl?
Let me just stay right here so I can know that.
Oh, my God.
Take it off.
Oh, my God, yes.
Come on, go up up here.
Oh, my God.
All right, go up there.
Put your fucking girl down.
Yes.
There you go.
I feel so good.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
you like that, yeah, you like that, yes.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yes!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Oh, my God!
Oh, yes!
Oh, fuck you!
Oh, my God!
Yes, baby!
Oh my god.
Oh yes, yes.
Yes, so good.
There we go, there we go.
Oh my god.
You're fun.
One, two, three.
Oh.
Fuck yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Yes, there we go.
Oh my god.
That's good.
Oh god.
Oh fuck.
Oh baby.
Just like that.
Oh god.
Oh fuck.
God that's good.
Perfect.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, this is so good.
Oh, my God.
Fuck yes, sir.
Oh, please, please.
Harder, Quentin, please, please.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck yes.
I can't take it anymore
You want me to do it like that?
Yeah, how do you like that?
Oh yeah, there you go.
Yes.
Oh yes, there you go.
Mmm, I can so fucking do all that.
Mmm, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
God, you think you're so good.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, God, yes.
Yes, that's what I want.
I want you to go.
Fuck.
Like this?
That's so cute.
Chew this cup.
Naughty America
Nobody
Does it better