position.
businessman. He wasn't much of an academic, but I was willing to take on
the challenge. Helping him graduate was just what I
improve his grades.
Really? Yes, absolutely. Great, so you'll help me? Absolutely. Cool.
After getting to know one another, we immediately started working on his
lessons. But after just a few minutes together, I started
developing those familiar feelings of attraction I felt
before. I'm not sure what it is. But I find myself helplessly
aroused by my clients. I couldn't help but tease them to
try and get them aroused as well.
Oh, Tyler, could you get that? I have, um, like, a bad back.
Here we go again. The old dropping the pencil trick works every time.
Thanks. You're welcome.
Energy is required for any type of work.
You know, I'm getting so frustrated.
I don't get it.
I read this same thing like five times
and I just can't understand it.
It's frustrating.
You know what, Tyler?
I think you're getting a little bit distracted.
You're having some trouble retaining information.
Tyler?
What?
Look, I just, I was saying that you seem a little bit
Distracted, like you can't focus for some reason.
What do you mean?
What are you saying?
I don't think that's allowed.
I don't think that's what he meant by, you know, anything to help.
Well, I mean, it should work.
Um, but if you don't want to play that game with me, I understand.
No, no, I, um...
Are you gonna try?
Oh, great!
Yeah, I will play.
Okay, great.
Question number one.
The 100 Years War was fought between what two countries?
France and England.
There you go!
Oh!
That's it?
Yes.
Good job.
Oh my God.
Okay, are you ready for question two?
All right, the Magna Carta was published
by the king of which country?
The Magna what?
Okay, you know what, we'll skip that one.
Okay, next question.
What killed a third of Europe's population
in the 14th century?
The black plague.
There you go, so good.
You gonna take them out?
Yeah, I'm gonna take them out.
Good job, Tyler.
Okay, here's the final question.
Who invented the printing press?
Who is Joanna's Gutenberg?
Yes!
Yes?
Oh my God, good job!
Nice!
It's so great.
Okay, well, I have a special bonus round for you.
Really?
Yeah.
You did so good.
Now, are you going to tell your dad about our special game?
No, of course not.
Correct answer.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Oh, that is so fucking...
Oh my god.
That is so fucking...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you sure we should be doing this?
You want me to stop?
No, no, no, that's not what I meant.
I'm definitely not gonna get caught this time
this time
That is so good.
Oh my god.
Oh, yes, this is so good.
Oh, wow.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, fuck you.
I'm going to get all this shit out of your mouth,
you fucking exchanges.
Heheheheheheheheheheheheheheheheheheh.
Oh, you fucking sex decreased baby.
You fucking motherfucking nuisance.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe.
Oh, fuck you.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Hehehehehehe.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that is so good.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
What do you say we continue this study session
in the bedroom?
Yes, I love that.
Oh God, I don't know what to do.
Whoa.
Oh, lordy goodness, gimme this.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh, you.
Oh.
Oh, my God, yes.
I need you to soothe me.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
I need you to soothe me.
Come on.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, fuck.
I need you to soothe me.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck you.
Mm-hmm.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah.
Oh, fuck me, please, yes.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Ah, oh fuck you.
Oh.
See, yeah.
Oh, that's beautiful, really.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my god it's so good!
Oh my God.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
Oh my.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, it's so hot.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God, it's so hot.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh, please don't.
yeah
oh my god
that was so cute
I love my doggie
Oh my god, that is so fucking good.
Oh, oh my god, yes, that is so freaking good.
Oh, you can't imagine.
Oh my god.
Oh, yes.
Oh, that is so fucking good.
Oh my god.
Oh, yes, just like that.
Oh my God...
Yeah...
Yes...
Mm...
Yeah...
Oh fuck...
Oh my God...
Oh yeah, you're okay...
Oh, you ready?
Oh...
Fuck...
Oh fuck...
Oh my god, that's so fucking good.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Come here.
We can get her.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, come on.
Let's just get that.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
I knew it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god.
It feels so good.
Flip over.
Oh my god.
It's so fucking sexy.
Are you in there?
I'm home.
Oh, fucking Jesus.
I'm just gonna get you there.
Oh, my.
Oh.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, yeah.
That is so fucking bad.
Oh my god.
Oh, you feel so good.
Oh, yeah, you're working up, too.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, baby.
I can't go.
Yes.
Oh my.
I can't go.
Fuck, yes.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Hell yes.
Yeah.
I'm all wet and I'm sweating.
Oh God, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Fuck you.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
Oh my, oh my god, oh my.
Oh shit.
Oh.
Oh my, oh my god.
Oh my God!
Enika!
Oh my God, Enika!
Oh my God!
Oh,
so good!
Oh my God!
You're so beautiful.
You're beautiful.
Oh my God.
You are the best.
here
ah
ha
mmm
ok
hold on
ahh
ah
oh
wow
Oh my, oh wow, good job, Ty.
Oh my god.
So good.
Oh my god, you did a really good job.
Oh my god.
So great for our next study session.
Yeah, next Monday, right?
Mm-hmm.
Looking forward to it.
Yeah, me too.
Oh my god.
Oh, my God.