What?
Yes, I got accepted.
Me and Alex are going to the same college.
When?
Next week.
Dorms open up so I'm going to go early and get all set in and everything.
No, you're not doing that.
What do you mean, no?
There's no way.
You in college, are you kidding me?
You can't even clean your room, Tyler.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? It's like social norm is to go to college.
Yeah, but...
You get a better education. What do you mean?
What?
Keep your part-time job. That's the right move to make.
There's no girls at JC's.
Okay, there are tons of girls everywhere. You're exaggerating.
Far, far, far away from home.
I never see the people I live with and I can't have fun.
It hurts, Tyler.
No, it hurts. I love you, but come on.
This is the kind of experiences I'm going to have in this house.
We got so close, Tyler. You can't do this to me.
I know, and I really love you as my mom.
I love you too. You're my young boy.
I know, but think about all the experiences you're going to have.
Come here, Tyler. Come here, Tyler. Let me show you something.
I think I have the solution to your girl's argument right here.
Oh, what are you doing?
Don't you think I have that solution right here?
But you're my still one. This is your...
I know, I know. But you can call me mommy. It's okay.
And mommies do anything for their young boys.
Mommy boobs.
Well, there's some girls that have boobs like that.
I'm sure of it.
No, no, no, no.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Honey, you're never going to get girls talking that much in college, okay?
Okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
Be quiet for Mommy.
Let me show you what you'd be missing, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
You're like a monster.
Anything for my young man to stay home with me.
Oh.
Oh wow, that is so good Oh my god, that is so fucking good
It's so stiff and mushy.
Oh my god.
It is so good.
It's so good.
Oh my god.
Oh my goodness, it's so good.
Oh, that is so good.
Yeah.
Give me your foot.
Mommy's big tits.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, good boy.
Put that back in your mouth.
Oh, yeah.
That is so good.
Oh.
Oh my god!
That's beatiful
Oh my god
Oh boy
That was so good
But mommy could see you, but mommy could see you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're cute.
Oh, you're so fluffy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, you know what mommy wants from you, right?
What?
I think you can guess, honey.
What do you want?
Give mommy some calm in her mouth, please.
What?
Yeah.
Really?
Please, please, honey.
Oh, yeah, yeah, just keep doing that.
It's so good.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, just a little something for me to remember me by.
What did you just do?
No.
You're not going to get anything like that in college, honey.
You really should reconsider, okay?
You know, I'm going to go to Alex's house.
Relax and think about it, okay?
Bye.
Okay, bye.
Bye honey. Say bye mommy.
Bye mommy.
think about a whole day going by without him.
their room gonna look like?
know how they're going to survive in college.
And on top of that, do you have to remind him to shower?
Because, oh my god, Alex forgets.
Yes, I have to tell Tyler every single day too.
It's like I am his mom or something.
It's like, and he thinks he's just going to go off
and live somewhere else.
It's like, no way.
I mean, their dorm rooms are going to be disgusting.
So disgusting, like stinky and everything.
I really don't think we should let them go.
Yeah, I think we should come up with a plan.
I mean, there's got to be something we can bribe them
with, right?
I mean, yeah, probably, but what?
Like, what do teenage boys like?
Boobs in video games?
Yes, they do like boobs.
Maybe we should do this in person.
I think so, too.
Yeah, like, why don't you come over?
Okay, I'll come over right now.
All right, see you in a little bit.
Okay, all right, bye.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey, man, how's it, how's it going?
Good?
Yeah, uh, you know, how was your day?
Um, you know, kinda, kinda same as yours, uh, uh, good.
You know, just, just good.
Did you do anything?
Um, I mean, I, I cleaned my room.
Um...
Uh...
And, uh, you know...
Yeah, just...
Your mom sucked my dick.
What? What? What?
What?
Did, did you say your mom sucked your dick?
That'd be weird if it wasn't, you know.
Well, I mean, because, uh...
It's not weird, right?
Well, I mean...
It's just your stepmom, you know, just...
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, maybe my mom, you know...
Your mom slept with you?
Yeah, yeah.
My mom slept with me, too.
Dude!
Okay, what the fuck?
Oh, you know, I don't want you to go away
She's like just come over here and like
college yeah yeah exactly they were just a few minutes of whatever exactly
I know, I've always looked at your mom's tits and...
I mean, I don't blame you.
I've looked at your mom's tits and shit.
She's right.
Yeah, exactly.
Her tits are off out of this world.
Hell yeah.
Hey, I don't know what to put.
Hey.
I do too.
Oh, hey.
Hi, honey.
How's it going?
What's going on, son?
How are you?
Oh, you know, just hanging out, you know.
Oh, I was just visiting you, too.
Oh.
Just hanging out.
Oh, you know you were coming over.
Oh, yeah.
Are you okay, honey?
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I was just hanging out.
I wasn't expecting anything.
What were you guys talking about?
Were you guys talking about college again?
Yeah.
College.
Schoolwork and stuff.
You know, we were thinking about it.
And we maybe shouldn't have
gotten so upset about
you boys going off to college.
Maybe we're a little hasty in trying to stop you.
You know what?
We don't mind at all.
We understand and we totally get why you guys maybe did that.
No boys.
You actually kind of encourage us to maybe change our minds, right?
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
It's possible.
Being at home with your mom would be fine.
Yeah.
I mean...
We were pretty wild ourselves, you know, so...
Yeah, we...
We're pretty wild.
Right.
Yeah, right. Just have fun. Lots of fun. Lots of studying.
Oh, shush. You know it's all about the girls. And we knew that too.
I mean, we like girls. Girls are fun. Yeah, that's how we met.
Didn't have to do all that trouble.
Oh, hi.
Yeah, what, hi.
Well, so, um, we were thinking that it might be a good idea
to, uh, send you guys off with a little present.
Sort of congratulations.
A bang, maybe?
Don't forget your mommy.
Oh, yeah.
Right on, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You're not going to forget me, are you?
Maybe you should start here, son.
Yeah.
That's it.
Yeah, that's so good, honey.
Oh my God.
Dude, your mom's not even wearing underwear.
Oh, I never do.
Oh shit.
You should get over here and smell it.
Oh yeah.
Did you do that for me?
Mm-hmm.
Smell your mom's pussy.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Doesn't your mom have a pretty pussy?
Oh yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh, yeah.
Mm, that feels good, son.
Uh-huh.
Oh!
They're so sensitive still.
Yeah.
Oh.
That's it.
Okay.
That's a good boy.
Yeah.
Oh.
That's it.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
Oh.
Look at that mom, your pussy tastes so good.
Yeah.
Kiss it?
Kiss her.
That's it.
Oh it tastes so good.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
What the fuck?
Yes, yes honey.
Oh gosh, give me that.
Is this huge?
Oh, yummy.
Yes.
Oh!
Fucking...
Oh, yeah, oh!
Just like that!
Yeah, practice for college, honey, yes.
Oh, he's drunk.
He's drunk.
Oh, he's really drunk.
He's really drunk, honey.
Kiss kiss, he's drunk.
Yeah.
Fuck.
You're drunk.
Oh, shut up you.
She's so drunk.
I don't want to be drunk.
Yeah, you're drunk.
Fuck.
I don't want to be drunk.
Oh, no, I don't want to be drunk.
You're freaking me out.
It's so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Yes.
This is so wet.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, you definitely need to practice that.
Lots and lots of practice before you go off to college.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
This is dry.
Yeah.
Boner, you've got here.
Oh, God.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I know.
Thank you.
It's me.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm going to stroke you right here.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
No, no, no.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Oh my God.
It's going all over here.
Yeah, it's going over there.
Oh my God.
Suck your son's cock.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Yeah, you like playing with your mommy's titties?
Oh, yeah.
Sucking my son's cock.
Yeah.
Like how mommy plays with it.
Oh, that is so fucking good.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I'm giving you bollocks, son.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God damn.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God damn.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Mm-hm.
Oh, yeah.
Shit.
I'm so damn.
Goddamn.
Oh.
I'm going to get it nice and wet.
Wet my mouth.
Okay.
Mmm.
Here, let mommy wipe it for you.
Mm-hm!
Yes!
Oh!
I love you.
Mom, I just have a little something for you.
Oh!
Here's for you.
Do you want to try it?
Yeah?
Want to try it?
Mm-hm.
Oh, wow!
All right.
Oh!
Breathe in.
Mm!
Oh, wow.
Yum.
Oh!
Mm!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, dude, you're mocking me.
I'm gonna suck your dick.
Oh, God.
Give it to me.
You wanna see Mommy suck you?
I don't know.
Fuck.
It's warm in the water.
Ahh.
I don't want to do this.
Fuck.
Update.
Oh man.
Is it OK?
Goodness.
It's OK.
Oh.
I need the gear to help me.
Wow.
Ah.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, your son's going to get so tired.
I know.
No!
Don't touch my baby.
Oh my god.
See if you can fuck your mom.
You haven't fucked your fucking parent yet.
You want to fuck me?
I'm gonna fuck your son.
What?
You're gonna fuck your son.
I'm gonna fuck your son.
What?
Oh my god.
It's because I did it for you.
You're gonna fuck him.
No I don't want to.
This is the last time.
Yeah.
I want to fuck you.
I want to fuck your mom.
Don't say it.
You want to fuck your mom?
I want to fuck your mother.
Don't say it.
You want to fuck mom.
Who?
I'll fuck your mother.
I'm going to fuck your side.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
So hard.
Oh my god. Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck.
Are you okay?
I like fucking you.
Oh my god.
Just look nice and deep like that.
Oh my god, yes.
Fuck yes, darling.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah.
Wow.
Can you smell?
Yeah.
It's a little easier.
Okay.
Oh my god.
That's it.
Take it out nice and hard.
Good job, Tyler.
You see that color, Kishore?
Yeah.
It's like a color.
It's like a skin.
Oh my God.
It's all right.
We've got all these times.
Oh, brother.
Yeah.
It's all right.
Oh, your teeth are too.
Yeah.
Oh, I love you.
Oh.
Oh my God.
That's a really good start.
Yes.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah!
Oh, yes!
Oh, my God!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh, that's it!
Oh, my God!
You're so beautiful!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Give me a hug.
So fucking really good!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Oh my God.
I have a taste of the pussy on your dick.
Fuck you.
It tastes so good.
Oh my god, yeah.
Mommy, can we have a hug?
She tastes so good on your dick, son.
Oh yeah.
Give me your pussy.
Come here, I'm sliding under you.
Oh, oh fuck.
Oh yeah, moms like to have fun too.
Yeah, no kidding.
Oh my god.
Touch your mommy now.
Touch your mommy.
Oh wow.
Oh, I'm getting jealous, give me that cock, honey.
Oh, I'm pretty jealous of his mom's mouth right now.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, come on.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Yeah.
Ah, fuck.
Get up, get up.
Get up.
Give it to me, give it to me.
Well, I have to say.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yes, Alex.
I'm so good.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Yes.
Ah!
Yes!
Uh-huh!
Mm, yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
Put it right back in that pussy.
Yeah.
There we go, right in there, that's it.
That's it, that's it.
Okay?
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Mm, yeah.
Mm, mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, fuck you!
Yeah.
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
It's like coming right to my face.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Wow, that was crazy.
I know, right?
Yeah, what else can we do?
Why don't we...
Oh yeah, let's ride the boy.
Let's do it.
Tell Mommy how pleased you're gonna be.
Oh yeah, I'm talking to my mom and everything, too.
Yes.
That was great.
That was awesome.
I want to hug Mommy too.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Say it.
Show Mommy how to ride your calf.
Right.
Mom.
Oh
I know, where did him go?
Yes, we need him.
Mommy's here.
Yeah.
That's it.
I'll have your way with mommy's pussy.
It's so hard.
Use mommy's pussy.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
You're so hard on my pussy.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, that's it, yeah.
Mm, that's right.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
So much of the infection on my face.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, the little dyke you used to be.
Yeah.
Shh.
We said we were never going to talk about that.
Oh my god, you feel so good.
You feel so fucking good.
Oh my god, you feel so fucking good.
Oh my god.
Take a fucking break.
Take a little break.
Oh my god.
Yeah?
Oh, you like that?
Oh my god, my son fucks me.
Oh, your son fucks you?
Oh my god, he fucks me so good.
Mommy, thank you!
Thank you, Mommy!
You're sucking it real good.
Thank you, Mommy.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes.
Ugh, it hurts.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Ah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes, son, yes, you're doing so good, son, yes.
It feels so good.
Yeah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, fuck.
That's it, that's it.
That's right, fuck that pussy on the next one.
Yeah, yeah, uh-huh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm so nervous.
Oh my God.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Let's feed her.
You got it, Mom.
It feels so good.
All right.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Oh, I think she wants a fuzzy lick.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
I think you're going, huh?
Let's see.
Uh huh.
Come here.
Yeah?
Taste it.
Mmm.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're so fluffy.
Yeah, come here.
Yeah.
We're going to get you a treat.
Come here.
yes
I'm really good
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, my fucking, fuck!
Oh, I'm gonna cover your cock!
I'm gonna fucking cover your dick!
Oh, my slits, don't they slip?
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God!
Put it back in! Put it back in!
Fuck, put it back in! Yes!
Oh, my God!
Oh, that's fucking nice, honey.
Yeah, fuck that jack-mother-pussy.
Oh, my God.
She's fucking good.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god.
You've got so many spots.
You look beautiful.
Yeah.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
This is my son's dick.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh, jeez.
Fuck.
Let me see.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my fucking god.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
here
oh my god
kick my head
oh fuck
oh my god
that's what that fucking
that's what that
oh my god
oh fuck
listen to the pain
yes
come here
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Your ribs are amazing.
My arms.
I'm out of breath.
Okay.
I'm about to throw up.
I'm going to go for another few.
I can't.
I almost got to the top.
No.
Oh I'm so awesome.
Woo hoo!
Carl.
Carl!
I'm going to go for another few.
Okay I'm going for another two.
Woo hoo!
Oh my god.
My arms are going to break.
Woo hoo!
Oh my god.
You're hurt.
Oh shit.
Oh boy.
Here we go.
Oh fuck.
Oh fuck yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, look at the air it's trying to build on me.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
I feel like I'm going to cum pretty soon.
Yeah?
You want to come in my mouth, son?
Yeah, I want you to come in my mouth.
Yeah, push it right down my throat.
Oh, yeah.
It's so good.
I want you to come to my mouth.
Yeah, push it right down my throat.
Come over mommy's face.
Oh my god, you come over mommy's face.
Yeah, come on mommy's face.
Stick your faces together.
Oh yeah, here's your face.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh f***.
Oh.
Wow.
Oh f***.
Good job boys.
That's how we send you off to college.
No you're stuck.
Oh.
Now you guys know exactly what to do.
Oh my god.