You
Hey, so you have that big league tournament tonight, right?
then if you lose I'm kind of like the consolation prize for you and all of
from your teammates.
Wow.
It's perfect, right?
What do you think?
I guess we'll see you tonight, then.
Okay, I can't wait.
Bye, babe.
Okay.
Oh
So, did you win or did you lose?
Whoa.
We did.
You won?
Champs.
Champions, yes.
Absolutely.
Oh my god, I knew you would.
I knew you would.
So, um...
I take it you're ready for this?
I am ready for this.
Yeah, it looks like it.
Yeah, let's just say I don't think you need the beers.
Alright, why don't we do it then?
Let's do it.
You showed them, huh?
Oh yeah, man.
Crushed it.
Alright, we'll take a seat wherever, guys.
I'm gonna go grab us some beers.
Too easy, bro. Too easy.
We had him from the beginning.
Had him from the gecko, man.
Had him from the gecko.
Yeah, what a good game, man.
Natasha.
Hey.
Hello, gentlemen.
What's going on?
What's happening here?
Congratulations on your win.
Thank you.
Natasha had something in mind.
And, you know, what's going on?
Well, she had a very specific way she wanted to celebrate in mind.
So if you guys are cool with it, if you're interested.
That's all right with you two.
I just wanted to congratulate you guys, you worked so hard for the win.
Wow.
You sure this is cool?
I'm totally cool with it man, it's what we do.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Alright.
Wow.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Let's go ahead and warm her up a little.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, it's my turn.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There we go.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There we go.
Oh.
Oh, God, it's so fucking good.
I love it.
Come on.
Yes, get sloppy.
Oh.
Oh my God, yes, show it to everybody, you're doing fucking well.
Oh my God.
Oh baby.
Oh fuck.
It's...
Oh yeah, just like that.
Yes, there you go.
okay,
I'll
be there.
That's fine.
Okay,
I'll call you.
You can call me.
Yeah.
I'm about ready to go.
Okay.
Bye.
Oh my god, oh my god, I'm fine.
Yes, oh my god.
That was so good.
Yeah, there you go, good girl, good sloppy.
Yes, oh yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, there we go.
Good girl.
Oh.
You want to take turns on that pumpkin pussy?
Oh, God, it feels so good.
Stay right there.
Give me more.
Oh, my God.
Right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck you.
Fuck me.
Oh, my God, please fuck me.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
Yes, oh, my god.
Fuck yes.
Oh!
Oh, my god.
Yeah.
Ooh!
Oh, my god!
Yeah.
God.
Oh my god!
I don't want to turn it off!
Yeah!
Oh my god!
I can't stop my hand!
Oh fuck!
Yeah!
Oh my god!
I can't stop my hand!
Ooh.
Yeah.
Mama.
Oh my god.
No, no, no, no.
Oh!
Stop.
No!
No, no, no.
No.
Please.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Oh, my god, it's so bad.
Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
Get on your back.
Get on my back?
Is this what you wanted?
Oh god.
There we go.
Oh fuck!
Please.
I can't breathe!
Oh god.
Oh my God, you're so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, that's me.
Oh my God.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Yes. Oh my god.
Yeah, put that in her f****** car.
You almost bit me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, I love the way you fuck me.
I love the way you fuck me.
It's so good.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Yeah, both hands.
There you go.
Yeah, fuck.
Both hands.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh
Oh, my God.
okay my gosh
okay
yeah
oh my god
okay
Oh, my God.
Mm.
Oh.
Yeah.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh!
Yes.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fucking God.
Ah, yes.
Oh, fuck, I feel so fucking good.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my god, you fucked my whole system.
Oh, yes.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Yes.
That's right.
That's right, take all those fucking pills, baby.
Oh my God.
So fucking good.
Oh.
Fuck yes.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
So fucking good.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Come on, baby, let's get your arms up.
Let's get your arms up right here.
You guys don't have to do anything to me.
Like this.
Oh my God.
Fuck, fuck, my, suck my ass, oh fuck, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh yes, oh yes, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Baby, yes, my baby, yes, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Stay right there, baby.
Stay right there, yeah?
Stay right there.
Oh, look at that, yeah.
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh my god, oh my god, you bit my ass, yes!
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh my god, oh fuck, this is so fucking good.
You asshole, yes, oh my god, oh fuck, oh shit.
Oh yes, Chokey, Chokey, will you fuck my ass?
Oh my god, yes, oh fuck, this is so good, oh my god, yes.
I'm so, please, please, I'm so, oh my god.
It feels so good!
Oh!
Yes!
I am a fucking asshole
Fuck
Oh god yes
Oh, fuck.
Oh fuck, I'm so weak.
Oh my god.
Come here, come here, sit on me.
Give me that ass, give me that ass, turn around.
Turn around, give me that ass.
I guess I'm gonna sit my ass on your fucking cunt.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, oh my god, I want another cunt.
I want another fucking cock and I want it right here.
I want it right here.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Let me have a seat.
Please.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
I feel so bad.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, okay.
Don't sit down.
Yeah, don't sit down.
But they will slither you.
Slither you.
Oh.
Uh-huh.
I'm sure.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Mm.
Slither you.
Yes, it feels so good.
It feels so fucking, fucking pounding in the ass, baby.
Fucking.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, my.
Yeah, right.
Just deep, baby.
Deep.
Deep like that.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, keep hitting me!
Oh, my god, yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, oh!
Oh, you feel so good!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my god, you're bleeding so much!
Get out of my ass, baby, yes!
Oh, my god!
Oh, fuck!
Yeah, baby, you want two cups?
Yeah, I want two cups.
Can I have two?
Come here.
Oh, oh my god, he has...
Oh, fuck...
Yes!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's so fucked up.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, I hate you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.
Oh, God.
I want you all to come on my face as a team.
Yeah.
I'm fucking running to you.
I want you guys to come on my face.
Please.
Please give me gum.
Please come on my face.
Please.
Tell him to come.
Please come on my face.
Please.
I want gum on my face.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
There, baby. Look at me.
Please, come on my face.
One more.
There we go.
Ahh.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my God!
I'm scared.
AHHH!!!
Oh my God.
It's really grippy.
Uh huh.
It is sendoff.
What would you have done if we lost?
If you lost?
Yeah.
Wow, she had it all planned, huh?
That was a really great team effort.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
It was all you, babe.
Yeah.