Seriously. You're late.
Well, happy anniversary, my love.
And let me tell you, you look absolutely stunning.
I hope you haven't forgotten my special gift.
Of course, how could I forget?
it's our annual tradition and our eighth anniversary.
So where is that special gift?
Jason!
How's it going, Professor Walker?
I apologize for being early.
I just wanted to make sure I wasn't
in the middle of traffic or anything, so sorry.
Look at you, always going above and beyond.
Apologize, pal.
Yeah, thank you again for having me and helping me with my midterms.
It means a lot. I just don't want to fall behind.
And it really means a lot to me.
Say no more. What else would I do?
Listen, come on inside.
Thanks.
Come on in.
Listen, go in there and have a seat.
I'll be right there.
You go in there.
Hey there.
Meet my wife.
Hello.
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yes, yes it is. Boy, you brought me home a good one.
Jason here is my top student.
I bet he is.
Tell her, Jason.
Yeah, tell me, Jason.
Straight A's.
I can definitely see that.
Tell me, Jason, would you like a refreshment?
Um, no, I'm all good.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm all good.
We're just here to study, so I probably shouldn't.
Ginger ale?
No, I'm all good. Thank you, though. I appreciate it.
You're welcome.
Hey, why don't we have a seat?
Now, now, now. There's no rush, Jason.
I mean, you did get here early.
Yeah, let us get you a drink.
How about that beverage?
Get comfortable.
Yeah, you guys are really kind.
I appreciate it.
Oh, you're so welcome.
Why don't you tell Mrs. Walker a little bit about yourself?
Yeah, Jason, I want to get to know you.
What do you want to know?
Oh, I just want to know everything.
Where are you from?
So I'm from the suburbs of Chicago.
I don't know if you know the area at all.
No.
It's kind of, uh, yeah, just a...
How old are you, Jason?
Um, I'm 21.
Jason's on the wrestling team.
You don't say.
Wow, you must be mighty strong and rugged.
It helps, you know?
Oh, I bet, I bet.
Yeah.
I bet it's really hard to...
He's so humble, isn't he?
He's very humble.
That's my Jason.
Humble.
I'm sorry.
Is this okay?
I just want to be respectful.
Jason.
Relax.
I'm just friendly, Jason.
I'm very friendly, in fact.
I do this with all my friends.
Trust me.
Yeah, you're a friend of ours now.
Yeah.
Yeah, you are.
Awesome.
You got a girlfriend?
No.
Girlfriends, maybe.
No, definitely not.
I don't know if I could handle multiple girlfriends at one time.
Yeah, I don't even...
Who does?
Like, you know how it is at school.
You gotta focus on both.
You know what, honey, I think we should just tell him.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Well, Mrs. Walker and I have been married for a long time now.
Now, today's actually our eight-year anniversary.
It's our eighth anniversary.
Eight years we've been together.
Congratulations.
When you've been with someone for that long,
you kind of got to spice things up to keep it special.
Spiced up and fresh.
You know what I'm saying, Jason?
Basically, he brings me every year a hot young stud
what do you think jason i just don't want to be assuming stuff here um
Um, are you suggesting that you are wanting me to have sex with your wife?
Yes.
I told you he was smart.
He is very smart.
Yes, he is.
Um, it's just, I can't tell if you guys are being serious or not.
Like I'm not trying to like.
This is very serious stuff.
No wrong answers.
Chase!
You are a young, stressed out stud.
The wrestling, my class, there's so much pressure on you.
So much pressure.
And today I just want to help you relieve some of that pressure.
Sherman. Look at me, pal.
Make my wife happy.
Make me happy.
You can do that for me,
can't you?
It's, I would say
something like,
I would say
I'm interested in this
respectfully, but I
for me
what, and I'm sure as you know, is what is
really important to me is school right now.
Whatever I
I say too for this.
I just want to make sure that whatever happens
is not going to interfere with it
or just like make, complicate things.
Look around.
Does this look like a college campus?
No.
No!
No, it's my home.
You're in my home.
You're our dad.
Make yourself at home.
School's out.
You want to make yourself at home?
Yeah.
Yeah?
So it's settled.
That is the right answer.
Like, just like that, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You have a seat.
Right here.
You seem nervous.
I'm just fine.
He just likes to watch.
Just let me hold your hair back.
Yeah, please.
Ooh, you're nice.
Much better now.
You're nice.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Tell me how you like it.
It feels really good.
Just like that Jason?
How do you like it?
It feels really good.
You like that mouth don't you Jason?
Yeah.
That's my girl.
Let's honor that.
Does that make you feel good?
Yeah.
That's good.
Look in the eyes.
I asked you the question.
There you go.
Okay.
It's a nice day, isn't it?
Oh, my God, yes.
Do you have a question?
I don't know.
I think he likes it, doesn't he?
He better.
He didn't give us enough good sense.
Oh, no.
Look at me.
Look at me, my stupid guy.
Oh, my God.
Good job, Jason.
Oh my god.
You're doing so good.
Whoa, this is a little less hot, buddy.
Stay here.
Oh my god.
No one's ever put their foot down like that before.
Is this okay?
Let me fix you
Is this ok?
Oh my god
You know if you want I can go down too
Oh what do you think of me?
As a giver
Are you a pussy Jason?
Yeah
Good boy
You want to suck my cock, honey?
Yes.
Yeah, you do?
Not right now, though.
You just stay right there.
Yeah.
Just watch this baby.
Watch.
Oh, yeah, keep stroking it.
Stop stroking it.
Stroke it for me.
For me.
Oh, my God.
Is that all right?
Yes.
Get your face over it.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, don't be afraid to get messy, Jason.
Mmm, yeah, spit on it.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
Is there anything that you like
that guy does when he eats you out?
No.
Why don't you suck on my big clit?
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
Oh, God.
Put those fingers in my pussy juice.
God, he's so obedient.
I love it.
Oh my God.
Oh, he's so good.
You can feel his fingers on my pussy.
It's so good.
Oh, his tongue is so nice, baby.
Oh my God.
Oh, it's so nice.
Oh God.
Oh, are you having fun?
It's wonderful to watch you in such.
Isn't it awesome?
Oh fuck, he's so talented.
oh tell me every single one baby
Don't stop! Don't stop!
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh fuck, he's so good at that, baby.
Looks like it.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
I want to fuck you now.
You want him to fuck you now?
Yeah, I want to feel your cock inside me.
Is that okay?
Come on.
You gonna suck my cock a little bit?
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, sure.
You know, at least together, we'll do it together.
Come on, Jason, fuck me.
Really?
Yeah.
That'd be nice.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah, fuck me, Jason.
Oh, I want to feel that cock.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Remember me.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
I feel so good.
Jesus.
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
Oh, fuck. Help me.
Do you want me to fuck you a little bit?
Oh, not right now. Not right now.
Give me your balls. Give me your balls.
Mmm. Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
Mmm.
Oh, my God. You're getting so close.
Mmm. Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God. Think we're gonna cum?
Oh, fuck. Come with me. Come with me.
Oh, fuck.
fuck oh my god i think he liked it baby
i was not expecting that sorry was this too soon no no i love it
how old are you 21 21
You're not done, are you?
I mean, I can definitely keep going.
You can?
Why don't you bend over for me?
Oh my God, he is great.
Let me, let me.
Well, it's just I'm all messy.
Just bend over, yeah, lay on your stomach, just like that.
Let me do it.
Oh, thank you.
Yes, okay.
Oh my God, I love your coffee right now.
Oh, fuck.
Thanks.
Sure.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
You like how I suck it, baby?
What's happening?
You like how I suck his cock?
I'm just focused on your pussy.
Your pussy's so good. It's the best pussy in the world.
How good is that pussy, Jackson?
Dude, it's fantastic.
It's hard not to cum. It's hard.
I get it, professor. I get it.
Oh, yes.
It feels pretty good, man.
Oh, my God.
I already knew how to do that, babe.
How am I doing, is that going to be it?
Oh yeah, it's going to be it.
Oof.
Oh, yeah.
Keep it going.
Oh, fuck.
Not bad.
Did I ride the youngster?
Yeah.
Is that what you wanted to do?
Then you're back.
Okay.
Oh.
Do you think there's something?
Yeah.
Can you spank it for me?
Like that?
No, not like that. Spank it.
Like hard?
Yes, baby.
You've never asked for that before.
Well, I'm asking for it now.
Spank it. Do it.
Like that?
Yeah.
Again.
Oh, that's, that's fine.
Oh, that's so good.
That's so good, that's so good.
That's so good, that's so good, that's so good, that's so good.
oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God,
Oh my god, are you enjoying this baby?
Yeah, do you want to suck my cock a little bit?
Oh yeah, yeah fine.
Let me clean this off first.
Let me fuck you over from behind you.
Oh my god.
Come back for me a little bit.
Thanks.
Huh? Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, yes, I fucked you, but not like you.
Yeah, I fuck her hard.
Yeah, right babe, tell him I fuck you hard.
Yeah, baby, you fuck me so hard.
Yeah.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, that's my girl.
That's my girl.
I fuck her hard.
Harder?
Yeah.
Really?
I thought I was going pretty hard.
No.
Sorry.
You want to hold her?
Yes.
You can hold her.
Okay.
Here.
I don't know why she gets ready to leave this room.
Oh my god!
Harder baby, come on.
Should we move or something?
Do you want to do something else?
What do you want to do, Jason?
Do you want to bring me over?
This is your guy's.
Maybe you should bet her over, sure.
Why don't you guys just switch?
Okay.
I need something for you, baby.
Come here, baby.
Cool.
This is so hard.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
it's kind of hard in that position right
oh my god
it was the bed
the way the bed is
I couldn't get my positioning right
oh my god
it's so good
I feel so fucking good.
Oh my God, I can't believe it, fuck.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck.
Oh my God.
Do you want it, babe?
Do you know what you want?
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God, you're a fucking 21-year-old, dude.
Oh shit, oh fuck, yes.
I don't think so
oh god don't stop
oh my god
spank your teeth
smack it like this
do it harder than he did
Jason
You sure?
Yes.
Like good?
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
She likes it when I do that.
Oh god.
You sure?
Yeah.
Oh fuck.
You want me to do it again?
Yeah do it again.
Oh.
Oh my god.
It's so good.
Oh fuck.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
I love this.
Oh, yeah. Mm.
Oh, fuck.
Oh. Mm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, you like watching me get fucked,
do you?
Yeah? Do you like watching me get fucked?
Fuck. Oh, you're fucking hurrying up.
Oh, yeah.
Watch me fucking take it.
You want to watch him come on me?
You want to watch him come on my face?
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah. Do it. Come on.
Fucking do it. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
If you're good now, come on.
That was good, wasn't it?
Yeah, way to go.
Yeah.
I guess we'll all shower up now.
Yeah, definitely.
Okay, I bet you have another one in you.
I can just tell.
I mean, if you want, I can probably do it again.
No, I think we're good.
I do want.
No, he can do it again, babe.
That's insane.
Really?
You're going to get it?
That's incredible.
I've done it before.
Why waste such an awesome gift?
Okay.
Come on.
You can do it.
Cool?
Yeah.
Hey, it's the lady's day, right?
It sure is.
It's the lady's day.
Yeah, he did.
Oh, he came a lot.
He came the most.
The most?
Yeah, maybe the most.
It's like everywhere, it's like down my asshole.
Oh, God, it's so juicy and wet.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, best anniversary ever.
Oh, it's so good. It was such an amazing anniversary.
You are a beast.
You are so good.
Thanks.
Oh my god, you were just so great.
It was a lot of fun.
You gave me so much calm. Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
God, that was so amazing.
I hope it was what y'all were looking for.
oh and more so fucking amazing anniversary
best anniversary ever