Naughty America.
Nobody.
Does it better.
Hey Alex, do you still take your coffee black?
Yes, nice to see you still remember.
Thank you for throwing this party for Lisa.
You know, it's great that we're still getting along together.
Oh yeah, of course.
I mean, her and I were friends before you and I even started dating.
Like I said, I'm just, you know, happy we're cool.
Anyway, what did you want me to do for the party?
Oh, well, let's see.
I mean, pretty much everything is booked.
The food has been booked.
The DJ has been booked.
The invites have gone out.
Oh, I booked the stripper.
You booked stripper?
Oh my God, yeah.
We used to always get each other strippers on our birthdays.
You never got me a stripper.
That's because I can't find a stripper
with boobs big enough for you.
Actually, speaking of big boobs,
How exactly are you doing with Lisa?
Cause she's kind of lacking in that department.
I can tell you that it hasn't been an easy adjustment.
Why do you think I make her buy push-up bras?
Oh my God.
I shouldn't laugh, that's messed up.
But like, honestly, what were you thinking?
Like, anyways, don't worry about it.
You can just always go out to lunch with me
and stare at my massive tits.
Oh, thank you.
What are friends for, Alex?
Oh, you're funny.
Oh, by the way, did you get her that dress you were about to buy her?
Yeah, yeah I did. It's upstairs in my room. Do you want to come see it?
Sure.
Okay, let's go.
Alright, here it is.
going to fit into this little thing.
Thank you for rubbing it in, Natasha.
I'm just playing with you, Alex.
I know.
I mean, you're the one who chose to be with Lisa, Alex.
It was a rebound.
I thought I'm going to get used to it, but I haven't.
I miss your massive tits, you know.
I love all about them and just remembering,
you know, going up and down while we're fucking.
Oh, I miss all about them, seriously, and you.
Wow, I had no idea you felt that way.
What if-
What if we, no, nevermind, you go.
I kinda was gonna say the same thing.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I missed.
Did you miss me?
Oh, that mouth.
Yes, I miss that face and my good titties.
Oh, yes.
Let me see them.
Do you miss me doing this?
Oh, yes.
Get on the bed, I want to play with those teeth.
You want to play with my teeth?
Just like that, right here.
Oh my god, I miss your hands on my tits so bad.
Oh my god.
Will you pinch my nipple, baby?
Pinch my nipple.
Yes. Oh fuck, you know I like that.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, jiggle my titties, jiggle my titties.
It's been such a long time since I had titties like this.
I know.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yep.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
I'll hear you back.
Let me see that pussy.
Yeah.
I'll hear you back. Let me see that pussy.
Yeah, I know.
Yes.
Oh, do you miss this pussy too?
Oh my God.
Oh my God, he has socks.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh my god, you're back.
Oh, fuck yes.
Fuck yes, I love you.
Will you do that?
Oh my god, you...
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, you need this.
Oh, fuck, you're so good, fucking yes, oh my god.
Oh my god, yes.
Fuck, yes, oh fuck, oh my god, oh fuck, yes.
Oh god, yes, she's kissing.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
Oh nice.
Oh fuck!
Oh my god.
Oh, god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, god.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my god.
Stop.
Oh, god.
Oh, my god.
I can't take this anymore.
I can't.
Oh my god, I missed it, I missed the clock.
That's it.
Oh my god.
Oh yes.
That's it, good girl.
Oh my god.
Oh yes.
So fucking good.
Yes, baby.
yes
mmmm
yes baby
you like that
oh my god
mmmmm
get back
yes
suck that
Oh, my god.
Oh, God baby.
Fuck.
Oh fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh dear.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
What's happening?
You okay?
Oh, dear.
Oh, fuck.
What's going on?
Get on your back, I'm going to ride that cock for you.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, baby.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, fuck you.
Do you want to eat this piece?
Yes, take a dip, baby, take a dip.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Oh yes. Oh my God.
Sit on that cock.
It just went right now.
You think?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, my god.
Oh, fuck, it feels so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck, it feels fucking good.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, I miss this chick in my fucking pussy, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, yeah.
I just can't wait for me to pass out, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
You're gonna have a strong nose, huh?
Yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck you.
You like that?
What?
You like when I pounce on you?
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, you make it feel so fucking good.
You make it feel so fucking good.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Aah, fuck.
Oh, thank you for me.
You made this for me.
Oh, my God, you — you —
Aah.
Ah.
Fuck you.
Aah.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, thank you for me, Alex.
You don't speak my lingo.
Oh, my God, you — you —
oh
Yes. Good girl.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
Ready for more?
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
You are bouncing.
You better....
You are bouncing so fucking hard.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Go, go!
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh you bouncy.
Oh my god.
Fuck ya.
Oh my god, it's so good.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck ya, oh my god.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh.
Aww, fuck me.
Yes, baby.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Yes.
I'm here.
Oh my!
Oh my fucking-
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh my cord
Yes!
Nop
Not again!
Oh, fuck yes!
Oh my god!
No!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, this is gonna make me...
Calm down!
Oh fuck
You're 16 or anything!
Oh my God!
Oh!
Oh fuck!
Oh man!
Oh!
Oh, fuck yeah.
You like this?
Yeah, I like this.
You miss that fuck?
Yes, I miss it.
My spot's so good.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
I miss it like this.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, oh my god.
Ah!
Oh yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh yeah.
Oh, my God.
You're gonna be fine.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I love how you do that.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
That's a good girl.
Oh, God, yes.
You feel that?
You feel that pussy?
Yes.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
Yes, baby.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
oh, my God, you're such a son of a bitch.
Bend over for me, baby, bend over for me.
I see those tits balls on your ass.
Fuck you.
Oh my god.
Good girl.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
It's so fucking good.
Oh yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh, oh, fuck yeah.
Yes.
Oh, you fucking pussy.
Fucking pussy.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes!
Yes!
That's it!
Lift it up.
Yes, baby.
Uhuh.
Yes!
Fuck.
Oh my god, yes like that, yes like that.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh
Yes.
God, yes.
Just like that.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, my god, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Just like that.
Oh.
Oh, my god, yes.
Oh, yes.
Come, Tasty.
Come here.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
That's it.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, baby.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, baby.
Oh my God.
Yes, girl.
Oh, oh my God.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Give me those.
Oh my God, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Can you do it?
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck you.
Fuck you.
I love you guys, I love you guys, I love you guys.
Oh fuck, you make me so sick.
Oh my god, you make me so fucking wet.
Oh fuck.
Oh fuck you.
Oh yeah, oh speak.
Speak now, speak, oh fuck you.
Yes, right there.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Oh, my God.
Yes, baby.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes. Get on your back.
I want to see those tears bouncing.
Mm-hmm
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck, it tickles so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes, look at those fucking tits.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yes.
So good.
Please, oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Don't do this, okay?
Oh, my God.
Oh my fucking god!
Oh fuck!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh shit!
Oh fuck!
Oh my God
Oh fuck.
I'm gonna get that bastard.
Yep.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God, I'm gonna have to suck your dick.
Yes.
Oh my God, I want you to come in my tent.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck!
Oh my God...
Oh, fuck you, you used me.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh my God.
Oh my god.
Yes, baby.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck, yes.
Yes, baby.
Yes.
Oh my god, you're so hot.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I miss this cock so much.
Nobody, nobody, nobody does it better.