You
Mm.
Oh, it's so nice.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Mm.
Okay, let me touch.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, slap it.
Slap those nipples.
Those hard nipples, yeah.
Come on, harder.
There you go.
Both of them.
That's it, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Put it between those tits.
That's it.
Ooh, the tits.
Yeah.
Right between those tits.
Come on.
You like that.
You know you like that, right?
Keep those elbows down, that's it.
That's it, like that.
There you go.
Fuck those titties, okay?
Yeah, there you go.
Oh, you like that, don't you?
Slap those nipples again.
Yeah, get them. Both of them. That's right, baby.
Yeah.
Back and forth.
That's right, back and forth.
Yeah, both of them.
There you go.
Yeah, you want that cock in your mouth, no?
Slow baby, look at me while you suck on that.
That's right, lick it again.
Suck those balls.
Harder.
There you go, get them all in your mouth.
Both of them, both of them.
That's right, push them in, yeah that's right.
Do it again.
Yeah, that's it.
Keep those elbows down.
Yeah, that's right.
There you go.
Take your time.
That's right.
Suck that cock.
Come on.
Mm-hmm.
You like that dick in your mouth.
Deep in your throat like that.
Yeah, yeah.
I can tell.
Come on.
Mm-hmm.
You like that dick in your mouth?
Deep in your throat like that?
Yeah, yeah.
I can tell.
Grab those nipples for me.
Harder, yeah.
That's right.
Suck harder, yeah.
There you go.
There you go baby.
Suck that head.
Yes, look at me while you're doing that.
That's it. Squeeze those dimples.
Look at me. There you go.
Just like that.
Oh
Yeah
It's like that cock come on
You like that cock
Like that cock in your mouth
It's a card on it
See those cheeks cave in. Yeah, just like that. Why you look at me?
That's right
Why are you sucking that big cock?
Yeah, you know you like it
Oh, you know you love to suck that dick, right?
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
It's so messy.
Let me have a look at it.
Oh, it's so fucking messy.
There you go, yes.
Come on, show me, show me you like that.
Oh, fuck.
Come on.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, you like that.
Soak them in it.
Just a second.
Look at the camera.
Harder yeah.
Slower yeah.
That's it.
Harder, yeah, slower, yeah, that's it, that's it, look at me.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I like that, I like that.
Oh, fuck, yes.
You like that?
Keep pulling your balls.
Mm.
Ah.
Oh.
Mm.
That's right, slap it on.
Slap it on those hard nipples.
Mm.
There you go.
Yeah, come on.
Beautiful, fucking hard nipples.
Mm.
All the time.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Oh my God.
Oh my God.
So cute baby. So cute.
Oh yeah.
Oh my God.
I love stroking your crotch.
I'm feeling how stiff it is in my hand I'm going to suck it
Nice and slow, alright look at me.
Nice and hard, yeah.
That's right.
Mmm.
Ah.
Oh
So car
Oh yeah.
Oh
Grab those tits for me. That's right. There you go
There...
Oh...
Oh, yeah like that...
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, oh...
Oh!
F**k!
Oh yeah...
Oh yeah like that...
Oh, that can't be real.
Oh, yeah.
Oh
Oh yeah.
Oh suck on that egg.
There you go.
Yeah.
Look at me, look at that.
Yeah, there you go.
That's it.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Don't stop.
Oh, don't stop till it's gone in your mouth.
Don't stop till it comes.
Oh, yeah.
Don't stop.
That's it.
There you go.
Oh yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Look at me, look at that.
There you go.
Oh yeah.
Don't stop.
Uh-huh.
Oh, I like that.
Yeah, don't stop.
Oh, fuck, it's so good.
So good.
Give me a big hug.
Oh, you're gonna make me cry.
You know, you like that?
Yeah, you like that?
Come in your mouth.
Yeah.
Yeah, look at me while you do it.
I'm so gonna do it.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, put that big hug in.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, oh
Yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh
Oh, oh, oh my god. Yeah, like that. Oh my god
Get all of it, okay
Don't stop, don't stop
In your mouth, don't stop
All in your mouth, don't stop
Don't stop
Oh my god
There's a lot there
Don't stop
Yeah, I know. Are you going to show me?
Yeah, before you swallow it.
Grab your tissue, just one more time. That's right.
Show me, show me what you got.
Yes, yes. What's your prize?
There you go.
So good. So good.
Oh, it tastes good, doesn't it?
Just tell me how it tastes.
Oh, he's so sweet.
Sweet, isn't it? Yeah, it's a good diet.
Anything left?
Mm-hmm.
Go.
Come on.
All of it, down the hatch.
Anything left?
Check.
Yeah.
There's always leftovers.
Right?
With you, I'd give you leftovers for days.
That was a good-sized lump.
Yeah.
With you, I'd give you leftovers for days.
That was a good size lunch.
Yeah.
It was sweet too, right?
It was sweet.
Protein filled, by the way.
It was a natural sweet.
You know why?
No fried foods.
Oh.
That's the key.
Is that the key?
And natural foods.
Yeah, I could have.
Like grass fed steak.
Right?
You know, if you're going to have steak.
and otherwise lots of plants and water
you know, go green
we're all green, yeah we are green here
we have green flavored cum, I guess you would say
you know I also do those little things that have like
yeah you know they have the like the celery and the
mint and yeah
so okay so okay
Okay so taste test, apparently like we passed the taste test.
Oh you definitely passed the taste test. I've had so
time. Yeah I haven't worked with you since before I took my break.
Ever? Like for a long time? Well okay for biggulpgirls.com
Yeah I know but I mean you know but in general. Okay so back to
today. How do you compare today? To? Just the past. The load?
I don't have we fucked before we did. Oh my god 10 years ago
Were you in a french may but I think we topped it
What do you think really? Oh, yeah, it's possible
Well, I'm not sure which one you're referring to.
I just, you seem natural because you're French.
Yeah.
To be in a French made outfit.
Because you are French.
You are classically French.
I am classically, oh, thank you.
Oh my God.
You are gorgeous, you know that, right?
I get more French as I get older.
I think so too.
I realize.
You get younger as you get older like me.
Oh, thank you.
We both get younger as we get older.
We'd have good kids.
Yeah, we'd have good kids.
I don't want to do that to my pussy.
Oh, really?
Sorry.
Okay.
Yes, you did.
They were so good.
They tasted great.
They were great.
Yeah.
Sweet little babies.
Yeah, they do.
And they look good on your tits, by the way, too.
They look really good no matter where they are, right?
It's called community growing.
Yeah.
Oops.
There's a little community.
That episode of The Simpsons.