whatever
okay babe
don't take it too long
I don't have time for this
you like the view down there?
yes, sorry
do you wanna try that one?
yes, please
What is this?
I'm so sorry.
You're a pineapple man.
You got me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, he is here.
Oh, that's it.
I'm going to suck your cock.
Give me that in my mouth.
What? You want to suck my cock?
Yeah.
Give me that.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
You're so handy.
Oh my God, I love it.
Stand down, baby.
Come on, baby.
Oh, yes.
Oh, that's so cute.
I love your face.
Oh, my God.
Mm-hmm.
Show me how good you are.
I love that cock.
It's so big.
Oh you.
Oh, yeah, oh, yes, hey
It drives me crazy. Oh, yeah, I just need a stroking cup in my head
It could have been
Hi, yes
Oh my god.
Hey, honey! Where are you? This is taking a lifetime!
I'm here, honey!
So speed it up!
Honey, what's going on? This is taking forever!
I'm sorry, babe. It won't be much longer.
I hope so.
I promise you.
Should I get a pedicure?
Oh, this is disgusting.
Gross.
Yes.
You can continue.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, come on.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
I need to take your mic back.
Oh, yeah. By the way,
what is your name, Ben?
I'm Ranjan.
Ranjan here.
Oh, that's really good.
Yeah.
Especially in such a great way.
Put it back.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, this is fucking good!
Oh my goodness!
Oh, I keep going!
Oh yes, keep going!
Yeah!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, fucking yes!
Oh my god!
It's so good!
Oh, yeah!
Oh!
Yeah, that's it!
Oh, yeah!
As I told you before, we take your food, and she's serious.
Sit there.
Give me your feet.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, baby, let me make you tired.
So oily, oh my God.
Oh, shit.
I'm going to play with your teeth the same way.
Yeah, I want to.
Yes.
You're fucking ridiculous.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
oh
oh my god
oh yeah
so good oh my god
just pop it like that
oh yes yes yes
ah
oh my god
oh yeah
ah
oh shit
Mmm.
to visit it more often thank you we appreciate it our pleasure to see you
Okay, so, how much?
250.
Okay, man, yes, 300 for you.
Thank you.
Thank you to change.
Okay, let's go.
Yeah.
Bye.