Naughty America, nobody, nobody, nobody, does it better.
Hi Diego.
Hi Ms. Nice.
Thank you for waiting after class.
Of course.
you a hard time about something.
I don't really want to talk about it.
Are you sure?
You can tell me anything, and you're my very best student.
I wouldn't want to see you fall behind.
I'm a bad kisser, so they've been making fun of me.
Oh my gosh, that's so mean.
Yeah.
Students can be so mean sometimes, can't they, Diego?
Well, is there something maybe I can help you
with to maybe make this stop?
Well, I never really learned how to kiss properly.
Oh, so no one ever taught you?
Well, I am your teacher. I could teach you.
I don't know if we should be doing that.
Are you sure? Who better to teach you than your teacher?
Mmm, I'm not sure.
Aww. Here, why don't you stand up.
Would you be comfortable just giving me a kiss on the cheek?
Okay, sure.
Sure.
Okay, go for it.
That was great!
You know how to kiss!
Don't listen to those girls.
Okay.
They're just...
...bitches.
Here, why don't you give me just a quick peck on the lips?
Okay?
Uh...
Okay.
Perfect.
You do that really well.
Thank you.
Are you sure no one's ever taught you?
Yeah, I never really learned.
Oh, you know what I think, Diego?
Hmm?
I think it's those girls who don't know how to kiss.
Maybe.
No? Did you ever think of that?
Here, let's do it one more time.
You're a good teacher.
Your glasses are foggy.
Yeah see?
Do you feel more confident in your abilities now?
I think I know how to kiss now.
Yeah? Do you want to give it another try?
Okay, sure.
Okay.
There you go.
Spank it.
Oh, very good.
Wow, I really like your tongue.
You're really good with it.
Thank you.
I bet you'd be even better with it.
Practice does make perfect. You have huge tits, Ms. Ness. Very good.
Give it a kiss.
Just like that.
Oh, that's so good.
Very good, Diego. Very good.
Oh, yeah.
Just let your tongue out like that.
Good job.
oh
suck it
oh there you go
and the other one
oh my god
oh very nice
oh god
let me try
Oh, such a good kisser.
Oh, yes.
Oh, good shot.
There you go.
There we go.
Mm.
Oh.
Yes.
There.
Oh.
That's mine.
Yes.
Good boy.
Oh, god.
oh my god it's so good at that so so good at that you're doing a great job
oh yeah bite it a little bit
Okay.
Yeah, just like that.
Oh, I wanna play with this now.
You just sit right there.
Actually, wait a second.
Swing it.
Oh, again.
We're from the bottom this time.
Oh, good job.
Yeah, keep going.
Sweet.
Oh, you're really good at that.
Have you done this before, Diego?
Never before.
Wow.
Such a natural.
Yes.
All right.
What about...
Do you know what a blowjob is?
Never had one of those before.
No?
Okay.
Well, you're about to have one.
Take these off for me.
Oh, good boy.
So stiff.
Nice, young, stiff cloak.
And no one's ever played with these?
Mm-hmm.
Oh
You're very nice miss nice
I'm learning a lot
I never think I'm going to get a head from my teacher.
Does that feel good?
Yes it does.
Okay.
No one's even ever done this?
Oh yeah, take this.
Two hands are always best, okay?
Always better than one.
You're very good to hang on.
Why don't you slap your cock on my big breasts?
Have you seen breasts like these before, Jake?
Never.
Never?
Yeah, there you go.
Squeeze it right in between them.
Good boy.
Yeah. A little fun with it.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Nice and warm.
Good boy.
You're the best teacher.
I like when you spit on me.
Yeah, you like when I spit on you.
God, it's important to know the things that you like.
Oh, that feels so good.
No, what happens?
It gets really wet.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Do you want to see?
Yes.
Yes, what?
Please.
Oh, good boy.
Come here.
Get on your knees.
I want you to play with this for me.
Wow, you're really wet.
Mm, very good observation, Diego.
Ah, ah.
Oh, yes, yes, there you go, you're doing great, exactly.
You're a natural, Diego.
I can't believe you've never done this before.
Yeah, just take your time, and lick up all the juices,
and put your spit on it.
good.
You can use your hands too, Diego.
Your fingers.
Yes, just like that.
Very good.
You're doing such a good job.
Oh, yes.
Oh, good.
Are you sure you've never done this before, Diego?
This is my first time.
Wow.
Oh, yeah. There you go.
Just like that.
Look, let me show you
You see that little thing up there?
This little ball?
Oh yeah
That's the clitoris
It likes to be licked and rubbed
Then just beneath that
is the hole that you can put your fingers into
It's basically the pussy
Oh, it feels nice
oh let's play with those two things as much as you want
yes and then slow again
And then with your other hand, put your fingers inside.
Oh, you're so beautiful, Diego, yes.
Uh-huh, yeah.
And then do them both at the same time.
Yes, so good.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Good job.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah, mm-hmm.
How's that, Miss Nice?
Very good, very nice, Diego.
Now, keep your fingers in there,
and use your mouth to stimulate my clit.
Yeah, just like that. Oh, my God, so good, yes.
Keep doing that. Oh, my God, keep doing that, yes.
Yes, don't stop, Diego. Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yes, don't stop.
Oh, my God, don't stop, Diego.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
You're so good.
Take this off.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, so good.
Yes.
Oh, fuck you.
I'm so hungry.
Are you ready?
Yes.
To fuck me?
Yeah.
You've never fucked a girl before?
Never.
Oh, thank God.
Okay.
I want you to meet Vega.
Oh my God, yes.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh God.
Oh, he has hair...
Mm-hmm. Oh my god, yes.
Uh-huh. Oh, so cute.
Mm, yes.
Yes, give me a second.
Uh-huh.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh yeah, just like that.
Just fuck it.
Oh my god, just like that.
Yeah.
Just fuck that pussy.
Does that feel good?
Yes, it does.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, yes.
They're so good.
I found you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, it feels so good.
Oh my god.
Oh yes, it feels so good.
So good.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Oh god, yes, yes.
Yes. Oh my god.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, yes.
Oh god, yes. Don't ever gonna make me come again.
Oh my god, oh my god.
No, no, yes.
Oh yes, you're so good, yes.
Oh my god.
Take your pants off.
Get on the desk.
I've never even seen this before on Diego looks amazing I like the view
Yes, you're getting really good at that.
Do it again.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh my.
Yeah.
Fuck yes, Miss Nice.
Oh God.
I like it when you call me Miss Nice.
You're the nicest teacher I've ever met.
Oh fuck, yes, yes, oh my god.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, yes.
Fuck, oh my god, yes.
Oh, oh, chill.
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes.
Oh fuck, oh god, yes.
Oh yes.
Oh god, oh fuck, yes.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, it feels so good.
Fuck yes, yes!
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Fuck you, son of a bitch.
Fuck you.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, you see right there.
You see right there.
Oh.
Oh
You ever done 69 before do you know I thought it was just a number
Get it.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, my ears.
Get it.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh.
Oh, God.
That feels so fucking good.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
OHHHH
UUUUHHH
Ohhhhh
FUUUCK
Oh my God
Oh
Oh fuck
MMMMM
Oh Fuck
Oh my god that feels so
fucking good
I think I'm gonna come
and get your cock to you though
Please come on my side
Fuck! Yes! Oh my god!
Oh, come on.
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Oh my god!
Fuck, yeah!
Oh, wow!
The conversion clock is so nice!
Oh, yes!
Oh!
Big change in my face!
Oh
Practice, practice, practice.
Practice makes perfect.
Uh-huh.
Oh, good.
Yes.
Oh, that's OK.
You're still learning.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good.
Oh, good.
Oh, very good.
There you go.
Yes.
Oh, good.
Ah.
Yes, Diego.
Just like that.
Oh, you're doing so good.
Oh, yes.
Oh, but you have to sneak with the kids.
In the woods.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, oh, very good.
Yes.
What if I can turn you?
Okay, Miss Mouse.
Oh God...
Fuck...
Oh my God, yes...
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, yes, yes!
Oh, my God, it's so good!
You've heard of doggy style Diego?
Never.
That looks amazing.
Yeah just put it right there.
Oh, that looks amazing.
Yeah, just put it right there.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Take that.
Mm-hmm, yes.
Oh, yeah, uh-huh.
Oh, yes.
Good, good, yes.
oh
oh yes
yes
oh
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, that's so good.
Good.
Good boy.
You're doing such a good job.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I feel so good, Miss Nice.
Oh, give it to me.
Oh!
oh
Oh God.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Oh God.
Oh.
Yes! Oh my God!
Yeah.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, yes, yes, just like that.
Oh god, yes, yes, just like that.
Oh, oh, oh, so good.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, you're such a good student.
You're so good, keep going.
Yes, you're doing such a good job.
Oh god, uh huh, oh yes, yes.
yes, oh, oh god, yes, uh-huh, keep going, yes, just like that.
Oh, I feel so good, my thighs.
Yes.
Oh, oh.
Oh, yes, good.
Oh, I just, I just keep fucking me.
Keep fucking me, yes.
Oh, my god.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, god, yes.
Oh, my god, yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, yes, please don't stop.
Oh, that feels so good, yes.
Oh, yes.
God, yes, yes.
Yes, you're good.
This is so good.
Oh, yes.
Mm, mm, yes.
Uh, uh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, yes, mm-hmm, yes.
Oh, you're so good.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Uh, uh-huh, oh, so cute.
Oh my god.
Oh!
Oh, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Do you like those painkillers?
Uh huh.
They feel so good.
Oh fuck yeah.
I'm gonna come to you.
Oh
ohhh
ohhhh
ahhhhh
oh oh
oh
wow
thank you miss Nice
really good
yeah
really
good job
oh
look at this you
look at my big breast
do you like that
yes I do
yes
oh you did such a good job
yeah
I am very proud
I'm very proud of you.
Thank you.
You know what?
You'll have to stay after class tomorrow, too,
for our next lesson.
OK, for sure.
OK.
All right.
Now I have another class.
So hurry up and get dressed.
All right.
Naughty America.
Nobody.
Does it better.
Hehehehe