Okay.
It's really good to have with beer.
It's really good with beer and it's good with bread.
I will eat it with the bread I bought yesterday.
I'm going to eat bread and eat it with the bread I bought yesterday.
I'm going to eat it with the bread I bought yesterday.
Hey mom, uh, can I get some money for lunch today?
I'm just gonna go hang out at the park with some friends.
I thought you were supposed to be in school.
Oh, that was an hour ago.
We got out early.
David, you know I don't have any money.
What?
Sorry, David.
Sorry, David. I'm really busy right now, actually. David?
Well, well, well, my son. What?
You like what you see, huh? You're growing up, aren't you?
You feel like growing up today? A little bit, yeah.
Honey, I think we need to have a family talk right now.
You ready?
Yep.
Let's come to the table.
Big boy you want to be, huh?
Come on.
Okay.
Let's go, honey. Come on. Get over here.
Sit down.
Hey, hon.
That's not your chair.
Over there.
You know this
Son
Yes
I'm going to explain to you the birds and bees, son
Okay
You like what you were looking at over there, weren't you? Those big tits?
Yes or no? Just a yes or no?
Yes, you know, yeah
Are you ready?
You ready to become a man?
Yeah, I'll do what I can.
Do what you can.
Grab your mom's tits now.
Grab her tits.
Now.
Grab it, squeeze it.
I want to tell you something
that you have no idea
about.
You are our adopted son.
Really?
Yes, you are our adopted son.
This is a lot to take in at once.
Squeeze them.
Wow, what?
Um, it's okay.
Remember, she's your stepmom. You can grab it.
Okay.
Is this okay?
Well done.
Squeeze it harder.
Yes, feel those tights, grab them both.
Not too hard, not too soft, that's it my son, yes, put them together.
You are learning my son.
Honey, look at her in the eye.
This is okay.
Well done.
Honey, say yes, it's okay.
Yes, it's okay.
Push them together.
That's it.
Not too hard, not too soft.
You like how your stepmom feels?
Mm-hmm.
That's it.
Take them out a little bit, that's it, nice and slow.
Look at those huge tits.
This is the first step in becoming a man. Thanks a lot.
Oh hun, our boys growing up, so proud of him.
Now keep making bread, don't say anything, just make bread.
Just keep doing that.
I'm going to take a picture of the cake.
I'm going to put it on my head.
It's a dangerous place, but I should take care of it.
I'm going to have to clean it up a little bit.
I'm going to cover it up with a towel.
I think it's better to clean it up a little bit.
So
Hey mom, I'm home.
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
Why are you sitting on the couch like that?
It's over 100 degrees outside.
Oh, um.
I'm just not wearing any bottoms.
Oh.
Okay.
Well, that's odd, but okay.
Do what you want.
It's hot out, so.
I'm going to go get a drink.
Okay.
Bye.
Say yes. Yes. Yes I am. You go there now. Take those covers off her.
Okay. And spread her legs. Make me proud son. Okay. You can do this.
Well, what do I do now?
Smell it.
Oh, I don't smell it.
Eat your tongue out.
Uh-huh.
It's like your favorite gummy bear.
Lick it.
Okay, maybe you can hold her face up if you want if that helps.
Come on. I know it might seem a little awkward, but mommy loves it.
That's it, not too hard. Yes.
That's my boy. I'm so proud.
I am so proud.
That's it, my son.
Honey, today, our boy grows up.
You will let him have your way with you.
You can release, but the most important
is that he releases all over you.
Yes, I understand.
That's it.
Don't talk anymore.
He will do whatever he wants with you.
Come on, my son.
your ass in his nose and your pussy on his tongue.
that out son hold that ass smack it honey
How does it feel, son?
Very good.
Don't stop.
You are growing up quickly.
I love it.
That's it.
Oops, honey, the laundry, the dryer just went off.
Go get those clothes.
Thank you.
Son?
Yeah?
How do you feel?
Oh, I feel great.
Come on, son.
at home all the time.
So that's why she's napping right now, but this is lesson number two now.
This is going to be thrilling for you.
This is the part where you're going to be able to release.
I want you to use your mom as you want, but still always respect her.
Take your pants down and show her that hard cock that you have.
Okay.
You ready for this?
Yeah, I'm...
Go sit down.
No, don't.
You're going to be fine.
You're going to be fine, son.
Sit.
Sit by her.
Rub her a little bit on the forehead.
Rub her tits.
And show her what a man you are.
Go to your mom.
That's it.
Take control, son.
I'll just take one out.
Well done.
Oh, hi hun.
Hey mom, you're awake?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, take control.
I'm horny and I want my dick sucked.
Okay.
That's okay?
Mm-hmm.
Take your pants off.
Your shorts.
Right from the sides.
Use them to bend over.
mm-hmm on our knees you take control yes that's it my son that's it
great son oh where did you learn that the poor hair oh I just trying to be
your balls too son. You can grab your cup up. Feels good son?
Mm-hmm never take control, but be respectful
I'm proud of you, son
don't forget respect that's okay though that's okay i like that
like how mommy's flowers all over that yeah let's let's oh my god
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Tell Mommy how much you like that.
Mommy.
I don't like it.
I love it.
Oh.
Control her, son. Control her.
There we go. Yes.
Felt like something was going to happen soon.
Oh, whoa, okay, oh, that's...
Mommy does a nice job there, yes?
Yeah, I feel something, feel something.
So, son, when you're ready to release,
Uh-huh.
Mommy does take it all in the mouth.
Okay.
She will take every single drop.
Control. Take control.
Okay.
That's it.
Sun.
Release sun.
Just let mommy finish you off and tell her thank you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I am so proud of you. Thanks dad. Thank you.
David.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Others.
Yet.
Now.
Hmm.
So, I'm going to go ahead and show you what I'm going to show you today.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
I'm going to try this soup.
I'm gonna try it with some noodles.
It's really good.
Oh!
It's really good!
This is a good soup.
It's very hot.
This soup is really good.
It's really good.
It's good.
Oh my god, that's so hot!
I think that's the hardest part for me when it comes to
people who know me and are familiar with my background.
I think that's the hardest part because
I can only see myself in the back of people's eyes.
The sound is so good.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Did you guys watch the last few weeks?
I hope you enjoyed the video!
I'm so excited to be back!
Thank you for watching!
I'm so happy to be on this video again today!
I didn't know I would do another one of these videos.
I'm very excited to do another video.
I thought this one would be fun to do.
I just wanted to share and I was like,
I'm gonna probably try and do a couple of these in the future.
I can't wait to do another video.
Oh
Come sit down.
Like this?
Uh huh.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Like this?
Oh my god.
Oh.
I was like what!
He was like yeah you want to go to the pharmacy.
He was like okay, I'm heading to the pharmacy now.
He was like wait a minute, I want to go to the pharmacy.
So he took me to the pharmacy.
Oh
I don't know, you're so pretty.
What else?
What else do I do for her?
Just tell me what you want.
Okay.
I just want to look at you.
Sit on me.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Sit around a little bit.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, this feels so good.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Oh
I don't know why I'm looking at her.
Then I start to notice that there are two things that I'm seeing…
I see a girl with a long black hair.
I'm trying to look at her face.
There's a black girl.
I thought it was a totally normal thing to do, but that's not the case.
I don't know why I'm crying, I don't know why I'm crying.
I don't know why I'm crying.
I don't know what to do.
I hope you guys enjoyed it, I'll be back soon!
I love you very much.
I wish we could go back in time and see it at this year's event.
I love you.
Thank you.
I thought I would never touch you.
But I have to.
I have to get back to Australia for the synchronization.
When I go back to England, I hope to see you again.
I mean, I really do.
Good job, son.
Oh, thanks, dad.
Honey, teach a man how to do doggy style.
I know that's your favorite.
Yeah.
Okay.
Make him a man, okay?
I will.
Thank you.
Okay, so.
Just put it in, okay, honey?
And you just do just like you were doing.
Okay.
Good job.
Right there.
That one?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Is that okay?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to say.
I'm going to sleep back on.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
and finally I gave birth
to my first baby
I was super excited
when I saw my first baby
it was a baby of a week
and baby was finally out
so I felt like I needed a little break
I was really excited
and we went back home
and my mom fed him
then I took him to the vet
and he was a really good boy
It's okay.
Oh, gosh, Mom, that was frickin' amazing.
You did so good, honey.
I'm ready for a nap.