Please come in.
Hello, doctor.
Hello, Mr. Faze. Long time no see.
Not since that, um...
Yeah, um...
Yeah, not since, uh...
I'm all right since.
Good to hear.
Yeah.
Happy to hear that. So, how can I help you today?
Yeah, um, so...
It's kind of related to, you know...
The same thing, but not exactly.
Okay, so you're having trouble in your nether regions?
Oh, okay. So, um, erection issues then?
Mr. Faze, I can assure you there's no such thing as running out of miles.
That's nice to hear.
Here, why don't we head over to the examination room?
Okay.
Why don't you go ahead and take your shirt off.
Okay, alright.
So, just my shirt, right?
Shorts too, actually. Everything.
Oh. Okay.
Here you go.
You're sure this is gonna work?
Oh, I'm sure I will
Yeah
Just want to make sure you're really relaxed
Yeah, I'm starting to feel very relaxed.
Good, good.
This is normal?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
How are you feeling?
Good.
It's very sensitive to the touch.
I like that.
Yeah?
That's different.
Just don't think too much.
Just let yourself feel the medicine working through your body
I really just want to open up all of the channels
to increase circulation I'm definitely starting to feel something
Yeah, that means it's circulating.
Now I just want you to take a few deep breaths.
I just want to test something, see if it'll work.
Breathing.
Sense of touch is really important.
Wow.
That's starting to feel so nice.
Good.
excite them.
Just gently, softly.
Wow, yeah, it's starting to feel super good Good, good
Okay, I'll put this
Don't worry, it's all normal
Definitely making me excited
Good, good
I see that
Let's move slowly
You are doing so, so good, Mr. Finn.
I am.
My God.
Keep those eyes closed, okay?
Keep breathing.
Keep breathing, keep breathing.
Oh good, oh yeah, we've definitely got circulation.
Just really focus on how your genitals feel.
Okay, I can do that
Nothing else
Oh wow
Let's get it a little bit wet
Let's squeeze it a little bit
Yeah?
Yeah, that feels so good
Does it?
Yeah
I'm starting to really feel it
I see that
I'm just gonna stroke it a little bit, okay?
Yeah, it's starting to feel so good
Oh my god
Alright, well...
Now I'm just gonna try something.
I want you to tell me how it makes you feel, okay?
Okay.
Oh wow, it's warm.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah, oh my god.
Oh wow, definitely feel that.
Yeah, see, look how hard you're getting.
Grab themselves.
Oh yeah, oh my god.
Yes.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, grow nice and stiff.
Oh P.S., oh my god.
Oh, you're definitely a grower.
Oh, yeah.
Oh fuck, look at these balls, it's gross.
Yes, oh my god, please.
Oh, it feels so warm, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Yeah, pull them down for me, I'd love that, ooh.
What about your cock, do you like the tip of it or the whole shaft?
Oh, the whole thing, wow.
No, no.
Oh yeah, look at all these blood vessels.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
Oh my gosh, she's so nice, oh my God, it's so hard to.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Something really fun.
I told you I'd make you feel really good, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
I want you to feel something very special now.
Mmm.
How does that feel?
So good, oh my.
Oh my gosh.
Oh wow.
Oh my God.
Oh my
Ahhhh
Oh wow
mmm
Oh so good
Mmm
mmm
Mm-hmm
Oh
Yes, oh my god
Oh my god
Oh yeah
Fuck
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God, yeah. I love when your tongue's in my mouth.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Does that feel nice?
Yes, I'm so excited.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, have fun with me, explore new ideas.
Put my cock in your mouth for me.
Oh, how's that?
Oh, wow.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah, just like that.
Oh my goodness.
Oh
Sometimes trying new things can be very helpful
Oh my gosh, that's amazing!
Oh my gosh, yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Oh wow.
Yeah, just like that.
Oh.
oh
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
You're gonna jiggle and something, yeah.
I love that.
You like that.
Oh, anything I can do to help.
Anything I can do to help.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh my gosh!
Wow!
Oh yeah!
Oh, tell me how good that feels.
It's so nice.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, yeah, just right there.
Oh, my God.
You know, I think it's my turn now.
You think it's your turn?
Oh, I like that idea.
Let's try that.
You want to lick my pussy?
Yeah.
Let's try that.
You want to lick my pussy?
Yes, lick my pussy.
Yeah.
Let me get a good taste of it.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Taste that, taste that pussy.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes.
Ah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, fuck, yes.
I feel that tightness all around your fingers.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you pulled it with your mouth.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, gosh, you're so good at that.
Oh, so cute.
Ah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, gosh.
Oh.
Ah.
Mm.
Oh, wow.
You don't need that.
You can march on that pussy.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yes.
Ah.
It's so good with your mouth and your fingers.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, yes, oh God, please don't stop.
Please don't stop, please don't stop, please help me.
God, yes, oh fuck, you're gonna make me cum.
Oh my God, oh my God,
You're gonna make me fucking cum, oh my god, yes!
Oh, oh, oh, fuck yes, oh my god, oh shit, oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh god, oh my god, it was so wild.
Oh, do you wanna feel this dripping wet pussy now?
Oh, oh fuck.
Oh god.
Oh my.
Oh my god.
Wipe your faces.
Yes.
Oh god.
Okay.
Yes.
Oh god.
I do not know what that is.
I do not know.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Come on back, honey, I'll just suck you down now.
Oh, God.
Tell me when.
Yes, just tell me.
Oh, God.
Tell me when, yeah.
Yes!
Oh my god!
I'm coming!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh, please.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah, right.
Yeah, I can see.
Oh, yeah, fuck.
The fucking pussy cheek.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, keep using my pussy for your pussy.
Yes, mmhmm.
Oh my God.
Do you like these baguettes?
Oh, so cute.
Oh, God.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh.
Yes.
Mmm, yes.
You're doing so good.
oh my god yes oh my god so deep yes right on the fucking spot
Uh, oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, God.
Yes, fuck you.
Uh.
God.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Uh.
Shit.
Oh.
Uh.
Fuck you.
Oh my god, oh, oh fuck, oh my god, right there.
Yeah, oh my god.
Right fucking there, oh my god.
Here, why don't you turn over?
Oh, yeah?
Wanna try that?
Oh, shit.
How's that?
Alright.
Oh my god.
Ugh.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my god.
Ugh.
Oh yeah.
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah, fuck you.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you do.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck you.
I don't know, I feel so fucking good.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I feel so fucking good.
Oh, God, it just feels so good in my pussy, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, fuck that pussy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God, yes, Jesus, that pussy, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh, God, you're so big again.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, you.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh.
It's so good.
Oh fuck yes.
Oh my god right there.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck!
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
My hands.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck!
Oh
Oh God, oh yes, I feel good.
Oh my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, you crack me so hard.
Oh, fuck it.
Oh, fuck, oh my God, oh my God.
Oh my god, I feel so good!
Oh fuck!
Oh!
Oh fuck yes!
Yes!
Oh!
Oh my god!
Oh fuck!
Oh!
Oh my god!
Fuck me.
Let me rest in peace.
Oh fuck.
Oh god yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Oh fuck yes.
Oh fuck yes yes yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, yes.
Oh, god, it feels so good.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, it's so good.
Oh, yeah, you feel me clenching around that cock?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god you made me come so hard
Let me taste that ass again, baby.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my.
Yeah.
Oh yes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, just like that, oh my god.
Oh yeah, peace.
Yes.
Oh, butt.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Does that feel good when I have my tongue up your ass?
Oh my god.
Yeah, just like that, just like that, you have a good time, oh my god.
Yes.
Oh my goodness.
Keep going.
It's OK.
Oh.
Oh thank you, Lord.
Lord, bless me.
Yes.
Oh.
You're cleaning my face.
Oh my goodness.
Oh!
Ugh!
Ugh.
Oh fuck yeah.
Oh.
Ugh.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Ugh.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Ugh.
Oh God.
Oh this medicine works miracles.
Ugh.
Can I take some for the road?
And you know, actually, Mr. FaZe, it was really just simple vitamins.
Your problem was that you were just too much in your head.
Try not to worry so much, okay?
Yeah.
Just relax.