please come in hello doctor hello mr. phase long time no see not since that uh yeah yeah
not since I'm alright since good to hear yeah happy to hear that so how can I help you today
Yeah, um, so, it's kind of related to, you know, the same thing, but not exactly.
Okay, so you're having trouble in your nether regions?
Exactly. Nothing bio or anything, just like, I can't really get ready for action.
Oh, okay, so, um, erection issues then?
Yes. I don't know if it's ever since the aftermath of my illness, or if it's an age thing, or, my goodness, if I've ever used it, or I've ran out of miles. I don't know.
Well, Mr. Faze, I can assure you there's no such thing as running out of miles.
That's nice to hear.
Here, why don't we head over to the examination room?
Okay.
Why don't you go ahead and take your shirt off.
Okay, alright.
So, just my shirt, right?
Uh, shorts too, actually.
Everything.
Oh, okay.
Here you go.
You sure this is gonna work?
Oh, I'm sure it will.
Okay, well now, Mr. Faze,
let's get you more comfortable.
I'm just gonna lean you back a little bit.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just want to make sure you're really relaxed.
Yeah, I'm starting to feel very relaxed.
Good, good.
This is normal?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
How are you feeling?
Good.
It's like very sensitive to the touch.
I like that.
Yeah?
That's different.
Just don't think too much.
Just let yourself feel the medicine
working through your body Wow really just want to open up all of the
channels to increase circulation yeah I'm definitely starting to feel
something yeah that means it's circulating now I just want you to take
a few deep breaths I just want to test something see if it'll work
keep breathing just going to activate the various senses okay sense of touch is really important
that's so nice there are a lot of nerve endings around the genitalia so we're
We're just going to lightly excite them, just gently, softly.
Wow, yeah.
It's starting to feel super good.
Good, good.
OK.
Get a lot of circulation into your muscles.
Now I'm going to mimic the actual environment that you wish to be aroused in, okay?
Don't worry, it's all normal.
Oh, you're definitely making me excited.
Good.
I see that.
All right.
Let's move slowly.
Oh.
You are doing so, so good, Mr. Finn.
I am. My God.
Keep those eyes closed, okay?
And keep breathing.
Oh, yeah. We definitely got circulation.
Just really focus on how your genitals feel.
Okay. I can do that.
Nothing else.
Let's get it a little bit wet.
Sweet.
Oh, that feels so good.
Doesn't it?
Yeah.
I'm starting to really feel it.
I see that.
I'm just going to stroke it a little bit, OK?
Yeah, it's starting to feel so good.
All right.
All right, well, I'm just gonna try something.
I want you to tell me how it makes you feel, okay?
Okay.
It's warm.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh wow.
Definitely feel that.
Yeah, see, look how hard you're getting.
Problem solved.
Oh yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh, you're growing nice and stiff.
You're definitely a grower.
get these balls
oh my god
it feels so warm
Oh, my God.
Are your balls dancing now?
Yeah, pull them for me.
You want me to pull the body?
Come down for me.
I'd love that.
What about your cock?
Do you like the tip, please?
Or the whole shot?
the whole thing, wow
oh yeah, look at all these
oh my god
yes
oh wow
Oh my gosh, she's so nice, oh my gosh, it's so hard to, oh my gosh, it's so hard to, oh
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my goodness.
Just like that.
Oh my god.
You know what?
I'm gonna show you something kinda cool, okay?
Okay.
Something really fun.
I told you I'd make you feel really good, right?
Yeah.
Okay, well I want you to feel something very special now.
how does that feel?
so good
oh my
oh my god
oh wow
Whoa.
Fuck.
Mm-hmm
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yes, oh my gosh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
So hard.
Oh my god, yeah, I love when your tongue's in my hand.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh yeah.
Does that feel nice?
That's your favorite?
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh, yes, ooh, ooh, fuck, oh my gosh, that's so good.
See, I told you I'd make you feel good.
Does that not feel good with my tongue up your ass?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, have fun with me, explore new ideas.
I'm going to put my cock in your mouth for a minute.
Oh, how's that?
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh yeah, just like that, oh my goodness.
Oh wow, I've never felt like this.
sometimes trying new things can be very helpful
oh my gosh yeah oh my gosh
Yeah, just like that.
Oh, that's so nice.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Oh, gosh.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Anything I can do to help.
Oh my gosh.
Tell me how good that feels.
It's so nice.
Oh, yeah, just right there, oh my god.
Yeah, right there, right there, yes.
Oh my god.
I think it's my turn now.
you think it's your turn? oh I like that idea
let's try that
you wanna lick my pussy?
yes
let me get a good taste of it
oh my god
oh yes
oh
oh fuck yes
taste it
taste that pussy yes
oh yes oh my god
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, yes.
Yes. Oh, good.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, fuck, yes.
I feel that tight hole around your fingers.
Yes.
Oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, you pulled it with your
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, gosh, you're so good at that.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, wow.
Oh my god, yes, oh my god, yes, it's so good, yes, oh fuck, oh my god, yes, oh my god,
He is so good, he is.
Oh, fuck, he is.
Oh, you were so good with your mouth and your fingers.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, good, he is.
Oh god, please don't stop, please don't stop, please don't stop, please don't stop, oh my god, yes, oh fuck, you're gonna make me cum, oh my god, oh my god, you're gonna make me fucking cum, oh my god, yes, oh, oh, oh, fuck, yes, oh my god, oh, shit, oh my god, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh my God, it was so loud.
Oh, do you want to feel this dripping wet pussy now?
Yes, I want to feel it.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Where are your faces?
Oh my god, yes, yes, oh my god, okay, oh, oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck, yes,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh good. Oh fuck you. Oh good. Oh it's my spot so good. Oh good. Oh good. Oh fuck you. Oh my god. Oh good. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh my god. Oh yeah. Oh fuck you.
Look at that.
Oh my god.
Yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, God!
Oh, yeah, man!
Yeah, you're cheap!
Yeah, fuck!
You're a fucking pussy, cheap!
Yes!
Oh, I keep using my pussy for your pussy.
Oh, my God.
I really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really,
oh my god yes oh my god so deep yes right on that fucking spot
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes, it's so bad.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just
Oh fuck you
Oh my god
Oh fuck
Oh my god right there
Right fucking there
Oh my god
Here why don't you turn over
Really? Wanna try that?
Oh shit
Oh god yes
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, oh, yeah, fuck it.
Fuck that machine.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, fuck, oh, mm, mm, oh, yeah, oh, you do that, yes, make that pussy with your cock, oh, fuck, uh-huh, oh, oh, yes, oh, oh, fuck you, oh, yeah, I like that, oh, that feels so fucking good, oh, yeah, oh, oh, it feels so fucking good, oh, god, that's sick,
Oh my god, am I dizzy, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes.
Yeah, fuck, I'm dizzy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, god, yes.
Jesus, I'm dizzy, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh
My god, yes
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, God, yes. Oh, my God.
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes. Oh, my God.
Oh my god right there
Oh my god
Oh fuck
F**k!
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, my God, oh, oh, fuck, oh, fuck, oh,
Oh f**k yes.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Yes.
Uh huh.
Oh f**k.
Oh
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh, fuck, oh my god, yes, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, God.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I feel good.
Oh my God.
Oh God.
Oh, fuck, oh God, you crunk it so hard.
Oh, oh, oh, fuck you, it's, oh fuck, oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God, yes, yes, oh fuck, oh fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, oh, my God, oh, fuck, oh, yes, mm-hmm, oh, my God, it feels so good, oh, fuck, uh-huh, oh, fuck, oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes,
Oh my god, oh fuck you, oh my god, oh fuck you, yes, oh my god, oh fuck, oh fuck yes,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, oh fuck yeah, oh yes, oh god, it feels so good, oh my god, oh fuck, oh fuck it, so good, oh yeah, you feel me clutching around that cock, oh my god,
Oh, my God. Oh, yes. Oh, my God. I feel so good. Oh, fuck. Oh, my God. Oh, fuck you. Oh, God.
oh fuck me fuck me please fuck me oh my god oh fuck yeah please don't stop oh yes
oh fuck yeah please don't stop oh my god oh my god fuck you're gonna make me cum please don't
stop oh my god yes oh my god you made me come so hard let me taste that ass again baby
Oh yeah, you like that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah, just like that, oh my god, oh yeah, make it stop, yes, oh my god, oh my god, oh
Oh
Oh, yeah.
Just like that, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, does that feel good?
Can I have my tongue up your ass?
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Tongue.
All right.
Yeah, just like that.
Just like that.
You have a good tongue.
Oh, oh my God.
Oh my God.
Oh, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Oh, that's how we are.
Oh, that's me.
I can feel it. Yes.
You're closing my face.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, dog.
Oh, this medicine works miracles.
Can I take some for the road?
Um, you know, actually, Mr. Faze, it was really just simple vitamins.
Your problem was that you were just too much in your head.
Try not to worry so much, okay?
Just relax.
you