overqualified for the bank. I didn't expect you to be this pretty.
Oh, I think so.
Okay.
Yeah.
I hope so.
Wow.
You, uh, dress pretty sexy for your appraisals.
You must get, uh, good remarks.
Um, well, I have always gotten great feedback.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Great reviews, huh?
Great reviews.
Five star.
Five star?
Yes.
Always.
But, anyway, should we get to the appraisal?
Oh, yeah, for sure.
This is a great house here, I think.
When was it built?
I actually really need, about one year ago.
Oh, nice.
But I really need it to come in at a high appraisal.
I'm trying to sell it for $2 million.
$2 million?
That's a lot of money.
In this area?
Yeah.
You got to help me out here.
Okay, this is nice.
Do you mind if I take some photos?
No, go right ahead.
Okay, it'll help me.
You just put your phone.
That's where you keep your phone?
Oh, it doesn't fit in my pocket properly.
Yeah, this is a very tight...
See, it's like...
It's a very tight outfit.
You're wearing it here.
It just doesn't look right, so I just put it in there.
Oh, yeah.
I don't blame you.
Yeah.
I'd do the same thing if I had a gigantic...
Excuse me?
Uh, nothing. Sorry.
Um, okay.
Take as many pictures as you want.
Okay.
I mean, the ceiling's interesting, so...
So...
Pictures came out okay?
Yeah, it's coming out okay.
Oh, sorry.
Oh my god.
What was that?
Oh, nothing.
Was that you?
No.
No, that was just...
Are you sure?
That looked a lot...
No, that wasn't me.
Yeah.
Wow.
That was a...
That looked like an interesting picture.
All right.
Show me the other rooms.
Do you want to see the bathroom in here?
Is it worth having a look?
Okay.
It's a nice shower.
It actually is a nice big shower.
It's a nice big shower.
I'm sure you could have a little fun in there.
Oh, yeah.
But I'm still not seeing $2 million worth here.
Oh, geez.
Show me around a little more maybe.
Okay. Let's go back downstairs.
Okay.
Here.
I see you've got another small bedroom there.
Nothing much.
I might put some things into the computer.
Yeah, why don't you put some stuff in there.
Let me see what kind of offer I can get you.
better if you're on your knees worshiping my big natural tits I can
see your cock bulging out of your jeans let's not play around you've been
this big before.
This big, this soft.
You wanna get smothered by them?
Slide that cock in between them.
Bouncing around your cock.
So, um...
Fuck.
So, I guess, uh...
I'm gonna get serious about this...
On my knees, huh?
...breast wash-up.
Yeah, that's right.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Look at that fucking cleavage.
Mmm.
That's those big tits on your face.
Oh my god, yes.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Oh god, I would love to
Slide my cock right in between these.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
That's good enough.
Fuck yes.
Oh, yeah.
Fucking squeezing, bouncing.
Fuck yes.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Don't you want to rub it off of my side of the scalp?
Yeah, slide that right up.
That looks so good.
Fuck yes.
Oh
Fucking good
You're gonna get me off, huh?
Look at that, you can't even see my cock in between those.
Disappear between those big titties.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Fuck yes.
Yeah, juggle those fucking titties.
All over my cock.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, right on those nipples, slap it on there.
Yeah, lick your nipple.
Yeah, just like that.
That looks so good.
Ah, fuck me.
I'm gonna need an escape up here right now.
Oh, god.
Rub that ass up in there.
That looks so good.
right on that shiny skin
oh god
yes
I'm gonna slap my big toes
yeah
slap my big toes
yes
oh god
Oh god, let's go over here so I can put my pussy on that one.
Oh god, you're so sexy.
Fuck yes.
I'm gonna wash up that pussy too.
Look at that.
Fuck.
Oh, my God, your tongue is so big, guys.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Look at that beautiful pussy.
Look at that.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, take those babies.
Yeah, you fucking bury your face in that.
I like that.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, that looks so good.
Oh, God.
Can I just stick that in?
Already?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, oh, oh, my God.
God, yes.
And I knew Percy would be good.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
That fucking dick feels so good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my...
Yes.
Oh, God damn.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes. Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yes, fuck, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, fucking take me, take me.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Oh yeah, yes, yes, oh fuck.
Yeah, yes, yes.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, that's it.
Oh my god, don't fuck me with stuff like that.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
And that fucking pussy's so fucking close to coming on that cock.
Yes.
Take that fucking dick.
Oh.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Ah.
Oh, my God, you...
Yeah.
Oh, my God, I love how you fucking...
Give me that dick like that.
Yes, yes.
Oh, look at this.
Yeah.
I'll fucking smother you with them.
Come right here.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, it's...
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck!
This is so fucking wet!
Yeah, fucking take it! Oh my god!
Fuck!
Yeah, I can't breathe! Fuck!
Oh my god!
Let me see those fucking...
Oh, yeah. Fuck yes.
Oh, shit. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, so fucking...
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Shit.
Fuck yes
Oh, God.
Oh, that's perfect fucking.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Shake all those big titties around it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, that feels so good.
So nice and soft.
Is that what you wanted when I walked through the door?
Oh, fuck yes.
Yeah, man.
These fucking perfect test moments.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh.
Ooh.
Oh, yeah.
Mm.
Fuck.
Yes.
Fuck. Oh, my God.
Yes. Fuck.
Oh, that feels so good.
Yes. Fucking give it to me.
Oh, my God. Fuck.
Oh, fuck, yeah. Your balls are hitting my clit.
Yes. Fuck, yeah.
Yes. Oh, shit. Yes. Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck. Yes.
It made me fucking cum on that dick
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Holy fuck, have you seen it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Oh, fuck
Oh, god damn
Oh, yes
Oh, my god, you have to fucking back to me
and just slam me with that dick
Oh, fuck
Yes
Fuck yes! Give me the dick!
Oh my god! Fuck!
Oh shit!
Oh yes!
Fuck yes!
Oh yeah, I can see it here.
Yes! Oh my god!
Yes!
Yes, yeah, I make those fucking tits bounce really fucking slammy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck!
Oh, you!
Yes, that felt so fucking good.
Yes.
Fuck, yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah, I love watching it coming like that.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
This isn't fucking hard to see.
Fuck.
Oh, god, look.
Yes.
Mm.
Fuck
Oh yeah
Fucking eat that pussy at the same time
Fuck
Oh my god
Let me get all that fucking spit for you
Oh my gosh, you eat that fucking pussy so good.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you fucking took it so good on that.
Yeah, squeeze that cock.
Yeah.
Yeah, I want that fucking cock in my pussy again.
Yeah, kick those legs back, I can see them.
You should give it to me.
Oh, yes.
Yes, fuck.
Look at that.
Do you want me to fuck that to you?
Yes, please.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes.
I look so fucking good.
Oh my god, fuck.
Yeah, look there's no person, push that button.
Yes, excuse us.
Look at that.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Look! Look at that.
Yes!
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Fuck yes.
Oh my gosh.
Yes.
I'm going to fucking shake those big tits around that cup.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, look at that.
Perfect.
Oh, god damn.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, look at that cum-puppet face.
You look so good with that shit.
Thank you.