Oh, look at this one.
Remember that Christmas we had in Palm Springs?
How could he forget?
You hint at another vacay every year.
Well, because she's a real trip.
I mean, I mean, it was a real treat.
It was a real treat.
So did you ever hear about that idiot Brandon's car?
Uh, no.
And I really don't think it's a priority for the police,
especially after that rumor with the FBI.
I think it could have been an honest mistake.
He's been going through a lot, you know.
Well, think harder.
You know, he wears the same sweater every year.
And he smells like eggnog.
That's what I was smelling.
Happy holidays! I hope I'm not too late.
You always make me wait.
I'm sorry, but you know, it's like I was driving.
I tried to take the 11, and then I take an exit on the Medina.
Mm-mm-mm. Put that anger away. You have to. It's tradition.
You don't want to show too much attention, won't you? Right?
Ayumi.
Ah, good to see you.
Good to see you.
He's late, so. Always late.
That's a beautiful tree.
Better than last year.
How was the drive?
It was good.
Green and green.
Honey, I'm home!
Tradition.
Yep, it's tradition.
Thank you ladies.
I do have one extra special surprise. Look who I brought with me.
It was good.
Come here.
I thought you were going to be at the retreat for at least another year.
They couldn't keep me away from the dynamic jewels.
can fall from those sticky fingers.
It must have been a long trip, huh?
Especially alone.
You couldn't find a partner on that side of the world?
And you, Jenna, how have you been?
Been keeping up on your reading?
Read anybody's diaries lately?
None that were as exciting as yours.
I still think some freshmen have copies if you'd like.
Wow, the three of you in a house all night?
That's a treat, amazing.
I need a drink.
I can help you with that.
No, no, honey, I got this.
Jenna, do you mind handling this?
Thanks.
Hey, get those back.
Do you have any Earl Grey?
I could use a little kick.
I'll say.
What are you really doing here?
This is my house now, and I really don't
think I appreciate you being here.
Aw, what's wrong?
I thought all of our previous friction was forgiven.
Water under the bridge, like you said.
Why don't you stay out of my life and out of Oliver's?
We know how this will end.
Oh, I see we've reached the veiled threat portion of the conversation.
Give it up already.
We chased you out of this town once before, and we can do it again.
It's called self-sacrifice. Maybe one day you'll understand that.
Why are you trying to take the only family that I have left?
You're boiling.
Here.
Thanks for the tea.
You know, these treats got me pretty parched.
Hey, Jenna?
Mind making me one of your famous eggnogs, please?
Ugh, fine.
Maybe more entertaining than you useless idiots.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Excuse you.
Couple of Blue Bulls.
We're going to come help you.
Yes.
Have you been naughty or nice this year?
Oh, very nice.
Another ball.
There's so many to play with.
There are.
Are you going to do anything else after?
I sure am.
Oh, I can't wait.
Oh, I can see how wide I can spread my legs.
Mm.
Still flexible?
Should I show them?
Oh, yes.
Mm.
What do you think?
I should have added the balls.
Mm.
So, what'd you say?
How many eggs it was to make a Naughty Game?
What?
You know...
Fuck this!
Something wrong?
Mistique, Mistique, come on.
You can't just leave us like that.
She's gone.
It takes a while to make eggnog, right?
How long does it take?
At least 7 minutes.
I can decorate that.
Oh wow.
You know I think I'd prefer your actual balls.
I know.
Yes.
Oh fuck yes.
Oh I have missed this cock.
Oh, shit.
So cute.
None of these don't need to be in here.
Bring the bells up, right?
I think you're gonna know.
No, you won't.
So you ever made the bell spin?
Jingle bells, jingle bells.
Oh yes.
let me suck on those balls.
Oh, man.
You have to suck on it.
Oh, yes.
Oh yes, nice and deep, stick those balls in there.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, yeah, I need to get this in there.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh.
Yes.
Yes!
I have the old menu.
My favorite.
What is your favorite?
Oh my god, I miss that so much.
It feels so fucking good in there.
Yes, yes, give it to me, oh, fuck, yes, take me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, yeah, I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, fuck, yes, yes, oh, fuck,
Oh, you might push me fast.
Give him a chance.
Oh, come on.
Fuck.
Yes.
I love when you watch.
You always liked it when I was watching.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fuck me.
Let me suck it. Let me suck it.
Let me see.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Yeah, that's so fucking good!
How do you say? Eggnog?
Eggnog.
Yes.
I think it takes a while.
When they cook the eggnog, we make the eggnog.
Yes.
Oh my God.
What are you doing now?
I want to end that off.
Yeah?
Oh, fuck! It's so tight.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Yes, please.
Yes, please. Yes.
Oh, my God.
This feels so good.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Let me get a pulse deep in there.
Oh, yes.
Fuck you, yes.
You know I fucking do.
Come on, give me that dick, baby, please.
Please, give me that fucking cock, man.
You want a cock?
Come on.
Oh, you want a cock?
Hold the cock, you're going.
Yes.
Oh my God, it's so fucking full.
Fuck.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
You know, I fucking love it. You know, I fucking love it. Yeah
I love when you work hard for my orgasms
Oh, yeah.
You're close to coming inside us, I don't know why.
Good, because I want you to keep fucking me.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
working for me yeah oh yes oh i'm gonna go back and forth between my
pussy and that's it oh yeah
a couple of strokes in there and a couple of strokes in there
yeah oh oh god oh my holes missed you so fucking much
You know I fucking did it.
Yes.
Fuck.
Yes, give me that
fucking cock.
Yes.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
Oh, fuck, that's good.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, baby, fuck.
yeah i want to taste
Oh, my f***ing god.
Yes, I need more of those f***ing dicks.
Here?
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
F*** yes.
Fuck yes! Oh my god!
Oh my god!
Yes!
Fuck it, turn me. Turn me. Turn me.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck yes, so good, so good, so good, so good.
Come on, come over here, just bend over for me.
Oh yes, you want to see the mic, correct?
Yes.
Good, yes, fuck.
Baby, fuck yes.
Oh yes, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, yes.
Yes!
I want you to fucking give it to me.
Yes, I love you.
I love you so much.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck.
Yeah, that's fucking good.
Like, damn.
Oh, my God.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I'm gonna fucking cum on this dick.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
How do you boys expect me to function after that?
Bring me this dick.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
You boys haven't fucked my tits.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
You're so talented.
Yes.
You're going to pay it off.
Yes, it is.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
You're going to have to cough again.
Mm-hmm.
No, I do.
Fuck you.
Fuck yes!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, don't fucking stop me.
I'm so fucking good at this.
Oh my god.
I'm so close.
I'm so fucking close to
coming on those two.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, yeah, that's it.
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh
Oh my god.
Get out of here.
can you tell what you're gonna take oh you're such a dirty fucking boy
right down that chimney
oh fuck you
Show me how much you want to make me cum.
Show me how much you want to make me cum!
Fuck!
That's it, baby!
Fuck yes!
Oh my god!
He really fucking showed me.
Come back here.
Give me more of that dick.
Give me more of that fucking dick.
Oh my god.
The dynamic duo back at it.
Oh fuck.
Oh I didn't know how sensitive my feet are.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes.
me?
I don't know!
Oh my God!
Don't stop, don't stop.
Come on down on me.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Here it is.
You want the heart now?
C'mon!
Mm-hmm. Give it to me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck. I'm gonna cry.
Uh-huh.
Oh!
Mmm.
Oh, fuck.
Damn.
Mmm.
You both had such nice big loads from me.
Mmm, you both obviously missed me.
So I guess Mystique and Jenna aren't draining those balls enough.
We're only cooking.
We need our own eggnog on the face.
I guess I better get dressed before they finish up that eggnog.
You have two more minutes.
Oh, let's get dressed.
Oh, this eggnog's pretty good.
Right?
Oh, would you look at that?
Not the watch.
It's time to open gifts.
Come on, follow me this way.
Happy holidays.
but maybe it's a new year so a new start.
Bitch. Kitch. I was calling my new diary
You got a little something on your leg.
Oh, it's just a little eggnog.