Ah finally! Come on then, I had a lot of patience today and not enough patience.
Put this gown on for me and take a seat on the bed. You ready?
So let's just run over the basics quickly. Your name, date of birth, do you
have any special needs? No, I meant like if you have any special needs in the
following area. So it could be vision, hearing, mobility. Okay, what about any
medications you're currently on? Allergies? Okay, so I was reading over
your chart and it appears that you wanted a physical to make sure that this
isn't purely a psychosomatic issue, is that correct? So it says here specific
issues over arousal and sexual activity. Okay.
Okay, um, what is your sexual history?
Mm-hmm, um, and how many sexual partners have you had?
Okay, uh, well, let's start with the physical.
I want you to just relax.
I'm going to check your heartbeat first.
I want you to take a deep breath in and out.
Deep breath in and out.
Your heartbeat is racing.
Hmm.
Let me take your temperature.
98.69. Interesting. Okay. Let's have a look at your eyes. Just follow the light. I didn't
You can put the light down there.
Okay, that looks fine.
All right, I'm gonna test your mobility.
Okay, ready?
Okay.
That's good.
Everything appears to be fine.
All right, let's check your blood pressure.
Just relax.
Wow, okay.
I mean, physically, you seem to be in great condition.
Although, I just wanna check your heart rate again
because the fact that your heart was racing,
it's a little problematic oh wait why are you squirming so much
let me remind you that this is a professional setting um okay um i want you
to open your mouth
and stick out your tongue say ah
Ah.
Oh, come on.
You can do better than that.
Like really like stick it out.
Like, ah.
Ah.
Nice and wide.
Mm-hmm, I'm not gonna get a new one.
Okay.
Come up wide.
Say ah.
Mm.
Ah.
Oh my goodness. This is so distracting. Oh my.
Well, everything appears to be in order. I'm surprised that you've come in for issues with arousal and sexual activity.
But let's take a closer look.
I'm going to enjoy this physical now don't get nervous I've done this thousands of times
times. And I've seen thousands of these. You know what? Get comfortable. First I'm just
going to take a little listen oh well you are throbbing you have a great dick
beat. The blood is definitely pumping.
Oh, it's starting to twitch. Let's take a listen to those balls. Oh, they're speaking
to me mmm they want to be drained but not yet I will be collecting a sample to
test your virility but I have to test a few other things first let's check your
Your temperature again.
Oh my, almost feverish.
Let's test your movement.
Oh, amazing.
And again.
Wow.
I have not seen movement like this
in all my years in the medical profession.
Very impressive. Just a very light tap on the balls.
Hmm. Very good.
Oh, before I do that, let me just look into your other eye.
Oh, everything looks great. Mmm.
Now I need to check the pressure down here.
Don't worry, I'm a professional.
Let's wrap this up.
I sure do love to pump a dick.
Oh my, wow.
How much pressure can you take?
Oh my goodness.
Wow.
Well, sir, I really do think that
this is all psychosomatic for you.
Everything appears to be.
A couple of other tests I can do.
I wanna test your stamina.
I can see that you can get hard
and stay hard,
but I wanna see for how long.
So in testing your stamina, I'm going to be in control of this dick.
I'm going to do whatever I want to it, and you're not going to come.
Even though I'm sure you could already.
A lot of my patients enjoy the feel of gloves wrapped around their dick.
Something about surgical gloves that drives them crazy.
See, they always feel safe in the hands of a professional.
Hmm, you like the feeling of my hot breath
on the head of your dick.
I know what you're thinking.
Hmm, you really wanna know what it's like
to get a blow job from your doctor.
Mm, well, normally I wouldn't,
but it will help me test your stamina and your virility.
Plus a little taste test of that pre-cone
will determine whether you're healthy.
and it does appear that you are.
Were you really being honest with me?
I don't see any issues with your desire
or your sexual function.
You've got a nice big dick and full balls.
You like that sound.
I suppose now would be a good time to talk about patient-doctor confidentiality.
Hmm. Anything that happens in this room stays in this room.
Oh my goodness. Hmm. Oh, is it getting hot in here?
Wow. Look at the way it stands upright.
Such healthy blood vessels pumping all that blood, making this cock rock hard for me.
me. Oh my goodness. I've never had a patient with a dick this big. I've seen so many cocks,
but I have to say this one is the nicest.
I have one other tool I'd like to try on you.
I don't normally bring this one out.
I mean, this is from my personal collection.
I just want to see how this dick reacts.
Ah, hmm, sensitive.
What about a little on those balls?
Hmm, I like that you're such a trusting patient
that you'll let me do whatever I want to you, hmm?
You know you're in good hands.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
Nice little trust test.
Oh, whoops.
I hope you don't mind if I bring them all the way out.
I like them. I saw your dick start twitching and they do come in handy when
I'm doing these physical exams. They tend to help with the arousal process
process. Although you didn't have any problem with that. So I am curious as to why you were
sent to me. But I'm glad you're here now. Maybe you'd like to test your stamina between
between these big tits, mm, mm, that's it, yes, oh, fuck yes, mm, I like the way those
Those big soft tits wrap around that cock, yeah.
Ooh, that makes you rock hard.
I love feeling that cock so hard between these soft tits.
I like the contrast.
Oh, you're making your doctor incredibly happy.
Mm, oh yes, why don't you thrust up between these tits?
Yes, mm, mm, that's a good boy.
Oh, you do have incredible stamina.
Mm, ooh.
Oh, I'm very impressed.
Stroke that big dick between these tics.
I hope that you know that everything that I am doing
is completely professional.
I wouldn't want you to think that I'm taking advantage
of my position.
And jiggle these soft tits around that tit.
I'm very impressed,
but I can tell that you're getting closer
between these tits.
And you wanna impress me more, don't you?
So you wouldn't wanna drain those balls just yet.
You wanna show me just how long you can last.
I'm in control of that cum. I get to decide when you cum. Plus, the more we edge you, the bigger
the sample size. We need as much of that sperm as possible to determine your virility and your
overall health. So we're gonna tease and edge that dick so that those balls fill
up with cum until they're heavy and aching to be drained and that's when I
will determine that you are ready to deliver me the sample that I need.
Well, I see that you're quite good at holding back that cum while I stroke you while in
between these tits, but I have another challenge for you.
you. I wonder how long you'll last once I slide this dick inside my wet pussy. You're
gonna try and impress me, aren't you? Yes, you are. And you're gonna fuck me for as long
long as I ask you to. I'm going to make it all wet with my spit.
Oh my god. I'm going to do a good job not coming from that mouth too.
Can't forget about these bowls.
The best way to test healthy bowls is to measure them in my mouth.
Oh, you haven't heard that?
Yeah, it's a well-kept secret in the medical profession.
Yeah, they haven't come up with an instrument yet.
As good as a mouth.
Don't you come.
Well my mouth determines that these balls are indeed very healthy and filled with cum to me.
but let's put you to the test
yes grab them
you don't like the way they feel so big and soft yeah
oh you're gonna like the way this feels too
Yes. Get me nice and wet and ready for this big dick.
Fuck. Such a helpful patient.
Hmm. Let's see if it's ready. Oh, yes. Oh, yeah, she is ready.
Fuck. Ooh. I'm gonna test the heaviness. Damn, that's a heavy dick.
Oh, wow. Feels so good. Yes. Wow. That is an incredible cup.
Fuck.
Let's see how long you can last inside that pussy, don't you come.
I'm gonna give you some speed tests, sometimes fast, sometimes slow.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, fuck, yes, oh my god.
But you know what the ultimate test is?
Feeling a pussy clench down on that dick,
feeling me cum on it, and being able to push through
and not cum, because just because I've had an orgasm
doesn't mean i'm done with sex and doesn't mean i'm ready for you to come
good yes
oh my god i'm getting so close on that day yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Why are you, like, feeling my pussy like that, grinding on you, yeah, getting every inch of that pussy all over that dick, fuck, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, you want to fuck me, yeah, show me what you've got, oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh fuck, oh my god, let me taste
my drink, oh my god, look at that pre-cup, yes, let me squeeze it out, oh yeah, oh my
Mmm, so sexy. Tastes so good.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Holy fu-
Mmm, oh my goodness.
Now so far, you've passed every test.
But I'm still not ready to collect that sample.
pull oh my god that's such a nice
Alright, fucks, fucks, deep fuck, yeah, you're like, you can spank me, go ahead, I love when
when my patients get into it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh,
yes, wow, oh my god, I feel so fucking good inside my pussy.
Oh my god, I wonder what the other patients are gonna think.
I'm making so much noise in here I think everyone's going to want a physical exam
wow fuck fuck yeah you're gonna give it to me yeah give it to me
do it, do it, do it, do it, give me that dick, yes, oh, oh, I felt you get close, I felt
you start to twitch, anyways, I'm gonna challenge you more, I'm gonna challenge you more, I'm
gonna jerk that fucking cock off inside that pussy, stroke you on the edge, pump that fucking
fucking dick inside me, yeah, oh fuck, yeah, pump it, edgy, oh yes, oh god, I bet you're
fucking leaking inside me, aren't you, with every stroke, with every pump, leaking that
pre-cum inside my pussy, yeah, pump it inside me, pump that fucking dick, oh my god, fuck,
Oh, you're going to make me fucking cum on that clock again.
You're going to make me cum.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Damn.
I am so impressed with you.
Oh, yes.
I have another challenge to you, it's a little different, how do you go with feet, cute little
feet, little piggies wrapped around that dick, wow, you're a dick,
is throbbing. Oh wow everything's coming with me this time. Oh my goodness. Wow. It's like
like your heart is in your cock.
I've never heard a dick beat so strong.
Wow.
So impressive.
How does that feel?
Yeah, soft souls wrapped around that shaft.
Yes.
Yes, mm, didn't think you'd like that, huh?
But it feels so good, doesn't it?
Mm, feels good for me too.
Here, wrap these toes around it.
Yeah, oh, you like my red pedicure?
Mm, those cute little toenails.
Yeah, oh, what about if I play with those balls too?
Yeah. Mmm. Oh my gosh. They're getting bigger and bigger. So filled for me. Mmm. Oh, fuck.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm. Mmm. Mmm. Mmm. Mmm. Don't you get any ideas? Not yet. Mm-mm.
Don't you dare.
Yes, I want to see how long you can handle it.
Oh slowest strokes. I can see that pre-cum flowing and I'm not quite ready for your sample yet.
Not quite yet. Keep that fucking cum in those balls. Don't you fucking dare.
don't you fucking dare not until i tell you to oh fuck oh i know how much you love these gloves
don't you yeah something naughty about them i mean that's just something so naughty
about being played with in the doctor's office, isn't it?
Mm, mm.
Oh, I can tell you're so close, but you know what?
I need to come one last time before I let you come.
Don't I deserve it?
Yes, I do.
fuck yes i'm gonna use that fucking dick to make myself calm
and you're not gonna fucking come until i'm done with it until i get mine
Fuck, oh my god, yes, oh fuck, yes, yeah, oh, oh, yeah, fuck, that felt so good, yes,
Yes, yes, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, huh, huh, huh, I'm getting so close, I'm so fucking
close on that, yes, yes, yeah, huh, yeah, like that, huh, I got it, I'm gonna fucking
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I'm ready to extract it.
Close your eyes.
Make it nice and fluffy for you.
Oh, you like that?
Yeah, you're so fucking close.
I'm gonna edge you just a little bit longer,
just a tiny bit.
I'm gonna give you a countdown, okay?
I'm gonna count down from 10
and then you're gonna give me that load.
You ready?
10,
nine,
eight,
seven,
seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, come for me, give me that sample, milk that cup,
Let's make sure we get every last drop out of that cup.
I got a little bit to clean up here.
Oh, that is quite a nice sample size.
In fact, it's large enough that I can take a little to myself.
Mmm.
Oh, it tastes very virile.
Anyway, I'm going to take the rest of this sample to get analyzed.
Although I'm pretty sure you're good.
So just get dressed.
You can leave your robe over here and I'll see you next time.