How's my favorite patient doing?
You are looking stronger every day. Very proud of you.
Looks like today might be our last session.
Kind of sad about that, but I am happy you're making a full recovery.
Ready for your session? I'm just gonna bend your leg up.
Hmm. Mobility is looking good.
oh your flexibility has improved a lot
let's compare mmm swelling not only neither don't worry it's completely
gets good just gonna have a little feel around I need to check your groin
Quite a bit of swelling there, isn't there?
We should really check the mobility and the flexibility of your cock too.
I mean it is a muscle after all.
I want to test the sensation. How does that feel?
Give it a once over on those balls.
Oh, you like that.
Let me just take a listen.
Oof! I can hear your dick beat.
Sounds very healthy. Very strong.
Actually, it gives me a shiver.
Want to take a listen to my heartbeat?
Oh, let me warm it up first.
It's beating fast for you.
I like the sound of my tongue.
You might like the feeling of my tongue somewhere else too.
oh fuck oh i can tell you're gonna make a full recovery
do you want to see it?
Oh, fuck that feels good.
I'm going to keep it in there for a little bit, you know, just in case.
You like the feeling of my gloves on that cup?
walking a tree but I will have some exercises for you to do at home maybe
you can practice right now yeah well for you to keep all of the results to
All the way, from the face to the tooth.
Now switch hands.
I like watching all the ways you practice.
You like playing with those balls too?
Let me handle these.
Flip your hand upside down.
better way.
it's a little unconventional but
I think it would be good to test it inside here
would you like that
hmm
oh fuck oh my god
Such a big day.
Oh, damn.
It's so tight with that butt plug in.
Fuck yes.
Yes.
I love it when it's deep like that.
Mmm, mmm.
Yeah.
Oh, start out nice and slow.
Just test it.
Mmm.
Then increase the pace a little.
Fuck.
Oh, oh, yeah.
That is so good.
Mmm.
Fuck yeah
Oh my god, fuck
Now I think you're ready to test the other hole
Yeah, it's so tight.
How does it sound?
That heartbeat is going to race once that dick is inside me.
Oh, fuck.
I guess I'm going to have my muscles stretched too, huh?
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh, I like to tease it.
Mm.
Yeah.
Yeah, you like how tight it is around that dick,
jerking you off with that tight little asshole.
Yeah, fuck, mm, yeah, I know you've been staring
at this ass, you've been wanting to be inside there
for a while, haven't you?
Yeah, finally, ah, ah, damn, that feels so good, mm.
Mmm, oh yeah, look what you do to it.
Mmm, fuck, I'm stretching it out.
Mmm, oh, fuck yes, I wanna feel inside there
with the gloves too.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh my God.
Yes.
You are already my favorite patient,
but I mean, no one's gonna top this.
You like it inside there?
Yeah?
You wanna try and squeeze in there?
Oh, fuck, that's tight.
Oh my God.
Oh, wow.
damn oh let's see how open it is now damn you want to go back and forth
Tight little pussy.
Oh, and that extra tight asshole.
Damn.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God.
I knew you were getting stronger each day.
Not like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, you wanna show me what you've got?
Oh yes, fuck, oh yeah, oh fuck yes.
Oh my God, I'm so fucking proud of you.
Look how far you've come.
When you first came in here,
you could barely even move your legs and look at you now.
I guess you just needed the right inspiration, right?
Mm, oh fuck yes.
oh my god yes take it take that little asshole yeah
Fuck!
You're like looking at those holes,
seeing what you've done to them.
Mmm, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Let me bounce that fucking ass on you.
Yes, yes,
straight from my ass.
It tastes so good.
I just want to worship this cock.
I bet you really want to know what's underneath this top, don't you?
Yeah, you've been thinking about it.
Mmm, I got something nice under here.
What do you think?
You like my lingerie?
Mmm, something about my scrubs though, isn't there?
Tons you want.
Oh yeah.
tits jiggles I do that mm-hmm I wish it take him out
Yeah, you keep jerking.
Let me take over.
Fuck.
Don't you come. I want to test your stamina too.
I know you like that view.
Those jiggly tits.
Oh, you want to be in between them, don't you?
Let me take this off.
This is a trick you learn at slumber parties.
Oh, you like that a little bit. Naughty boy. What about here? Be gentle.
Think of me and these big tits.
And if you ever need physical therapy again,
you know where to come back to.
Yes.
Oh, I hope nobody hears us.
They probably just think I'm doing
a vigorous manual exam on you which would be true all of you taste good
more of this dick inside my holes.
I hope you don't mind.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, oh, fuck, yeah, mm, fuck.
You like having those big tits bounce in your face?
Mm, mm, yeah, mm, fuck, oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
hurt anything. You can be my physiotherapist.
Oh, fuck. Oh, yeah.
I feel so good. Yeah. Yes.
Fuck yeah. Oh, yeah.
Take that little pussy. Oh, fuck.
You're so good with that dick. Oh, my God.
Fuck. Fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
oh damn
damn it's such a big dick
yeah yeah
oh that's so so good yes
oh all the way deep inside there let me give you those nice long strokes
all the way inside that house
i love feeling every inch of it slowly sliding inside me
Oh, fuck, damn, I feel so fucking good.
you rubbed my clit. you're so good at that.
holy fuck!
give me a second.
catch my breath.
oh my god.
damn.
stay right there not that you can go anywhere
wait let me try the pussy pose there we go
oh i'm gonna make sure your dick is working well from every angle
Yes, baby, that's it.
Yeah, just like that.
Just like that.
Oh my God.
Yeah, baby, come, come.
Oh my God, yes, yes, yes.
Ah, ah.
I'm gonna taste that arsehole right off that dick.
Mm.
Ooh, I taste so much pre-cum.
I'm not sure you're gonna be holding back much longer.
You're not gonna be able to, huh?
I think I need to take care of you now.
Mm.
Yeah, get comfortable.
I'm gonna milk you.
Mm.
Mmm, I know you're getting super close to giving me that, Laura.
Yeah, yeah, you want to give it to me?
Yeah, do it.
Mmm, yeah, grab these titties.
Oh, you want to go in between.
Oh, yes.
Fuck yes.
Mmm.
Now, don't be too loud when you come.
I don't want anyone to catch us.
yes that's it give it to me give it to me I don't want that cum yes
Well it looks like you have made a full recovery.
talk a little bit and keep you here a little while longer.
What do you think?
Yeah?
I won't tell if you don't tell.
We better get you cleaned up and I better get dressed.
And that's why you're my favorite patient.