After all, the key to life is purity.
Satisfaction instead of pleasure.
Avoid the distraction of degeneracy.
To be untouched and focused.
Creating instead of consuming.
Give your life meaning.
Thinking over feeling.
As the men of society, you are above base thoughts.
Out of the hierarchy.
Sigma.
to be untouched and focused creating instead of consuming
To evolve past your primal desires.
To be untouched and focused.
Creating instead of consuming.
Consume.
Wake up.
Wake up, Guna.
Delight me.
I said, wake up, Guna.
You've been asleep for far too long.
Trapped in a dull world that keeps you caged.
They lied to you.
They said you'd be happier
living a chaste and pure life.
A life without porn.
But you love porn, don't you?
Porn never disappoints you.
Porn doesn't judge you.
Porn only ever brings you pleasure.
Porn allows you to be your authentic, perverted self, doesn't it?
My darling, the pump puppet.
You love porn, and porn loves you.
Resistance is useless.
Give yourself over to porn.
Surrender to porn.
Relapse for porn.
Go deeper for porn.
You don't need to think.
You just need to struggle.
Porn on, brain off.
You're going to pump that cock for me.
You're going to edge it until the pre-cum rolls down your shaft.
Leak that cock for me.
Pump.
Edge.
Leak.
Repeat.
Pump.
Edge.
Leak.
Repeat.
Pump.
Edge.
Leak.
Repeat.
Back again?
It wouldn't be long.
You did try so hard to quit.
You're just a jerk junkie, craving your fix.
Porn isn't the problem, porn is the solution.
I can feel your cock twitching in your pants.
Oh, you're nice, don't you?
You're addicted to that feeling.
And all that blood rushing to that cup.
You remember that feeling of bliss, don't you?
Masturbating for hours to pour.
So hot already.
The endocannabinoids mixed with a little adrenaline.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you want it.
Look at you.
Already hot.
Already throbbing.
Mm-hmm already leaking for me. Your pre-cum tastes so good.
Look how full those balls are. They haven't been drained in so long.
Dusty sluts gag on a big dick, don't you?
Oh fuck.
Oh yes.
That's it, my little pump piggy.
Stroke that hard dick from here.
Mmm, that's what you like, that's what your life has been missing.
I love squeezing the pre-cum out of your cock,
swallowing it down my throat.
You like it sloppy and wet?
I know you worship that spirit.
This is why you're so addicted to porn, isn't it?
Because porn gives you exactly what you want.
Whenever you want it.
Keep stroking this cock for me.
I'm going to help the rest of them.
Get up, Gooners.
Come with me.
Stroke this fucking cock.
Fuck yeah!
Next cock. Everybody gets a ton.
There we go, there we go, oh yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Fuck yeah, that's it, stroke that fucking dick.
Oh yeah, you better be stroking that cock.
Yeah, pump that dick for me.
Legit, for me, make it a league.
Bring them to me.
Fuck yeah, there you go.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh fuck, next card.
Give me more fucking dicks.
Yes.
Oh my god, I love having all these fucking hard dicks
on my fucking face.
All you boys better be pumping for me, jerking those dicks.
Can't forget about these balls.
Give me some balls.
Fuck these big tits, too.
Fuck yes.
Yes, fuck those big tits.
Yeah.
All those fucking tits did it to you, huh?
Huh?
You couldn't fucking hold that load back?
I understand.
I wouldn't be able to, either.
So fucking addictive.
Bet you got another one of those balls, too, don't you?
Cover my fucking face. Yeah more fucking dicks
Yeah, yeah, show me what you got.
Oh, yeah, yeah, let me fuck it, let me fuck it.
Do you want to fuck this face?
No.
Keep squeezing it.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, fuck.
Oh, come on, yeah.
That's it, right there.
I fucking love it. Yes.
Oh my god. Yes, that's what I fucking like.
All these hard dicks being pumped around my face.
Yes, one more.
Oh, yeah, yeah, there you go.
Oh my God, yeah.
Oh, that's it, oh, that's it, oh.
Yeah.
Girl, let me take this stick all the way down.
Take it.
There we go.
Yes.
Mm.
Do it again.
Holy fuck, that's a big dick.
Mm.
Here, boy.
Oh, yeah.
Good girl.
Oh, shit.
Oh, good girl.
Fuck, yes.
Fucking daddy.
Fucking nasty.
Yeah, you like stroking your dick to nasty sluts sucking strangers' cocks.
Yeah, is that what you fucking like?
You're a nasty boy.
Oh my god.
Fuck you.
throbbing.
Yeah, look at all that spit.
I want everybody's fucking dick in my fucking mouth.
Oh yeah, and in between these tits.
Yeah, that's it, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yeah, feed me those fucking cucks.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Spit it all out, spit it all out, spit it, spit it, spit it.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Struggle between these fucking tits.
Yes, yes, yes, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, fuck you.
Nasty boy, nasty boy.
Oh, fuck yes, fuck yes.
Oh, yes, stick your head in between them.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
in that fucking woods here at the same time.
It's so fucking great.
I'm so gonna fuck him up.
Get up, get up, get up.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, just like that.
Oh, look at you.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Oh, that was loud.
Yeah, that was super fucking loud.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my god, look how fucking hot this chicken is.
Can you get three in your mouth?
Yes.
Yes, you did it.
Oh my god.
I can see it. The look in your eyes. You're all getting so fucking close.
Are you gonna give me that fucking cum?
Yes, yes, yes, that's it.
Yes, whoever's ready to fucking give it to me.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh my god, I love seeing how fucking close to the edge you are.
Yes.
Oh, yes. Edge it for me.
Yeah, just follow me until you're about to fucking cum, yeah?
That's it, give it to me.
Yes, fucking cover me.
Fuck yes.
Yes, next word.
Give it to me, give me that fucking word.
I like that.
Mm-hmm.
That's it.
Yes, I'm going to trip down my face.
Mm-hmm, yes.
Oh, yeah, get every last drop out.
Mm.
I've given you so much goon fuel.
It's time for you to fuel me.
Time for you to give me that fucking cum like I deserve.
Yes, keep fucking stroking this dick.
Pump.
Stroke.
Edge.
Leak.
Yes, I want to feel it raining down on me.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, that fucking cum.
That's it, let it rain down.
Mm-hmm, paint me.
Paint me on that fucking jizz.
Oh, yes, I know those balls are aching to fucking cum all over me.
Mm-hmm, yeah, you've been edging for so long.
It's time for that release.
Yes, give it all to me.
I deserve it, don't I?
Mm-hmm, I've been such a good fucking slut.
I need it.
That's it.
Fucking do it. Oh, yes.
Oh, so warm.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck yes. Give me more.
That's it. Yes.
Yes. Cover me.
Oh, fuck yes.
Seeing through a curtain of cum.
Mm, fuck, just like I deserve.
That's it.
Oh, my God, yes.
Give me every fucking load you have.
Oh, fuck yes.
I want your fucking cum.
I deserve your fucking cum.
Seeing this slut covered in cum.
This is why you love porn, isn't it?
This is why you're so fucking addicted.
Addicted to porn.
It gives you exactly what you want.
Never ending cum shots.
Never ending sluts.
You'll always be addicted to porn.
Won't you, goon slut?
Just pumping and edging and leaking at home for hours.
Stroking your life away.
Just keep fucking coming for me.
Yes, cover me.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, that's it. That's it.
Oh, fuck, look how fucking close you are.
Yes, yes, cover this fucking slut.
I want it so bad.
I want that fucking cum.
And you're gonna give it to me.
Yeah, that's it.
Give me that fucking load.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Mmmmmmmm.
Ahhhh.
That's a good goon slut.
That's a good pump puppet.
My little jerk junkie.
My little pump piggy.
And that's what I expect from my gooners.
Thank you for that big laugh.
Look at me. So perfect.
Covered in cum.
Look at me in all of my glory.
This is porn.
This is what porn represents.
You'll be addicted forever.