in your services.
Oh, OK.
Well, that's kind of weird, but I
guess I see no problem with it.
Sure.
Why don't I let you see the list of massages that I can do,
and you guys can choose from these.
Awesome.
Um, I don't think we have a number of any of those.
They're so expensive to even, like, get one of them.
Maybe we can ask her to split one.
Like go halfsies on it?
Yeah, like halfsies.
Alright, let's ask her that.
Okay, so um...
We can't really like afford any of them,
so we were kind of thinking
maybe
me and him could go halfsies on a
singles massage.
Go halfsies, so a half of a
massage for each of you?
Yeah, if that would be possible.
We appreciate it
So what kind of massage do you boys want?
neuro, please
Okay
Well, let me show you to the massage room
Okay, boys come on in
This is the massage room.
Okay.
Great.
And Apollo, you can do the same right here.
I'm just going to remove your socks, okay, Apollo?
Okay.
All right.
Are you boys comfortable?
Oh, definitely, yeah.
All right.
I'll start over here with you, Joshua.
I don't know if you can see it, but I have a lot of earwax on my left ear.
How's that?
It's really nice.
Does that feel good?
Do you like how slippery it is?
I just want to alleviate any tension you have right here.
All right, Apollo, I'm going to start you off now.
Oh, okay.
It is a little cold, okay?
How does that feel?
It feels really good.
I just really want to get your upper back here.
Okay.
How was that?
Oh, it was good.
It was good.
You were like a baby.
I was.
It was so good.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
It was a lot better than I thought it would be.
It was, it was a lot better.
How's that?
Oh, good, good, good.
Okay.
I'm just giving you a full back massage right now, lower and upper back.
You nice and loosened up.
I'm going to move back over here.
I'm going to move back over here to Mr. Joshua.
Are you ready for a little more?
Yes, please.
Okay.
Oh, I think you could use a little more.
Oh, yeah.
How's that?
Oh, it's super good.
Mm.
Does that feel nice?
Not bad.
Yeah.
I like it.
I'm
Oh
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Just massage your neck, and turn your head this way.
Now turn it this way.
There you go.
Alright.
I'm with you for now.
Oh, okay.
Back to the street, Joshua.
You ready for more?
All right, why don't you turn over, Joshua, lay on your back.
Okay.
Here, come down a little bit.
Come on, bro, you're hogging her.
What?
She just got over here.
Now, now, boys, there's more than enough for me to go around.
Dude, quit hogging her.
She just started boys. Don't worry. There's enough of me to go around
It's my turn now.
No, it's not.
Dude, she touched your junk already.
Why did you even come here?
Oh, is that why you boys came here?
Interesting.
Whenever Tommy invited us over, we always thought you were pretty hot.
And then, we've seen your masseuse, so we just, like, had to come here.
Oh, I see.
Well, that is very interesting information.
That's so embarrassing.
Now she knows we're virgins.
Oh, you're virgins?
Come on, bro. Why'd you have to say that? That's so embarrassing.
Oh my god, you two are funny.
She knows me, virgin.
So, nobody's ever touched your cock before?
Really?
It's my turn.
Or yours, Apollo?
No.
Well, why don't you turn over for me, Apollo?
I think it is your turn.
In fact, I think it's both of your turns.
Okay.
I'm gonna give you both a very special new room experience.
Oh, they're so warm.
Very hot-blooded, aren't you boys?
So you guys have never touched breasts then?
Why don't you touch mine?
There you go.
Oh, my God, there's so much.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, shit.
Wait right there.
Mm.
All right, I'm gonna really grab them, yes, ooh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, just like, yeah, you can jiggle them around.
You know, I've always thought about doing this.
Really?
Then now's your chance.
Yeah, me both.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, just balance them, slap them if you want.
There you go.
There you are.
Oh, yeah, play with this.
Play with my friend, Harry.
They're so nice.
Oh, you boys are getting really stiff.
Just like I like that.
Woah...
Oh!
Oh my God
Yes
Oh wow
Do you like it when I play with your balls?
Oh my God! Yes
Yes so much
You?
Yes, I love that
That feels so good
They're so good with your hands
That's part of my job
Oh my gosh, these cots are so warm in my hands, they're so stiff.
Why don't you guys touch my pussy?
Oh my goodness, oh that is so nice.
Who wants his cock sucked first?
Me.
Oh, he kind of got it first.
Dude, you're so lucky.
You're going to be quicker than that.
Now you keep stroking your cock.
I want you to feel my warm, wet mouth.
Yes, please.
Oh.
Oh, it's hot.
Your mouth feels so good.
I'm so glad you know what you're doing.
Alright.
Let's give some to your little friend over here.
Oh my god.
Hold my hand.
Holy shit.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh, that feels so good.
Oh, that's so hot.
Oh, I can't believe this is actually happening.
I can't either.
Oh, fuck.
I can't believe I'm sucking my son's friend's cocks.
This is so good.
Oh, you don't know how many times I've thought about this.
What if I lick your balls? Would you like that?
Yes, please.
Oh, my God.
Now let go of my hair and stroke your cock for me slowly.
Oh, I like that.
Oh, my God.
Mm-hmm.
This is the best feeling in the world.
Oh, yes.
Mm, that's the other boss.
Mm.
Do they taste good?
I don't know, I'm just going to...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Your mouth is so nice and warm.
I don't know if I'm doing something.
Oh, fuck.
This is so hard.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Okay.
I think you won't really like this.
Then you stay right there.
Okay.
What are you gonna do?
Here's what you're going to do.
You're going to grab my tits.
Uh-huh.
OK?
And you're going to squeeze them to heal all of that.
Oh.
How does that feel?
It feels so good.
I've never had this happen before.
Oh, good.
Oh.
I'm going to call this tit-fucking.
I love tit-fucking.
Oh.
It looks horrible.
It's gonna be like in a fucking cartoon or something.
Oh, man.
Can you just bounce that?
Oh, my God.
It's gonna be a good series.
I feel so bad.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
Oh, good boy.
Oh my god.
Just like that.
Oh my god, just like this.
I'm so tired.
You're doing such a good job.
I wanna try that.
When's it my turn?
Just wait a minute, bro.
Well, your friend's getting a little bit eager.
I wanna try and fuck them too.
Oh.
Wait.
Oh my god.
Give me your arms.
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm so ready.
Alright.
Squeeze them together, just like that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, my God. Your tits are so, so big.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I love that.
Oh, my big tits go around like that.
It feels so fucking good.
That's unstitching?
Yeah.
Oh, you little fuck.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yes.
Jesus.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, yes.
You're a beautiful woman.
Thank you.
Okay.
Never mind.
Hey, don't look at me.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fall over.
Oh.
Oh my God, you boys are really turning me on.
I think I need some cock inside my pussy.
Yeah?
Yeah, you guys ready?
Okay, fine.
Mm-hmm.
I guess you're going to lose your virginity first.
I'm so jealous.
Now get your turn.
You want to see this Apollo?
Yeah.
Alright.
There. There you go. Good boy.
You are so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
That makes me feel so good.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, yes.
Enjoying the view out there?
Yes.
I think it spanked my ass.
Yeah, it spanked.
Oh, it spanked the other side.
Bad boy.
Alright.
I'm going to go sit there.
And you...
Come look at me.
Put it...
Right in my butt.
A little higher. Oh, there you go.
Go slow.
And then go fast.
Good boy.
I'm going to give you that cock in my mouth.
Oh yeah.
Oh fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Girl, I can't believe we're fucking Thomas.
Mommy was so crazy about him.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, you boys are doing such a good job.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
That tickles.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my fucking God.
Oh!
Oh, my ass.
Yeah.
Oh!
Bro, high-five.
Oh, my fucking God.
Oh!
going.
Like that?
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, my God!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, my God, I'm like that pussy!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, my God!
Oh, yeah, stroke that foot.
Yeah, stroke that.
Yeah.
Come back to your room.
And tell me if Mom sucks your cock.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Oh, silly thing.
Oh, my foot.
Oh.
Oh, here it's hurting.
Oh my God, oh my God.
mm-hmm.
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck yeah.
So good.
Oh, that's...
Why don't you, why don't you pull out for a second?
Why don't you go like this.
Like this.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Give me your paw.
Mm.
you.
Oh, I am so nice yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh.
Mm-hm.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh.
Mwa, mwa, mwa.
Mwa, mwa, mwa, mwa.
Mm, mm.
Mm, mm, mm.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ah, ah, ah.
Oh, so cute.
Oh, my God.
Ah, ah, ah.
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Another idea.
Why don't you boys
lay side by side?
Uh-huh.
Oh, God.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck. Yes. Oh, my God.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Yes.
Mm.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
All right.
It's your turn.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God!
Oh fuck me!
Oh fuck!
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
You getting a little sore right here?
Put a little bit more oil in there.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my heart!
Have mercy on me!
Oh!
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes!
I want to go to sleep.
Oh, my God!
I want to sleep.
Oh!
Oh, fuck.
What did I say?
Oh.
Ooh!
Oh!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh fuck, oh my god.
This feels so good.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, yes!
Make this evening, god.
Oh my god, make it come.
Oh my god.
Oh, God, yes, give me another hug.
I'm so...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh my God.
I don't want to look like this next time you're chasing me.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh Christ.
Oh God.
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
Oh, come on.
Oh, my ass.
Oh, you fucking come on, my ass.
Oh.
Oh, you guys made such a mess.
Well, oh my god, I am so glad Tommy has such cute friends.
Uh, I don't really think you'd like that if you found out.
Uh, I think we could arrange that.
Yeah?
I'd like to maybe help out.