I'd probably give an F if I'm famous because I'm cute
Ain't no better way I can say this
Because it don't matter about the size
I could give it to Taylor and I'd take it in
Open your ears, I still flow in your triggers
Can't wait to hit the wheel and whip him round a Mercedes
I want Ferraris and Bedleys, I want Fazzati and Fendi
You see my face on the telly, you scream my name like I'm Jerry
I run the house like I'm Jerry, got Mr. Tom and my celly in for me
Jerry, Jerry, Jerry
You know they call me Jerry, Jerry, Jerry
Mr. Springer, I'm a Jerry, Jerry, Jerry
You know they call me Cherry, Cherry, Cherry
Miss Springer, I'm a Cherry, Cherry, Cherry
Cherry, Cherry, Cherry
This year I'm doing it big, I'm talking bigger than Rick
Got all these people talking like they coulda did what I did
Don't give a hush where you fit, don't even care who you with
I'm gonna blow up this shit, you'll probably be blowing the sink
Ain't into rocking with fakes, cause all my shit is legit
And if you ain't getting now, then you're probably just fixed
And I ain't trying to insult you, I'm just telling you what I think
I got a lot up on my mind, I'm just hoping you take the hint
Ain't trying to cut you at the spot, no, no
Big up everybody, making grub, uh-huh
Remember when I used to have a job, oh la
I could barely keep up with the squad
Couldn't wait to hit the wheel, whipping round a Mercedes
I want Ferraris and Bettys, Jimmy Choo and Giuseppe
I'm on the block like I'm Jenny, you scream my name like I'm Jerry
You see my face on the telly, got Mr. Tom and Marcelli
It's Bum Cherry
Fuck, yes, oh fuck, oh my god, you're so hot for me already, I love it.
Just do this like this, just like this.
Fuck.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Oh, that feels so good.
Fuck yes.
Those titties are all yours.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Do what you want to my buddy.
Hmm, hmm, hmm, fuck, oh my god, yes, fuck, oh, touch me, fuck, yes, hmm, oh, fuck, yes,
Yes.
Oh, good.
Good.
Yes. Good.
Damn it, it feels so good.
Oh, yeah.
Pussy in the wet.
I love the way you make out with him.
Mmm, fuck yes.
Oh my god.
You like how warm that pussy is?
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Mmm.
mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Oh my god, what the fuck?
This coke deserves to be washed.
Fuck, oh my god, this is a fucking weapon.
Ah, shit.
Oh my god, look how big this dick is, what the fuck?
It's not even fair for one man to have this much dick.
I can barely fit it in my mouth.
How many hands do I need for this dick?
Mmm, four hands for this giant cuck.
Oh, goddammit.
Mmm.
Mmm
Yes, just like that.
Shit, baby, fuck.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Just like that.
It's so good.
I fucking love it.
Get this whole dick wet.
Fuck, that's hot.
I love seeing it
glisten with my spit.
Yes.
Oh shit, get them bars baby, get them bars, yes, mmm, mmm, mmm, it smells so fucking good,
oh shit
fuck what a perfect dick you're so blessed
Goddammit.
Fuck.
Oh my fucking god.
Holy fuck.
Oh my god, it's so big. God damn it.
Wow.
Oh my god, it's so fucking thick.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh fuck, yes.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes!
Fuck, baby, oh my god!
I am fucking crazy with that dick!
Holy fuck!
You're a fucking animal!
Oh my god!
Fuck!
Oh, I wanna see it!
Yeah, I wanna see it!
Fuck!
Oh my god!
I can't believe that fucking dick that's in there!
Holy fuck!
You're fucking crazy!
Yes, yeah, do what?
Suck my dick.
Yes.
Suck it.
Damn me, man.
I didn't know that we got in here, I didn't know that we got you, I didn't know you were
so fucking crazy, when did you become so fucking crazy, today, today, today, that's something
Then you're over dead.
Yeah.
Holy fuck!
Yes.
Just like that?
Oh my god!
Fuck!
Ah!
Mmm!
Fuck.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Get that table. Fuck yes. I'm just teasing my clit on that car.
Fuck. Put it inside me. Put it inside that pussy. Fuck. That's a big fucking dick. Oh
Oh my God, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh my God, it's fucking deep in there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my God.
Just swimming over that cup, dancing like that, fuck.
Oh my god, yes, I already got my legs shaking, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god, so are they fighting me, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god,
What the fuck, what the fuck, what the fuck, it's so fucking thick, here, I'm stretching
that little pussy, fuck, god damn, fuck baby, I really like the way that little pussy jerks
Yeah, give you those false jerks, fuck, yeah, fuck, oh my god, you're so good, you're so fucking good at saving, oh, fuck, oh yeah, keep me close, keep me on that dick, keep me on that fucking cup, I'm not going anywhere, I'm not going anywhere, fuck,
Oh my god. You're so deep in my guts. So deep in my stomach. What the fuck?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my fucking god.
God, you're a fucking psycho, you're a fucking psycho, I fucking love it, what the fuck,
Why would you become such a fucking psycho?
Fuck me.
Fuck this bitch.
Yes.
Damn.
I feel your heart beating.
It's so fucking hot.
Fucking hot for me.
I can't work hard for a meal like that.
Let me suck that dick.
I can't taste this pussy.
Look how you're stretched now.
Look at that fucking cunt.
Oh my god, you're so good with that fucking mouth, dude.
Dude, fuck you.
Oh my god, this cup is so perfect.
I can see.
I need that fucking cup.
Yes.
Fucking hell.
God damn it.
Okay, don't fucking bring that cup.
Are you on your way back here, huh?
Come on, show me how you fuck.
Show me how you fuck.
God damn it.
Fuck, now I can watch it.
I can watch you as you fucking destroy that
pussy, stretching it out
in a big hug.
Oh my god.
I can feel you throbbing.
It's so fucking hot.
Fuck. Yes.
Yes, mm, fuck, oh, oh, god damn it, I can feel your foreskin, rolling back and forth
over that head, bare inside that pussy, dropping all that fucking pre-cum inside me, fuck,
Fuck, yes, yes, fuck, yes, oh my god, so fucking quick, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck baby,
Baby, yessssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
Yeah I fucked up
Yeah
Oh my god it's so good
Slap it on that clit baby
Oh god this is so fucking good
God
Oh yeah
I want you to roll your foreskin back and forth on my clit
I wanna see it
Yeah
Fuck that's hot
I fucking love that
So fucking sexy
You're gonna treat that pussy right, treat that fucking pussy right, yeah fuck, oh my
god you're so fucking deep in me, oh my god, you're so fucking deep in that pussy, oh my
god, fuck, fuck, straight in me, oh my god, fucking straight, I don't know, I'm trying
I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, what the fuck, what the fuck, what
the fuck, you fucking drive me crazy with that dick, you drive me fucking crazy with
that cook yeah yeah oh my god it's fucking good yeah you work hard for me like god i see you
working hard yeah baby
oh yeah god damn it the fuck did you come from
Oh my god, you're gonna make me fucking fall in love with you, fuck, you're a fucking
I'm going to be fucking crazy, Jesus Christ!
You fucker!
Oh my God!
What are you fucking doing to me?
What are you trying to do to me?
What are you trying to do to me, huh?
What are you trying to fucking do to me?
Do it, fuck!
Oh my God!
Oh my god, oh my god, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh fuck, it's crazy, oh my god, oh my god, yes, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, fuck, fuck, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh
I need that fucking clue, I need that fucking clue, I need it, I need it, I need it, I need it, I need it, I need it, fuck, yeah, you better hold on to me because you're going to fuck me up, you're fucking dead, you better hold me, you better keep me there, yeah, oh my god, oh my god, baby, fuck, that dick is so, that dick is so good, that dick is so good,
Don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
Look how good your dick looks with my tits, mmm, perfect match, ooh, fuck yeah, mmm, feels
so good, yes, slap it on then, mmm, fuck yes, god damn it, that's hot, mmm, let me suck
Just like that, try it.
Just like that.
Ah, it's so good.
DROP DROP DROP DROP
I need that dick back in the sandwich
I fucking hate it
mmm fuck yes
mmm fuck
mmm slap that big cluck
on my ass
mmm fuck yes
mmm god damn that's a
big dick
Yes! Oh baby! Fuck yes! Oh my god! Fuck! Fuck! Yes!
I'm stretching out that little pussy right there!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Oh my fucking god! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Fuck, baby! Fuck! God damn it!
Fuck! Yes! Look at how you stretch that pussy! Fuck!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, you made that fucking pussy yell, god damn it, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
Fuck baby, you fucking destroy me, split me fucking open, oh my god baby, what the fuck, you never want me to be the same huh?
I'm afraid of that big dick, god damn it, oh my god, oh my god, oh, oh, oh, baby, fuck,
oh, oh, shit, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh my God.
You like that shit?
I don't know.
Farts!
Farts for your team.
Farts, farts.
Let's do it like that.
Just like that?
Yeah, just like that.
Just like that.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, like that.
Farts!
I can feel it.
Farts.
It's just like that.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh my God, it gets so fucking deep.
It's like I'm gonna fucking,
I'm gonna really fucking choke that chick, God damn it.
God damn it.
Fuck my fucking flesh.
Look at me just like that.
Don't take your fucking ass off me, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just like that, just like that, just like that, just like that.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, oh that's it, that's it, that's it, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, oh fuck baby, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
pussy fuck? Oh my god, baby. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Oh my god. Damn, baby. Damn, that
dick is fucking crazy. Oh, you're getting close. I feel it. I feel you drumming and
inside that fucking pussy, my soul is being purging.
I wanna choke that pussy, choke that fucking dick
in my pussy, look at you got me speechless,
I don't even know what I'm fucking saying anymore.
I got that just fucked brain melted, yeah, oh that's hot.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, that cum ball inside my pussy.
to me, doesn't it? Yeah. That's my fucking kind. I deserve it. He's a good girl. I was
a good fucking girl and I deserve that load. Every little step of it. Finally. Yeah, build
it up in me. Yeah, I want it. I want it. I want it. Give it to me.
Oh my god, your cum tastes so fucking good.
Give me every last drop of it.
Oh, there's still some in there.
It's got such a long shaft to come out of.
See, there it is.
Let me dig it out.
It's so fucking hot.
Oh my God, you fuck me so good.
But you can never forget this, dude.
I worship this day.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.