You gotta try the punch. It's a secret family recipe I found online.
Oh, it's alcohol free, but I have beer or wine if you prefer.
Oh, no, the punch sounds great.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And thanks for hosting.
So, speed dating, huh? Should be fun.
Yeah.
Cheers.
I'll start with Phoenix.
Huh.
Phoenix and Rex.
Randy and Holly.
I'll take Angela.
Okay, sounds good.
Perfect.
I'm just gonna grab my phone so I can start the clock.
Cool.
Yes, we'll have a seat.
Yeah, we'll take a seat right over here.
So, Phoenix, where are you from?
California.
Let me just start this.
Now where were we?
The punch is good.
Really?
Yeah.
I should send the website an email.
So what are you looking for in a man?
Oh wow, right to the serious stuff, huh?
I don't know.
Someone with similar values, a big heart.
I do a lot of volunteer work.
Really? I volunteer at the mission on Tuesdays.
No way! I'm there on Thursdays!
Oh really?
I can't believe we were so close to meeting each other before tonight.
Better late than never.
Yeah.
Cheers.
So that's when I said...
You know what? I'm gonna go get some punch.
Yeah, um, actually can you get me...
No, we're good here. Excuse me.
Oh, clumsy me. I dropped my cup. Don't mind me.
Now, where was I?
So when did you move in?
Um, like four years ago.
Oh, so you must really like it here.
No problem.
I do, actually. Really, really strongly would.
Yeah.
This song is so good, isn't it?
It's like one of my favorite songs.
Yeah.
I'm really glad you did.
Oh, this is the part where it really starts to get fast, isn't it?
Oh my god, it really just turns me on so much.
Oh my god, it's so f***ing good.
Get the f*** off, slut.
Saved by the bell. Time to switch.
Yes.
I was so close.
Hey! My turn! Move!
Oh, don't mind me. Sorry, I was dancing.
Sorry.
You look like a lot of fun.
Ugh. It's my wife.
I thought we were hitting it off anyway, so if I could just get you-
Uh, no.
Get the fuck out!
I'm gonna get that beer off the rolls.
Well, I'm not married.
Yeah?
What's your name?
I'm Rex.
Nice to meet you, Rex.
Nice to meet you, too.
It's crazy.
We know each other even though we're so close.
I know.
It is crazy.
What?
That we haven't...
Yeah, that we haven't gone out on a date or just spent some time together.
Well, Mike's so fucking hot.
So, when do I get to see the bedroom?
Oh, wow. You are something, aren't you?
Oh, yeah, I am. You have no idea.
What? What's wrong?
Nothing. Is it, uh...
Is it cold in here, or is it...
I mean, I don't know. Everyone seems to be fine.
Did you get to try the punch?
Are you okay?
I'm good. I, uh, I'm really enjoying speed dating.
Yeah, so maybe we can take this a little further tonight, huh?
Oh, that sounds like a great idea.
I mean, yeah, we should really get to know each other.
Have you had a recent girlfriend?
No, been single for a while.
Hmm.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You are just forward.
Why do I feel like you're just distracted?
I don't know, it's like,
I got a little, did you try the blenches?
I did, it was-
It's really good.
Okay.
I'm really enjoying this piece of you.
Yeah, it's my first time.
How about yours?
Um, first time?
Yeah, it's crazy.
Um, so, uh-
What means you're being hosted?
It's just...
What the fuck?
What is that?
I think it's the ice maker.
Are you trying to out-slut me, Little Miss Perfect?
Come here.
What the fuck is this?
Look girls, we can settle this.
What the fuck kind of party is this?
Yeah, I think we should get out of here.
You're right, we can settle this.
You can tell us who sucks dick better.
Listen bitch, he's mine.
No, he's mine.
No, he's not.
He's mine.
Listen, listen, listen.
We can share.
Oh my god, you're so fucking hot.
You slut.
What, are you just trying to finish
what you've already been doing, huh?
Oh, I'm sorry, how far down did you get on that?
You wanna see if you can do better?
Oh, go ahead bitch, let's see you first.
Here, I want to watch you every fucking inch.
Don't be touching your fucking balls.
I got it all the way down my throat.
Get off that. Let me try again.
I can stroke him better. I have better handjob skills.
What makes you think that?
Look, he likes it.
I get it to it with both hands.
Oh, is that right?
You might want to make it wet.
Fucking foot.
This poor thing's been in your fucking neighborhood the whole time.
Look at that.
What are you just like, miss the balls entirely?
You don't play with them at all?
You've got jokes, huh?
You should never forget the balls.
Real sluts play with balls.
Yeah, I don't want to put them in your fucking mouth.
All I said, say what you did.
Oh, finally remembered them.
You little fucking rat.
Look at all that fucking spit coming out now, huh?
I think he could stroke it faster.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
You're trying to make him come really, really fast, huh?
He's like, no, I can do that.
No, no, I've been hearing all the fucking things.
See?
Somebody likes something.
Oh, fuck.
You just can't keep your fucking mouth off of it, huh?
Oh, does it feel really good, baby?
Is it too good?
Is that too good?
Just right at the top, just like that.
You make them come first.
You don't win a prize, bitch.
I do.
The prize is come.
Give me your fucking spit.
Oh look at our poor boy over there, does he feel good?
Would you rather feel a fucking tight vagina like mine?
What makes you think yours is as tight as mine?
too perfect on this.
Go ahead.
Whose pussy do you want first?
Oh, you want hers because she's been sucking your cock more?
Or you want mine?
You know, your bitchiness is kind of hot.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Look at your cute little fucking face.
Am I fucking hot?
Just like that?
I'm not gonna lie.
You have a really great ass.
That's good.
Your tits are fucking outstanding.
They're not fucking pulled out yet.
You can't just walk around with your fucking ass
all like that.
Oh my god.
Stroke.
Stroke that dick inside that pussy.
Spit all over it again.
I'm gonna drip up my asshole in this fucking cock
and stroke it off.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
I've been wanting your fucking cock so long.
Go ahead, Logan.
It's yours.
Did I tell you you can lick my fucking pussy, too, Saf?
Tastes good.
Oh my god.
That's what I'm waiting for.
These amazing fucking tits.
You get fucked?
I beat you up with those tits.
I like it.
Feels like you're slapping me and my little fucking white face is down.
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel so fucking good.
Oh my god.
Get to me.
Oh, look at you, you're taking off your shoes.
Oh my god, that feels so fucking good.
Oh my god, fuck.
You're not supposed to play with this fucking cart, I am.
Oh my god, fuck, yeah.
Lean back, lean back on that fucking cart.
Yes, yes, take me, take that pussy, fuck.
Let's see what gets that big dick, huh?
Look at the, that big dick just waiting
in the fuckin' inside of you.
Stretching that pussy here.
Do you like being stretched down
like a good little fuckin' slut?
It's gonna make me cum.
It's gonna make you cum?
Yes, it's gonna make me cum.
It's gonna really make you fuckin' cum
or are you lying to me?
Please, please, please,
it's gonna make me fuckin' cum, please.
Come on, come on that fuckin' cock.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's see if you can cum better on that fuckin' dick.
Me or you.
You're gonna make him fucking cum on you.
You fucking slut.
No!
I like a nice semen.
Wow, you take that dick so well.
Fuck.
Cut it down.
Kind of see a way to get your cockiness, huh?
Uh huh.
You've got some skills.
You do too.
But I think I should be able to do it.
to do something better than you.
Or you think so?
Yeah, I'm gonna put in my fucking asshole.
Yeah.
I'm gonna make him stick this big dick
deep in my fucking ass.
I don't think you're gonna fit that.
You know, I'm gonna let him fuck me and Doggy
so you can feel my big fat ass slap up against this abdomen and cock.
So that's how you're gonna step it up a notch?
Uh-huh.
My big fucking ass.
What is this?
Well, since your mouth is free.
You've got jokes, huh, little one?
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, the way you're suctioning on that fucking pussy.
Okay, I want to see what all the fuss is about.
What?
Oh, okay. Your ass does look really good slapping up against him.
Damn.
That's quite a view.
I hope you don't mind if I take a sip.
Did you just sit on me, you fucking bitch?
I sure did.
Oh my God, that feels so good.
Fucking sit on me, I don't even care.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
keep fucking me please
harder please
oh damn give it to her
give her what she wants
oh god
keep going keep going
oh my god
give her that dick
oh come on
and she claims she can take it.
She claims she can take it.
Give it to her, huh?
Oh, there you go, tough girl, huh?
You take that fucking dick all the way deep inside you.
I'm fucking in on this fucking bitch.
Oh, you know what?
I think she can take it a little harder.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Go beast mode on her.
You deserve it after being such a fucking bitch
Yeah it's so crazy
I can feel his fucking cock in my pussy
While you fucking squeeze me like that
You just push down right there
I can fucking feel his fucking cock
I can fucking stroke him
While he's inside of me oh my god
Yeah, I'm stroking that fucking dick from the outside.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck what?
Shit.
Come on, I'm fucking going.
Come on that fucking dick.
Oh, God.
With your little body.
You're so fucking cute.
Oh no.
You fucking stay there little one.
You know what's gonna happen next.
I am not a fairy
so you fucking slut.
Such a fun ride.
This is why we're not friends, the fucking apartment building.
I don't know, this feels pretty friendly to me.
Actually, it feels really good to me.
Go ahead and bounce that fucking ass on me.
Spill over his fucking cock again.
You're a good little bitch.
You know what?
Excuse me? I have a lot to offer, thank you very much.
Really? Besides sitting?
What about this pussy?
Oh, fuck you.
I'm so glad to know I get to be a holster for your fucking cunt.
You're such a good table.
I am. You're lucky.
Fuck. Oh my god.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh my god, that feels so good.
You feel so fucking good.
your fucking pretty little clunk.
Yeah, I feel so fucking good inside me.
Are you pouncing your fucking tits from them too?
Or are you just taking a dick?
I thought you were going to be entertaining.
I'm just enjoying myself right now.
And whatever the fuck I want.
You know what's great?
Is that I will enjoy my fucking soul.
Fuck.
Yes.
We can work together to fuck you.
Holy fuck.
Oh my god, that's so good.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
But you know what I have that you don't have?
What do you think you have?
I have big, natural tits.
and I think he likes them
you should come get it wet
since you're so good with that throat
he's so cute
oh yes
get all that good spit from the back of the throat
I'm going to show you what I can do with these.
I like the way they move.
I do.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
I'm so fucking sorry.
Look.
Let me fucking bounce on it.
Oh my god.
Not as big as yours.
It doesn't matter.
You can fucking hold your hips and make me bounce.
Yeah.
Damn, you came for pets.
I told you I'm a good swimmer.
I still think you should wrap your tits around these.
The problem is my tits just don't work like yours.
Give me your lube.
Bounce them all over.
Make them fucking glisten.
I want to see the fucking lights in this hotel room fucking showing.
You want this?
You get my little tits.
They're not natural, but they're so fucking hard.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck it.
You're a corner.
Just give me my fucking tits.
Damn, that looks so good.
Are you playing with your neck?
I know, I felt great, but I want you to fucking suck his cock.
What were you saying about your fucking nudge, Rachel?
Come here.
Where am I going?
Flip.
Tell him what you want.
I want everything.
Beg him for it.
Please give me that fucking dick.
I need that dick inside me, please.
How bad do you need it?
I fucking need it.
That's those fucking tits like that.
Look at that.
You jerk your fucking pussy.
You jerk your fucking tits.
Oh my God.
Beg him again.
I love the way he teases this.
Come on, baby.
Give me that fucking dick.
Are you too close to come in?
Give me that fucking cup.
There's just too many of us to take.
He's too close.
Honey, that's a big dick fuck inside me.
Yes, please.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Damn, that's a big fucking dick.
Yeah.
You want him to take it all the way in like I did, don't you?
I think it's only fair.
Oh, fuck you.
Guess what?
I can fucking hold you down while he swims all the way inside of you.
Oh, fuck.
Hold it in there for her.
I'm rearranging those organs, fuck.
Oh my god.
Tell him how much you like it.
I like it, I love it.
Fuck!
And I'm being trapped, fuck you.
I don't have to fucking choke you to fit in your place, do I bitch?
No.
No, I can just hold you like this, huh?
And then you can get fucked however I tell you to.
Damn.
You want to fuck me harder?
Yeah.
I'll show you I can take it too.
Go ahead.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
I'm not going to let you fuck her harder than me.
You better fuck me just as hard.
Come on, come on.
Yes!
I hate you.
Come on, it's fucking cock already.
Do you not know how to fucking cum?
I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close, I'm close.
At least you're good for a cum, aren't you?
I'm good for more than that.
Or is it true?
You want no secret? You're good for a cum and go.
Bitch!
Now where were we?
Bye.
You know what's great?
Is that you can have my ass and my pussy.
You're gonna let him put it in your ass?
Fuck, look it just slides right in.
Oh my fucking god.
How did you do that?
Fuck.
Oh no, Luber, anything.
No fucking lube in it, you know that?
You didn't even spit on it
and you didn't fucking offer the courtesy.
All I have is your fucking pussy juice in there, huh?
I could do that.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, I could do that.
Tell me.
Tell me you can do that.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
You show me your fucking tits.
Make sure his cock stays nice and high.
Oh my God, I'm gonna fucking cum like that.
It's so weird how I could just tighten on that fucking asshole.
While she just sits there and watches that fucking asshole take it.
Oh my god, your clit is so in line.
I'm about to cum, fuck.
Yes, cum.
You want me to be complete?
Yes.
Oh, you're going to suck it right out of my asshole if you pull through?
Yes. Yes, I will.
Tell him.
I'm going to suck that fucking ass juice right off that dick.
Right back in there.
Look at that. It just slides in there.
Wow.
Oh, fuck finger my fucking cunt. Whoa
Push down in there. Yeah, push down on his fucking cock right there
Just like that.
Oh my god, your pussy's so wet.
Fuck yeah it is.
Yeah.
more, but it doesn't get anything.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Wow.
Oh, that's it.
Rub his dick.
Rub his dick again harder.
Harder?
Yeah.
Oh.
Why don't you show me, please, and show me why you fuck my asshole.
Your heart hurts.
Don't fucking be nice to me.
Be mean to me.
I'm going to cum.
Yes.
Oh, wow, I feel it.
I feel your pussy coming.
Oh, my God, yes, please.
Oh, my God.
You're so sweet.
Stop fucking me.
You want to turn on it?
You think you can take it like that?
Yes.
Yeah, I can take it like that.
You want to fuck her ass?
How do you want to?
What do you mean?
I'm a little fucking gaping at him, so...
Oh, shit.
oh it's so big oh so you can just do a no loop too huh yeah whoa oh my god
Look at that fucking crotch.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Oh my god, that feels so good.
Yeah.
Ha.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, that's amazing.
That's really sweet.
Yeah.
Can you fucking take a dick in your asshole?
Uh-huh.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Fuck.
Shit.
Oh my god, you're so sexy. Fuck.
Ah! Ah!
Ah! They're fucked!
Oh shit.
Calm for a minute.
You're falling off the couch there, girl.
Oh fuck. Yeah.
I'll just hold you right there and rub his feet for you.
What's your problem?
I want more.
Well, I want more too.
Well, he gets the pick, and look, he picked me.
Well, I'm sure he's going to come back to me soon.
Well, what is it? Did your asshole close up?
Huh? It needs to get restretched down?
Yeah, because you fucking stole it from me.
Oh, did I take too long?
Yeah, you did.
Oh, it looks like it stretched out pretty quick again.
Fuck yeah, I'm gonna get a little fucking whore.
Yeah, it is a slutty asshole, isn't it?
Oh, you got jokes, don't you?
Show me your tits while it fucks me.
I'll give you a round of applause for taking my dick.
Well, it's your turn.
Oh, yes please.
Told you he'd come back.
They always come back, don't they?
He ate that.
Oh damn. Oh damn. Alright, well let's see you shake your tits then.
It's so hard. You know I don't do that.
Let's see you do this.
I can't. I can do this?
See no evil, hear no evil.
Hard way to get me to shut the fuck up, huh?
Why would I want you to shut the f**k up?
You're right, how are you?
Yeah, but it's been way too long, hasn't it?
I thought I was going to let you go.
You b**ch.
Oh my god, you're a little better than that, don't you?
How are you gonna do that?
Bend the fuck over.
You were playing in it, why can't I?
If you're gonna be a good neighbor, at least share with me.
Okay.
Give me that.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I don't know, is it?
How much sugar do you fucking want, huh?
My asshole.
You like to watch me finger your fucking asshole?
Fuck, oh my god.
Yeah.
Yeah, damn!
Oh my god, it's so fucking nice in there.
You're really opening it up.
I know, I love it.
Oh, don't worry, I won't hurt you.
Oh my god, tell him.
My ass looks so good, I'm gonna make him fucking cum all over right now.
Oh my god, are you getting close in that asshole?
Oh my god.
You wanna watch it? I wanna be right there.
I wanna be right there.
It's fucking awesome!
Yes!
Oh my god, it's too sexy!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, it's so fucking hard right now!
I can tell, he's so close.
I can tell.
Oh yeah, it's fucking killing me.
Give it to us.
Oh my god.
It's so fucking warm and delicious.
That's what he gets for not picking on us.
Backing that up?
Ah!
Oh, he is fucking just coming back inside your asshole.
Oh, shit.
Damn.
Oh my god, it's so fucking hot.
My ass is just gaping all over the window.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Damn.
Damn, I can't believe it's still so hot up here, mom.
It's so fucking good.
Oh, fuck it.
I thought it might fucking...
You want a little taste?
Did you step on my face?
Yeah?
Was that a good idea?
No.
Are you still mine?
Say it.
I'm yours.
Hey, good news.
My wife left for town and, oh man, I knew I shouldn't have left.
Oh, don't worry.
Sorry, I wasn't ever going to fuck you.
Yeah, me neither.