Hey Emily, what are you doing?
Thank you for inviting me.
But I want to quit this time.
I'm like a zombie.
I haven't been able to sleep properly for a month.
Thank you.
Hey Emily, what are you doing?
You know, right?
Do you remember?
About the dream.
It will never disappear.
That dream you had with your Egyptian wife?
Kiki...
It's been like this for a few weeks.
Of course, I did everything I could.
I went to the doctor and went to therapy.
I tried all the martial arts, but it didn't work at all.
It doesn't make any sense at all.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, I don't have a way to introduce her to you.
She is the last...
Really? I'll do anything.
Will you tell me about her?
Yes, she is a very good person.
I think she can help you.
Yeah, and then?
And then?
Is this it?
Your phone number is 06-39-715-4532.
This is your phone number.
Are you okay?
Okay.
That's all?
I'll call this person right away.
Thank you.
That's a nice dress.
This is Emily.
Please come in.
So, Emily, what did you do today?
What can I do for you?
I've been having a weird dream for the past few weeks.
It's like I'm the queen of Egypt, the queen of Egypt.
And I have a dream of becoming the king of Egypt.
That dream is very intense.
I've been having that dream every day for the past few weeks.
I understand.
You seem to be trapped in your previous life.
What? Am I the queen of Egypt?
Do you want to break up with your husband?
My husband?
I'm not married yet.
Emily, if you want to be released,
you have to believe me.
My husband...
I want to talk to him.
That's how you do it.
What are you doing?
Ouch!
Hey, don't tease me!
Emily, I finally found you.
Stop it. This is not funny.
This is not a dream.
We can be together again.
Let's rewrite our memories forever.
I...
I'm really sorry for making you wait so long.
I'm sorry.
Oh
I've been thinking about you for a long time.
I want you to love me more.