Why can't you do such a thing?
You're a pain in the neck.
Get out of here.
Hey, hurry up.
It's been a while.
I heard you succeeded, but did you really become a top?
You've always known that I'm special.
What did you come here for?
I don't want you to fight with Jodan anymore.
Why do I have to do such a thing?
For me.
For me?
I don't have the guts to quit for you.
It started again.
Do you even know what you're saying?
I loved you more than anyone else.
We were together all the time.
But you left me and went to Jordan.
I can't believe you're saying that now.
Don't say that.
I came here today because I want to stop fighting with each other.
I want to stop being a monster.
We broke up because you became a monster who lost yourself.
I'm not a monster.
Emily, I'm not. I didn't mean it.
Kneel down.
I didn't mean to transform. Please.
But I can't stand you anymore.
I'll let you go.
Oh, my God.
I can't take it anymore.
I love you so much, Emily.
I sent my sister, but Jordan is going to die soon.
I took Jordan from you.
This is all mine.
Oh, my God.
to get out of here.