Oh
Manuel, you'll speak when spoken to.
She'll do, I think.
Manuel?
I agree.
Any objections from you?
It's not your first time, is it?
Hmm.
Get on your knees.
Good girl.
So pretty.
Let me see that pretty mouth.
Hmm.
Mm, fuck, mm, it's so warm and wet.
Stick it all the way out.
Mm, fuck, I'm gonna put that tongue to good use.
Mm, oh man.
Mm, fuck.
Look up at me, those pretty eyes.
Take my tits off.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I can't get out of here.
Fuck.
Stick it out.
Do what she says.
Good girl.
Oh, my God.
Let's go back to that dick.
Let me show you how to do it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, let me see that tongue, yeah, that's hot, that's hot, like, oh, my fucking shoulder, yeah, it's red, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's choking out,
Chug on that big dick, good girl, yes.
Yeah, make her nasty, she's too quick.
Make her nasty, she's too quick.
I want you to spit all over that fucking dick.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Spit all over it.
Yes, nasty little slut.
Oh, I love it.
No, no, no.
Get up here.
Good.
You gonna be a good little slut for her?
Yes. Yes.
Can we make a stick?
Yes, please.
How bad did you want this dick?
Oh, I want it so bad. Please.
Oh
Oh, yes, I love it.
Please, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I feel so good.
Yes.
She had to go from side to side.
Oh, my God.
I think that little pussy is fucking sick.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to stay right here.
I'm going to get fucked on top of you.
Oh, please.
Yes. Oh, yes. Fuck. Oh, my God. Yes. That feels so good. Yes. Fuck. Oh, my God. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes, oh my God, fuck, yes, that's so sad, man.
Yeah, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
I love that, I love that.
Oh, yes, bug, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh my god, this little pussy tickles.
Yeah, oh my god, we tickled you.
Yes.
Like the way my husband fucks me in the ears?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yes, that tickles, it tickles, it tickles, it tickles.
I love the way it tastes.
Good, good, yes, mm.
Use both your hands.
Yes.
Yes, good girl.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
So much right here.
Oh my god.
Oh yes.
Show us what you can do with that tongue.
Yeah.
Good girl.
Yeah, go, yeah, suck it hard,
like you want to make it come, come on.
Make it all wet so my wife can't fucking sit on it.
Make it all wet so my wife can't sit on it.
Hands off.
You can watch, but you can't touch.
Yes.
Oh god.
No.
I don't know.
Hands off of you, too.
Good girl.
You're gonna keep being a good girl, won't you, bud?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Get on to all the stuff.
Please, please.
Oh, my god.
Please, give me that.
Oh, that looks so good.
Oh, it's so big.
Go inside that little pussy.
Yes.
Fuck.
Mm.
Oh, yes, fuck, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh my god.
Oh, please.
Please what?
You wanna come on that dick?
Yes, please, I wanna come on it, please.
Yes, yes.
Yes, fuck those hips.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
Oh, my God, this is so good.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck, that feels so good.
Oh fuck yes.
Oh please.
Oh, yeah, it's work.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Bring your arms back here.
Here.
Shoes down.
Yeah, that's good.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Oh my god, I love this
Oh, fuck.
Bury that face in there, come on.
Bury that face in there, come on, come on.
Bury that face in that pussy.
I'm so close, it's so good.
It's time.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God!
Come here.
Get up.
Now watch her.
I don't want you, I don't want you.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, yeah, yeah.
Your sex is so good.
I need it.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my god.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, my god.
Yeah.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
I'll be watching you.
Show him, show him.
I just want to please you.
Good, good, that's what I need.
Oh, my, your pussy's so fucking white, it's mine.
Oh, God.
Oh, I love that smile.
Keep showing me how you feel.
Take that tongue out.
Yeah, take that tongue out.
Okay, you got it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, okay, put it in.
Come this way, come this way.
oh my god
oh it's so fucking big inside me
Yeah, I fucking love it.
I love it so much.
Please, please, I fucking need it.
Oh, I love the way you tease me.
I love the way you fuck me.
Yeah, you used your pussy on me.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Oh my god, fuck.
So close, baby.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Oh, she needs to be in that position.
She doesn't really like her position, though.
Oh, okay, I love it.
Now, I'll give that to her.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm around the way for a second.
Oh, okay.
I won't show it.
Oh, that's so strong.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I want to see that dog.
Deep, deep, deep, all the way.
Put it all the way deep in that fucking pussy.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
Sit on her, sit on that face.
Right there.
Yeah.
Look at those little pussies right here.
Here, yes.
Give me that hold.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, a little pussy on the head, yeah.
I see that booty.
Yes, on that ass.
Go back, go back, go back.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, I'll go right back.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, I need more, please.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
More, please, more, please, yes, harder, yes.
Come on, come on, see the pretty face, I'll do it one more time.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, shit.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, let's do it, yes, get that fucking dick
inside our slutty little pussy, yeah, use that fucking
pussy, yeah, get it, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, push it deeper,
get down, get down, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
It's good.
It's fucking pretty.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Let me see it.
Oh, it's so fucking pretty.
Thank you.
You're such a good girl, babe.
Would you like the taste of my husband's con?
Boy, you've done your job.
So why are you still here?
Oh, but...
I said get out I'll see you again soon we'll be in touch