Oh, hello Brazzers!
I'm very excited to be here recording with Angela White again.
It's the last scene of my trip, so...
Well, you know, the final boss.
Did you flip over?
Oh, thanks.
Flip over...
Okay, let's see.
Well, I want to do everything with Angela, so...
Let's start.
Penetration on all.
I don't know if there will be, but I'll say yes, just in case.
Oh, this too. Yes, yes.
Biting? Of course, Angela can do whatever she wants with me.
Bondage? Also. Yes.
Choking? Yes.
Covering my mouth? Of course, please.
Cream pie, I don't know if there will be cream pie or if it will be facial, but well, let's say yes
just in case, it can be both if you want
Cool swapping, this is not for me
Deep throat, please, yes
Nipple pinching
Yes, please, I want to
touch those big melons
I love Angela's tits, they are the best in porn, so yes, please
Okay, next.
Yes.
Yes, too.
I don't think we're doing it today.
So, no.
Okay, this one, yes.
Rock penetration.
Yes.
Scissoring applicable today.
Slapping, spanking and spitting.
All three, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, and yes.
Okay, guys, that's it.
Let's see Angela.
I'm very excited to see what she's wearing and to see how beautiful she is.
Here I have the script, so now I'll give it a last look.
Come on, let's see if it's ready.
It's amazing. It's almost ready. What bigger tits do you have? I didn't remember them
being so big. They're much better in person. Wow, I'm very excited. Let's greet her.
Hi. Hi.
Wow, you look amazing. Thank you. I've missed you.
Oh, you're welcome.
Oh, you're so big.
Did you miss them?
Yes, I did.
Yes?
I miss them every day.
Have you been dreaming about them?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, so nice.
Wow.
Oh, let me see.
Let me see them.
Why don't you get on your knees?
Oh my God.
I know you missed these big tits, didn't you?
Oh yes, they are amazing.
Let me see.
Yes.
Oh yeah, put them right in your face.
Mm, fuck.
Mm.
Oh yeah.
Oh, let me slap your face with them.
Mm.
Mm, yes.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Mm.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Ah, smutty with these big tits.
Oh yes, I'm so happy.
No breathing for you.
Oh, yeah.
I love the way you lick and suck on them.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Suck them as hard as you can.
Yeah.
I think it's time I got on my knees
oh yes
oh my god
fuck
wow
Wow. I missed this. Such a nice big dick for me.
Fuck. Yeah, get it out.
Oh, fuck. It's so perfect.
Perfect.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, you know I love this foreskin.
Oh yeah.
I remember.
I'm sticking my tongue in it.
Oh my god.
Love the way it rolls back and forth.
mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Oh yeah!
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum!
Oh!
Oh yeah!
Oh my god!
Let's have a go.
Thought you'd buy the balls.
Oh yes, the brick.
It's mine now.
Oh my god.
Ah, fuck.
Yes.
Yeah, let that drip down to these tits.
Mm, let's spit it up.
Fuck, so much spit.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I can't forget about these balls.
Oh, please.
Oh my God.
Fuck.
Tickle them with my nails.
Oh, yes, so nice.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god, it's so fucking big.
I love it.
I'm going to stretch out my pussy with this big dick.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, I can't wait.
Yes, I need that dick inside me, come give it to me, yes please, oh yes, yes, yes, oh
my god, fuck, yes, oh fuck, yes, oh that's so fucking good, oh I miss that dick, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, take it.
Fuck.
My God, yes.
It feels so fucking good inside that little pussy.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
My God, it's so fucking big.
Yes.
Fuck.
Yes, baby, do it.
Fuck, yes, yes, fuck.
Fuck, oh my god, I love the way it feels.
Yes, oh my god, your balls deep inside there.
Yeah, it feels so good inside that hole.
Oh, fuck, so good.
Yeah, I can feel your full skin rolling back and forth
inside that little pussy, how much I love it.
Fuck, yes, oh, that's it right there, fuck.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, oh my god, yeah, you're gonna make me come like that, fuck, yes, yeah, do it, fuck, Jodi, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god, yes, let's do this, let's do this, right there, right there, right there, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Oh, yes, oh my god, yes, Jodi, fuck, yeah, yes, yes, take me, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck,
Yes fucking do it. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
MMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM
Oh yeah, let me taste that dick.
Yeah, I wanna taste my dick.
I wanna watch you fuck me.
Yeah, I so wanna watch you.
Yes, yes.
Fuck yes.
Yeah, yeah.
It's so good.
Yeah, it's so good.
Yeah.
Yeah, oh my god, fuck, yeah, yeah, so big and soft, yeah, fuck, yeah, that's good, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god, fuck, yes, good,
Oh, your dick feels so fucking good like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Talk dirty to me in Spanish.
Oh, you are nasty.
Thought you were an angel.
I'm not so much of an angel, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
I can watch it go in and out of you.
Damn, that looks so good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's so good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
You're gonna choke me, trip me, you're gonna trip me like that, yeah, yeah, yes, be fucking nasty, yeah, do it, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god, yes, fuck, yes, that's good, fuck, fuck, yeah, do it, be nasty, be nasty, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it, that's, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop.
Oh, you're getting me so fucking close.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck.
You're gonna make me cum like that, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuck!
Oh my god, yes, yes, right there, right there, right there, oh fuck, yes, oh my god, you
have so much stamina, I fucking love it, yes, fuck, oh, that's so good, yes, fuck,
Fuck, yes, mm, oh yeah, I got you by the balls again.
Make you fuck me, let me grab him.
Yes, there we go, yes, mm, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck yeah, that's my fucking dick,
that's my fucking dick, yes, yes, yes, fuck, mm.
Oh, yes.
Mmm.
Fuck. Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Fuck. Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, that's so fucking deep.
It's like that, yes, fuck, oh, fuck, yes, oh, yes.
So fucking good, yeah, mmm, mmm, mmm, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck, that's it, oh my god, so deep like that, yes.
Yeah, use me, use me, fuck, oh, yes, fuck, yes, fuck.
Fuck, yeah, oh yeah, use me, fuck, yes, oh my god, fuck,
yeah, oh god, that's so good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
oh fuck, my little toy, yes, fuck, oh, you just here
to fuck me and do whatever I want, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Mm.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Mm.
Let me ride you.
OK.
Give you a little break.
Mm.
Oh, my god.
This dick is so fucking nice.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Mm.
Oh.
Fuck you, oh no, put it back in me, put it back in me, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh fuck, it feels so good inside that pussy.
Yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
God, you, fuck, fuck, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
I love the way you suck on those nipples.
Yes, fuck, fuck, fuck, oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Fuck, that dick is so fucking nice.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Fuck, you like it when the big tits bounce in your face?
Oh yeah, I know.
Oh yeah.
I fucking love you.
Oh my god, that feels so fucking good.
Yeah.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, fuck,
Oh my god, it's so red.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Oh fuck.
Holy fuck.
Damn, that tickles me.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
I feel so good.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I feel so good inside me.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck!
Oh my god!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh fuck! Yeah, yeah, yeah! Give it to me!
Fuck!
Oh my god!
Yes! Yes!
Yes, oh yes, fuck, fuck, oh that feels so fucking good.
Yes, yes, yes, just like that, just like that.
Oh my God, fuck Jodi, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my God, Jodi, you're gonna make me cum again, fuck.
Fuck, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes, oh, yeah, oh, fuck, oh, yeah.
Oh fuck, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh fuck, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, fuck, yes, oh, oh, good, fuck, I missed that day, oh, oh, he's so fucking close again, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God.
Lay down here.
Bring me these legs.
Put them up here.
Come here, come here.
Yes, just like that.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh fuck, yes, make that fucking dick disappear between the teeth, yes, so long as we fucking slam these teeth, yes, jiggle them around that dick, yes, yes, fuck, yes,
nice and slow
slowly stroke
that dick
oh my god
fuck
so what's titty fucking
in Spanish
guana
guana?
I'm not saying it right at all
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, yeah.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Suck it again.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Fuck, it's so perfect.
Oh yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh my god.
Fuck, yeah.
Yeah, it's so fucking perfect.
It's such a heavy dick.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh yeah.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm,
mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm,
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh.
Can I lick that off?
Bury my face in there.
Oh, my God, fuck, that made you even harder.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
These balls seem so full.
Oh, yes, they are.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, this cum belongs to me.
Oh, yeah, you don't need that cum in your bowls anymore.
I'm gonna fucking taste it.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck yes.
Yeah, I want these bowls empty.
Mm, fuck yes.
Oh, fuck.
You're so hard.
You're throbbing for me.
Mm, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I can feel you getting closer and closer.
Yeah, fuck, yeah, oh, my veins are bulging.
Oh, yes, look at my voice.
You want me to take your bowl?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Do you want it?
Do you want to come?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm
Oh, it's so fucking bad, yeah, oh my god,
those balls are so fucking full, mm, yes, that's it, yeah.
Oh my god, yeah, it's fucking shaky, yeah,
fucking throbbing for me, mm, yes, oh, one more,
I want that fucking letter, every last drop of it,
Fuck yeah, you're going to give me that fucking cum?
That's my fucking cum.
Fucking give it to me.
I deserve it.
Fucking cum.
Yes, fuck.
Yeah, that's my fucking cum.
Give it to me.
Yes, fuck.
Fuck, that's a big load.
Holy fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, look, you fucking covered me.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Missed you, Geordie.
Ah, I'm pissed.