Where's the pipe that needs servicing?
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry. Yes, I think it's under the sink, I think. That one.
Is that sticky tape?
Hey, do you need any help at all?
Not unless you've got a plumbing certification or a huge car.
Oh, fuck it's hot.
Oh shit, fuck, I think I'm actually stuck.
Could you give me a hand?
That's not a wrench.
Nope, but it sure does,
I sure do use it to tighten pipes a lot.
Well, you may as well put it to work.
Billy for that.
Oh my God.
Fuck, yes, that feels so fucking good.
Yes, I had to get so fucking big, oh my god, yes, yes.
Yes! Yes! Fuck!
It feels so good.
Fuck yes!
You really get deep in there, don't you?
Oh my god, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Here, this is for the other pipe.
I keep it in my tool belt just in case.
Fuck.
Oh yeah, lift the whole thing up.
Make it nice and shiny.
Yeah.
Fuck.
I wanna feel so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, your tongue feels so good.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Let's see what you can do with that pipe.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, yeah, oh my God, yes, fuck.
Oh, that feels incredible.
Damn, you really do tighten pipes with that, don't you?
Fuck, oh, put it back in there, yes.
Oh, oh, look at how hot that dick is, fuck.
Oh yeah, keep going just like that, fuck.
Yes, fuck.
Oh yeah, you're gonna be so fucking close like that.
Oh my God, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh my God, you're gonna make me fucking cum like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god. Oh, and I think you got me unstuck.
Thank you so much.
Treasures work down there.
I know, I don't know why. It always happens.
I think I got it.
Fuck!
Yes, baby girl, that's so good.
Oh, you came to the right house, mm-hmm.
Oh, that's so good, that's so good.
Yes.
Yeah.
Aw, look how good that dick looks in there.
Trapped in there.
Yes.
Yes, let's put them together for you now.
Oh my fucking god.
Fuck.
Look at those fucking holes.
Shh.
Spit all over them.
Mm.
So fucking good.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, baby.
Oh, man.
Oh my god, put the fucking, yes.
Go back and forth, just the tip.
Back and forth.
Fuck, you're so fucking hard for me.
Oh, I know, you just want to fuck it, don't you?
Yes.
All right, let's start with that pussy.
You're so fucking hard for me.
Oh god, yes! Fuck, that's good! Yes, baby!
Wait, you ticked that little pussy. Yes!
Fuck, yes!
Yes!
Oh my god!
Fuck, make me cum, make me cum on the dick!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh my god, you're so fucking hot for me.
You want to go back and forth?
Yes.
I need to go to my fucking home.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Don't.
Stop.
Oh my god, it's so fucking perfect.
Oh, I fucking love it.
Oh my god, it's so hot, I can barely get it down my throat.
oh my god
yes
yes yes yes
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my fucking god.
Have you seen these tits yet?
Have you seen them?
Fuck yes.
Mm, fuck you.
Ugh.
Mm.
Oh my god, yes!
Yes, oh my god, look at this.
That's so fun.
It's so nice and wet now.
Fuck.
Fuck yes.
It's so fucking wet.
Yes!
Hmm, so nice and wet and ready for my arsehole. Look at all that fuck.
Stay right there.
Right in that pussy first.
Oh, fuck, oh my God, I feel so fucking good
but I don't know where I need it.
There we go, and that, yes, oh my God, fuck.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, that's so fucking good like that.
Fuck, yes, oh fuck, oh, your dick feels so good
in that nose, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh my God.
Put it back in, put it back in.
So good inside that house like that.
Yes.
Yeah, take it, take it, that's yours.
That's your fucking home.
Oh, oh.
Keep going, keep going, you're gonna be so fucking close.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck yeah.
Fuck.
Oh yeah, I can feel your cockiness.
You're so deep in that fucking asshole.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Keep fucking me like that.
Oh my God.
That looks so good going in and out of that asshole.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh fuck, yes, yes, keep going like that
or you're gonna make me come in.
Please, yes, please.
Oh, yes!
Come on, here.
I can't.
That was so good, inside me, yes, yes, yes, oh my God.
Oh my God, I'm gonna be fucking crying.
Oh my God, fuck, oh my God, I'm so, I'm so, I'm so sorry.
Oh my God, all right, there's a difference,
there's a difference right there.
Oh my God, I have to take off, fuck.
Oh my God, fuck, yes, yes, yes,
get close to the side of the pussy, baby,
Yeah! Yeah!
Fuck!
There it is! There it is!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I'm gonna cum!
Oh my fucking god!
Yes! Fuck!
That's my two nights fake life.
Mm, mm, mm.
The pipe's being cleared, pressure's being relieved.
You should be good for at least 72 hours.
I don't even know what you fixed.
Neither do I, but your plumbing
definitely passed the stress test.
Okay.