Do you like the sound?
This is ready for you.
With me like this.
I will be your slut.
Or just a little bit bad girl.
Just a little bit.
Makes me crazy.
Do you see the spots?
Yeah.
Do you want me to take it off?
I take off my panties and you will show me your small dick.
That's a good deal.
This I will make when I want you shut up.
Just put my wet band-aids to your mouth and it will be quiet.
You know what is this one.
Make my things bigger.
For example my toilet.
But for your small dick, it doesn't work.
So sorry.
You see it well?
You just need to put it here.
And then slowly...scroll.
you see my pussy yeah check it
i feel my clit is now full of blood
oh it makes me so horny
Want to see it again?
Yeah, just put it here.
Just a moment.
I want you to join me like this.
Yeah.
Shit, how are you doing?
Did you see this?
Yeah.
Oh, it's such a perfect.
it's so hard now
maybe a little bit, yeah, wow, he's so cute.
It's so big.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm tired.
Oh, slowly.
Yeah, I want to feel it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yeah.