Wow, what a beautiful place you have here.
Thanks.
Make yourself comfortable.
Thank you.
Sit on the couch.
Wow, it's getting lonely over here.
You know, I had a great time tonight.
Oh, me too.
That restaurant was amazing.
Maybe you could help me with that?
Mmm, I would love a back rose.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Thank you.
Ah, mmm.
Ah, that feels so nice.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm. You really know what you're doing with those fingers.
Oh. Oh. Yes. Mmm. I love it. Mmm. Excuse me?
Oh boob, that's not what you were trying to do, was it?
Okay, I think that's enough of that, mister.
Oh, you've got me so horny now.
Let me give you a better view.
You're good on them.
Mmm. Yes.
Oh.
Oh. You're good at massaging
tits too, aren't you?
Mmm.
Oh, yeah. Jiggle
them.
Mmm.
You like that noise they make?
Oh.
Mmm.
Fuck. They're heavy, right?
for me, yes, oh I love the way you squeeze them, yes.
Bounce them.
Fuck.
I want to see how hard these big tits made you
oh my goodness you're so fucking hard that makes me so wet baby
I need to see this hot dick.
look how hard you are for me
oh wow that's incredible
i need to see it properly oh my god that dick is so big
I'm playing with it.
Roll to the tip of your cup.
I just wanna wash it, babe.
Damn, that's a big dick.
So fun to stroke.
Can't forget about these balls.
Mmm, I want to make out with your cock.
Wrap these big tits around it.
Oh, it's so hard between these soft tits.
Oh, that feels so good.
Fuck.
Damn.
Oh, jiggle these big tits around him.
Yeah, you like that.
Mm.
Yes.
Well, better slow it down.
Don't want to make you come too quickly.
Mm.
There's a lot of things I want to do with this hot dick.
Mmm, a lot of fun I want to have with it.
I need the stick inside me.
Let me get a little more comfortable.
I won't be needing this.
I want to fuck.
How do you want to get started?
I love writing.
Let me just grind it on it first.
Tease you.
Yes.
God, your dick feels so good inside my little pussy.
Fuck.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes.
I'll sit right down, I get it deep in there.
Oh, creating new space inside that pussy, fuck.
Oh, oh, and I want to see you.
Let me taste my pussy off this dick.
Yeah, I want to see you as I ride you.
Yes.
Oh, yes, that's it, baby.
Stick it in me.
fuck fuck yes yes yes oh my god baby yes yes that dick is so fucking good
see oh my god yes yes yes oh good you're gonna be humming so much
oh my god yes baby fuck
Fuck.
Oh, your dick feels so good.
Yes.
Oh yes, don't stop giving me that dick, baby.
Oh, it's so good like that.
Fuck.
yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, right there, I'm gonna cum, baby.
I'm gonna cum like that, I'm gonna cum like that.
Please don't stop.
My, my.
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Oh my god, baby, you made me cum so fucking hard.
You're so good with that cum.
Let me taste my cum off you.
yes yes yes oh like that i'm gonna come baby
oh oh oh oh
oh you got me coming so hard so i'll put it back in
Fuck.
Damn, it looks so good inside my pussy.
Yes.
Fuck.
Walk that dick inside there.
Get nice and close for me.
Yeah, get nice and close inside that pussy.
And then you're gonna choose where you come.
I can feel you getting closer in there.
Oh, I want to suck your balls until you come.
Come over here.
Your balls are so filled with cum.
Oh fuck, oh and your dick is so hot and your veins are bulging.
I can tell you really want to cum, so where do you want to cum?
Mmm. I love cum on my face.
Yes.
Your cum tastes so good.
Mmm, any left in there? Oh, no.
Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
Thank you, baby.
I had a little fun with you.
We should do this again sometime.
Mmm.
See you soon.