This thing on.
We serve, we serve spicy Yeah, we know it's a lot
We thicken the plot Bring it up real hot
Serve spicy Give it all that you got
One chance, one shot Guess it up, we'll stand to start
A real life piece of art We serve, we serve spicy
Yeah, we know it's a lot Bring it up real hot
We serve, we serve spicy Second time we come around
yum yum
What we serve, we serve spicy
Yeah, we know it's a lot
We thick in the plot
Bring it up real hot
Serve spicy
Give it all that you got
One chance, one shot
Uh, uh
Gas it up, we'll send a star
A real life piece of art
We serve, we serve spicy
Yeah, we know it's a lot
Bring it up real hot
We serve, we serve spicy
Serve spicy
it up real hot, we serve, we serve spicy.
Just want to take a seat here for me.
Right here?
Yep.
relax.
Can I take this off for you?
Sure.
You can put your head back there.
Listen, I'm a little nervous.
I'm being honest, I'm really nervous.
I do not like coming here.
That's okay, just try to relax.
I promise I'll be very, very gentle.
Okay, sweetie?
All right, open wide for me.
That's a really good job.
How's it looking, girl?
Oh, good.
There's just, I think, a crack a tiny way in the back.
Where?
It's just back there if you can,
I might have to get in a bit closer to see.
Oh, okay.
Let's see, open wide again for me.
Little crack in the back there, I think.
Oh, where?
I don't see it.
Just here?
If you can get in a little bit closer, you can probably see.
Oh, oh, there it is.
Because we might be able to fix that with a crown.
Yeah, I think so.
Maybe just definitely he's been flossing, as you can see.
Oh, yeah.
His gums look really healthy.
That's what I thought, too.
He must really, really prioritise his dental pads.
Oh, we appreciate that.
We do.
We love people that look after their teeth and mess off us.
Nice breath, too.
Really fruity and minty.
Oh, doctor.
Okay, sounds good to me.
I'm gonna need you to keep your mouth open for me.
Oh, you don't mind if she takes care of that while I keep working, do you?
Head back, open wide.
Just get a little more comfort as well, if you don't mind.
Say ah.
Say ah really loud.
Oh yeah, that's good.
That's very good.
Just check one more thing.
Yes, yes, very good, very good.
I'm very impressed with your hygiene.
Yeah, you know what?
Your enamel is nice and hot, just like I like it.
Gal, do you mind coming up and helping me up here?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my god, he really does have great hygiene.
Mm-hmm, he sure does.
Oh yeah, he loves getting smothered.
Fuck yes.
I love feeling that fucking tongue on my big toes.
Smothering every single puff.
Fuck yes.
Oh, yeah, just like that.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Bounce your fucking tits in.
Yeah.
Yeah, push them in every way.
Just like this.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Open wide, fit both titties in there, yeah.
You're so good with that fucking tongue.
Because I used to have such a good jawline.
Boy, you can get in there too.
Fuck.
Oh, I felt so spoiled.
Oh, yes, fuck.
Yes, fuck.
I'll stretch that little pussy out.
Fuck.
He's so perfect.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, my fucking god, yes, just like that.
I can't believe I'm rolling inside of your face!
Fuck!
Oh, that's so fucking hot!
Use it, use it, use it!
Fuck, keep moving!
I need you back and over.
Don't fly.
Yeah, I need that cock.
Yes, I need some of that cock.
Please.
Oh, yeah.
Put your face in there, too.
Fuck, baby. Oh my god.
Oh, you're so good with that mouth.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes, baby.
Fuck.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
I love almost through the fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just like me. Just like me.
Just like me.
Yes, baby. Give it to me.
Oh.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's brilliant.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
That dick feels so fucking good.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, Keith.
Just like that, just like that, just like that, just like that.
Just like that, just like that.
Oh, my God.
You're still like me.
That dick felt so fucking good.
That's the way you worship those fucking tits.
Yeah.
It's like that baby keeps going.
Oh my fucking dick.
Oh my god.
Oh my god I'm gonna cum.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Suck these fucking tits.
Suck these tits.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes, I fucking love that.
I'm going to stick your tongue in between every one of my fucking toes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God, yeah, feed me your tits.
Yeah.
Oh, that's so good, baby.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes, yes.
Take my hug.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes, I love that.
Fuck you.
Yeah! Oh, I love it when you suck it hard like that. Yes!
Yeah! Oh, fuck, baby! Yeah! Yes, keep giving me that dick!
Fuck!
You can see, okay, see this?
Oh! Yeah!
This is so funny!
All the rage is on that pussy, just watch.
I'm not talking.
Fuck, baby, don't stop, don't stop! Make me cum again on that cum!
Yeah, baby, that's right. That's what I need, baby! That's what I need!
There's a very fucking face in this, too.
Yes, yes, fucking worship them.
Yes, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes.
She needs some more of your cock.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm, baby.
Ooh.
What's it gonna do with that?
Mm.
Ooh.
Damn.
Mm.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God, it's so fucking pussy, babe.
Let me fucking taste that pussy. Let me taste that pussy.
I hate it! I hate it!
I'm fucking mad at you!
Use it, use it, use it, use it!
Holy shit!
Fuck! Oh my god!
Oh, yeah, let me get to these bullets.
Yes.
Oh.
Fuck, babe.
Yeah, baby.
Let me fucking put that to you.
Yes, baby.
Oh.
Oh, she does that so fucking well.
Yes.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, babe.
Yeah, get it down your throat, baby. Get it down your throat.
You got it, baby. Come here.
You know what you're doing, don't you?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes, fuck.
Oh.
Fuck, baby.
God damn.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck!
Yes, baby.
Oh, my God.
Damn.
My love.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
Fuck!
Oh, yes.
Oh my god, your tongue is so sore.
Oh, fuck.
God damn.
Using the tip like that with my fluffy hand.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
We got you.
Yeah, sit down, baby. I want to ride you.
Oh, fuck yes.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, that feels so fucking good.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
She feels so fucking good.
Go.
Yes, yes, good.
So fucking close to coming on that cock.
Oh fuck, yes, yes, yes.
I guess I did, baby. I guess I fuckin' did.
Yes, baby.
Oh, my God, yes.
Yes. Yes.
Good, baby. Work that fuckin' fist.
Work that fuckin' fist.
Fuck. Yes.
Yeah, rub that clit for me, baby.
Yeah.
Give me these, baby. Give me these.
No, fuck me.
I don't give a fuck if you're tired.
Give me what I fuckin' want.
Yes!
Put it back in me.
Yeah, there you go.
There you go.
You're so fucking sweaty and tired.
You're gonna give us what we fucking want.
Such a good boy.
Keep going. Keep going. Keep going.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, babe.
Oh, my God.
Come here.
I'm like the fucking sweat.
Oh, come on.
I told you to get up.
Come on.
Fuck.
Come here.
No.
Fuck.
Come here.
Give her that fucking dick that she deserves.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
What's going on?
Yeah.
Doesn't look the most like it.
I don't know if that's right, little fucking cunt.
Yeah.
Hey.
Fuck.
Oh my goodness.
It's not the king of those tips.
Now you want to be suffocated?
Yeah.
Open your mouth.
Yes!
You know what, she's fucked up with pussy.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Fuck, baby.
Hmm.
Oh.
Yes, baby.
Oh my god.
Fuck, baby.
Yes.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Look at all this sweat.
So give us that fucking cum.
We want every single fucking drool that's inside of those balls.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, we want that fucking cologne.
We want every single fucking drool for that.
I'm sorry, baby.
Oh, that pre-cum tastes so fucking good.
Oh, yes, that's so fucking hot.
Oh, my God, yes, back and forth, back and forth.
Oh, my God, yes.
We want it so fucking much
It's fucking so good!
Those veins are bulging.
Look at all that fucking pre, cause it's so hot.
It really fucking is.
Fucking years of pre, those fucking faces.
I can't wait to fucking taste it.
Yes, baby.
Those balls are so ready to fucking come.
They really are.
I used to cum when I was so fucking bad
Yes, baby, you give it to us
Yeah, fuck
Oh, my God
Oh, fuck
Oh, my fucking God
Oh, fuck, that cum tastes so good.
Yum, every single drop.
So sensitive now.
You did so well at your dentist appointment.
Oh, come on up here.
Oh, I think you forgot this.
Oh.
How's your shot?
So, uh, what's my next appointment?
The receptionist can help you with that.
Make sure you keep up the good flossing.
Will do.
See you next time.
Doctor, you're going to be late for your next appointment.
They can wait.