You're the best big brother I could have ever asked for.
Wow, this looks really pretty on you.
Like, pretty enough for a date?
It's perfect for a date.
Yay.
So, should you suck a stick first, or should we do it together?
I don't know.
I could eat your pussy while he fucks me.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Okay, are you almost done?
Finishing touches.
Okay.
Oh, hey, Parker.
Hey.
You should ask him.
Yeah, go, go.
Um, so, I have a question.
Okay.
Hey, could we get your advice on a date?
Um, sure.
Would you rather go somewhere super fancy or just stay at home all casual?
stay at home I guess so like what do you do on a date just do you go out do you
like just watch a movie usually I order out because I'm not the best at cooking
I guess yeah watch a movie and have a little cuddle sesh okay so movie that's
your ideal date yeah sounds simple enough yeah okay is that all
yeah sure thanks yeah that was very very helpful thank you parker okay
Okay.
Bye, Parker.
Parker.
Parker!
We need to show you something.
What's up?
Well, so we need your opinion
to rate outfits for a date.
Please.
okay we actually also got you your own date with you yeah so basically if you
help us with our date we'll hook you up with a date yeah sure easy enough so
your options are purple or pink purple do you think this one would make my
My boobies look bigger?
Yeah, I guess.
How about me?
Red or blue?
Blue.
Oh my gosh.
Do you think it'll make my ass look good?
Yeah, sure.
Wrong answer.
Her ass always looks good.
So are you just gonna stand there and watch us pervert?
Yeah.
Turn around.
Duh.
Yeah, turn around.
Okay.
Okay, now peeking.
All right, well.
It's so tight.
I know.
It's kind of hard to get on.
Okay.
Do you need a hand?
Cute.
Okay.
You can turn around now.
I guess.
What do you think?
Wow, y'all look really cute.
hot. Thank you, thank you. Well, the girls that we set you up with tonight are also
very hot. Yeah, um, one's brunette, petite, super cute. Yeah, and the other one is blonde
and super fun and bubbly. And they both have really nice tits.
Oh well, I can't wait to meet them.
I'll book a change.
Yeah, yeah, you go do that.
Dude, your stepbrother is really slow.
I know, but I heard he's got a really big dick.
Shut up.
What's going on surprise we're your dates and we're skipping right to dessert
So big I dare you to lick it first
The rumors are true. I was thinking the same thing
Did the rumors say it tastes good too? Because I know. We're gonna have to add that one.
You look so pretty with that cock stuffed in your mouth.
Oh, fuck, this is so much fun.
Oh my God.
We should give them a better view.
We should.
Look at how pretty these are.
I bet you were taking a sneak peek at them earlier on.
I caught you looking at us... a few times.
I think he likes it. I guess he does.
My cock is throbbing.
Fuck.
Yeah, I'm making a third hand in here.
Maybe touch his balls too.
All four hands at once.
It's way funner when we do it together.
I know, right?
Oh my god, I'm gonna make you come together.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I get it all wet, bestie.
I think we want to feel your cock inside of us.
Yeah, right now.
I want to go first.
Fine.
Hurry up or I'm gonna steal it from you.
I wanna see.
Oh my god.
Stop, brother.
It feels so good.
Oh my god.
You like this,
huh? Don't you?
I do know he does.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh
Mind sucking his cock for a few more hours. I know he tastes so good
Only after he makes me cum though
Just look at your stepsisters titties
I just want to bounce off of you.
Oh, yes.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, I love it.
I'm getting tired.
I'm tired.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, yes.
It feels so good.
I'm having so much fun with you guys.
I know.
You're gonna need to hang out with your family more.
I know, you've come all the way out.
Oh my god.
I feel her body shaking.
Oh my god, I think I'm gonna cum.
I think I'm gonna cum.
Oh my god.
That feels so good.
I think it's your turn, bestie.
Is it?
How do you want to give me this cock?
I do, really.
Let's get these off.
Don't just stare at it, fuck it.
Oh my god.
You weren't lying.
I know. It feels so good.
I can't even think.
Oh, fuck.
It's so fucking tight.
Give me more.
Do you feel better now?
Yeah.
I know what else will make you feel better.
Just the one you talked about?
Yeah.
Oh my god, Bessie.
You're so good.
I can't think about his dick and pussy.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
I'm not done with you yet.
Oh
I think I'm going to cum, I think I'm going to cum.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
slide in. But it looks so hot from over there.
I can't wait to see it bumping into you soon.
I know. I can't wait.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
Fuck, yes.
Fuck, it feels so fucking good.
It's your turn again.
I need to recover after this.
I love watching it slide in my eyes.
Oh, it's so big step.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
I love it when you're on my clinic.
I think I want some attention, too.
Oh, yeah.
It feels so good.
Oh, fuck.
I love watching you guys fucking touch yourselves and hug each other.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
I'm getting close.
Oh, yes.
Mmm.
I feel so good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I think I want one last time.
Yeah.
That's not too selfish.
Mm-hmm.
Oh
I want to do this all the time with you.
I know, me too.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Are you seeing this?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
No.
Don't you dare stop. Don't you dare stop, please.
Can I just sleep over tonight?
Don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
I can see your cut in my stomach
Holy shit
I want you to feel good too
Yeah, you're making us calm all day.
Oh my god, no you don't.
I think I feel something building up.
Oh no.
Yeah, you'll put all out.
Oh, f***ing hell.
What are you doing to us?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
It's so hot.
Oh, fuck.
Wow.
So much cum.
Oh, my God.
You really did empty him.
I know.
so i guess that was better than just snuggling and watching movies huh you're so right
so about that sleepover