so good so bad dancing like it's 10 degrees don't look don't touch anybody about me
my lips your kiss got me feeling jealousy make your mind your mind to stay up with you
put me first like every day all i ever wanna hear you say
It's me, I'm the one who takes it higher
Like your tongue is on fire
This ain't a game that I've already won
I'm not
Hey, whoa.
That'll be $42.50.
Yeah, I left my wallet downstairs.
Do you mind bringing that pizza in?
Okay, sure.
You're just a fireplace, though, bro.
Nah, I'm not sure.
A little rent-y for the weekend.
You can use your table.
Where are we going?
I'm sorry, bro.
Oh, you're coming with me?
Come on.
Come on, bro.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Who was that?
Who was that, bro?
What?
Come on over.
Potatoes.
Potatoes?
Enjoy, boys.
How do you feel?
Yeah.
From Ashley and Tony's wedding.
Oh, my God.
What's up, man?
Good to see you.
I know.
Oh, my God.
That was a fun night.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, bro.
Come on, man.
You're kind of blocking the thing.
Hey, come on.
Blocking the pizza.
Come on.
But, ah, man.
Don't ask me what it is.
I'll tell you what it is.
There you go.
What's up?
Jesus.
God, it's so nice to see you.
Good to see you, too.
You know, I was gonna call you, I swear.
Mm-hmm.
It's okay.
It was like a one-time thing.
It doesn't have to be.
Oh, doesn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Really?
What about your friends?
Um, I mean, they're busy right now.
Maybe I'll run a second.
Okay.
Oh my gosh, I missed you.
I missed you as well.
Yes, I love that you miss me too.
God, baby.
Yeah.
You know what I never stop thinking about?
What?
This fucking mouth, baby.
Fuck.
Let it go.
Fuck, yeah, let me see that big cup.
Fuck, I missed this.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, yeah.
Fuck.
Damn.
I fucking love sucking.
I just did it.
Oh.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Don't, don't, don't.
Oh my god.
Oh my god
Fuck
Oh my god, I miss these big balls too
Those fucking balls, baby
God damn, baby
Oh my god
Yeah, shit, yeah
Yeah
Fuck
Open up wide, baby
Open up, open up, open up, open up, open up, open up, open up, open up, open up, oh my God, yes, baby, oh, fuck, fuck, baby, fuck, baby, oh, God, fuck, yes, baby, lick those balls, fuck, good girl, baby, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl, good girl
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
There's no sleeping in the wet.
Yeah, I don't know how to fucking do it.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Fuck.
God, baby.
Oh, my God.
Give me a second.
Yes, baby.
Fuck.
You're so fucking hard for me.
Fuck you all those fucking chicks, baby.
Fuck.
Yeah, I fucking do.
Yeah.
That's what I fucking do.
Yes, baby.
Oh, shit.
Hey, I found my wallet.
Oh, awesome.
Yeah, it was just, um, $42.50.
Okay, um, the tip, too, includes it?
Yeah.
No.
No?
That's it?
No, no.
It's fine.
Okay.
Um, you know what?
Don't worry about the tip.
I just, no, I would just love to have some of your dick.
Some dick?
Yeah.
Oh, I would be big.
Oh, I had to go a few months ago, brother.
Oh, she looks fine.
Fuck.
Fuck
Yes, yes, back and forth, back and forth, back and forth baby, yes, oh, oh, back on
it now, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, yes.
Oh.
No.
Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yes, baby, yes, yes, baby, fuck, yes, that was fucking good, fuck, oh, fuck, yes, oh, my God, fuck, yes, baby, fuck, yes, yes, baby, yes, baby, yes, yes, baby, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Yeah, just like that, just like that, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, come on, come on, come
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, fuck, oh my god, yeah, stick that tongue out, stick that fucking tongue out, baby, yeah, oh, yeah, good, fucking face, bro, yeah, yeah, bro, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Yes!
Oh my god, yes!
He's fucking taking all that fucking dick.
Yes, baby.
Yes.
Fuck, yes.
Smack her fucking face, bro. Smack her.
Yes, yes. Smack that fucking face, baby.
Yes, baby.
Oh my god, yes.
Yes.
Fuck, use your fucking face.
Just like that, baby.
Just like that.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Yes, come on, one more time, one more time, one more time, oh, fuck, yes, fuck, oh my god, yes, baby, fuck, yes, oh my god, those fucking tits, man, those fucking tits, man, yes, baby, you fucking slapped those fucking tits in my dick, baby, slapping those fucking tits, yes, oh, yes, oh my god, yes,
Use that fucking mouth.
Yeah, baby. Fuck.
Stick that fucking tongue out, bitch.
Yes, baby.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, my fucking God.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Yes, baby. Yes.
Yes, fuck.
My pussy's so wet. My pussy gets so wet sucking these fucking nuts, baby.
Look what you fucking did to me.
Yes, my pussy's wet as fuck.
Yes, baby, fuck.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, yes.
Yes, baby.
Yeah, buddy, fuck my pussy.
Yeah.
Oh, my fucking God. Yes, baby.
Yes.
Oh, my fucking God, baby.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh fuck yes baby yes, yes baby yes, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh
Get down, man. Get down.
Yeah, bring me back down. Bring me back down, baby.
Mm, fuck. I want to taste your fucking cum.
Yeah, I want to fucking taste it.
Mm.
I love watching you fucking jerk off, I wanted to jerk that fucking cock right into my fucking
mouth, I want to fucking taste it, I miss the way you fucking taste.
Vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok, vok.
I want to fucking taste it.
Come on into that fucking cup.
Yeah, I want to fucking taste it.
Yes.
Give me that fucking cup.
I want it.
I want to fucking taste it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Give me that fucking cup, please.
Please.
I fucking need it.
I need to fucking taste that cup.
I need to taste that load.
Yeah, I need it, baby.
I need it.
Yes.
Give it to me.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Don't just let that go, don't get that destroyed.
Oh my god.
Yes, baby.
Yes, oh my god, I can see how fucking close you are.
That dick is fucking throbbing for me.
Yes, oh my god, baby.
Yes, I need that fucking nut.
Yeah, I need that fucking cum.
Give it to me, baby.
Oh, my dick is fucking throbbing.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
You're going to give me that fucking load?
Give me what I fucking deserve.
I earned that fucking cum, and I want every last fucking drop of it.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, give it to me.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, give it all to me.
Fuck.
Oh my god, there's more in there, I'm gonna get it.
Oh my god, fuck.
Pittle that fucking cum.
Oh my god.
Swallow it all up.
You got some right here, baby.
Do I?
Oh god. You know I don't waste a drop, you remember.
Well baby, it's only fair. I mean, I got all my homies out there on the couch.
Do you think they'd be down?
Oh, for sure.
I would love some of those. Let's go.
Hey, listen.
Don't say I never did nothing for y'all.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Hey, what's that?
Oh, my God.
Wow.
It's better than pizza.
Pizza.
Oh, God.
Yes, baby.
I want more than a tip though, I want all those fucking dicks, oh my god, you hurt me,
Oh, shit.
Yeah, damn.
Yeah.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Right there.
Oh, right there, baby.
Yeah, damn.
Oh.
She is going off with it, though.
Yes, yes.
Give her a good ticket.
Hey.
Oh, shit.
Let's see what we got over here.
We're going to go down the line.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, sit there and let her crawl over here.
She's going to crawl around so you can see.
Oh, yeah.
She's going to crawl.
Oh my god, that shit right there, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
I can't believe he's going to hide her.
Fuck, I'm going to try every one of them.
Come on.
Hold it.
We give her a good tip.
It's going down.
I've been thick and thick.
That's what I'm talking about.
Fuck it.
Oh, man.
Keep crawling.
Everybody gets each other.
Yeah.
Oh.
Mm.
Yes.
This is the best pizza delivery I've ever had.
Oh, yeah, keep figuring that little fucking pussy.
Fuck!
Here you go.
Let me bring it over to my friends.
Come on.
Yeah, you guys want some?
Put it down on the floor.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Oh, fuck.
That's so fucking good.
Over to that right there.
Over to that right there, y'all.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look
Come in here.
Oh, right there.
I want your fucking book.
Oh.
Yeah.
Get up in there, Eddie.
Oh, yeah.
Right there.
Grab that there.
Grab it.
Yay.
Oh.
Yeah.
Give me them titties.
Oh.
Come on.
Right there.
There you go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
That shit right there. That shit.
Oh, there you go.
Oh, fuck this.
There we go.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Put them both in there.
Oh, yeah.
I know.
I got you.
Yeah, Robin will live in my fucking face.
Give me one of them hands.
I got this.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes.
Fuck.
Mm-hmm, yes.
Mm, yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes, there you go.
There you go.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, that's awesome.
Yes!
Damn, these are just so fucking nice.
Oh, yes, let me do this in that bow.
Yeah!
Oh, here you go.
Yes, yes.
Mm-hmm.
That's perfect.
Yes, right there.
Yeah!
Oh
Oh, yes.
Give me some of that.
There you go.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Good girl.
Oh, shit.
Hold that mouth open.
Say, ah.
Ah.
Uh-huh.
Keep checking.
Ah.
Yes.
There you go.
Ah.
Yes.
There you go.
Oh, shit.
Give it to her.
Yes.
That mouth.
There we go.
Oh, yes.
God damn.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
Get her.
Make them dicks disappear.
Make them dicks abracadabra.
Don't forget about those balls though.
There we go.
There we fucking go.
Oh just like that.
Look at you.
I like that.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
What am I doing?
Line up, line up.
Yeah, it's right there.
Look at the cheese.
There you go.
I got you.
Shit.
Yes.
Stay right there.
Don't move.
Take your time.
Serve it up.
There you go.
Womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, womp, wom
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm gonna push you all the way there, man.
Keep them dicks moving in rotation.
Yes, uh-huh, good girl.
Abracadabra.
Oh, there we go.
Make it disappear.
Good girl.
Make it disappear, yes.
Oh, there she goes.
Suck that shit.
Oh, there we go.
There you go, piece of shit.
There you go, bud.
There we go, look at that.
Oh, yeah.
Give me more, give me more, give me more.
Get back there.
Come here.
Don't rub him.
There you go.
Oh, shit.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God, yeah.
Uh-huh, yes.
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, use that hand to stroke that other dick over there.
Yeah.
Uh-huh, yes.
Ah, yes.
Mm-hmm, yes.
Mm-hmm, yes, get it.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
The mouth table.
Oh.
Yeah.
Ah, yes.
You ready to fly?
Yes, I'm fucking ready.
Yes!
Right in there, right in there.
Right in there, that's perfect.
Open up, open up.
Yeah, right there, right there.
Right there, let's go in a circle.
Right there, right there.
Yeah, I need more fucking cock, I need more fucking cock.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh shit, shit, shit.
Hey, this is mine.
Hey, hey, hey, that's my ex, that's my ex.
Oh, shit.
Oh, what are you doing here?
Oh, bro.
One more time, I'm gonna help.
Come on, dude, be good.
Come on, dude, who wants it?
Who wants it?
I want it, god damn it.
Go, go, go.
Come here, come here, come here.
Put it around, toss it around.
Oh, there we go.
Yes, yes.
Oh, just like that.
Holy shit.
That's the pieces on us.
Bro.
Work them dicks.
Get it.
Oh shit, yes.
Yeah, there she goes.
There she goes.
You got it?
Ah, yes.
I want to get you upside down.
Uh-huh.
Come on.
Uh-huh, yes.
Mm-hmm, yes.
Give it to her.
Keep stroking.
Keep stroking, yes.
Wow.
White House today, baby.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Keep it going, yes.
Pieces on us.
Work them dicks.
Mm-hmm, yes.
That's fucking good.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Got that extra sausage for them pieces.
Yes!
Don't suck on that dick, don't suck on that dick.
Let's get it down a little.
Come back, let's get it down, let's get it down.
Yeah, right there.
Woo!
Get on your knees, get on your knees, yes.
There you go, dicks around the face.
Come on, y'all, dicks around the face.
Dicks around the face, yes.
That's a good little slide, yeah.
Yeah.
Goddamn.
Look at them tears of joy.
Tears of joy coming out of my eyes.
Oh, they not just happen when we catch it?
Yes, come on now, man, come on, please.
That shit's that good, right?
That shit's that good, man.
That shit's that good, hey.
That shit's that good, I said that shit, damn.
You say shit, we're getting tainted.
Karen, Karen is Karen.
I don't see you.
You got more than I imagine, she got it, she got it, mm-hmm.
Yes, fuck.
Look at that shit.
Oh, yeah, mm-hmm.
Here you go, put something back in your mouth.
Perfect, perfect, perfect, yes.
That's the flow.
Goddamn.
Toe slap. Toe slap.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Put them to his mouth. Put them to his mouth.
That's how you do that.
That's how you do that. That ain't no regular head right there.
That ain't no regular
head right there.
Yeah.
Let me take a look at my face.
Yes, baby.
Come over here.
Yeah.
Good girl, baby.
Keep it in rotation.
Yeah, right in rotation.
Wait a second.
Yeah.
That nose is on fucking stomachs right there.
That's good.
Get my balls.
Oh, shit, man.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
I always got a bitch in your hands.
Ah, yes, who wants their balls washed?
Uh-huh, yes.
I need my balls washed right here.
Right here.
Scooter out. Scooter out.
Scooter out.
Come here, baby.
Oh, it's pretty good.
Oh, baby.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Uh-huh, baby.
Yes.
Oh my god.
I want that two-and-a-half motherfuckers.
Man, you want the two-handed?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my fucking god.
Two-handed. Two-handed.
Two-handed bandit. Let's go.
Two-handed bandit. Oh, my
god. Let's go.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Wow.
Two hard workers.
Yes.
Yes, get them dicks.
Work them dicks, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, fuck!
I fucking love DJs.
Yeah.
I like that.
Yeah!
Uh-huh.
Ski skirt.
Get back down.
Get back on the floor.
That was crazy.
Yeah.
I saw you do that.
That's a good slide.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Goddamn.
Hey, you like getting covered in my fucking squirt?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's good.
Oh, that shit.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
That's a little bit, huh?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
There you go.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Goddamn.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62
Oh, fuck.
Alright, we're gonna switch you back in.
We're gonna switch you up.
Switch you up.
Right here.
Alright, now we swap it, we swap it.
Yeah, keep that busy, keep that mouth busy,
keep that mouth busy, keep that busy, keep that busy.
Yeah, line it up, line it up, line it up, line it up.
Yeah, sit down, don't lose that fuckin' mouth.
Don't lose that fuckin' mouth.
Go straight out, go straight out.
Yeah, you're up and moving, bro.
Yeah, other side, other side, other side.
Come on now.
Both sides, both sides.
Yeah.
Get him.
Fuck yeah.
That's a good fucking girl.
Get it.
Good girl.
There you go.
Turn that mouth to the right.
Right there.
Perfect.
There you go.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, use your fucking mouth.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
Open cities. Open cities.
Open cities.
She's such a good slut.
Put it down. Put it down.
Put it down.
Yeah, I want that fucking cum.
Take that face.
I want every last drop of that
fucking cum on my face.
Nah.
Yes.
Pay me with that fucking cunt.
Oh yeah.
Give me that fucking.
There we go.
Come on.
Suck that dick.
There you go.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Shit.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Fuck baby.
Oh, yes!
Oh, I never lost hope in that fucking cum.
You ready for all the homies? You ready for all the homies?
Yeah, I want it.
Thank you for sharing.
Yes, of course, baby.
I feel all those bullcats.
Get in closer.
Look at them dicks in her face.
Yeah, give me that fucking cum, I fucking earned it, I fucking need it, yeah, there you
go, keep on chugging, keep on chugging, how's your day, yeah, keep on chugging, don't worry,
You got plenty of coffee, baby.
Yeah, suck that dick, baby.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Are you going to give me a fucking second, Lord Jesus?
Yeah.
Oh, you know I am, baby.
I'm going to get those for you, baby.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I love seeing you fucking stroke those dicks for me.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Yes, baby.
Fuck.
There you go, baby.
Yeah.
Just some more coffee.
Submerge yourself, fucking submerge yourself.
Just fucking submerge yourself in the water.
Like these big fucking tits.
Give me some fucking comfort in these fucking tits too.
Oh my God.
Mom.
Oh yeah, suck that dick.
Oh fuck.
Suck that dick.
Yeah, see this fucking dick.
Such a little fucking slut.
Oh yeah.
Hey guys, let her know. Talk to her guys.
Guys, talk to me.
Come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, give it to me.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Yes, put it all over me.
Yes, baby.
Fuck.
I want that fucking cum, give it to me I want to cum on your face, I want to cum
on your face, I want to cum on your face, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Mm-hmm. Oh, that's good. That's good.
Oh, look at my pretty little fucking face getting covered in cum.
You're so fucking sexy, baby.
Oh, I'm ready for my entire face to be covered.
Yeah, what about this side? It needs some cum.
Oh, fuck, here we go.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, it's everywhere.
Oh, shit.
It's completely fucking covered.
Rain that cum down on me.
oh yeah get out of that side oh yes oh yeah oh my god that cum tastes so good let me get
it all out every last drop that's a healthy cum baby eat that cum oh yes
damn look at that dick oh i can tell you're close yeah those balls are
They're all fucking filled with cum and I want them fucking drained.
Yes, I want every last drop of that cum, baby.
I deserve it.
Please.
I'm such a good little slut for you.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, you like the way I fucking grub those balls.
One second.
Oh, here it comes.
Yes.
Oh, you got two.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Double shot.
Oh, gosh.
Come on.
Oh my god, all I can see is cum, fuck yes, mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Oh my god, Tati is so much bigger than a fucking slug, oh my god, fuck, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, baby, yeah, let's cover me in that fucking cloth, yeah, I want fucking more, yeah, I want fucking more, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Yeah, I deserve it, I fucking deserve it, all those fucking words, calling me like this
any fucking horror that I am, oh my god it tastes so good too, oh fuck, look at it all
all over my face and my mouth.
Smear it all over my face.
Fuck.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, I can tell you're close.
Oh, fuck.
Give it to me.
Yes, another load.
God damn, number two for you, baby.
God damn.
You did miss me, huh?
I sure fucking did.
Yes, baby, give it to me.
Oh, fuck.
We might be glued.
Fuck, baby.
Squeeze those last couple
drops out of me, baby.
Get distracted.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, you're sensitive now.
Oh, my fucking god.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
You're pretty covered in cash.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa.
You like seeing me covered in your friend's cash?
I sure do.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Thanks, bitch.
Sure.
Of course, bro.
What do I look like, a gatekeeper?
Come on now.
Fuck.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
Let me come on, let me come on, let me come on.
Yeah, why the fuck do you want that fucking camera?
Take it, take it, take it.
Watch out, Eddie, he's right there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, give it to me, give it to me, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, right there.
Oh, fucking hell.
Shit all over me.
Shit all the fuck over me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh shit, right there.
Sit right there.
Roll him down.
Yes!
He's a fucking shooter.
Oh, fuck. Look at that.
Yeah, there you go.
Look at all that
fucking cum all over me.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I want to cum with this cum all over me.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, make yourself cum.
Make yourself calm, baby, make yourself calm, yeah, we know what to do, get this bitch up!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Oh, man.
Yeah.