All right, I'm just gonna check your heart.
Oh, you have a strong heartbeat.
I just need to get on this side.
Oh, oh, your heart is beating fast.
Hmm.
That's great.
So, Mr. Chocolate, what about any fever or chills?
I mean, I'm feeling a little tired,
but where's the real doctor at?
Well, I'm a real nurse,
but it's gonna be at least an hour.
An hour?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
He's really busy.
Damn, these pens are so slippery.
Sorry, you could make a donation while you wait.
A donation to what?
Well, this clinic doubles as a sperm bank.
Oh really?
Mm-hmm.
We pay a lot of money for healthy sperm
and I bet you have plenty of it, Mr. Chocolate.
Well, okay, let's do it.
Yes!
I make a little connection too.
That's the fun part of my job.
I'm married.
I'll bet.
But I have to get the sperm out of you some way
and I'm sure your wife will be very pleased
procedure absolutely okay excellent take a seat
technique which does provide pretty good results but I find with the
addition of a little... I've never extracted a donation from anything this
already quite full and it's very promising mmm but I'm gonna fill them up
further before I extract that sperm
oh yes with every stroke I can feel them getting bigger
Such healthy sperm.
Fuck.
that dick between these tits.
Mm-hmm.
Oh my goodness.
Mm.
Oh fuck.
Fuck, it feels like you haven't had a release for a while.
It's going to make your sperm even more pertinent.
Let's get you untrapped.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Mm, fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
I don't know why your heart feels between these two.
Mm.
I wouldn't mind following me over to the bed
and trying this method.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck!
Oh my god, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yeah.
It's fucking deep in me, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck, fuck, oh my god, yes.
You're gonna make me cum on that fucking coke.
Oh, that's so good.
It's jerking my dick inside the place.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, oh my god, that dick is fucking insane.
Yeah, oh my god, oh, you stretched that pussy out, yes.
Yes, oh fuck, yes, baby, oh yeah, take that pussy.
Fuck, you're so deep inside me, yes.
Yes, baby, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God, you're so good with that dick.
Fuck, yeah, oh my God, fuck, oh my God, oh my God, fuck.
Oh, you're so good with that dick.
Why don't you lay down here and let me ride you?
Yes.
Get comfortable.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, yes.
I can feel you're going to give up me such a good specimen.
Come on, let's edge this cock some more.
Mm, mm, fuck.
Oh my god, that dick is so hard, fuck.
Oh, fuck, oh my god, that dick is so fucking big, yeah.
Oh, god, yes, fuck.
Oh, yeah, I love the way it feels inside me.
Yeah, ooh, mm-hmm, oh, fuck, fuck, oh, yeah.
Tease it a little, oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, yes, fuck, oh, my God, fuck,
Fuck, that dick is so fucking big.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah.
Yes, keep giving it to me like that.
Oh my God, I love watching it.
Oh, not a second, fuck it.
Oh my gosh, you guys are going to make me fucking puke on.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my gosh.
Yes, stay right there.
Yeah, smack it on that pussy, smack it on it.
Yes.
Oh, just tease it there.
Oh, my God.
Let me check on those balls, oh yes, look how much bigger they are.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh wow, I can feel you getting closer and closer.
Yeah.
Just take some time to milk this dick.
Oh, fuck.
Fill up those bowls as much as we can.
Yeah.
This is my favorite part.
Just jerking a dick.
Feeling it getting closer in my hands.
Feeling your veins bulging under my fingertips.
Your cock throbbing.
that's what i love about my job
and just seeing how big these balls get look at that
Let's edge this dick a little more,
and then I'm going to take that specimen.
You want these big tits in your face as I ride you, huh?
Okay. Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, I bet those big tits bouncing gets you clicks, it doesn't it?
Yes.
Oh, I love feeling you get closer inside me.
Oh my, fuck.
Oh yeah, let me see.
Let me see it.
Yes.
Oh, it looks so good inside that pussy.
Oh my.
I'll use that pussy to jerk it.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Feels like I'm going to need that specimen cup soon.
Yeah, you're getting close and so sexy.
Yes.
Yes, uh-huh, oh, fuck, yes, yes, uh-huh, uh-huh, yes.
Badger, save me, yeah, get that load as big as you can.
Oh, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, fuck, uh-huh, uh-huh.
let me check up on those balls
oh fuck
hand me that cup
yes
Oh my god, that's it, baby.
Baby, I want that fucking specimen.
Oh my god, I can tell you're getting close.
When you're about to come, I want you to stand up, okay?
So I can get every drop.
Yes, baby, stand up for me, stand up, yes, yes, oh yes, give it to me.
Give me every last drop.
Yes.
Fuck.
that color, that texture.
Mm, I'm gonna dig it out of that eye.
Oh, that is perfect.
Mm, mm.
Thank you for your donation.
The doctor will see you now.
Mm, mm.
Some for me.
Mm.
Mm, mm.