picture if you will subtle invitations whispers only go so very far she was from a place
that i've only pictured in my dreams once or twice
most don't get the chance lovers don't collision
you say more with your hands
communicative it's the little things that hold us
oh my god
oh you're so wet
pussy wants you to touch her
I'm so fucking pretty, look at that, please give me that tongue, just that nose, smelly,
Fuck, you smell so good.
I don't want that tongue to eat.
Not yet.
Oh my god.
Such a tease.
Where's my phone?
Oh, please.
Oh my god, please give it to me, oh my god, please give it to me, oh yes, oh yes, oh my
Oh my god.
It's so pretty.
She's getting so wet looking at you.
Just like that, Claire.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh my god.
Can I come on your tongue?
You want to taste that cup?
Oh!
Oh my god.
It's like somebody else wants to have the bum.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
I feel so good.
Wow.
Yeah.
Mmm.
That's so good.
That fish was
She's just buried in there.
Fuck yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
I'm jealous. I want to taste.
I want to taste this.
Stroke it into her mouth.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's so fucking hot.
You can taste this.
Get it nice and covered in spit.
There you go.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Shhh.
Yes.
Mmm.
Those soft lips feel good wrapped around your cock.
Yeah.
Yes, fuck, you like those big matcha tits wrapped around that cock.
Fuck.
Yes.
Yeah, go on, suck.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Fucking tits.
That's what you're gonna fucking use.
Mm, man.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Look at her, look at her, look at her, look at her, look at her, look at her, look at
Yeah.
Fuck.
Come here.
That's it there.
That's it.
Oh my god.
Fuck yes.
Oh my god. Just like that.
Oh my god.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Fuck me.
Come here, sit here, sit here.
Oh my God, it's horrible.
You deserve to be worshipped.
Yeah.
Should we Eiffel Tower him?
Put that head back down.
Oh my God, I'm going to puke.
Sit on my face. Face me. Face me. Take me away.
Sit on my face. Sit on me. Sit on me.
I'm just going to puke.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, take that fucking hug.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god, it feels so good.
Oh my god, fuck.
It's so good.
Look at that.
Juice right there.
Yeah, take all that.
Oh fuck yeah.
You're taking it so fucking good.
Oh my god, she's so good at that, she's so good, you need to ride with her.
Stay up there.
Please stay up there.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Please give me that back.
Give me that back.
It's so hard.
Look at that.
Just like that.
Oh my God.
That.
It becomes this incredible...
Oh
Move back here so you can eat some pussy
Yes, your tongue deep in there.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah, give us a hand.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, that's right in the middle.
You're getting nice and deep.
Oh my god.
Yeah, we teased it.
Fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That hurts.
It's so hot.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck.
It's fucking good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Just a little cheese.
Tastes so good.
Want about a little bit more?
Yes? Just a little bit.
Can you say yes?
Yeah, there you go.
There you go.
Such a good boy
Yeah, that's the only problem.
Because it's still happening next to me all the time.
It's still happening.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. So bad.
Oh.
Oh, you f**k are so weak.
Holy s**t.
Oh my god.
Oh s**t.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Look how present they are.
God, it's so fucking pretty.
Oh yes, that's your mother.
Yes, oh yes, oh please put it back beside me, yes, yes, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
Yeah.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run
Oh my god, yes, fuck, she's so good at that, fuck, she's so good at that, yes, yes, oh my
gosh, yes, yes, oh yeah, use me, use me, yeah, yeah, put your body, yeah, yeah, use me as
She's a 16.
Yes!
Oh my god.
Fuck yes!
Yes!
Oh my god.
Please make that pussy come.
just like that
oh
yeah there you go
oh take all that fucking time
oh my goodness
yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes
fuck that pussy
oh
fuck
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Good, like that, yes, yes, yes, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, yes, yes, oh my god, yes, fuck, fuck, that's good, oh my god, so deep like that, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god
Yeah, rub my little clit, baby, I'm so close.
Yeah, yeah, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Oh, I want to taste that.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Yes, please, yes, please, yes, please, yes, please, yes, please.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yes!
Yeah, put it back in.
Oh my!
Yeah, put it back inside.
So beautiful.
Hold her.
Take it all in.
Spread.
Down.
Hold her like that.
Sit up. Hold her like that.
Hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold
Fuck!
Yes!
Oh, you fuck!
Paisley!
Holy fuck!
Out of here.
God, I love hearing you guys on that fucking couch.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck it up, you're going to have a dick burn soon.
Both, both, both.
Stay there, stay just like that.
Come here, you know what I want to see?
Stay there, just go, stay just there.
Come here, come here, come here, come here.
Come here, stay there, come here.
Now look, now look.
Sit back there, both of you.
Oh, fuck you.
I got you.
Just like that, there, there, there, there.
Oh, if I can eat that.
Hold it. Hold your hand.
Give me your hand.
Let me taste it.
Yeah, that's all I'm sure of.
Oh, yeah.
He's like nice and slobbery with him.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Shh.
Fuck, dog.
Shut up.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Shh.
Oh, man.
Let's wash it this way.
Feels so good.
Put it over your face, I want to see it, put it over your face, I want to see it, I want
to see it.
I put it over this fucking face, I want to make a mess of me.
Yeah. Yeah. Fuck. Shit.
Look at that dick on the top left. Look at that dick on the left.
Here we are.
Fuck.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Shit.
Yeah, stroke that cock.
Stroke that cock.
Nice and messy.
Here, here.
You can talk so good.
I'm fine.
What?
What? Huh? What?
Quiet, quiet, you're getting fucking close.
No, I know I'm not, I'm joking.
I'm struggling not to fucking cum.
Oh, I get you now.
It's bossy, it's bossy.
Yes.
So, so, give it a jerk off in this routine like that.
Come on.
Oh, nice and slow.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, make love to that cum.
What about switch the fist upside down?
Yeah.
Jerk it like that.
Just get it nice and hard.
What about all four hands?
Intertwine your fingers.
Rub it on your palm.
We'll slow it down.
I love my macronutrients.
Looks like the tip of his head is sensitive.
You're too fucking hot for that.
You know what, let's cuddle.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, there you go.
Oh
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
That's incredible, that's incredible.
Oh my God, it's so good.
Oh my gosh, she's so fucking pretty.
She's so fucking beautiful, look at her.
Look how pretty she is, you're so fucking pretty.
You're so pretty, you're so fucking pretty.
Fuck, oh my God, good girl.
Yeah, good girl, good girl, yeah, good girl.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, oh my god, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that
There you go.
Stay there.
Come here.
There you go.
Come.
Right here.
Come right here.
There you go.
Oh, I love watching his balls bounce.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, there you go, there you go, oh fuck yeah, oh my god, yeah, oh my god, fuck, that's
That's crazy, that's crazy, yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, come here, say it, on your back, on your back,
on your back, come here, come here, come here.
It's okay.
Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.