Perfect.
Hey, Maudie.
Hmm?
Get those tools, we can hang that back.
One second.
We already did it.
Yeah, it was super easy. Do you need your tool back?
Um, yeah.
Great, thanks.
Thank you.
Hey, I was going to get to that leak today. I was going to fix that later on this afternoon.
It's okay, you're always so busy. I thought I could do it.
Daddy, actually, can you hand me that wrench?
Um, sure thing, here you go.
Not that one. You know which one I'm talking about. You tell me how to do this.
I'm sorry, I got it for you.
Thanks, that's the one.
Get this tightened.
You sure I, uh, I can't help?
Oh, no. It's okay. You taught me how to do this, so. I think I got it, but it's so hot down there.
Geez. Can you hand me that towel?
Thank you. My God, I'm so hot.
I meant to get to that this afternoon, like I said, but you already did, so.
Well, if you want to help, you can clean up. I have some other things I need to get finished, so.
Um, yeah, yeah, sure, sure. I'll clean up to you. Thank you, sweetie.
Thanks, Daddy.
How's it coming?
It's all right. Look at that. It's looking great.
Got it right down to the bare wood, huh?
I'm going to paint it pink.
Pink, really?
I was going to say, you're kissing golden hands.
These hands can do a lot more.
Yeah, I suppose they can.
What's wrong?
I don't know. I feel like I taught you everything I know, and now you don't need me anymore.
It's like I kind of feel useless is all.
No, you taught me to be strong and independent.
Look, you've taught me so much. Maybe you deserve something in return.
I appreciate that, sweetie.
No, I'm serious.
Yeah?
Yeah. Come on.
I just want to let you know that you've been the best stepdad ever, and you've done so much for me.
And I think it's high time that you see what else these magic hands can do.
Okay, um, I'm a little confused.
Don't act stupid, Daddy.
Oh, honey, honey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Listen, I see where this is going. I don't think this is a good idea.
I know you can, because your cocks already rock hard.
Oh, honey.
If we get caught, though, I mean...
Who cares?
Hmm?
Let me take these off.
Another thing my magic hands can do
is remove those.
If your mother ever finds out.
Like I said,
in fact, I think you're focusing too much on me
and not my hands.
Good focus.
How do you feel?
Oh my god.
Am I doing a good job?
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Told you my magic hands could do so much more.
Oh yeah, they sure can.
Oh my god, it feels so good on my cock.
My cock's looking for my hand when it goes away.
It's so hot.
Oh my God.
You think you can teach me a few other things?
Like how to make your cock feel good.
Oh my God, sweetheart, I think you got that one covered.
My fucking hands feel amazing.
Oh my God.
It was Aria and then Daria
Oh my god
Oh
No peeking
Maybe.
Let your imagination run wild.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh yeah, fuck.
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
I want to hear you stroke it for me, I want to watch you stroke it, yeah, yeah, just like
that daddy, show me what I want to see, and I'll let you feel what you want to feel,
Oh, fuck you.
You've behaved so well.
I can't take this anymore.
I don't want to taste you anymore.
Oh my god.
Yes, please.
Oh god, that makes me so horny.
You just want everything off, don't you?
Don't stop.
Oh, yes. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Tell me what you want.
I just worked so hard today.
I just want to be rewarded with your big fat cock right now, please.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
Once we do this, we can't go back.
Stick it in me already.
I feel so good, oh my God, please, please, oh, don't go faster, please, faster, faster,
oh, oh my, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yeah, just make your cock feel good.
I feel so good with you, darling.
I feel so good.
You're making my pussy so happy.
Yes, yes.
I can barely stay still.
It's so good.
Oh, my God.
Oh
Yeah, I'm getting nice and teet-teet.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Right there.
It's fine.
You're a little pussy, honey.
Yeah.
I remember my coat when you pounded me.
You were a little pussy for daddy.
You feel it? You feel it?
Come on, baby. I feel your little pussy getting tight for daddy.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Come here. I want to taste it.
Tasty pussy of daddy's cock.
Oh, fuck yes.
Fuck daddy's cock.
Just like that, honey.
Oh my god, yes.
My pussy tastes good.
Your pussy tastes good, doesn't it?
My fuck tastes good.
Oh, my God, out of here, I just like to, fuck, shit, fuck, yeah, oh, God, yes, please, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, yes, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God,
It feels so tight.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes
Oh
Oh, fuck, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, oh, yeah, fuck, yes, yes, yes, oh, I guess we're both
doing heavy labor today, let me give your cock a workout, yeah, oh, fuck, yeah, oh,
Oh, my God, it's so tight.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Nice and deep.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
I want to feel your back
and deeper
oh my god
oh god
oh fuck
let me get back up here
Yeah, fuck me good, Dodie.
Yeah, fuck me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, throw me up in Tonya Cork like that.
Fuck.
That's so good.
I love it.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
What else do you want to do to me, Johnny?
Very innovative.
You're going to teach me something?
Oh, God.
Oh daddy, oh daddy, oh my god, I love you so much, oh my god, I feel like I'm in a dream now, oh my god, and there's no way for me to run too, you just want me to run, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Do you want some?
Yeah.
Yes.
I promise.
I'm so worried.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, I'm getting even hotter than when I was working under the sink.
Oh my god, you're making my body heat up so fast.
My pussy loves you.
I love you, daddy.
Oh my god, fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, fuck, oh my god, oh
my god, fuck, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
Yeah, yeah, it's like a gift from you and me.
Come here, Daddy, honey.
Yeah, you feel it, you feel it.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Can you struggle while it's inside me?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
You know, you can take it wherever you want.
It's so hot matching it.
You're so dirty, Tony.
Are you okay, Cody?
Yeah.
Fuck.
Finally, I made these titties shake.
So deep.
Daddy, please, please, use me.
Fuck, yes.
Yeah, just use me.
Use me.
Please.
Daddy.
Show me how much you love me, Daddy.
Show me.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fucking hell.
I can help you take care of all the house things and your cocks' needs.
Oh, my God, baby.
Just put it on the to-do list.
Oh, yeah.
Let me fix your horniness.
Yeah, you want to give it to me, don't you?
I'm going to put it right here.
Don't you want to make me messy?
Take it, take it, take it, take it.
Oh, thank you, Daddy.
Oh, my God.
Don't stop.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
please daddy please come here come yeah feed it to me
make a mess out of all my makeup you and my pretty face yeah yeah yes please please please
i can hear your cock wants it so bad
Don't you want to connect to me?
Please, daddy, please, please.
Fuck.
Fuck. Oh my-
Be nice and deep.
So I can milk out every last drop of cum for your cup.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me,
give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me, give it to me,
Look, look, look, look, crazy, oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Mwah!