He ate both of our asses, so he had his tongue in there.
Oh my god, this is so hard.
Oh my god.
Oh, my God.
I don't think she made it.
Sit on my face right now.
Oh, yeah.
What?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
Oh, God.
You want to taste it then, Jenny?
Yes.
You want to lift the shoes?
Yeah.
Such a pretty girl, right?
Such a pretty girl.
Don't stop.
Oh God, she's so good with her mouth.
Don't fucking make her cut me in, motherfucker.
Take those shoes off.
Oh, fuck, where's my moustache?
Where's my moustache?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes, you can.
Oh.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
I love you.
I don't want it.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes. Take your fucking tongue out, yes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just love this so much.
Oh, God. Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god, it's a big fucking owl.
Tell him you're a whore
You're a whore
I don't know, do you want to look at him?
Yeah, push it, push it, push it hard on him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Give him fucking time in there, yes!
I love that.
Oh, fuck yeah!
Yes!
Like that, harder, harder, harder.
Oh my god, yes!
Not deep enough.
I know, I know, I know.
Give him fucking time in there, do you?
Give him fucking time in there.
See that? Oh, my God.
Look, I'm sweet. I want it, too.
I want it, too. I want it, too.
I want it, too.
Oh, Jesus fucking God.
Oh, Jesus.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
With my phone.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Come here, come here, sit down
Sit down for a second
On the ass
On the ass, on the other side, give me your ass
Show me your ass
Show me how you sit on the ass
On the other side
Give me, tell me how you want to do it
Tell me how you want to do it
On your little ass
Go on, jump, give me, give me
Come here
Oh, fuck you. Yeah, what's the matter?
What's the matter?
Oh my god, I'm so tired.
Fuck.
Get your ass in there.
You get so fucked, you fucker.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You fucking ass.
You fucking ran around.
You give a girl a fucking dick.
You give a girl a dick.
Yeah.
You wanna fight that little asshole?
Yeah, bring it to me.
Bring it to me.
Let's do it like that.
Look at her.
I'll cut you.
Fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, I've got this. Do you think it's that bad?
Can I taste it?
You can taste it. Suck on my ass, you son of a bitch.
Oh my god, I've got this. Do you think it's that bad?
Can I taste it?
You can taste it. Suck on my ass, you son of a bitch.
No, don't fucking take all the crump.
You better fucking shut up and wake up.
Let's wake up.
Bring it back to her.
Get back right there.
Fuck.
Yeah.
I want to see, I want to see your face.
Deeper, deeper, deeper.
Okay.
Let me fucking strip my dick in your mouth.
Deeper, deeper, deeper.
Yeah, that's, that's right there.
Oh my god, her tongue feels so good.
It's so fucking good how she is, huh?
Yeah, push it back, push it back.
Right there, right there, right there, right there.
Right, oh god.
Yeah, there you go, there you go, there you go.
You want to play when you do this
You see how much I want to play when you do this
You're going to fill my mouth with your pee
Die, die, die, die, die
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it
That's it my love, that's it my love
Right there. Right there. Look at that eye. Look at that eye.
Just there. Just above his ass. Like that.
Look at his ass. Look at his ass.
Look at his ass. Look at his ass. Look at his ass.
Again, again, do it again, do it again
Clean it well, clean it well, I want to see it well
Yes, this big ass, yes
You're fucking good man, you're fucking good
Oh, my God!
Yes! Yes!
Right there.
Right there. Come down, baby.
Come down, baby. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Come down.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
All right, you all right?
Tell her, dude, tell her. Tell her what I'm telling you.
Tell her what I'm saying. Tell her what I'm saying.
At least it's gonna fuck my pussy after putting it in your ass.
See that?
After putting your ass in my pussy, yeah?
Yeah.
Fuck your fucking ass.
You like it?
It feels good?
I'm gonna put your ass in my pussy right now.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom right now.
I'm gonna do a little fucking hard work.
Get down, get down, get down.
Angie, stand up. Get up.
Show me your ass. Show me your ass again.
Right there. Mm-hmm.
I can't fucking stop right there. Fucking head, right? Right?
Right there, baby. That was so nice. So nice. So nice.
I know, baby. I know, baby. Look. Look, look, look, look.
Oh god, yeah, get back down, get back down, get back down this time
Now this time, this time right, this time right
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, oh God, God, come, come, oh God, oh God.
Oh my god, I told you he was going to be good.
Mmm.