made you a little slave ass pig
you little fucking
slut
you thought you were going to have your way
with me
and now I'm having my fucking way
with your little tight ass
oh
slide it back
oh yeah
oh
Oh, I want you to fucking come for me.
I'm going to burn this asshole.
Oh, I'm so fucking deep.
My fucking asshole.
Oh, yeah.
Fucking take that fat cock
your little tight asshole. I'm going to stretch your asshole out today.
I'll teach you how a real man fucks.
Take that big cock of mine.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you like that?
I fucking take a manza.
Let me get it back in my tight asshole.
I guess I'll untie you for this.
It takes a lot to get the mistress on her knees
But I know I'm going to destroy that asshole afterwards
So I guess I'll let it slide
Now bend over
You little fucking slut
What a good little boy
I'm gonna fucking pathetic little man.
Take a little bitch
I can take every fucking inch of my big fat cock.
Let's get that back in there.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yes, you took that fucking cock
all the way deep in your little asshole.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to ride your ass like a fucking pony.
Oh, kitty, up.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Take that.
I'm a fucking cop just stretching in a fucking tight asshole.
Oh, fuck.
I'm a fucking bitch.
I love tucking your tight ass.
Oh
I love fucking taking men's ass and making them my little anal slaves.
He's so, so fast.
When you're mad, to suck other things, it's like a good little slave.
I bet that ass tastes really nice
After I fucked it real
Real hard
Oh
Let's just come
I think I'm gonna keep you around for a little while
You got cock on your face, you little fucking whore.
Put it back in your mouth.
Kiss my ass.
and that's time to put you back in my trunk
come on