Welcome to S.W.I.T.E.
Your mission, if you choose to accept, is to do the next tip-on.
Agents Maxwell and Johnson
will be assisting you on your first assignment.
Your first assignment starts
now. This recording will self-destruct
in five seconds.
Oh
worship his big fucking dick
I fucking love it!
Oh my god!
So fucking delicious!
Yes!
Oh yeah!
Big fucking tits!
Yes!
Oh, my God, yes.
I'm fucking going to rub it all over my fucking face.
Yes, I'm going to slide it between these fucking tits of yours.
Yeah, I'm going to make fucking tits around it.
Yes, yes.
And then there's a fucking what in there?
And those big fucking tits wrapped around that cock.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It looks so fucking good.
It feels so fucking good.
Yes.
Please bring your fucking cucks back.
Fuck yes.
Make them fucking dance.
They look so fucking good.
Yes.
You know what I mean, those fucking balls.
There's a fucking bolt.
Yes!
Oh my god!
Oh fuck!
Yeah!
Oh shit.
Oh, fuck you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh yeah, give me both of those fucking balls.
Are they cold enough?
Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck.
for me and my fucking sloppy wet mouth.
So f***ing perfect, yes, yes, yes, f***ing perfect.
I love this show.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Fucking milk those fucking balls.
Yeah, I'm gonna fucking drain you.
Fucking cum.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh my God.
How much did I fucking cum all over my face?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, give me every last drop look at that fucking during those balls
Well, there's still more in there for me look
Fucking during those balls
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know what I'm talking about.