And look what we have here.
Big natural titties.
It's Australia's finest export.
Oh my, thank you.
Angela White.
They're germongous.
Boobs.
Do boobs just grow like this in Australia?
Or is this an oddity there too?
It does get you lots of attention, doesn't it?
They do.
They get me into trouble.
I figured you had the trouble too.
I'm definitely glad to have you in the USA here.
I am glad to be here.
I know I'm going to have lots of fun.
Absolutely.
You can watch those bounce all day.
Well you can if you like.
That's what we're doing today.
Not oil up these big natural titties.
Too easy with them.
Get that cock hard.
I see those pop out of the eyes.
Should we do it again just for fun? Yes.
yeah imagine them bouncing around your cock
I don't they're so big and squishy you can just dig your fingers into them
You catch yourself playing with them all the time.
Yeah, I do.
They're just so soft and malleable, I can't help it.
Yes, please.
Really take care of these babies.
Why, thank you.
Let me just see what's going on down there too.
Can't ignore the rest of the sexy body.
It really does hurt.
There's fat pussy lips.
I can suck on them too.
Little clit out.
Yeah, let's see that booty turn around.
Perfect little asshole, too.
Aw, thank you.
A cute little pink hole to get destroyed.
Let's see where our breast massage specialist is.
There he is.
Let's bring him on in.
He looks a little preoccupied over there.
I hope I get more than a breast massage.
What do you think he's jerking off thinking about over there?
Come on buddy, you're jerking off thinking about him.
Some serious contrast.
Gigantic.
We're going to shine those titties up today.
Yes, please.
I think he's enjoying the sights here.
Such a big monster dick.
Oh, my God.
That pre-cum drives me crazy.
You have him pre-cumming already?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Just splash all over my butt.
I see that.
He's opting for the booty shine first, huh?
Yeah.
Booty shine.
I like that he pays attention to everything.
Tenderizing that booty.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
I'm only a little bit nervous.
all those big balls rubbing up on me. I fucking love it.
Do you know how sexy that sounds with that accent?
Do you want me to blush?
Do you want those boobs?
Time to grease up those gigantic titties.
Yes please.
I think we need to oil up these big tits.
Oh yeah, look at it dripping down.
Oh yeah, I'll let you.
You should charge admission to this.
Oh, that sounds hot.
I just want to eat it.
Oh, I had some fun today.
We're all in store for some fun.
I think so.
How heavy are those legs?
Oh my god, they're so heavy.
So, so heavy.
I should have some for my face.
That's crazy.
This is fucking magnificent.
Oh shit.
It's so big.
Can I just tease it?
Oh my god.
oh shit oh my god oh my god your cock is fucking enormous
he just fucking shoved it in it didn't even go easy on me
oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah oh that's good
That fucking pussy gets stretched out. God damn it. Oh my god.
Oh, fuck. Oh, yeah.
cock. Mmm yes. Slap it on there. Mmm. So slippery. Yes.
Oh, God, no teasing no more.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Yeah, you should hurry, don't take me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, let me get on top of that dick.
Yes, mmm.
Oh my god, it's fucking huge.
Holy fuck, yes.
Oh my god.
That's huge, yes, oh fuck, give me that dick, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck it, Jacob.
Yes, it is.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fucking cocking up.
Oh, fuck, yes!
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah, Jacob.
Oh, God.
Yeah, yeah
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, fuck!
God damn it, it's so big!
Yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, yes!
I love that fucking...
Oh!
oh my god look at all that fucking cum all over your dick
suck it
oh my god
God damn it!
Oh shit!
Oh fuck yeah
Oh my
God
Fuck
Oh shit
Oh yeah
Oh
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, that cock is so fucking big.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yeah.
She's a little fucking ass. Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Mmm.
Tease you with these big titties.
Oh, fuck.
Mmm.
Oh.
Stretching out that ass.
Mmm.
Oh, yeah, let me spread those cheeks. Look at that
Oh, yeah, grabbing his fucking tit
Oh, fuck. Yes. Yes. Yeah
Oh
Fuck
Oh, you drive me fucking crazy.
Let me spread that little pussy.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh shit, you're so fucking deep.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
How's it feel baby?
I feel so fucking good
I feel so fucking good in that arm
Oh fuck yes
Oh fuck
Oh yes
Oh yeah
Oh fuck
You're making those big tits jiggle
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Ah
Oh my god
Yes yes yes
Oh shit
Oh my god
Fuck yes yes yes
Oh my god look at all that fucking cum
Fuck
They're fucking hot.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Jiggle it on that big dick.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, my monster dick.
Your monster titties.
We could fucking play all day like this.
Oh, look at that, Preycom.
We could play all day.
Yes, we could.
I love the taste of that.
I want you back in my ass.
Yeah.
Should've bend me over and stick that big dick in me.
Oh my god, look at that.
Fuck that.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, that feels so good.
Oh, I'm such a sucking ass.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh my God, Buck.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, yeah.
Put it back in that ass.
Holy shit.
All right, that's it.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah, you're twisting it
around in that ass.
I'm gonna fucking blow all over you.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Is that fucking cut getting close for me?
Oh my god, yes.
Yeah?
Oh yeah, I want that comb.
Yeah, I want it.
Yeah.
I see those titties.
I wanna see those big titties.
Mmm, these big titties gonna make you wanna comb.
Make you wanna blow everywhere.
Oh my god.
oh my god oh my god like oh my god likes you come so fucking much
Did you pop that in there?
Did I?
Both my balls are on his foot.
It's all over my face.
Holy fuck.
All in my mouth.
Oh my god, it's all over my tits.
Oh my god, look at it all.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm