Teksting av Nicolai Winther
Dramatisk musikk
I'll look for it now.
Hey, where were you looking at just now?
You looked at me with such a big gaze, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Do you admit it?
Hey, did you always look at my butt?
Always?
It's always been like this.
What should I do?
You can be honest.
Don't tell me you're expecting something like this?
Hey, you can get a little closer.
Hey...
Hey, you have to be honest.
There's no going forward.
Do you like your teacher's butt?
You don't like it?
Which one?
Which side?
I like it.
This big butt.
Do you want to touch it?
Yes.
Then, just for now.
I want you to touch this butt as much as you want.
You want to touch it, don't you?
I want to touch it.
If you don't do it quickly, the doctor will leave.
If you want to touch it, touch it a lot.
Touch it a lot.
Your butt is the only thing you always look at.
You can touch it a lot.
How is your butt?
It's very soft.
After all, young boys touch their butts like this.
Is it something that makes you feel better?
Are you going to cheer up?
Cheer up?
Then let's do more fun things.
Let's do more fun things.
Look closely.
It's so close.
I wonder what it smells like.
Look at the softness and other things.
I'm going to massage your face with the body of your teacher's buttocks.
Does your butt feel good?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
You've been looking at me for a long time, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
You just have to do what you want to do with this butt.
What do you mean by what I want to do?
You can do whatever you want.
It's okay if you don't like it.
How is it?
I want to see it.
Do you want to see it?
Can you see it?
I can see it very well.
Continue.
Like this?
Can I spread it?
Yes, you can
It's so beautiful
You can see my anal, right?
Yes
Spread your muscles more
Can I do it like this?
Yes, you can
Of course, you can
いいわよ。
先生のお尻、ベロベロ舐めてちょうだい。
すごい。
すごい。アナルがぐちょぐちょになっちゃう。
Lick it.
Lick it deeper.
Lick it all the way to the bottom of your butt.
Sensei's butt is fun, isn't it?
You've been working out with this little foot, haven't you?
Yes.
It's sandwiched.
It's sandwiched, isn't it?
Look at this.
It looks like a pie.
It's like fishing, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It feels so good.
It's so itchy.
I feel like I'm going to collapse.
Your bandages...
Your bandages are stuck in my wrist.
What should I do with this bandage?
What?
Do you want to go home when you get out of the hospital?
No, I don't want to go home when I get out of the hospital.
Hang in there.
Can you do it?
Hang in there until the doctor says you can do it.
You don't have enough energy, do you?
Hmm...
Oh...
Oh? What?
What's wrong with Kintama?
Kintama...
Oh...
Stress...
I can't hold it in anymore if you do it so fast, can't you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
You can feel better
If I do that, I'll go out
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
It's a lot of money.
Did you save so much money?
No.
You have to study properly.
Yes, I understand.
Did you really understand?
Yes, I will study.
It's good to see your teacher's butt, but you have to study too.
Yes.
Look.
See?
Ah!
Are you still here?
No, I was left alone for a while.
Are you done with your work?
Oh, I still have some work to do.
You're late for work.
Eh? No, I guess so.
Hey, I'm in class.
Isn't that because you only look at your teacher's butt?
What? No, that's not true.
I told you the other day, didn't I?
I told you to study.
Yes.
If you can't do it, I'll be late to go home.
I'm sorry.
How do you take responsibility for this?
Responsibility?
Give me back my precious time.
Excuse me.
How do you take responsibility for this?
How do you do it?
How do I do it?
Do you want to touch your buttocks?
No, I don't.
Your hands were stretched while you didn't like it.
I'm sorry.
Do you like your buttocks that much?
I like it.
You don't even know how to study.
You're such a pervert.
Is that so?
You like this butt so much.
It's because the teacher's butt is beautiful.
Are you curious about the future?
Yes.
Do you want to see it?
Yes
Then say it properly
I want to see your butt
One more time
Louder
I want to see your butt
Your butt
It's the best
Let's look closer.
Ms. Haiki, do you come to school with this?
Hmm.
This kind of book will be published when it is difficult, right?
That's right.
Look.
I want to touch it.
You can't touch it.
Don't touch it. Just look at it.
Just look at it.
You're excited, aren't you?
I'm scared. I'll do it.
You're moving this hand, aren't you?
Yes.
Isn't it getting bigger?
I'm so excited.
Can you lick me?
Yes.
Ah, iiih.
Motte Ake-chan mitai ni berberu namete.
Kodetsu ima yo.
You want to feel good, don't you?
You want to feel good in your teacher's buttocks, don't you?
Let me move my chin so much.
Show me your big chin.
Show me your legs.
I'm so tired.
Open your legs.
I'll rub your butt with a lot of water.
How are you feeling?
Touch my boobs.
It's almost the limit.
How many times do I have to do it?
It feels so good.
It feels so good, doesn't it?
Let's do something that feels better.
If I put it in this basket,
I think it feels really good.
Hey,
Hey, don't you want to put that big Chimpo in this messy baby?
I want to put it in.
Do you want to put it in?
Look at how messy your baby is.
どれだけぐちゅぐちゅだか見てみて。
そう。もっと近くで見て。
光ってる?そんな距離じゃ見えないでしょ?
近い?
ほら。ほら。
ああ、すごい。
ほら。
I can't do it anymore.
What? You want me to mess up more?
Right?
Is that so?
Yes.
I messed up even more.
Is it warm?
It's warmer in the back.
In the back?
How is it? It's warmer in the back, isn't it?
It's warm and I'm shaking a lot.
I can't be satisfied with your fingers.
Give it to me.
Give it to me, the teacher's baby.
Look at me.
To the teacher's
messy baby.
I want to put your baby
in there.
I'm still just working out.
It's just keto.
Keto feels so good.
It's so good.
I only put in keto.
I'm not satisfied with this.
Look at this.
Look closely at where your penis is stuck.
Show me where the teacher is.
Yes, that's right.
Move your chin more.
More.
Taste your chin.
目の顔とまんこが丸見え
ほら、この形であなたのチンポをここにぶっ刺して
ほら、その、ぼっきしたチンポちょうだい
そう、気持ちいい
どう?普段勉強してるところでセックスって
Don't you get excited?
Yes, I get excited.
Oh, wow!
I can feel the soup!
Can you see it?
Come here.
今度はこれで入れて
腹筋したチンポで
子宮の奥まで突き上げるのよ
いい?
見せてください
I'm always looking at your butt during class without studying, aren't I?
I have a big butt, so please mess with my butt more and more.
Ah, it's amazing!
Ah...
I'm sweating.
Ah, it's amazing. Thank you.
There's a lot of it.
After all, you're a bad student.
What?
You found out, didn't you?
You were looking at me secretly.
What are you talking about?
It's you, isn't it? If you admit it honestly.
No, it's not like that.
You guys are secretly looking at me without looking at anything.
What?
What is it?
You were peeking at me in the nurse's room,
and you made me puke here, right?
What? No...
Hey, your hand is in the way.
You were peeking at me in the nurse's room,
and you made me puke here, right?
Eh? No...
Ah...
Hey...
What is it?
I have a special lesson for you.
Eh? No...
Teacher, what are you doing?
Lesson.
This is a lesson.
Wait a minute, teacher.
I'm going to teach you how to hold your breath.
I'm sorry.
It's a lie, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Kakao
This is the first lesson.
Do you have the endurance?
Your back is weak.
Wow, it rips really hard.
The stiff nipple rips really hard on the teacher's nipple.
It stings.
The nipple really stings.
I wonder if I should take it out.
Right?
行きたくて、ひくひくしてるの?
先生、出してください。
出してください。
ダメ。
授業が終わった後に出したいなら一人で出しなさい。
Ah...
Hmm...
Are you Doemi-chan?
Eh...
Ah...
Hey...
Are you really?
No, I...
Are you Doemi-chan?
Hey...
Ah...
No...
Ah, that's right!
I'm Doemi-chan!
Ah, it's you again!
I can't do it!
Can you do it one more time?
What?
What am I?
I'm a foodie.
Can I take it out?
No, you can't.
I think I can do it.
Wow, you're still fine, Bukkijinpo!
Wow, you're still fine, you're still fine, you're still fine!
Ah, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it!
今ビンタしたからこっちに行ってたのがこっちにも行ったでしょ
Eh? Is this it?
That's it for today.
Eh? What is this?
What is this?
Why are you dressed like this?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm a little excited.
What is this?
Why are you so excited?
What's wrong with you?
I just had a class, didn't I?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's a endurance class.
Do you like your butt that much?
No, but my butt is like that, too.
What?
What do you like?
Ah...
I wonder if I can make you not use this...
It hurts...
Ah...
I want you anyway...
What is this?
It's this, isn't it?
Hey, you want this anyway, don't you?
Don't you think it's a nice view?
Is it painful?
Of course it's painful.
I'm being pressed with my butt.
It won't move.
Was it painful?
Yes.
Then I'll make it more painful.
Even though I'm lecturing you right now, what's with this sloppy chinko?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, what's with this sloppy chinko?
Hey, what's wrong? Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
Do you feel something?
Do you feel it even though you have a lot of acupuncture on your neck?
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of acupuncture on your nipples.
You feel it, don't you?
I'm sorry.
This feels good.
Do you like to have acupuncture on your nipples?
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
What happened to you?
Wait a minute.
You're in the way.
Teacher!
T-teacher!
Huh? That's...
Hey...
What are you doing?
Do you want to study for your endurance again?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm sorry, Dr. Yamaguchi.
Hey, why are you touching it without permission?
I'm sorry.
Say it again.
What?
Say it.
You said it so many times before.
It's embarrassing to shout.
Say it.
What about me?
What?
Say it.
What about me?
I'm a pervert.
What am I?
I can't hear you.
I'm a pervert.
More.
Say more.
I'm a pervert.
What's wrong?
This change is amazing, isn't it?
Then I'll give you a reward.
Your favorite butt.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
Hey
I'll give you my favorite butt
What are you talking about?
You like alcohol, don't you?
It hurts.
I don't know
Nani?
What is it?
Please let me touch it.
I don't want to touch it.
What? Why?
I told you I don't want to touch it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you feel the same way.
Right?
You know, I was bitten by your crotch, and my nipples were pinched, right?
Oh, wait a minute!
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, wait a minute.
What's wrong?
What's this?
Is this it?
Yano...
Are you spitting out the guman-jiru again?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey...
You're...
You're good enough with your hands and feet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, you're good enough with your hands and feet, aren't you?
Such a pervert is...
I'm sorry, but I don't think I can put you in someone else's house.
Let's see if I can hold it in.
I can't hold it in.
Where are you going?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Why did you try to run away?
I won't forgive you for running away.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm going to put this in your belly.
What?
No?
No, it's fine.
What?
You've been pooping all this time.
I'm curious what kind of poop it is.
Ah...
You're a pervert, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Look at me.
What?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
What?
That's nice.
Show me more of that pleasant face.
That kind of face.
I love that kind of face.
It was hard, wasn't it?
It's amazing.
My chin is stuck.
It's like a maid.
Do you know how to do it?
You have to start from the bottom.
From the bottom?
Yes.
Do you know how to move?
Yes, I do.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Not yet, not yet.
What?
Ah, I don't want to.
Look.
Why don't you stop?
What?
I don't want to.
You don't want me to stop?
Ok, let's do this!
Wow, that's amazing.
What was that?
It was so much fun.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, ah.
Eh?
Sensei.
What?
Sensei, it feels so good.
Do you want me to hit you?
I can't do it.
It's okay. I'll hit you a lot.
To you who can't do it.
Right?
Ah.
Hmm.
Do you want to be hit more?
Yes
I'll hit you
Is this okay?
Are you okay?
I'm only interested in your progress.
It feels good.
Hey, can you say it from behind this time?
Yes
Can you do it?
It's okay
I can only make you stand up
I have no brain
Wait!
Like this?
Yes!
Your back is amazing!
What?
Your penis in the mango is the best!
Are you going to do it?
Is it okay to go around?
Yes
I feel my back slowly
Ah, this is amazing. It's coming all the way to the back of my body.
Ii wa yo? Ii? Tataku wa yo?
Kana hentai chinpo ga
Arigatou gozaimasu
Ganbareru?
Oh ii na
Why did you quit?
I can't hold it in anymore.
You can't hold it in anymore?
Then you should just quit.
What? Can I?
But...
Put it on your butt.
Okay.
Put it on your big, big butt.
I hope you don't get sick.
I'm sorry.
Do you think you can be forgiven?
You can't be forgiven.
It was the best.
Teksting av Nicolai Winther