This is looking really good.
I hope it tastes as good as it looks.
I know.
Marco painted it?
Yeah, it was great.
Who do we have coming over?
My sister.
Yeah?
I told her all about you.
I'm so excited for you guys to finally meet.
Me too.
I think she's here.
Yeah.
Hey!
Oh, I'm so glad you could make it!
Of course!
I wouldn't miss the chance to meet your new boyfriend.
Ooh, are you hungry?
Dinner's ready.
So hungry.
Let's go.
Okay.
There's so much fruit in there.
It's really, really good.
Why do I like it?
It's delicious.
It turned out better than I was expecting.
So what have you been up to?
I know you said you've been busy.
Oh, you know, just kind of like taking care of the place.
Anyways, it is a tight fit, not gonna lie.
You should definitely check it out.
Oh yeah.
Oh!
Oh my God!
I dropped my fork.
So close.
Is everything okay, honey?
Oh, yeah, everything's great.
Some Chinese food.
So how was work?
Oh, work was great, yeah. Got off a little earlier today than usual.
That was definitely nice. Yeah.
You know, I've been thinking about changing up the decor a little bit,
doing something different with that place. Yeah, like what?
I haven't decided for sure. Yeah, Jim was like talking about your
office. Yeah.
Yeah.
Talking about computers and shit.
Oh, I forgot.
He's the one that just, he's always talking to it.
Yeah.
Does any of it-
It's so annoying.
Does it ever make sense?
I mean, kind of.
Yeah, I mean, I guess after a while,
you listen to him enough,
you start picking some things up,
I don't know, computer stuff has never made sense to me.
Yeah, me neither.
Oh yeah, oh my God.
I guess I could see how listening to it all the time
would be really annoying,
especially because computer stuff doesn't make sense.
Yeah, so boring.
I don't know how you do it.
I know, I fucking hate my job, honestly.
Well, have you thought about looking for a different place?
Hey, I found a bowl. Great.
Yeah, must have been lost way down there. It was really lodged.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my god, it's so thick, I'm putting it in the back of my throat.
You want to f***ing f*** these teeth?
Oh fuck yes. Oh my god, you're putting me in big tits.
Oh, and your sister doesn't have tits like this does she?
Ugh, fuck my fucking titties. Yes.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh my god, you're such big fucking jerks. Yes.
That big fucking heart I can't get between my huge jerks.
Oh fuck. Oh fuck you.
Oh yes.
Oh my god, you're so f***ing mean.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Fuck yeah. Oh my god.
Yes. Yes.
That's it. Yes.
Fuck my fucking pussy.
Oh, fuck your sister's twat.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck.
Yes. Oh my god.
Oh my god, that tickles so much.
Oh, yes! Oh, fuck yes, George, I'm fucking pushing you!
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
I sweat like couldn't lose a pulse.
Back here.
Oh, yes.
Oh, no.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
You're so good.
Fuck, you're so good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God, you're so good.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, yeah, I can't believe it.
Yeah, fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck you.
Dan.
Dan, where'd you go?
Wait, babe, are you in there?
What the fuck?
Babe, are you in here?
Ellie! Oh babe, what's going on?
Oh, um, I spilled the middle of my clothes, so I need to take a shower.
Any idea where you might have gone?
No. Have you checked outside?
Checked outside, no. I didn't go look in the backyard.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Speak up.
Oh my god.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God, it tastes so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yo.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Give me that fucking dick.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Give me that fucking dick.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck yes.
What? Yes, oh my god!
Oh fuck yes!
Oh yes!
Yes! Oh fuck yes!
Oh fuck yes!
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Oh fuck yes!
I don't know what to do.
Oh f**k yes!
F**k yes!
Oh, fuck you.
Oh my god, I'm so sick.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh my god, just like that, fuck.
Fuck, oh my god.
Oh my god.
I'm so sick.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to stop. I'm going to stop. I just want to eat a hardhawk.
Oh shit.
Yes, yes, please.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh
Oh, fuck yes, oh my god.
Oh my god, this is so good.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh, fuck yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, please give me that fucking dick.
Please.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Why are you scared of me?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you fucking covered my tits in your fucking gown.
It's so fucking hot.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Dan?
Oh, shit.
Where the hell are you?