Cursed from the day that I left the womb
To live out my days in this whitewashed tomb
Every day's a struggle for equality
I can't give up or else I'll lose this part of me
I just wanna feel beautiful
In the skin that I'm in
I just wanna do natural
Is that too much?
I wanna be, wanna be, wanna be beautiful
I'm just gonna feel beautiful
In the skin that I'm in
And I just wanna do natural
Is that so?
I'm just gonna be beautiful
With the skin that I'm in
I'm just gonna do what I have to roll
Is that so hard?
I'm gonna be, gonna be, gonna be beautiful
I'm gonna be beautiful
I'm gonna be, gonna be beautiful
I'm gonna be, gonna be, gonna be beautiful
Beautiful
I love tapioca.
It's crunchy.
I know.
It's tapioca.
It's pink.
It's different.
It's strawberry tapioca.
It's cool.
I can feel only your nipples, right?
It's getting harder.
It's cute.
You like it, don't you?
It's good.
Gyou-kun, you're touching it gently.
What do you like about it?
You like it, don't you?
It's moving.
It's tickling.
Like this.
Oh, that's nice.
Tightly.
Oh, it came off.
Oh, that's amazing.
That's amazing.
It got smaller.
It got thinner every time.
Oh, that's amazing.
It's getting bigger.
Like this.
Mm-hmm.
Ah, I see.
Try it on.
I'll try it on.
I like it like this.
I like it.
It feels good.
Why are you standing here in this outfit?
You're standing here in this kind of outfit.
That's true.
If you're wearing this kind of outfit in this kind of place,
you wanted to do something sexy, didn't you?
I was waiting for it.
You were waiting for it.
I want you to do it.
I'll do it for you.
You're licking your nipples from both sides.
How does it feel?
My nipples are getting fluffy.
That's amazing.
Wow, that's amazing!
Wow, Papa!
That's amazing!
I didn't know you could do this with just your nipples.
Let's try putting your pants down.
I haven't touched your nipples yet.
That's right.
You don't have to touch your nipples.
Wow!
What is this?
It's like a balloon.
It's just your nipples.
That's amazing.
Let's pinch your nipples like this.
Let's peel off the skin.
Just the skin.
Peel off the skin.
You have a lot of patience.
You have to pinch your nipples until you can do it.
It's going to be weird.
What's going to happen if you pinch your nipples?
What?
Only the nipples?
What are you going to do with the nipples?
I'm going to do it.
You're going to do it?
No way.
I want to see it.
What? What? What? What?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
What? What? What's wrong?
What? What? What?
She's so slimy.
She's so patient.
Do more.
What do you think?
I think I can do it.
You think you can do it?
What? What?
I think I can do it.
I can do it.
What's going to happen?
It's going to be so cringy.
I haven't touched my nipples yet.
What should I do?
Your nipples are the only thing that makes you feel good.
Go.
Your nipples.
Chikubi?
Chikubi ga nani?
Ara ara sugoi sugoi sugoi sugoi!
Mmmmm.
Chikubi ike shichou?
Chikubi ike shichou no?
Nani?
Shite.
Yutte gorou?
Yuku toki yuunda yo chanto.
Chikubi ike shimasu te.
Yutte no?
Chikubi ike shimasu.
I can't do this.
What?
There's a lot of them!
This is so much fun!
What are you looking at?
Cut!
They're all in this kind of outfit.
What are you doing in a place like this?
What are you doing?
Let's stick our butts out!
See?
They're in this kind of outfit.
They're spreading their butts. You want them to move their butts, right?
Right!
Let's move them.
Should I cut it for you?
You look like you like it.
Here, here.
Cut it, cut it, cut it.
Make it stand out more so we can see it.
So we can see it.
You did a good job.
You're so cute, Anaru.
I'm asking you to give it to me.
Should I give it to you?
Do you want to give it to me?
Oh, you're excited. You look like you're having fun.
Your butt is warm.
My butt hurts.
It's hot.
She's swallowing it.
It's so hot.
It's hot in my butt.
Look, look, look.
She's swallowing it.
It's getting hot.
It's so hot.
She's swallowing it.
Oh my god, it's coming in right away.
It's not even touching it.
Oh my god.
It's hissing.
It's making a noise.
It's getting in.
It's making a weird noise.
It's standing up.
Do you want to put it in together?
Let's put it in.
Oh, it's in.
It's coming in.
Please loosen it up.
It's loosening up.
It's like a baby.
It feels good.
Wow, this is going to be fun!
It's going to be fun!
Stick it out properly.
Stick it out?
There are two pieces in there.
Can I?
What's going on inside?
It's kind of wriggling inside.
What?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, stick out your butt properly.
I'm going to do it too.
Oh, I'm getting more and more into it.
Chimpo went in.
Go all the way in.
Your butt is shaking.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
There's an embarrassing voice coming out.
Do you want me to go all the way in?
Your butt is shaking.
If you do that, it'll tighten up.
I want you to touch my butt, but I won't touch it.
Where do you like it? Tell me.
Here? Downward?
Here?
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
Are you alive?
Come on, wake up.
It's okay.
It's not the time to lie down because it feels good.
Are you okay?
Is this okay?
It feels good.
It's the best.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're shy, aren't you?
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Are you okay?
It's a big deal.
Here we go.
Hang in there.
Wake up.
Are you okay?
Look, look, look.
You like this, don't you?
It's amazing.
I'm going to fall down later.
I'm watching you.
Hey, wake up.
Don't do that.
Hey.
I'm surprised.
It's amazing.
Look at this! The muscles are so tight!
It feels so good!
What's going to happen?
With your butt?
Yes, with my butt.
That's amazing.
I put a lot of effort into it at the end.
Your muscles are amazing.
I feel like I'm being pushed forward.
That was fun.
It was fun.
That's amazing.
Let's stop here.
That's enough.
Let's go somewhere.
Let's go over there.
I want to go too.
I found something interesting.
It's shaking.
Do you like it?
It's very sensitive.
It's sensitive.
Do you want to go to the sensitive part?
I'll touch the sensitive part a lot.
I'm so excited.
Only your nipples?
All of a sudden?
My nipples are like a switch.
That's amazing.
I'm so excited.
It's true.
You're so fast.
I'm just trying to make you feel better.
I'm so excited.
It feels good.
It looks like this.
It's coming out from the side.
Wow!
Was it this big?
It's so big.
It looks long.
It's so long.
It looks like a mushroom.
There are so many of them.
Tomo, you're so cute!
You're amazing!
What's going to happen?
Do you want me to bite your nipples?
Wait a minute!
Wow!
Your nipples are so tight!
What's going to happen?
Wow! You're so cute!
You're amazing!
My face is on the screen!
Really?
Look!
Look at the camera.
Hello.
It's moving.
What are you doing?
You're so cool.
You're so cute.
What are you doing?
You're going to fall, so let's put you to sleep.
It's dangerous.
You're still standing.
You're still crouching.
You're still sleeping.
Just go to sleep.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to pet me.
You want me to pet you?
I'll pet you.
It's getting softer and softer.
I like the strong one.
What is it?
It feels good.
It's getting softer and softer.
It feels good when it's small.
It looks fun when you rub your nipples.
I love to rub my nipples.
Are you rubbing your butt?
Do you want me to rub it on your face?
Rub it on your face.
What's wrong with you?
Are you going to go?
Are you feeling okay?
You can't go.
I couldn't go.
I can't stand it.
Poor thing.
I'm going to tickle you more.
You have to hold it in.
That's right.
You can do it.
But I think I'll have to stretch it out quickly.
It might be hard.
You're making a loud noise.
Oh no, oh no.
No, no, no.
Look, look, look, look.
That was close.
You're going to be in trouble.
It's not over yet.
You still can't do it.
I want to go.
Do you want to go?
Poor you.
I want to go.
I want to let you go.
It feels good.
Go as far as you can.
We'll watch you.
That's nice.
That's good.
Oh no, it's coming out.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Wow, wow, wow!
Isn't that a little too much?
It's still coming out.
Why?
More, more, more!
Come on, come on, come on!
It's not enough.
Are you okay?
You said you were going to die.
We beat them all.
It was fun, but...
I want more.
Let's keep drinking tapioca.
Let's go look for tapioca.
Are we going to look for tapioca?
No, we're going to drink tapioca and look for it.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go!
Yay!
That was fun.
We've arrived at the hotel.
No, no.
It was quick from Tokyo by plane.
Yes.
Ah, please take care of the presentation meeting tomorrow.
As planned, I'll get your voice back at 14 o'clock.
Yes.
Please take care of me.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry.
What's wrong?
It's not your fault, is it?
But...
I was going to rent a hotel for the two of us,
but there was only one room available,
so we ended up staying in the same room.
I can't help it.
It was an urgent business trip.
It seems like there's no room on weekends.
It can't be helped.
I'm really sorry.
So?
Will you satisfy my stress?
What?
I haven't had sex recently.
Do you understand?
You know what I mean?
You and I are going to spend the night here, right?
We can't have sex without doing anything.
Oh, it's okay.
You can sleep there.
Don't do anything.
Just lend me your bed.
No, that's not...
Don't bother me.
You don't look like you're having a meeting with someone.
I am, don't I?
Wait, what's this?
It looks fun, so mix it up.
Mix it up, mix it up.
I thought it was just the two of us.
Mix it up.
What were you doing?
We're like a pair of hyenas.
Oh, that's good.
Kanta, don't forget to take off your jacket.
This is not good.
It's not bad.
Who made this room?
That's right.
Let's kiss slowly.
Give me your tongue.
It's not good.
I kissed too.
I want to kiss you, too.
Wait a minute.
If you don't want to be scolded by Sekihara, listen to me.
Feels good.
I love your nipples.
My nipples are sensitive.
They are.
Look at them.
They are so cute.
Let me pet them.
Do you like it?
Yes.
That's good.
I'm getting excited.
What are you missing?
Don't get too excited.
Do you think a big adult would be satisfied with a kiss and a nipple?
We're in the second half.
Wow.
I'm the first one to do it.
You're my subordinate.
It's okay. Just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
I want to see it!
Wait! Wait!
It's so big!
It's so big.
You're so cute!
You're going to eat it all?
What's this?
Stop it.
Next, it's my turn.
I'm going to eat it slowly.
I'll lick it for you.
You like to be licked, don't you?
You're starting to become cute.
Wait, that's...
That sound, it's coming out right away.
It's coming out right away.
That's right, you can't do that.
You can't do that if you lick it right away.
Your butt!
You like this kind of thing, don't you?
Oh, you're looking at the butterfly, aren't you?
Yes, I'm looking at it.
You like butt, don't you?
Oh, that's...
This side, too.
Oh, me, too.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Look, there are three of them.
Which butt do you like?
This one?
Me.
Me, too.
Touch the one you like.
Choose one.
I'm so happy!
Hey!
You!
I won't forgive you anymore!
Hey!
Why am I not the best?
I'll put you on!
It was fun, wasn't it?
I want more.
More?
I can't choose!
You can't choose?
Are you happy?
Which one do you like better?
Ah, I can't choose.
You can't choose?
I'm going to massage your buttocks.
I'm going to do it here.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot.
How is it? Is your buttocks the best?
Ah, it's good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's so itchy.
You can touch your boobs.
So cute.
I'm so tired.
I can't help it.
How are your pants and shirikoki?
What?
They are so wrinkly.
You're being teased!
You like this kind of thing?
You want me to rub your feet?
You like that kind of thing!
Could it be a stocking fetish?
Which do you like better, the butt or the stocking fetish?
I don't know.
Me too.
Wow, amazing.
The butt is down.
You're good.
She's holding it in.
She likes it.
Look.
Wow, amazing.
Wow, amazing!
Squeeze it. Wow, amazing!
There's a lot of it!
Wow, amazing!
If you use this, it won't feel good, right?
Can you drink it?
Wait a minute!
Will it come out?
It's coming out!
No, you can't!
What should I do?
It stopped.
It's going to stop.
If you stay here, it's over.
Look.
Hold on.
You can do it, right?
Look.
How is it?
It hurts.
Are you going to go?
No, I'm not going.
You're going to be a toy.
I want to put it in too.
Wait!
What?
Who made a mistake in today's room?
Do you want to be sued by Sekihara?
That's right.
Look, even though you want to put it in, it's still shiny.
You too, with all this mess.
There's no way I'm not going to put it in.
That's right.
Put your hand out.
My...
Pants...
Break the place you want to put it in.
Really?
Yes.
Then you can show your will.
Break it.
Bili bili.
Ah!
Wow!
Is it here?
How can you break it so hard?
Wow!
Did you really want to put it in?
Did you want to put it in?
If you break it that far...
Wow, look!
I want to put it in here.
You want to put it in here, right?
Do you want to pee?
You look embarrassed.
You want to put it in, don't you?
I'm blushing.
What about you?
What's wrong with you?
Here you go.
It's okay. I want to put it on too.
You can put it on with a suit.
I don't want to anymore. I'm so lonely.
How is it?
It's the best.
It's good.
I'm sure you'll feel good when you get a chimp like this.
I'm sure I'll feel good.
You're the best.
I love you so much.
Don't do that!
That person will come out right away.
What should I do?
I can't do it!
Can you do it?
Amazing!
Where do you want to put it?
I want you to put it in mine too.
You don't want to put it in mine, do you?
I can't choose.
There are so many sweet things.
Just focus on my butt now.
Focus on mine too.
My heart is shaking.
My heart is beating too fast.
It's so intense.
Let's do it together.
I'm not done yet.
Really?
Why not?
Because I'm so dissatisfied.
I'm dissatisfied, too.
What are you crying about?
You can go back to your room.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
I want to lick you.
Do you want to lick your nipples?
That's amazing!
This is so good!
Let's do it together!
Chikubi, you like it, don't you?
It's easy, isn't it? All you have to do is lie down and sleep.
Work for us.
We love you.
I'm so tired.
Me too.
I can't breathe.
I can't move.
How long are you going to sleep?
It's too early.
Can you move?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make you feel better.
Can you do it?
Can you move?
I'm going to put it in.
It's different here.
The hole is wrong.
Did you put it in properly?
Yes, I did.
Then, I'll put it in this hole.
Move it properly.
Move it while putting it in the hole in your butt.
Wow, amazing.
I can see it.
What are you going to do?
You have to move!
I'm going to sleep.
I can't sleep.
I can hear the sound of your hands.
Don't stop it!
Let's do the other side too.
It looks like you can do it!
Keep moving it!
Stop!
It looks like you can do it!
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Don't say that yet.
That's right.
Go to sleep.
It's not enough yet.
I won't let you live.
I'm going to enjoy it all the time.
Zubo zubo yo!
Please let me sleep.
I don't know what I should do.
It's so hot!
Come on, come on!
Are you going to go?
Hey!
It's going to stay like this!
It's really bad!
Go inside! Go! Go! Go!
Wait a minute!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Did you go inside?
Ah!
Ah, I really got out of bed.
What?
Ah, wow, wow, wow.
Ah, it's coming out.
Amazing.
Ah, it's dripping.
It's dripping a lot.
Ah, no.
Ah, it's intense.
It's out.
It's going to be a baby.
That's crazy.
Ah, there's a lot.
Really?
Congratulations!
Then, let's celebrate.
Do you want to do a celebration sex?
Let's do it.
You fell in love with me.
I'm glad.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
I would like to start right away.
Are you okay with the aroma oil course today?
Yes.
All right.
Today is service time, so we will have three surgeons.
There will be three of us for the surgery.
Oh, I see.
Thank you for coming.
Excuse me.
Let me check your body.
Okay.
Please relax.
Is there any part of your body that you want to touch?
I see.
Yes, that's right.
The legs, the thighs, and the muscles.
It's a little tight.
Let's stretch the whole thing and focus on the legs.
Yes.
Excuse me for the oil.
I'll apply it.
If it hurts, please tell me.
How do you feel?
I'm going to massage your whole body.
Okay.
Please relax.
Is your strength okay?
Yes.
Um...
Can I do it with these three?
Of course.
It's special today.
Okay.
Please relax.
Is this a special fee or something?
Oh, that's not it.
It's not like that.
But we have more services than usual.
More services?
Yes, please do whatever you want.
Excuse me.
What do you do for a living?
I work at a construction site.
That must be tiring.
It's hard in many places, isn't it?
Yes, let's remove it.
You're standing still, aren't you?
Well, that's right.
That's right.
Standing still is tiring, isn't it?
Please relax a lot.
Did you hate it?
No, I don't hate it.
I'll do a lot of it.
It is a procedure that includes massage.
Is this the first time you've had an esthetic treatment?
Yes.
I see.
We'll focus on massaging the lymph nodes.
This will improve your blood circulation.
It will make your skin better.
It will also make your skin dry.
There's oil on your face too.
Excuse me.
It's getting warmer and warmer.
Our oil uses ingredients that make your body warm.
We use the ingredients that make your skin warm.
Open your legs a little.
We'll massage your ears as well.
We'll massage the small parts as well.
Ah, it's tickling.
Excuse me for a moment.
I'm going to apply a special oil.
How is it?
It's amazing.
It's too thick.
Please use it well.
You apply the oil well.
It's all gone.
No, it's just a little bit there.
It's true.
Then I'll apply a little more.
Let's take a look at it.
It's amazing. It's very elaborate.
By using a lot of special oils imported from overseas,
the effect is doubled.
Let's go to the bottom.
Let's go from both sides.
Please open your eyes.
Let's apply the oil to this side as well.
Let's make the parts thinner.
I'll do my best.
What's that?
It's a lot.
It's shiny, isn't it?
It's shiny.
It's nice.
It's a massage using an esthetic shorts.
How is it?
It's a little too much.
You don't like it?
No, I don't.
But everyone is doing it naturally.
Everyone is happy to see you.
It may be a little confusing if you don't wear it.
Yes, it is.
It's wonderful.
Please relax.
I'm tired.
I'm tired, too.
It's a good sign that your blood circulation is improving.
Let's clean this up.
Yes.
How do you feel?
Is this a service?
Yes, it is.
Of course.
It's amazing.
Wow, it's so fluffy.
This feather touch is very effective.
Let's apply it.
We'll do a neutral massage here.
I'm going to massage you with this.
It's okay. Leave it to me.
Don't worry about anything.
We're professionals.
Does it feel good?
Please lean on me.
What do you think of the therapist's technique?
It's a bit too much.
What's wrong?
I'm just loosening it.
We'll use various places to loosen it.
How is this?
How do you feel now?
Ah!
It's really crumbling.
Yes, it is.
Are you okay?
It's proof that the blood circulation is getting better.
Sir, the timing of the waste is important.
If it's about to come out, please don't let it come out on its own.
Yes, I will.
I'll take care of it here.
Yes, I'll be patient.
Yes, that's right.
If you feel like you're about to have an abortion, please report it to us.
Yes.
You're such a good boy.
I'm going to give you a lot of breast milk.
No, wait a minute.
There are a lot of important ingredients in this.
There are a lot of grains, so let's squeeze a lot.
Are you okay?
You've been able to hold it in, haven't you?
That's the way it is.
It's getting warmer.
Your whole body is warm, isn't it?
Are you okay?
Then I will massage you with my body.
We will prepare it for you.
This is a massage.
How do you feel?
How does it feel to have a chest massage?
It feels good.
There are 3 therapists today.
We will do a chest massage with 3 therapists.
There are many different types of breasts.
Are you ready?
I'm going to give you a lot of massage with various boobs.
I'm going to give you a massage.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
What do you think, Ms. Gyaku?
It's tickling.
How is it?
This cheek, too.
There's another one here, too.
Which cheek do you like?
There are a lot of nipples.
There's a neck here.
The stimulants in the cow's head are good for your kidneys.
How much is it?
I don't know.
It's too much.
I'll rub it a lot.
Oh, that's not good.
Oh, wait a minute.
Are you okay?
Did you do too much?
Can you hold it in?
It's not good yet.
Let's do more.
Okay.
Are you okay?
No.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it.
You can do a lot of massages with three people.
You are a human being.
Let's pack your head too.
Mr. Shimazawa, please look at me.
Please give me some ointment.
Yes, I'll bring it to you.
No, wait a minute.
It feels good.
The other side is also shiny.
It's very shiny.
Please give me a lot of ointment.
Thank you for waiting. This is the extra oil.
There is a lot of ointment.
How do you feel about the ointment mask?
Can you close your legs a little?
Excuse me for the anal.
It's tickling.
Are you all right?
I'll massage your cheekbones.
That's great.
Your cheekbones are tickling.
Your fingers are all the way in.
You like your butt too, don't you?
Oh, I see.
Let's do a lot of detoxing in various places.
Please be patient even if you feel like you can't do it anymore.
I feel like I'm falling.
How do you feel?
Do you want to do a detox?
I think I can do it.
There is still a massage left.
There is still a special massage left.
Is that okay?
From now on, I will do a detox using my internal organs.
Do a detox.
Please let me do it.
I'll do it.
It's a special sauce.
How is it?
It's a bit...
It's cute.
Please take a look.
How is the customer's chimp?
It's shiny.
Let me see.
It looks healthy, doesn't it?
I don't think so.
Does it feel good?
Wow!
Is this a massage?
Yes, it's a massage.
It's a special massage, isn't it?
It's a gentle massage.
Oh, it's gentle.
How do I look?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Was it too strong?
No, it's okay.
It's a strong massage.
It's good enough to be too strong for an indoor massage.
That's right.
Please give me a good massage.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I'm going to give you a more intense massage.
I'm going to give you a massage.
I'm going to massage your anus at the same time.
This is not good.
Please don't be too conscious.
It's amazing.
Please hold on.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
It came out.
Let's check it out.
It came out a little bit.
Let's put it in again.
It's not done yet.
Excuse me.
The old waste was a little loose.
More, please.
If you don't do it now, you won't be able to do it.
No, I can't do it.
You just said it.
Let's massage your palms at the same time.
Oh, it feels good.
You have such a big chin.
How is it?
How do you feel?
A little bit?
Tighten it up.
Oh, wait a minute.
Please enjoy it while looking at the therapist's big butt.
How is it?
Do you like big butts?
Do you like your butt?
You can use your hands to pat it.
There is a relaxation effect.
Relax, relax.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
Massage.
Massage your chest.
I'll give you a massage on your head.
It's good.
Please relax.
You're shaking a lot.
I'm a therapist.
Please relax.
Relax.
Amazing.
Your waist is amazing.
Your muscles are sagging.
My muscles are sagging.
I'm sorry.
I put in a lot of my own blood.
There's a lot of water coming out.
I can't breathe.
How do you feel?
It's amazing.
It's a mess.
It's a mess, isn't it?
Are you feeling better?
Your heart is beating fast.
It feels good when your heart is beating fast.
I feel like I'm going to sleep.
Please concentrate on your sleep.
Okay.
Yes, ma'am.
Please concentrate on your whole nervous system.
Please concentrate on my lower body.
I'm sorry.
I'll do everything for you.
Wait a minute.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
Really?
Please detox your body.
Please take it out.
I'm going to eat it.
It's going to come out.
Please take it out.
Are you okay?
Please take out the last one.
If you leave it, it's bad for your body.
There are a lot of them.
I'm so happy.
There were so many of them.
Are you feeling better now?
How are you feeling?
I'm still standing.
Are you feeling better now?
I feel like there's something left.
It tickles.
Does it tickle?
Yes.
It's thick.
There's still a lot of sperm inside.
How was your massage today?
Did you feel better?
Please come again if you feel tired.
I'm always waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for waiting.
You look so cool.
I wonder what a good-aged adult is expecting.
Do you want me to bully you a lot?
It can't be helped, isn't it, Chimpo-chan?
It can't be helped, so...
Hentai Chimpo-chan, we'll bully you a lot.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm getting nervous.
Do you want me to bully you?
You want me to bully you, don't you, Chimpo-chan?
I'm nervous.
She's excited.
So cute.
Your body is getting hot.
Your nipples are pink.
They're standing up.
I want you to touch here.
So cute.
Your nipples are also pink.
She's getting up.
Which one do you want?
I want to give you a good massage.
You can't drink this, can you?
I'm so sick of it.
Don't spill it.
Apply it.
Is it good?
Do you like it?
She's so cute.
Jinpo-chan is so cute.
She wants you to play with her.
She's so cute.
I won't play with her yet.
I want you to play with her.
It's good, isn't it?
Later.
Hang in there.
Where are you licking?
Where?
Like this?
What are you saying?
I don't know.
Why?
Say it again.
Say it.
What are you doing?
I don't know. I can't hear you.
Oh, wow.
Me too.
Goodbye.
Do you know what this is?
Listen to the sound.
I want you to do a lot of things for me.
I have a tattoo.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
I really want to put it on my lips.
I want you to feel good.
But...
I don't want to.
It's hitting your head.
Do you want me to hit your head?
It's still hitting your head.
You're being teased.
Take your time.
I wonder if there's a lot of them.
There's a lot of them.
Amazing!
I'm going to play with them while looking at them.
You're excited, aren't you?
I'm excited, aren't I?
I'm excited.
Oh, I see.
I see.
You can eat a lot of ramen with this, can't you?
Wow, you're so energetic!
I'm going to break your underwear.
You're such a pervert.
It's not enough, isn't it?
I don't think it's enough.
I don't think I can do it.
What do you want me to do?
Yeah, I think so too.
Do you like it?
I like it.
You like it, right?
I don't want to be tickled.
Me neither.
I'm going to break your chin.
I'm not going to be a useful person anymore.
Yeah.
Why are you still in this state?
Are you a pervert?
I'm a pervert.
I'm going to break your perverted chin.
Let me pat your chin.
Your chin is getting more and more stiff.
I'm scared.
It's good, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Like this.
Look at your chin.
Do it like this.
Like this.
Oh, that's great.
Look.
That's how you do it.
That's great.
Wow, you're so good at this!
I want to know more about you.
Oh, that's nice.
Here, I'll take it off for you.
Do you want me to do more fun things for you?
Stand up.
Put your butt here.
Put your hand on it.
That's right.
Wow, you look great.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Look at your butt.
Let it out.
Look, you're doing a good job.
That's good.
Then it won't make a good sound, right?
This way, right?
You have a lot of hair.
I don't want to.
You're protecting it.
I can't see it at all.
It's true.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
It's dirty.
Let's smell it.
It stinks.
How is it?
It's dirty.
Why does it smell so bad?
I don't know.
It's all over the place.
It makes a good sound.
It's squeaky.
Let's do it again.
It's all over the place.
Show me your butt.
I can't see it.
You're so mean.
Let's separate your butt and play with it.
I'll push it to the back.
You like it, right?
Here I go.
Here we go!
It's blowing!
It feels good!
Look, it's in your fingers.
Don't pull your butt.
It's blowing all the way in.
This is amazing.
How is it?
Amazing.
What do you think?
You like it, right?
Ah, it's getting more and more like a dog's ass, isn't it?
Haha, it's going back and forth.
Ah, it's going all the way to the back, isn't it?
Yes, it's going all the way to the back.
Ah, I love it.
Look, look, look, look, look, look.
It's like a girl is being dug up.
It's so embarrassing.
Ah, look, your finger...
My finger is making a hole in your ass, isn't it?
Ah, it's so embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're going to do it?
You're scared.
My fingers are so dirty.
You're the only one who feels good.
That's right.
You two should feel good too.
If you do that, I'll keep rubbing it on you.
Don't put it on your butt.
You have to make it feel good.
You can't do it on your own.
Amazing.
Your butt is shaking.
Why are you shaking?
Which is more fun, your butt or your boobs?
Your butt is shaking.
It's okay.
What a pervert.
Focus on this side, too.
Is it okay for you to enjoy it alone?
You can't lick it because it's in your mouth.
I'll give you a hug. You like it, don't you?
Your ears are all red.
I can't move.
It feels good.
Make it feel good.
Don't make it too tight.
Make it tighter!
Do you want me to take this off?
How is it?
Don't make it too tight.
I want to open it.
Open your mouth.
Don't show it to me.
Look at your butt.
Don't make it too tight.
It's fine.
Look.
It's amazing.
Let's make your face bigger.
Look.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wow, it's so thick.
It's so thick.
Wow, wow, wow.
Let me taste it.
Oh!
You can't see it, but
there's an omanko here.
There's an omanko here.
If you don't open it, the omanko will be in front of you.
It's true.
Do you want to lick it?
Put your tongue out.
I just took off my disgusting costume.
I'm going to come down in front of you.
Come on.
Make sure you lick it.
It smells good.
It smells like a female scab.
Does it smell?
Look.
It was really spicy.
Make sure you lick it.
Is it good?
It was good.
Have a good drink. You look so happy.
Put your tongue in properly.
Should I step on your nipples?
Don't put on the condom.
It'll get dirty.
It'll get shiny.
I'm sorry.
Let's get rid of your nipples.
Have a good drink.
It was fun.
I want to lick you too.
You're licking a lot.
It's tickling.
It feels good.
It's okay.
Let's all lick you.
It's tickling.
I want to lick it.
You want to lick it?
Say it clearly.
I want to lick it.
Beep, beep.
See, it's coming down.
It's a big baby.
Pull out your tongue.
It's crazy, isn't it?
I won't tell you anything else.
It's a baby.
It's making a loud noise.
Is it good?
It's a baby.
It feels good.
See?
Don't touch it!
It's a mint chimp.
Really?
I want you to brush it a little.
Hurry up and brush it.
Oh, no, no.
Your chimp is covered in soot.
Yeah, it's covered in soot.
I'll brush your dirty chimp with soot.
Really?
I got a lot.
Chimpo is so happy to be petted by Chimpo.
Chimpo is so excited.
Chimpo is so happy.
Chimpo is so happy to be petted by Chimpo.
It's hard. It's not easy to do it on your own.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
Are you going to do it?
It hurts.
It feels good.
Don't do it.
Don't do that.
You can't do that on your own.
Are you going to go before my mark comes down?
I don't like it.
I told you to lick it.
Lick it well.
It's so juicy.
I can't wait to eat it.
It's so good.
Tell me how it tastes.
It's delicious.
What do you mean delicious?
Delicious?
It's delicious.
That's too much!
You want me to twist your neck?
Here, here, here.
Be more firm.
Make sure you feel good.
What are you going to do?
Oh, no, no.
I'm running out of hands.
You're not going to use this, are you?
No, no, no.
You can do it!
It's not enough, is it?
Do you want more?
I want more.
What do you want?
What?
I want to put it in.
What do you want to put in?
I want to put my chinchin in a big bowl.
You want to put this stinky chinchin in a big bowl?
Do you want me to put it in?
Yes!
That's a good reply.
I can't help it.
Ah, you want me to put it in.
That's good.
Then I'll put it in for you.
Hey.
Are you kidding me?
Do you want me to put it in for you?
What should I do?
I can't see it, so I don't know.
Thank you.
You don't say thank you.
That's right.
Are you going to put it in?
Thank you.
What if you put it in the anal?
What should I put in?
I don't know what will go in.
In the anal?
What should I put in?
I don't think anything will come out until the end.
I don't think so either.
Will it go in?
Oh, it's coming, it's coming.
Something is hitting it.
What is this?
It's going to come out.
Is it hitting you?
Is it?
What's going on?
Oh wow!
It's stuck!
Oh no!
It's getting bigger and bigger.
What's going on?
I want it.
You want it, right?
Don't forget your honorifics.
That's right.
It's good.
It's not like this.
How is it?
It's warm, isn't it?
It feels good.
Sit here.
Firmly.
It's because you're an adult.
You're being so soft.
If you don't say it when we say it, you won't be able to do it, right?
Well, I can do it.
Wow, that's amazing.
I'm going to make sure you don't use this anymore.
If you put it in your belly button, it's already ours, you know?
Do you get it?
There's a lot of stuff in here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's a little red.
What?
Are you going to move your body?
I can't let you go out on your own.
I'm not alone.
If I let you go out, I'll take your nipples off.
I'm going to lose my nipples too.
You're going to lose them, aren't you?
Do you want me to let you go out?
Are you ready to take your nipples off?
I can't hold it in.
It feels good.
It's dangerous.
That was so close!
I was about to throw it out.
Who said you could throw it out?
Did you get permission to throw it out?
Do you want me to make a hole again?
Do you want me to bully you more?
I want you to bully me.
It's a waste of space.
That's right.
I'll attack you at the same time.
I know where it is.
Wait a minute.
This way.
Where is it?
Here it is.
I'll make you feel better.
Did you understand?
That's good.
Put your hands behind you.
Shake your hips.
From the back, I'm going to do your dirty butt together.
Yu-yu, move yourself.
Stop.
Good.
Spread your butt.
You can do it.
It's in.
Chinko is doing the same thing.
I'm sure you'll be able to eat both of your delicious chimp.
Thank you very much.
You're so cute.
You're so cute from the back to the front.
Thank you very much.
This side, too.
Wow, wow, wow.
You can do it, you can do it.
Good luck.
You're so good at tapping.
Yeah, you're right.
They'll move on their own.
It's the same thing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Look, look, look.
Where are you going?
Hey.
I can't.
Where are you going?
Do you want to do it one step at a time?
One step at a time?
I don't know how to do it.
You don't know how to do it, do you?
I don't know how to do it, do you?
Oh, that's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
I'm licking it.
What are you licking?
Look.
This way.
You're starting to get it.
Yeah.
I'm starting to get it.
You're starting to get it.
I can see it clearly.
Oh, no.
Oh, that's so cute!
Wow, you're making a lot of toys.
We made a lot of toys, too.
This one, this one.
All of your body is our toy, okay? Do you understand?
You're going to keep playing with toys until the end, right?
I can do it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you feel good, Chimpo?
Yes, I do.
You can do it, Mo-chan!
You're doing great.
You can do it, Chimpo.
You can do it, Mo-chan.
You're doing great.
Do you want to go out with me?
I want to go out with you.
You want to go out with me, don't you?
I really want to go out with you.
It's raining a lot these days.
Why are you holding back?
When are you going to hold back?
I want to go out with you.
You really want to go out with me, don't you?
What should I do?
I'm going to give you a lot of it.
Oh, my God.
It's not good if you don't give me a lot of it.
Give me a lot of it.
What's wrong with you?
It's coming out.
Your muscles have shrunk a lot.
Amazing.
It's all coming out.
You put up with it too much.
I can smell something.
This is bad.
Oh my god.
It's coming out.
It's amazing.
It's not too much, is it?
It's coming out a lot.
It smells bad.
Does it smell bad?
It's amazing.
Oh my god.
It's cute.
It's really good.
I'm not licking you!
I'm licking you!
You're weak!
You're not eating well!
My team won!
Are you going to do it again?
Because it's still hard.
How is it?
But it's over today.
It's an interesting day.
I'll play with you next time.
Until then, eat a lot.
Give it to me.
Let go of my hand.
Let go of my hand!
It's hot!
It's delicious.
Don't push me away.
Cheers!
Let's drink!
It's so good!
I'm about to get drunk.
I'm getting dizzy.
Me too.
I'm always dizzy.
You brought a good girl today, didn't you?
That's right.
You can choose the girl you like.
What kind of girl?
You haven't tasted it yet, have you?
I haven't tasted it yet.
I'm curious about that.
Shall we taste it?
Do as you like
You've been looking forward to it, haven't you?
What should we do?
For that...
You're waiting like a pervert, aren't you?
I'm sitting
You're so cute
Why are you so nervous?
What color do you like?
What color?
Red?
It's black, isn't it?
It's a color of passion.
What color do you like?
Black?
It's a color of passion.
What color do you like?
Who is it?
Look at this face.
Even though I'm doing this,
this child is so thin.
It's true.
It's so funny.
It's so thin.
Amazing.
The shape of the penis is clear.
That's great.
It's so embarrassing.
This is so funny.
The veins are all cut off.
It's so funny.
I can see the shape of the organ.
Look, look, look.
It's moving.
Does it feel good?
It's going to go away if you rub it like this.
It's really embarrassing if it goes away like this.
That's right.
Can you hold it in?
It's getting bigger than before.
I can see your legs. Can you open your legs a little bit?
Oh!
Gintama, this is...
It's crazy.
What about you, Nari?
Oh, I like Gintama more than my butt.
If there's a hole, you'll want to put it in.
I know, I know.
It's really disgusting to dress like this.
You're the same, aren't you?
But you're excited, aren't you?
You're going to step on the ball, aren't you?
I'm going to step on it, too.
I'm going to sleep on your butt.
You're going to lose your head.
I'm glad you have eyes.
I bought a new one.
How is it?
It's very puffy.
I wonder if I can taste it.
How is it?
The reaction is good, isn't it?
I'm nervous and sweating.
Who do you want?
I want you.
I'm glad you're okay.
Don't spill it.
Here, drink it.
I'm glad you're okay.
It's delicious.
Me too.
Open your mouth.
Straight to the back of your throat.
You're waiting for it.
You can't open it, Gokkun.
It's so good.
Open your mouth.
Wow, it's so good.
Don't spill it.
Drink it all.
Thank you for the food.
It's so good.
Your face is so cute.
It's so cute, isn't it?
Can I take off this nipple?
Please don't.
Don't take it off.
It's so wrinkly.
You're only playing with your nipples.
I feel like my panties are going to be torn.
It's going to be a big mess.
Is it going to be like this just with the nipples?
Do you want me to give you a hug?
I'm going to bully you a lot.
I'm going to give you a hug.
Do you want it?
You don't want it?
No, I don't want it.
It's so good!
Why are you so sad?
You should get involved with me too.
Me too.
Don't look at me like that!
What's going on?
You look like you're going to puke!
I'm going to make you puke for real.
That's funny!
You can go to heaven.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, you're having fun, aren't you?
You're having fun, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
What did you do?
You look so happy.
You look like a pervert.
Your face is all red.
Do you want more?
I want more.
I love you.
You want me to hold you?
I'll hold you with my hands.
I thought you were this way, but you're this way.
What is this?
Why are you rubbing your body?
Your nipples are so hard.
How do I do it?
I'll make your nipples round.
Did you ever get attacked by three people at the same time?
That's great.
I can't breathe.
I'm going to die.
What's wrong with you?
You rubbed it and it got on your face.
It got on my face?
You must have been excited.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
It's your fault.
What's going on?
Oh no.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
It's so hot!
It smells so good.
It's in the broth.
Stop it.
It smells so good from the bottom.
It's so good.
It looks so good.
It looks delicious.
It's hot.
It's getting hot.
It's amazing.
There are a lot of genies in here.
It's so big.
Don't you want to see the hole in the butt?
I want to see it.
You want to see it, don't you?
It's okay. Don't move.
I can see the whole thing.
It's okay.
Wow, look at her. She doesn't drink at all.
She doesn't drink at all.
Is it good?
I'm going to rub your nipples.
Look.
Wow.
There's a lot of it.
Look.
She's rubbing her nipples.
It's amazing that she's rubbing her nipples.
It looks delicious.
How does it feel?
I'm so embarrassed.
It's so embarrassing.
What's so embarrassing?
It's like you're chasing after yourself.
You're chasing after yourself.
Oh, no!
I like this kind of thing.
Me too.
I brought a good one.
You can do whatever you want with it.
I like it a lot.
It's fun.
It's a cute bed.
It's like a car with a tight neck.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
I feel good.
Let's take a picture together.
You are so cute.
You are so clumsy. What are you going to do to me?
I will pick you up.
Look at me.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm starting to want to put it in.
I'm starting to want to put it in, too.
I'm going to put it in.
See?
It's okay, isn't it?
You're not going to put it in?
No?
I'm going to put it in, too.
I've been holding back.
I was trying to do it right away.
Just a little bit.
It's getting hot.
You can put it in your favorite bowl.
That's good.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I can do a lot of things with this.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
You have a really big face. Are you okay?
I'm in trouble.
Please touch my head.
My neck is getting really stiff.
It feels so good!
Don't be like that!
I like your nipples, you know.
Ah, it feels good.
You like it, right?
Yes, I like it.
Really?
I feel like I'm holding something.
That's how it feels.
It's coming out.
Amazing!
How does it feel?
It feels like I'm on a mission.
I feel like I'm on a mission.
It's amazing.
I can't do this.
It hurts!
I'm in trouble!
Amazing!
It feels so good.
It's my turn now.
My head is spinning.
Look at this.
I'm going to put a little bit of this powder in here.
I'm going to put it in here.
No, don't put it in.
I'll give you a massage on your back, okay?
Look.
It feels so good.
You're eating a lot.
Your back is so sexy.
Isn't it nice?
You can't resist, can you?
You're still doing it.
This is my baby.
He's playing with it.
He's looking at me.
Just a little bit.
Which one do you like?
I can't do it.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wow, wow, wow.
This side is amazing too.
Your fingers are all in there.
Wow, wow, wow.
No, no, no, no.
What, does it feel good?
Does it feel good to be treated like a pervert?
It feels good.
I want to go too.
I'm about to cry.
It feels so good.
I want to go too.
Let me go.
I want to go.
I can't do it.
I can see the hole in your butt.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't see it.
It's amazing.
It's white.
What are you looking at?
I can't tell which one you're looking at.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
You two were looking at me, weren't you?
I'm going to do it in a different style.
You're in a great mood right now.
Wait a minute.
Don't come in.
I'll do it.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do it.
It's hard.
That's good.
That's so nice!
You put it on earlier, didn't you?
It's nice, isn't it?
I want to try it on my husband.
You can't put it on your husband because it's too tight.
I like it too.
Is it tight?
It's nice, isn't it?
It feels good.
Yes, it is.
It's definitely a good one.
It's amazing.
Hold it.
It feels good.
It's nice.
Chikubi, you look like a baby.
That's true.
You're too strong.
Chikubi, you look like a baby.
I don't want to talk about this.
It feels good.
You moved your hands.
Ah, it's going in, it's going in.
Ah, amazing, amazing.
It's going in, it's going in.
Ah, it's going in, it's going in.
You can do it!
Amazing!
Look, look, look!
You can do it!
Amazing!
I can't take it anymore.
It's like a waterfall.
It's so warm.
Come here.
Are you going to take a bath?
No, I'm not.
You're going to take a bath, right?
No, not yet.
I thought you were going to take a bath.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
Really?
Come here.
Come here too.
Yes, yes.
Come here.
Nose, nose.
Make it flat.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
Wow, wow, wow.
Follow me, follow me.
Don't move, don't move.
Come on, come on.
Ah, I can't stop it!
It's amazing.
It's gone.
It's going to come out.
I've never done this before.
Why are you doing this?
I went home.
Stop it.
You can't do that!
I don't want to!
What is it?
You look like you like it.
It feels good.
Here, here.
It's good, isn't it?
It feels really good when you do that.
You are so serious.
It feels good.
I can't do this anymore.
How many times do you want to go to the hospital?
Why?
You didn't bend your back, did you?
I want you to heal me.
What?
What about my part?
Look at me.
What did you do?
I'm sorry.
No way.
There's a lot of them.
Really?
Wow, there's a lot.
Wait a minute.
I can't believe it.
If we keep it like this, we won't have any left.
It's gone.
I'm so happy.
I want you to give me a lot.
I still have some left.
Give it to me.
I can't do it.
I'll put it in properly.
I'm sorry.
She's grumbling.
Oh, that's amazing.
Look, look, look, look, look.
The butt.
Can you do it?
She's grumbling.
Look.
Oh, that's amazing.
Oh, my God.
Oh my god!
How did you do that?
It feels so good!
Oh my god!
It hurts!
There's so much in there!
I don't want to do this!
You guys are so mean!
Wait a minute!
Yes, that's right.
Let her go.
It's so nice.
There's a lot coming out.
Don't stop it.
I'll hold it for you.
It feels good.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, why are you doing this to me?
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't know what to do.
I'm just messing with you, you know?
See?
Does it feel good?
Which one feels better, Chin-Po or Anaru?
Don't touch me!
It's so hard!
I can't do this anymore!
It's coming out!
It smells like ramen!
That's right.
I hope you'll get used to it soon.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to give you a voice.
You're making a weird noise.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry. I can't hold it in.
Why did you stop?
Sit down. Sit down.
Stretch your legs. Stretch your legs.
Wow.
Look closely.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's going to come out.
What's going to come out? It's not done yet.
I'm sorry. It's going to come out.
What's going to come out?
I don't know.
Do you want more?
Yes.
I see.
You can't enjoy it if it comes out too soon, can you?
I'm sorry.
This is amazing.
Ah, it's so good.
It's good, isn't it?
It makes such a great sound.
I'll shake your hips as much as I can.
Don't cry.
Hey, give me more.
Give me more.
You'll come out, right?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Give me more.
I can't believe this is happening.
I think I'm going to puke.
I feel so good.
There are so many.
This is the last one, right?
Wow, you're still going to be able to come out, aren't you?
Yes, I'm still constipated.
I can't do it anymore.
It's because you're constipated that you can't come out.
Let's do it little by little.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it anymore.
Ah, I can't do it.
It's okay, you can do it.
Ah, it's amazing.
Ah, I can't do it.
Hurry up.
I can't do it.
I'll rub your butt.
Ah, I can't do it.
This is bad.
I can't do it.
It's going to come out!
What's going to come out?
It's going to come out again!
Oh no!
It's so hard!
Wow!
It's coming out!
It's coming out a lot!
Wow!
It's coming out!
It's still coming out.
It's amazing.
Look.
It's still coming out.
Don't raise that shoulder.
Be quiet.
Step on it.
It's still coming out.
Let it out more.
This one did a good job.
It's been a long time since I've done this.
How about this much?
That's right.
It was fun.
It's a good toy, isn't it?
I'll bring it again.
If you look forward to it, I'll bring it, too.
Me, too.
Yay!
Let's have fun.