I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? I'm not scared.
How are you?
It smells good.
Oh, are you crying?
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe I'm going to cry.
Have you been selected to monitor a new app?
A timer app?
If you use this app, can you stop time?
How to use it...
Activate this app and...
Stop and shout...
Stop!
What?
No way!
It really stopped!
When you want to move it,
you shout, move!
Amazing!
What can I do?
It's about to start.
You can't do it.
No, no, no, no.
When did you make it?
It's like this in a boys' high school, isn't it?
Excuse me.
Are you a student here?
You're not allowed to stand here.
Yes.
You're suspicious.
No, no.
Who are you?
What's wrong with you?
You're so suspicious!
Stop it!
I'm going to steal your cute handkerchief.
I wonder if there's a man in the men's room.
I don't know if I can do this.
Shall we start?
Please be quiet.
I'm going to be in charge of the class.
I'm Meguri, a temporary teacher.
What?
What about the teacher?
Oh, the teacher...
Oh, I wrote it down because I wasn't feeling well.
What?
First, I'll take the attendance.
When I was asked for my name,
Even if I touch him, he won't move at all.
I don't know what to do.
Well, then.
Everyone's day.
I wonder if I can observe your cute day.
I really stopped.
I wonder if he can't move.
He's out.
I'm still not excited enough.
He's got a little skin on.
Sato-kun, you're eating a lot.
Just like that.
Stand up straight.
See? You moved a little bit.
You're working out seriously.
You're so cute.
You're so cute, Gomo-chan.
You look like you're in good shape.
Ouch!
You stink.
You smell like you're going to die.
Even your butt.
You're so plump, Gomo-nee.
Oh, Kimura-kun's chinko is good, isn't it?
Oh, Meda-kun.
You have a strong pectoralis major.
A high school boy.
Oh, I'm naked.
You have a lot of gyarandu.
The glue is sticking to my hair so well.
I think this garland is connected to my penis.
Which one? Which one? Which one?
This is my favorite shape.
When I do this, I get excited.
When I look at such a fresh person close to me, my body gets hot.
Oh, Ueda-kun.
I wonder if my blood is getting stronger than before.
Even though my body is stopped, I wonder if I can hear my voice properly.
I wonder if you can hear my voice.
You can hear my voice, right?
I just touched it a little bit.
More and more.
It's becoming a right angle.
90 degrees. This is 90 degrees.
I can see it clearly.
Sato-kun's penis is bigger than mine.
As usual, I'm standing up all the time.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
I get nervous when I'm surrounded by the kids.
I want to be able to observe everyone's behavior.
I want to feel good.
The sound is so good.
Oh, the golden egg.
It looks like there's a lot of sage in it.
I want to lick it.
I want to make it.
I don't want to. Manjiru came out.
Manjiru
I'll give it to you.
I wonder if I'll give it to Manjiru.
I don't want to. Manjiru came out a lot.
You're so cute.
I'm starting to feel better.
I saw everything.
I can't stop.
I'm jealous.
I'm going to be a teacher.
I have a lot of things to do in the future.
I just tried it and it felt good.
It's the best.
My manko is dirty.
Well, Iko-chan.
Everyone.
Oh no! Ueda-kun, your tongue is sticking out.
Why are you sticking out your tongue?
I wonder if I can clean my dirty dog with my mouth.
I wonder if I can have you clean it up with my own hands.
Your lips are so soft.
You have a lot of flesh, Satou-kun.
I can feel my clitoris being stimulated by these two thick lips.
Wow, it feels so good.
Next is Ueda-kun, who is looking forward to it.
Was it Kimura-kun? I forgot.
Who is it?
Haru-kun?
Why are you putting your tongue out?
You're so mean.
You smell like my mean baby.
I want to make you feel better.
I'm so ticklish.
I'm going to pass out.
What should I do?
I can't stop crying.
I've been waiting for you.
What is it?
Here.
I've been waiting for you.
Manco.
It's so hot.
It's so warm.
It feels so good.
My man-jiru is all over the place.
Please take it in your mouth.
I'm going to take a picture of you guys.
I want to take a picture of all of you guys.
I want to do it.
I can't do it.
I used a lot of my hips, so I'm sweating a lot.
It smells so oily.
It smells so sour.
I think I'm sweating the most.
My forehead is sweating so much.
It smells so good.
It stinks.
I don't know what to do with my face.
It smells like men right now.
I don't want to do this.
Shin, why are you working out with no underwear?
Hey, why?
It's smelly.
See, I'm not wearing any underwear.
The smell of sweat soaked into the jersey.
The smell of sweat and the smell of this little sweat, it's so smelly.
I want to take a look at my feet.
Too smelly.
I'm sweating so much that I'm drooling.
I'm going to take a lot of drool and drink it.
You're sweating a lot, aren't you?
You're all sweating a lot.
I'm going to get a lot of it.
I'm starting to get a little hot, too.
Hey, I'm back from the morning.
Let's take a bath together.
What a great view.
In my case, I'm going to play with my sweaty, smelly t-shirt.
Look.
I'm being played with.
Like this.
I don't like it.
I got stung in the nipple.
It feels so good.
I'm starting to miss other cats.
Hey, you.
Ah, wait a minute.
It smells so bad.
How is it?
Show me.
You have to take off your underwear.
I'm going to take off my pants.
Oh my god.
Why?
Why did you make me stiff while I was working out?
You're so handsome.
That's good. You have a lot of power, Jinpo.
What do you think, Jinpo?
Oh, my God.
It's so sour!
I'm going to use my waist
I don't want to
I can't see
I can't open my arms and spread them out like this.
I look like a baby, don't I?
I look so mean.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't move.
Oh, my God!
I can't take it anymore.
What are you doing?
Your gimbap?
It stinks!
You're such a thief!
Your gimbap!
Oh, it's so good.
It's so good.
So good.
I love it.
I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore.
Ow!
You too. You can feel better now, okay?
My chest is getting harder and harder.
It's getting harder and harder.
What? What? I'm going to get tired and come out, right?
Hey, it's getting harder and harder.
Hey...
Oh, I'm sorry I left you.
Oh, that's amazing.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you Pai-sensei!
Well then...
Move!
What's wrong?
Where's the health care worker?
I need to take a break.
I'll be right back.
He seems to be in a bad mood.
Please let him rest.
Is that so?
What?
It's nothing.
Let's go to bed.
Let's rent a bed.
Yes.
Then lie down on the bed here.
Are you okay?
You're on a date after school, aren't you?
I was going to go to her house for the first time today.
Are you going to graduate from the same school as me?
I said I didn't have parents.
I said I wouldn't be able to do it, so maybe that's what will happen.
Oh, it's not good if you're late for the time being.
I hope you get better.
Stop.
Stop it!
Here you go.
This is the first time I've experienced this kind of bust.
It's a waste.
I'll steal your bust.
You're really my type.
Which one? Where?
Where's the bottom?
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's so annoying.
Oh, it's getting longer and longer.
The next one is from Dotei.
It's this sticky one.
I'm going to take a good look at your body.
I didn't get to eat it, but I have to eat it first.
It has a very clear shape.
It's a good shape.
I like the other faces, but I also like Chinko.
I'm going to be a type of Chinko.
It's so good.
Which one? Which one? Which one?
The curry is so crispy and looks so good.
It looks so good.
I don't know what to do.
I want to swallow it all up in one gulp.
This is so disgusting.
Can you look at me for a second?
Move!
What are you doing?
Stop!
I can't do this anymore.
I'm going to ask you to make me feel better.
You can see it from there, right?
You can see it, right?
Don't you think so?
This is a girl's egg.
Look at this nasty mouth.
I'm going to do it with my mouth.
I'm going to put a lot of this on my face.
Look, look.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
If time stops, will I be able to say I love you?
I'm so happy.
Hey, you like him, don't you?
You like him, don't you?
This way, please.
You look so happy.
You're so cute.
Wait a minute.
I want you to do it more comfortably.
Here.
It hurts.
I can't do this.
My fingers hurt so much.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's do this.
I don't want to.
You can't see my sexy anal-marumie, can you?
I'm so excited.
My index finger is growling.
I can't do this anymore...
Why does it get so weird?
I'm starting to get a cramp.
If I put my finger in the egg, it gets a cramp.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, let's get married, okay?
I want to be with you.
Don't leave me.
You're my first baby.
You're a baby, aren't you?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I got you, so I won't let go of you anymore.
I won't let go of you anymore.
Just like this. Just like this.
From the back. From the back.
Look at your friends properly.
Just like this.
Mom, stop it.
I'm going to do it in 10 steps.
You can't do it anymore, can you?
You have to do it well.
I don't want to do this. I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
It's painful.
Look. I want to feel it more.
Look. It's sticky.
My nipples are sticky.
What's wrong with my nipples?
It hurts.
I was trying to run away, but I can't run away anymore.
Move!
Okay.
I can't run away, can I?
I want to move on.
I have to take care of myself.
I'm watching you from behind.
I'm watching you from behind, my friends, and I'm feeling good.
I'm so nervous.
I can't take it anymore.
I want to see it for a little while.
Please look at it for a little while.
Please look into your friend's eyes.
It's annoying.
I'm sorry.
It's a shame that I'm not your first girlfriend.
If you have a child, I'll take responsibility for it.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to take a picture of you and your girlfriend.
Don't move.
Please forgive me.
I'll take a picture of you and your girlfriend.
I'm going to put Seiji in it, too.
Pose.
Make sure you smile.
That's good.
Let's take a picture together.
Chinpo and Seiji and me.
Like this.
That's how it is.
Then I'll have to send this to my girlfriend.
I wonder if it's this one.
Send.
I've sent it.
I'm sorry, my girlfriend.
I can't believe it.
Look at this.
It's about to start.
It's a new anime.
It has big boobs.
It's super cute.
I'm going to marry an anime character.
That doesn't make any sense.
What are you talking about?
What is it?
It's not good to escape reality.
It's not a good thing.
I'll teach you how good Nami is.
I'll teach you how to do it.
Do you watch anime all the time?
What are you looking at?
Oh, you can't do that.
The two-dimensional world?
That's right.
The two-dimensional world...
doesn't come close like this, does it?
I wonder if my sister's boobs have been hit.
The boobs are big, right?
I like big boobs.
You like it, don't you?
It's raw meat, so you can touch it.
It's soft.
You can touch a lot.
When I thought I'd never see a woman again,
I just touched my boobs and it got so stiff.
It's all gone now, isn't it?
I wish I could...
...taste the freshness of a woman.
It's gone.
It's my real boobs.
My real boobs are falling off.
And my nipples too.
They're bulging out.
Can you tell?
How is it?
It's bulging out.
I'll show you a little bit more.
Show me a little bit more.
Don't move your body.
Look at your knees.
Stand on your knees as they are.
I love your boobs.
Look at your face.
You love your boobs, don't you?
I love your boobs.
I'm sorry.
Please puff more.
Puff, puff.
Do you want me to do it for you?
I'll do it properly with my mouth.
I love you.
Big boobs.
Move!
I think I'm going to go to bed now.
I don't know what to do.
It's amazing.
My body is so fresh.
It's so big.
I don't know how to say it in Japanese.
How does it feel?
It's my first time.
It's so warm.
This is called a breast breast.
Look at this.
I think this is the inside of a mango.
I want you to feel good.
I'll wrap you in a mango.
I feel like my nipples are being sucked into my boobs.
I want to be more comfortable.
You want to feel good, don't you?
It's okay to feel good.
It's a place where your boobs feel good.
My boobs are so tight.
I don't like my nipples.
I can feel my nipples moving, too.
It's too bad. You want to see it, don't you?
You want to see what's going on with your nipples, don't you?
Then I'll show you.
Move!
No!
It's better to be in the 2nd dimension!
What are you talking about?
You can't do that!
Don't make me feel good!
It's better to be in the 2nd dimension!
If you're so flustered...
See?
This is what you've become.
It's okay.
It's so smelly, look at it.
It's so gross.
The body of a virgin.
It's so sticky.
What should I do?
From now on, I'm going to be with a girl named Namami.
It's going to be so nice.
Look.
Let me see.
Move.
What are you doing?
Are you stupid?
I'm going to do something with your breasts.
I'll teach you how to do it.
Actually, let's have sex.
What?
Really?
Yes.
Okay, let's go upstairs.
Okay.
Take off your pants.
Stand up.
Sensei.
This is not a joke.
I didn't do it.
Sensei, let's do it for the last time.
What do you think?
Sensei is always shy.
I want to get pregnant with everyone's baby!
Let's go!
I really can't stop.
Move!
I can't move right now.
I want to do whatever I want to do.
I'm going to do it for you.
You have a thick chin.
Don't you want to pinch me?
It's not like that, is it?
You've been looking at my boobs all the time, haven't you?
At the very front seat.
You know that, don't you?
I brought it for you.
You're going to react, aren't you?
Then, this is...
It's getting bigger and bigger.
What are you moving?
Can you move your body a little bit?
You are such a sexy girl
Chikubi is so cute.
It's so good.
This is it.
It's my favorite.
It's so good.
I'm going to pee.
Look.
Look at my feet.
I'm going to pee.
I don't know if I'll be able to do it.
I'm going to get a new pair of jeans.
I have to know more about women's bodies.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You love me, don't you?
I want to look at you, don't you?
I can do it!
I can't do this anymore.
Wait a minute.
It's so embarrassing.
Which one?
Which one, which one?
All of them.
Awww
I'm such a human being.
Please put me in your belly.
I don't know what to do.
I can't do this anymore.
Wait a minute.
It's so hard.
But I'm still in the middle of a sex education, so what should I do?
Do you want to put it in raw? Do you want to put this on?
You want to put it in raw, don't you?
This is what I prepared for you.
This is a good one.
There's a back and a front.
I have a lot of things to do.
Let's go to the teacher's room.
Do you want to put it in?
Give it to me.
I want to see it, but I can't see it.
I'm going to take this condom off, isn't it?
I'm going to take it off, aren't I?
You like it raw, don't you?
I like it raw, too.
Then, wait a minute.
This is better.
I feel like I'm having a hard time with my hands.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
It feels good.
Chimpo-chan, you're doing great.
You're doing great.
Look at the back of your head.
Chimpo-chan, you're doing great.
Chimpo-chan, you're holding my hand all the time.
It's weird, isn't it, Jinpo?
It's about time...
Move!
No, no, no!
I don't like this, everyone.
It feels good, doesn't it?
When you feel good, what do you say?
Move!
You're still going, aren't you?
Hey, you were about to leave, weren't you?
See?
It's no good, isn't it?
It's your turn, Ueda-kun.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ueda-kun, let's go.
I want to put my feet in the water.
Please.
I can't believe I'm doing this all by myself.
I'm so tired.
I feel like I'm going to pass out.
I'm going to do this properly.
I think I'm going to have to add some more
I'm going to have to add some more
I'm going to add some more
I don't have it, so please give it to me.
I want it.
Please give it to me.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'm getting old, aren't I?
Do you want a baby?
Come on...
You want a baby?
I want a baby.
Let's get married.
If you get married, you'll feel good every day.
You can do it.
I want a baby.
I can't do it.
I can't do this.
This is it.
It's too hard.
I can't do this.
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
Teacher!
It's dangerous!
It's okay!
You guys are full of spirit!
Look at everyone!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.