Thank you so much for joining us.
I'm excited to see how it will turn out.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It hurts, doesn't it?
My body is getting hot.
It's wriggling.
I'm going to do it on my own, you want to go to Komotsu, don't you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It must be nerve-racking.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're so naughty.
Your face is so wet.
It's ringing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to put this in your blood.
Oh, that's cool.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I can't do this.
It's so hot!
It feels so good!
The thunder is running in my stomach!
It's so hot!
Please let me stay longer!
Do you want it, Chimpo?
Yes, I want it.
Chimpo, I want it.
You've lost a lot of weight.
Here it is.
Wow, amazing.
Chimpo, give it to me.
Chimpo, show me.
You can use it as you like.
I can't help it because I want it.
I want it.
Oh
It's so cold.
It feels so good.
It feels so good!
Oh