So finally! Hi! How are you doing? I'm well. I have something for you. Oh, thank you. Oh, you're welcome. You know I love pineapple juice. Yes, from our, from our, from our, uh, from our conversations online. I remember that. Yes, oh my gosh, after all these years. Yes, wow. Finally meeting my pen pal in person. Oh my gosh, I can't believe it. How have you been?
pretty good I mean better now that I'm fine I finally get to see you in person
yeah how are you liking America uh-huh very very nice yeah it's really hot
right now so I don't know if you're used to that well you're very hot right no
hotter than the weather no definitely I'm I'm feeling the heat so what was you
know how are you feeling right now very hot it's very sunny outside I was
thinking maybe we could go somewhere else later on but for now this is fine I
have my pineapple juice I'm feeling cool down now thanks to you yes okay cheers
Tears to meeting?
Absolutely.
Boop.
Finally.
This tastes really good, might be useful for later.
So how is your mother and father doing?
They're doing well.
I wrote about them the last time, so you know, all the last drama and details, you know,
same old, same old.
They're doing good.
I just want to go visit them.
Are they a little bit better with the idea of you going out with an Asian man?
Um, still haven't brought that up yet.
No?
No.
It'll be our little secret.
How do you think they're gonna, well...
Well, they know that we're talking.
They know that I have a pen pal.
They just think you're teaching me another language.
Okay.
But they don't know the whole background story.
so yeah maybe once we hang out a little bit and get to know each other like in person
they'll understand a little more they just don't get it they wouldn't understand well
eventually we're gonna we may have to broach that subject you know we can talk about it more
somewhere else if you want oh i really love the bow on your hair so feminine thank you i kind of
of went a little over top today. No you didn't. I just wanted to be a little extra and look super
cute for you. And the color. Since it's like the first time meeting in person. And the colors that
you've chosen, oh they're just so feminine. Just wait until you see the underneath. It gets even better.
Uh-oh. Sounds like trouble already. Maybe. You're gonna have to find out for yourself. Well I guess all that time
that we spent talking on you know it is led up to this yes and I can feel the
tension in the air if you know what I mean the tension and the slight
nervousness oh I'm not nervous a bit I'm a little shy I'm raring to go well
we'll see how shy you are I don't know some I can get a little crazy sometimes
times but crazy's good crazy's good shy and shy in public crazy in private oh isn't there an
american song that goes something like um a lady in the street and a freak in the sheets oh for
sure something like that that's definitely that describes me perfectly oh melody the freak i'm
intrigued yeah you only know me for my letters you don't know me in real life yeah well
your letters that certainly certainly certainly have things heated up at this
point I mean it's like boiling well well I was thinking maybe we should go
someplace a little bit more private like back to my back to my place yeah
Yeah, whatever you want to do.
I am so hot out here right now, honestly.
Like, long sleeve was not the move.
I actually rented a house, a really nice place not too far from here.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
All right, let's do it.
Let's go.
Yeah, okay.
Want to take me?
Pardon?
Yes, absolutely.
Let's go.
I love it.
It's so cozy.
Glad you like it.
Very neat.
So now we're going to take these pictures so when we go back home, we have something to remind me of.
Aw, sweet.
To get together.
I would love that. Yes, okay. Do you like my outfit today?
Of course I do.
Okay.
Hope you enjoyed lunch.
Oh, I did. It was good.
I'm going to love this little feminine outfit you have.
Thank you.
Okay, look back at me.
Let me see those eyes.
There you go.
Thank you.
Okay.
Ditch the purse.
Get rid of the purse.
Goodbye, purse.
Okay, Melody.
Let's get a little bit more, a little more provocative.
We've done quite a bit.
You want to remember me in other ways?
Oh yes, we've built quite a bit of tension going on between us, all this time we've been corresponding.
It's time to move things up to the next level, don't you think?
I hope your mind is going.
Oh my gracious. You never sent me any pictures like that. Oh my gracious.
Oh
This is what you were asking for
You would like that though
Okay. Should I take the shirt off first?
Why don't you just tease me a little bit? Can I see one of your nipples?
Maybe. Are you going to beg me?
Hmm?
Do you want it? How bad do you want it?
Very badly.
Hmm.
Come on.
Do you want to say please?
Please. Pretty please.
You never got pictures of them, but seeing them in person is pretty good too, huh?
It's better.
Just tuck these strings in.
There.
You can have a lot of naughty photos to look back on.
I'll bend you over for me, Melody.
Hands on the couch.
Yeah.
You know what this is.
Are you awake?
Oh my gracious,
these are gonna be great pictures back home.
More imagination.
Oh, this is like a good stretch.
This is a good angle.
You have to get a few, a few different shots.
Stay on it.
Get back down there.
All these pictures of you can be kind of really horny.
Not kind of, yeah.
Yeah, standing naked in front of you for the first time.
It's kind of weird.
Yeah, right.
It's kind of weird me not being the only naked one.
I'm just saying.
Okay, well, we can fix that.
Yeah, that would help you take your shirt off
while you take pictures of me.
Mm-hmm.
It might help me a little bit.
Right.
Give you some motivation.
Okay.
Don't be so nervous.
See, you didn't need that.
Definitely the motivation you needed.
Well, how do we take this
to the next level?
I was waiting for you to say something like that.
All right.
All right, to the next step, next level.
Yeah, let's get a little more explicit.
Why don't you touch yourself?
Okay, let me see.
Yeah, open up for daddy.
There you go.
There you go, there you go.
My pussy's already so wet.
I hardly start touching myself.
Open your lips up with both hands, there you go.
Oh yeah, let's see that beautiful pinkness inside.
Oh my gracious, that's wonderful.
Oh yeah.
Let's get a close-up of that, all right?
Oh, I feel good now.
Oh my gracious, look up in there.
Do you want me to open up your hand?
Open your legs so we can see that landing strip.
Oh yeah, there you go again.
Daddy, where are my hands?
What do you want me to do?
Daddy's down on the couch.
Okay. Yeah, at least this way.
Hold one of your breasts up, let me see.
There you go, right there.
Get some rear action going on here.
There you go.
Don't look at me.
Head down, ass up.
Face me.
Feel your eyes on me.
I see that face.
It's so hot.
You're wearing way too much clothes.
Okay.
I think I need to help you take them off.
Well, go for it.
Yeah.
These are going to be some good photos for later.
I'm kind of nervous.
Wait, can I touch it?
Of course.
I'm asking after the fact, but this is what you've been waiting for, oh shit, I think
I think it's time to put that camera down.
Not before you kiss down the legs of it.
I wanna go somewhere more private.
Where's your bedroom at?
Okay, so let's go.
The two of us.
My little blonde princess.
I feel so good.
Making me tear up.
I'm gonna scoot back a little bit.
I
They look so full and ready for me to train.
I want to drain them all into your pussy
I know it's exactly what you want
Like I'm making a mess
oh shit oh god oh oh oh fuck oh shit oh my god oh you're gonna make me lose it too soon i don't
want to blow it in your mouth yeah i want it in your pussy right now i want it right in your hole
I want to taste that pussy first.
I want to taste where that cum is going.
Oh, you're going to tease me now?
That's not fair.
I got you.
That tickles.
I need to see your skills.
Oh, you're such a tease.
Mmm, you're making my legs shake already.
I love your little brush.
Oh, you love it?
Yeah, you can tug on it if you want.
Oh my god, no one's ever done that to me before.
That feels nice.
Mmm, you smell wonderful.
Mmm, thank you, Daddy.
I hate you.
Fuck.
Mmm, you taste wonderful also.
Oh my god, you're so dirty.
I'm perfect.
Hold your lips apart, baby.
Yeah.
Explode your clit.
I want you to pull the hood back.
Show me your clit.
It's so tight.
It's okay.
Oh, you are such a tease.
Oh, fuck.
Multitasking
I like that
I feel so good
Yeah
Just worship my pussy
Make love to it with your mouth
Fuck
Oh fuck
Oh, you can't just tease me with your fingers all day.
Calm down.
You're just hitting all the right spots, and I can't control my legs or my body right now.
Oh, fuck!
Is that your cervix, baby?
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh my god, that beat me way ahead.
What are you going to do to me now?
Daddy, will you take my shoes off?
I'll help you with this one.
My toes are ticklish.
Oh god, that both of them.
I'm so heavy.
Oh, fuck.
Please stop teasing me.
Please, I'm begging you.
Please put it inside my pussy.
You're going to be a good girl?
Yeah.
You're going to do everything I tell you to do?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I know.
Uh.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Make love to my pussy.
Yeah.
Yeah, shove your cuck to me, I'm sorry.
I just want to make your cuck feel good.
Oh, oh fuck, oh god, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I cleaned up just for you.
Yeah, use my pussy.
Listen, listen, listen.
I know you want to feel good.
I know you just want to use my cute little body.
Just make your cock throw a mess out of me.
I'm just using you.
I'm just your little toy today.
Just for you to use and play with.
Your little doll.
Your cum dumpster.
anything you want
yeah
does it feel good baby
yeah you love this pussy
yeah you need it
yeah
oh my god yes
oh
yeah just look at it
look at it sliding in my pussy
yeah oh I can feel
all the wet juices oh my god dripping out of my pussy every thrust you make it's so hot
i'm getting wetter every thrust
Oh, they're so sensitive when I'm horny, oh, I'm coming back for seconds, ah, ah, yeah,
Yeah, that's right. That's right.
Not just how to use me.
Oh, I like this. I like where this is going.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, no, yes, that's right, yes, that's right, yes, I'm going to taste all my sweet juices,
yeah, all because of you, making me so crazy, you know what I mean, yeah, yeah, yeah, for
your cock, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, please let me ride your cock,
I need to run your clock, please, please, please.
I can't stand this.
I need more than your fingers.
I got you so big.
Oh, fuck. Oh shit. Oh, oh this pussy's killing me. Oh fuck
fun to have still. Don't you want to thrust your cock inside? Oh god it feels so good wrapped around
around my cock. Oh my god you feel so good. Oh god. Oh shit. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh shit.
Too much I want you doggy style
Head down and ass up
What do we got here
What am I going into here
Look at that
You know what I've been thinking about lately?
What?
Two fat cocks stuffed inside of me.
Really?
Well, I have a buddy named Connor
that I may have to ask about that.
We may be able to arrange something, darling.
Are you gonna make my fantasies come true?
I just...
Oh, like...
I want you to be happy.
Yeah, I wanna show you the cocks.
I want you to explore all your fantasies.
Will you shove your cock in me, Daddy?
No, you'll get your you'll get my cock soon enough
Now put your head down like I asked you to ass up. Yeah, there you go
Be good for daddy, yeah, maybe I'll set you up with another dick
What you want?
Yeah.
Uh huh.
If I make you cum, a nice big fat load inside my pussy, will you make it happen?
Not right now.
Patience.
Bring that pussy to daddy.
Yeah.
Put an arch in your back.
I want to see that.
There you go.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Oh boy.
Oh my god.
You're such a tease.
mmm get that ass back up in the air get the arch in the back there you go there
you go oh how about if I just give you a big lip maybe the first inch is that
Is that okay?
Yeah.
You happy?
Get the first inch.
Oh my gosh, I'm trying to go and stay down.
that's what you want it right that's what you want it right
um oh my god it goes so deep and doggy i can't oh god
Oh
Get that dick
Closing what
What?
Toy, too.
And you can use my gift box toy, too.
Corrine, what's in my balls?
We can be each other's toys.
Yeah.
You're gonna get what's in my balls, too.
Oh, I want that ball.
You want that, right?
Yes, Daddy.
I want everything you want.
I wanna give you all the pleasure in the whole world.
Make your cup feel good every day.
I'm gonna come, I'm gonna come, faster, more, more, more, more, more, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh
Fuck oh
Yeah
oh fuck yes yes oh it's so good it's like it was made for me it was made to fit inside my
Do you like my pussy perfectly?
I'm your personal pussy pocket.
Oh, thank you.
mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
I just love teasing me and making me a mess yeah yeah yeah you know exactly how to use
your crook huh you like lots of practice huh yeah oh it's like you know all the right spots
Put it back in. Put it back in, mommy.
Oh, yeah. Oh, fuck!
Oh, God.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah, you're so fit. Oh, my God.
I know you love this pussy I can't wait till you're sharing it with someone it's gonna
be so much fun yeah can you imagine one cock stuffed in my pussy while the other one's
stuff down my throat it's very intriguing yeah i can't stop thinking about it like right now
i just want to put that cock in my mouth while you're fucking me
we're gonna work on making that happen for you little lady yes you do but first let's work on
on making your cut and draining your pulse.
Because I'm sure that's all you can think about right now.
I think I've got two loads for you tonight.
Oh, yeah.
My God, just watch that long,
my shaft going in and out of you.
Nice and slow out.
So slow.
Right to the tip.
And slow back in.
Ah, fuck.
Deep.
Oh, you feel so warm and wet.
Back out.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Make me drop my load.
Yeah.
Maybe I should stop then, huh?
Give me goosebumps.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Open your legs, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, fuck this pussy, I know you love this landing strip.
Yes, you better get a good close-up on it.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh, fuck!
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, this is just what we both needed,
huh, baby?
Yeah.
my legs just like that. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Yeah, nice and slow, baby. Nice and
I'm so sorry, mm-mm, ah, ah, mm, mm, ah, fuck, mm, mm, it's okay, ah, mm, ah, yeah, mm, ah, yes, yes, mm, yeah, ah, ah, ah, mm, ah, yes, yes, yes,
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Fuck. Yes.
That's a workout.
I'm sure it is.
Please give me a fat load of my pussy dye, I need it, I've been craving it all day, I've
been thinking about it this whole time you were traveling here, before I saw a young
person who's been dreaming about it. I just need to be filled up finally by you, you know
what it feels like? A clean white cone dripping out of my pussy. Please, please, please, please,
I need to feel it. I need to feel it inside me. I need to feel it flowing inside my pussy.
I need to feel it flowing inside me. Please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Yes, it does.
Okay.
Your pussy is so good, I don't think I've got another load for you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, back for a little bit.
Do you like that?
Yes, Daddy, please.
Okay.
Do I deserve it?
I don't know, do you?
I think I do.
I think I was a good girl.
Do I get my other gift too?
Stick it in. Give it in.
Right there, Daddy.
Give it in.
Yes. Yes, Daddy.
Oh my God.
Yeah, your skin's so soft and nice and muscular.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, just feel good, Daddy.
Use me as your little cum doll.
Yeah, your little cum dumpster.
Yeah.
Come all over me.
Make a mess of me.
Please, Daddy.
Please, please, please, please.
Please.
Please, please come home honey, please, I'm begging you, please, I need it, I need it, I need it more than you do, I need it more than your cock needs it, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Why is it like so shaky?
I feel good daddy.
Is it cuddle time?
Boy did we make a mess.
Good grief.
Come here, come there, come everywhere.
What do you want to do about it?
I guess we better get cleaned up.
Yeah?
Before another...
You drained me. I'm done.
Okay.
I'm done.
I just stepped in to come.
Wow, you made me a mess.
Look at me.
A mess.
That's my job.
I don't know how much cum is left in me, I tried to push it all out, but we'll see.
Oh my god.
A lot.
Oh fuck.
Oh wow.
Still going.
going. Oh, fuck. I'm trying. I don't think that's how this works. I think that's it,
it but that was quite a bit. Will you turn the shower on for me? Okay. Alright.
I need to get all this cum out of my fucking pussy and my body. I'm covered in it. I'm
so soft. It's like lotion. Natural lotion. You'll have to adjust the temperature yourself.
Is it?
Okay.
Good.
Like you.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh.
It's actually getting hot.
Okay.
Does that make it hot or cold?
It's turning to the left to make it more cool.
Ooh, it's so much.
Okay, maybe I need some of this.
Oh!
Get you cleaned.
Scrubbed up.
Gonna walk around smelling.
So sticky.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Me?
Yeah.
Tell me you don't love it.
It really is like lotion, but it's so soft.
There's more of where that came from.
Teasing you with my glistening wet body.
You've got to give me a chance to recover at least 24 hours clean.
Maybe, if you're lucky.
How can you resist this?
I'm going to lock you out of the dead room.
You wouldn't dare.
That's not fair.
We can't deny you did it.
Mixture, it's a mixture.
Perfect hand print.
Is that a mixture of us inside of your pussy?
Yeah.
It's so beautiful.
It is.
It's quite raw.
I'm telling you, you're not going to be able to resist me a few hours later when I'm begging you to get this pussy.
It's all swollen and red.
I'm going to have to get some help with you.
I'm going to be a bad girl.
Yes, always.
Naughty, naughty.
Who else would I be if not Melody Marks?
The naughty little slut.
I'm already getting ready for round two.
I'm going to get started now.
Oh no, a quirky girl.
And super wet, and not because of the shower.
You should.
Where's your friend?
Um, he's up a bit.
Yeah?
yeah yeah yes I did I told him about you know your that you're curious about you
know having some fun three of you know yes that's him okay okay slow down this
is very hot this is much so this is my pen pal that I told you about
like about two or three yeah something like that yeah and it's been a while we were like well you
finally have to come to america and yeah meet us john's a good guy yeah well i'm a very open-minded
man connor and um anything that's why we get along anything that anything that makes my my little my
little baby here happy i'm i'm more than willing to oblige pretty well i must say thank you how
How do you like her outfit?
Gorgeous.
You like that?
I like the colors, too.
Yes, I was going for extra today.
Right.
Yeah.
Black is my thing.
Yes.
Can I stand up?
Can I walk around a little bit?
Yeah, let's just walk around a little bit, for a bit.
Yeah, it's so nice out.
I just love letting the sun hit my face and stuff.
It's a little hot.
Yeah, well.
That's quite the attraction.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my gracious.
Chips.
We're definitely into glamour here, aren't we?
I think you outdid yourself on this one, Shawn.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
It's been so long.
It's all, there's a lot going on, like my ADD kind of kicks in a little bit.
Okay, I'm okay with heights.
It's the fear of falling.
Right.
It's like the feeling that you get as you fall.
That's why I can't do roller coasters. I was about to ask if we did roller coasters. I don't do them either.
I literally, if there was no railing here, I could lean back and feel fine.
I can't. I'm like, notice I'm keeping my distance here.
No. Don't be scared. There's glass. We're all safe here.
Okay. I trust you. Yes, trust me, Vinny.
Uh oh. I don't know about that.
That whole trust me thing. Hmm.
I don't think you guys have anything to worry about.
Remember what you got me into last year before she went for the kill. Um, yep, something like that
There we go again promises
Chong likes to play hard to get
Nice
I've been seeing a few little cute shops
Along our little walk and while we're getting to know each other
And I was wondering if we could stop in a little lingerie store and pick up something cute to put on for later
You do not need to ask us twice on that. Oh, yeah
so you agree let's that's a deal that's an absolute deal okay let's do it
all right let's uh let's just go to the let's head there like no need to fuck around yeah no
whatever next shop we see whatever one catches our eyes all right let's go up here then okay
we have to walk up the escalator yeah i know i'm lazy i'm a princess this is blasphemy this is
blasphemy what the heck also a really long escalator yeah this is yeah honestly i'm
suing i'm falling now yeah now we're suing yes i actually just went to the gym the past two days so
um yeah my thighs are already feeling it oh wow look at those guys oh yeah yeah
Yeah, I think.
We're going to find a shop eventually.
How did we even?
Oh, I see.
OK.
Pretty hot, huh, Sean?
Yes.
She's hot.
Oh.
Whoa.
Watch this one.
She's nothing but trouble.
How'd you find her?
Oh, well.
I hope I don't live to regret this.
I don't see how you possibly could.
I don't think you could.
You didn't say that last time.
I love your hair.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I wanted to tell another girl that I liked her dress, but I was too nervous.
I was like, I like your dress.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
Y'all are so cute.
I love your outfits.
Thank you.
I love love. I'm too friendly.
That's a good thing. You like to make friends.
I guess.
I mean, this is the place to make friends, right?
Apparently so. It's very friendly and outgoing. It's always good.
Fuck.
Could use some pineapple juice right about now.
Yeah.
Is that a Red Bull?
A functioning escalator.
Smell that Janja.
Careful.
These shoes are very sturdy.
Yeah, you got some actual sole support there.
Oh yeah, for real.
These are probably the comfiest pair of shoes I own.
Nice.
What do you think, Connor?
Do you think that she can handle both of us?
I don't know. She's pretty small, but yeah, she seems up to the challenge though. Honestly, I think I'll I think
Like I said before we have nothing
Yeah
That's pretty
Texas flag
Almost
Honestly, this is good for vacation, but I don't know how people live here. No, it doesn't seem very little
No, it doesn't seem very livable good place to visit. Yes. I would probably stay in
in an air-conditioned place most of the time but there's a uh but the heat does feel much better
than snow yes there's a lingerie shop right around here okay take the outfit there's a lot
of options in here i might have to get a few uh-oh what do you think
got a little sneak peek got something there
We'll get some of this cute red and black outfit and you'll wear me a doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly-doob
It doesn't seem to be focused.
Um...
Now it's serious.
You gotta press the button down
halfway, and it does that green thing.
Okay.
Finish following through with it.
You'll see the green thing pop up.
Yeah, right there.
Think we're in big trouble, Tom?
I think so.
I think we'll be alright.
You want to start teasing on the top?
Mm-hmm.
Whatever you want to start with.
Are you not wearing pants up there?
Maybe.
We might have removed them in the process.
It is hot.
It is a little hot.
That thing was boiling.
A little hot and bothered.
I'm a little hot and bothered myself.
My panties kinda got a little soaked.
Well, they don't work.
I had to remove them.
Poor you.
Should I get on the floor for a minute?
If you would, I'd stay ashore.
Yeah? Okay.
Very.
Yeah, let's see. Let's spread those lips.
How does it look?
How about let's see it?
Good enough to eat?
Stick that ass in here.
Look back at me again.
Can you see that pussy?
It's like foot in the way?
Yeah, pretty little pussy.
Oh yeah, landing strip is wonderful.
That gives me something to shoot for.
Yeah, some anal nose.
Oh man.
Get like an upward angle from the pussy up.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, he knows that from you.
Oh, yeah.
You got a finger in there?
Maybe if you're nice.
Alright, Connor, I'm gonna let you take over.
Alright, it's your challenge.
You can't handle it?
Yeah, I'll see if I'm up to the challenge.
Oh, my gracious.
Do you need to keep standing up?
More standing?
Yeah.
Okay, do you want me to take this?
Yeah, you start to use the top.
Oh, yeah, I'll use the top now.
Okay, tights the same height?
Mm?
These look good?
Yeah.
Okay.
Great tits.
Thank you.
I do them myself.
They are nice.
Oh.
I'm going to go ahead and just take that off, however.
You want to use it for me?
Um, I can totally do that.
Or Sean can do it.
Or Joey can do it.
Yeah, there you go.
Just the top, baby.
Yes, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
You want that also?
Not yet, not yet.
Okay.
I got it to you so far.
There's so much hair.
The hair's like Goldilocks or something.
There's a little red riding hood.
I'm gonna try and maybe do a thing.
I wanna be the big, bad wolf.
Okay, here, let's try this.
That looks good.
I see what you're going for.
I don't know.
Let's try to do a little mermaid look.
All right. You know?
Maybe a little more hair.
Is this going?
I don't know if it's long enough.
That's good.
Maybe a little more.
I like that.
It's a lot all over the shoulders.
Teasing off the skirt.
Yeah, now you wanna zip it for me?
Yeah. Mr. Impatient.
I don't know how you can be slow-poking and being patient.
Wow.
An inch lower, you've got a little more ass in there.
Have fun with this.
We've got a great camera.
We've got great friends here.
You've got a little more ass you could get in there, too.
I'll get stuck here.
You can proceed.
Grab those cheeks and open that for us.
What do you want?
Oh lord.
You looking this side?
Yeah.
Excited.
Alright, why don't you take it back over here, I'm going to get carried away.
I guess I want that back.
Thank you.
I'm moving my close up.
That does look...
Let's put it back at me.
Why not?
Okay.
Yeah, maybe I should just...
Yeah, if you're on the floor, you're like all the way in here.
That's good.
This is good?
Yes.
Do it on a horizontal.
Yeah.
You're going to stay like you are.
I'm going to go back this way.
I'm going to grab a few from this side, too.
That's good, too.
I feel bad I have lines from my panties, but I'm editing not too far.
Can you see my arms?
I can see it all.
Yeah.
Let me get like full-ended doggy.
Facing this way or facing towards you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This way too.
Do you want to put on an outfit, Mika?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, let's do that.
Where is that?
That one's right here.
I'll do you now.
Thank you.
Okay.
First, I need to take these off.
Oh boy, I should take the stockings off, huh?
They won't match.
They will not match.
We didn't get this through.
It's okay.
I assume it's the only stockings you have.
It's all right.
It's okay.
It won't survive.
Okay.
Okay, now, this may be the difficult part.
Let's figure this out together.
Okay, as you know, we just got this, so.
Yeah, not really, actually.
Wow.
Just elaborate, yeah, I'll put this in the camera.
I know, this is obviously where my
That makes sense.
Huge goes.
Right.
These go up on my hips.
Then the rest, these go through.
That's true. That's what the legs are. So pull that through, yep.
I'm fucking confused.
This is, yeah, this is...
This is, yeah, this is the top.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Okay, so this goes up here like this.
And then my leg goes into this part, like this, okay, I did it, all right, and my left
part goes in the back, this part goes in the back, this is so cute, I love it so much,
oh my god, oh, and then I put this on, like so, also, just to the other side, if I can
Okay.
Just like the other one.
Whoop, whoop.
Okay.
There you go.
Okay, okay.
All right, yeah.
Okay, now it's good.
I love this so much.
This one's a little more straightforward.
I think so.
I think you might need to help me with that as well, also.
Yeah, okay.
So I'm gonna put her here and her here.
Get my hair out.
I like all the help and all the hands on me.
The tightest one.
The tightest one?
Yeah.
I didn't want to squeeze it.
Oh, I want to be squeezed.
There's a lot of little strings going on.
Rhinestone camera.
Oh, yeah.
It feels so cute.
I'll take a few like photos of this.
Oh, of course.
I know it'd be wrong if you didn't.
It'd be blasphemy.
Oh, yeah.
Snap a few, Joe.
Sure.
I'm distracted.
I think we took so many cute photos already.
Are we ready to...
but are we getting impatient for something more?
Maybe.
Yeah, what do you have in mind?
Melody?
Something more active.
Oh, how much more active?
What are you talking about?
I think you know what I'm talking about.
Hey, Connor?
Yeah?
I think we got her warmed up.
All right, I think it's time to move on.
Bigger and better.
A little bit more...
Erotic?
Yes.
What is that little purring, moaning, kitty kitty sound coming out of you, Melody?
I think I'm getting a little tired of these photos and I want to do something a little
more active.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
No, I don't know what you mean. Why don't you tell me what you mean?
You want me to use my words?
Yes.
Well, I want to suck your big fat cocks right now.
And if you don't let me, I might just get really naughty.
And you guys won't be able to handle yourselves.
So, you can follow me, or you can keep taking photos of the pirates.
We should probably follow her, Sean.
Yeah, I think we will.
So, are you guys ready?
Are you ready?
I think so.
Are you sitting?
Are you guys going to help me?
Yeah, you might have to help us too.
Oh my god.
You weren't expecting that.
No!
Okay.
No, I'm scared of the second one.
Oh, you probably should be.
Oh no.
I am terrified right now.
I don't know how I'm going to handle these, honestly.
We're gentle, somewhat.
Yeah.
Please be careful with me. Oh
I'm tiny
Pull my foreskin back baby. There you go
You guys are gonna have to like deep throat me so I can get some like good like cock sucking spit
I know you really are enjoying this, aren't you?
Oh my gosh, I have so much running through my mind, right?
I can't.
I don't even know what I want to do first.
Do I want to stuff me first?
I can't.
There's too many options.
you guys. Maybe next time. Is your pussy wet? I'm thinking about two cocks using me at the same time. It makes me so fucking horny. I just can't stop looking at them. They're ginormous. They're bigger than my face. Oh my god. I'm scared. I can't even get it all the way down my throat. I'm going to try
God, you could really kill me with this thing if you wanted to.
In yours, I can hardly put my mouth around.
My fucking God.
Oh my God.
I had so many talks to please.
I'm like, which one do I pay more attention to?
In the moment, I'm like, I want to suck both of them at the same time, but I don't think I can put them both in my mouth.
All right.
Let's try to look into my pretty blue eyes while I suck your cocks.
You have really pretty eyes.
Oh.
We've got a bad one on our hands here.
Yeah.
I fucking love it.
I'm just imagining them sliding into my pussy
and my mouth at the same time.
You want Chong to eat your pussy?
Yeah.
Yeah, Chong's quite good at it.
Yeah, I want it right now.
Yeah.
Do I get a turn already?
How generous.
How would you like me?
Right here?
Yeah, right there's perfume.
I made a mess. I'm all spitty.
Oh my god, this is so hot. This is like
a fantasy. Oh my goodness. I really did not know
what I got myself into.
Don't tease me.
Oh my God.
Yeah, don't just tease it.
Don't just look at it.
Oh my God.
He was good at easing in, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my gosh, so much to focus on.
I can't wait till your mouth is on my pussy next
I'm gonna turn from both of you guys
You guys already have me daydreaming about your cocks
Yes, please take turns
she is. Talk about how pretty my eyes are. Bring your cock over here right now.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Oh. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yes.
I can't wait to fucking push your cock with my pussy. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh my god, you guys deserve it, oh my god.
Oh, look.
I can't stay still, I can't.
I'm so nervous.
I haven't been flipped in so long.
Oh, your crotch is so big.
Oh, God.
Are you getting hot?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yeah, you wanna try?
Yeah, use my pussy, use my pussy, that's what I want, yeah, you can fuck me as hard as you want, I'll do whatever you want to me, yeah, yeah, please, yeah, grab onto me as hard as you want, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yeah, ah, yeah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
It feels so good, yeah, just like that, yeah, I can't even think, I can't, bye, bye, it feels
so good, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you for giving me the cup, I need this
more than you know oh my god yes just take turns with my pussy
we're already breaking the outfit
yes please yes please yes please
Oh
Fuck oh my god
Oh my god, you might break me.
You might break me.
Oh, it's so deep.
It's so deep in here.
It's locked.
Oh my god.
Bend over a little more.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh my gosh, look at your handprint.
That's so hot.
Oh, shit.
This pussy is good.
Thank you.
Thank you for giving me your cocks.
Oh my god.
I can't imagine both of them and me
this whole time.
Oh my god, there's a spit I was talking about, oh my god, oh my god, your cock is so fun
to stroke, there's just so much, like oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
He's just looking at me and he's so fucking horny.
Everyday.
Yeah, yes, yes we can.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm joking with myself on this dude.
For you.
Oh fuck, oh fuck this is good.
Oh god.
Why haven't I done this position in so long?
Fuck.
Yeah, Zuni. Yeah, you want me to push you? Yeah, come on. Come on. Come on. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah. You can lift me up. Yeah, you can lift me up. Yeah.
Get back here while I do the first one.
Yeah, I will do it. I will do it.
So big. I got so lucky.
Do you want me to come forward?
Do you want to push me?
Yeah, you're slicking back towards the camera.
Just push your forehead a little bit.
No, right there.
Oh, fuck.
This is my favorite position.
It's so good.
You're just using your tongue.
I don't want to do this anymore, I'm gonna be a little drunk.
I love this, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Watch it, I love watching it slide in me, yeah, yeah.
Oh my God, oh that's so hot, oh my God, yeah.
I'm not gonna need to watch this later, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yeah, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Show them what I look like, all cute.
Let's get you up on the couch.
Yeah, it looks like a seat. It's so cute.
I like getting used to it.
Fuck.
I just became a missionary on the couch.
Oh my gosh, yes, please.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel so good, oh my god, oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I feel good, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, mm-hmm, yeah, oh,
watching is my favorite part, yeah, yeah, yeah, just watch it, spit on it, spit on my pussy,
Let's see.
Yeah.
Shut up.
I'm close enough.
I'm gonna get down here.
Yeah, it's turning up, it's turning up.
yeah it's kind of getting in the way huh
oh my god
oh
i can't even breathe in your mouth
I don't like to go to camp.
Yeah, I'm just fucking dressed like my mom.
You're not really high.
I can't get my dick high that high.
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Talk to me.
I'm scared.
What's going on back there?
It's so deep.
Oh my god.
It's talking to me.
I know.
It always happens in talking.
I'm scared.
I guess it's my favorite position next to the piledrider.
Sorry, I keep moving.
I'm going to make you guys come inside of me and fill me up and not with just your clucks but with all your cum and drain your balls of my pussy and I'm going to walk out every single last drop of cum until there's none left.
Sounds good to me.
Oh shit.
Almost.
Oh my god.
You wanna lay on your back?
oh my god oh my god oh yeah let's try to get comfy
yeah i get comfy to fill my pussy up with all your cum
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah,
Let's see how they come.
I want to watch it.
I feel it.
Thank you for filling me up.
I really needed this.
I might be filled up a second time.
Are you ready?
I don't think you are.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
you're going to be at the same time, so.
Yeah, you can spank me.
Yeah, spank me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, mm-hmm, yeah, whatever you want.
Yeah, you can grip me as hard as you want.
You can grab onto me as hard as you want.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can take your nails into me
if you want, I don't care.
Whatever feels good, yeah.
Save me!
Yes!
There's so much all over me
Nice
Nice.
Oh my God.
What a load.
Oh, I love watching it drip out of me.
It's so hot.
Oh, I'm gonna get the rest of this out of me.
You guys filled me up to like max capacity.
Double the load.
Double the fun.
you should follow me
watch out
that's a nice ass
thank you
oh god
gosh
there's so much cum in me
it's like
like blowing bubbles
of cum out of my pussy
Oh my god, there's so much, we made a mess, you guys made a mess of me.
We're very sorry.
Don't apologize.
I don't sound sad because I only got two loads in me, so we're going to have to play again soon with a bigger mess.
I tend to agree.
Maybe invite another friend.
Yeah, the more the merrier, right?
Yes, please.
You want to help me clean up?
Yeah.
Do you want to rinse off? You're welcome, Sue.
it's like working a spaceship turning on another shower yeah i know what you mean
everyone's different make sure you get the right temperature
it's opposite of what it says it's opposite of what it says
as you pull towards the bloomful hot and towards the rich.
Interesting.
It's just fucked up.
A DIY plumber.
Oh, it's getting there.
Slowly but surely.
It's going to get, like, scoldering hot, like, immediately.
Oh my gosh, it's still dripping out of me.
So slippery and soft.
My skin's going to be so soft.
The cum is very good for the skin.
Great patience.
You got any more pen pal friends?
No.
I was wondering if this one wants to wash my dick off.
You want to come in here?
It's getting there. It's getting hot.
We've got to save the water here.
I would be careful.
I'll pour it in for you.
This is good water conservation as well.
Such a good thing, pal.
I know.
I'm the best.
What can I say?
Nothing like a woman takes care of a man.
Who says that the only Asian woman knows how to take care of a man?
Hey!
Did they say that?
I haven't heard that.
Yeah, this blonde here is going crazy.
She's wife material.
Yes, wifey material.
Yeah.
Take you home.
Thank you, darling.
Do you attend?
Um, I have shoes on, um, but you know what, I can take them off for you.
That's not that difficult actually.
I'm very sensitive to water temperature, but that's hot as fuck.
I thought it was strong.
No, it got hotter.
Okay.
It got, it got hotter.
Like, there's every time when you're, like, getting a shower, you were taking a shower,
and like...
I do take, I, no, I do take showers in this, but like, yeah.
This is always like the most wholesome part.
Getting cleaned up.
together. See, it's not that bad. It's relaxing. It's warm. It's like a hot tub.
I'm getting used to it. Let's put a little floor out. Yeah. Yeah, fun time. You about to be my new pen pal? Yeah, I think you can start writing letters if you want. Yeah. We've already skipped that part. I don't know. You can always backtrack a little bit. You know, whatever.
Do you need a towel?
Yes, please.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is the towel I need.
See, you're trying, yeah, just, yeah.
Oh, I'm so cute.
You are, exactly.
My god, exactly.
My spanking marks.
I love them.
Whoops.
Boop!
No, I love them.
Like, you gotta flame you somehow.