Go home cause our date is tonight
Wave your hands from side to side
Let the beat move your soul
Tonight it's Oakland and my lady
So don't stop, here we go
I'm gonna go out to the club to sing and dance like a freak
And every girl will look at me
We're here but no time to speak
I'm here to free my mind, to free my soul
Don't care what you think, nobody knows
The only one that I'm in love with is me
If you keep on wanting more, I'm gonna show you the door
Never ever seen before, a chick like me is hard to ignore
You waste your time, don't need your money, honey
Cause I got mine, yes I got mine, I got mine
Hey, I'm gonna club for club, get them to time
To go home by note, what shall I do?
I am not tired, with six parents around
You think I'm crazy, what's up baby?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I can feel your nipples.
Oh
It's so hard.
It's getting really hot.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It's really hard.
Is this better?
Or is this better?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Yes.
I can't do it.
Look at me.
How about here?
I'm okay.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels so good.
I want you to lick my hand.
What is this?
Wow
I'm sorry
You are stretching a lot
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh
Oh!
Oh my god!
I feel so good!
Oh, I feel so good.
I feel so good.
I feel good.
Ah, come on, let's do it once more.
Hmm?
Let's do it once more.
No.
Oh
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I feel so good.
It feels so good.
It's rubbing.
You know it's rubbing, right?
Yes.
I don't want to do this anymore.
You don't want to do this anymore?
Yes.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to eat a lot of ramen.
It feels good.
It's really hot.
It feels good, right?
It's really hard.
Did I come out again?
You want to go out more, don't you?
Does it feel good?
Here, here.
Ah, it's a little bit too much, isn't it?
Still?
I don't know what to say.
Is that so? But your nipples are sticking out.
It's not good.
What?
When people come in.
It's okay.
Doesn't it feel good?
Well, it feels good.
Right?
No.
If you look at me, the staff will be fired.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, but my boobs are touching the floor.
Are they touching the floor?
Are your boobs touching the floor?
No, I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good.
But it feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
It feels good.
I've been watching you from a distance.
You were so close to me.
You were looking at me with an angry look, weren't you?
Yes.
Oh, it's so soft.
Is it soft?
Yes.
Do you want me to rub it on your face?
Excuse me.
What is it?
Can I lick it?
Do you want to lick it?
Can I take a peek from below?
From below?
Can I?
Sure.
I'm going to do it again.
Oh
Come on
I can't get out of here.
You can't get out of here.
You can't go out.
No, I can't.
I can't go out.
I told you not to go out.
I told you not to go
Hey, come over here
You're standing up, aren't you?
Are you excited?
Hentai
Does it feel good?
Your muscles are tight.
It's getting really stiff.
Does it feel good?
It's really bulging.
It's so big.
It's so tight.
Are you doing it yourself while looking at it?
You're so big that you don't stand up.
It's so tight.
It feels good to rub.
It's so hot in here.
Do you want me to lick you?
Hey, come over here.
I'll do something better for you.
I feel like I'm going to die if I don't eat it.
Oh no, I can't take it anymore
Oh, my God.
I think I can do it.
It feels good.
I don't want to put it in.
Can I put it in?
It feels good.
Why?
But it's still hard.
Can you do it?
I'm going to squeeze out all the air out of my body.
I want to put it in, so let me stand up a little more.
Make it a little more flat.
Hey.
It's getting bigger.
I told you not to go in a while ago.
I'm sorry.
It's still standing.
It's still moving.
Isn't that enough?
Here, here.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's so soft.
It's getting stuck.
Oh, my God.
I can see your panties, and your jacket is broken.
Are you looking at me?
Can you see me?
Please look at me.
My bra was blue.
My neck hurts so much.
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm getting a cramp.
I can't do this.
It's getting warmer here.
Is it all wet?
I'll use a toy.
Ta-da!
A hair dryer.
Ah, it feels good.
I can't do this anymore.
It feels so good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my God.
I can't take it anymore.
It hurts.
I can't do this anymore.
Are you already touching it by yourself?
Do you want to see this side too?
Do you want to see it?
I want to see it.
Look closely.
Okay.
Yes, ma'am.
Look at my nipples.
Are you excited?
Yes, I am.
My nipples feel good.
Do you want to take a deep breath?
It feels good.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I am.
It's getting really hard.
It's getting harder.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good.
Are you looking at me?
Ah
Do you like to be hugged?
Yes
Oh
I don't know.
I love you.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
It's so relaxing.
I'm so excited.
Me too.
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
Look at me.
I want to put it in.
Can I put it in?
Yes.
I'm going to put it in now.
It's hard.
It feels good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know what to do.
I feel like I'm going to have a heart attack.
Mm-hmm
Oh no, I can't do this.
I'm going to do this.
I'm going to move a lot.
I can't do this.
Oh
I can't.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, it feels good.
I can't do it.
Hmm...