I
Oh, my God.
Oh
Oh, my God, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die.
It's been a long time since I've had a cat, but it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat, so it's been a long time since I've had a cat,
You look like you've turned into a pervert
It's all because of that
Show me your body
Should I show you my body?
It's been a long time since I've had a baby, but I'm so happy to have a baby.
I'm so happy to have a baby, but I'm so happy to have a baby, but I'm so happy to have a baby.
Yeah
I'm going to say a little bit
I don't know.
You said you'd listen to whatever I say.
Of course.
You have to eat well.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious.
I guess we have to be...
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I'm going to leave you here
What's wrong with you?
um
I'm full
There are so many
You will become cuter
Will I become cuter?
You are so cute
I will pull you more
I will make you cuter
I've been looking at you for a long time, but you've changed.
I can't take my eyes off of you.
Oh
So modern
You have a cute face.
Do you smell something?
What kind of smell is that?
It's a nice smell.
It's a nice face, isn't it?
What are you doing?
You are so thin.
What do you want?
You want to pee?
I want to pee
You want to pee, right?
Try to cry more
I'm going to make you feel better, Mr. Hoshino.
Move it to the limit.
I'm gonna do this again.
It's been a long time since I've had a baby, but it's been a long time since I've had a baby, and it's been a long time since I've had a baby, and it's been a long time since I've had a baby, and it's been a long time since I've had a baby, and it's been a long time.
No, no, it has something to do with it.
It has something to do with it.
Why?
You can see the future for yourself.
Give it back.
You want me to give it back?
Yes.
Then give it back.
Look.
Look at this.
What?
So cute.
Do you want to talk to me?
Talk to me.
You are so cute.
I can feel your cute face.
Do you feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's cute, isn't it?
It's difficult, isn't it?
Don't do that.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll pull you down, not just up.
Let's go back to your room.
I'll continue.
Your hair has become amazing.
My hair?
Do you want me to take off your pants?
Then, you can continue to the other side.
What?
I'll take off your pants.
Will you take them off?
I'll take them off.
Do you want me to take them off?
Yes.
You have to play with them.
You have to live.
Yes.
I'll pull them inside.
What?
Can I take this off?
No, you don't want to take it off.
I don't want to take it off.
Okay, this time, I'll put it in this way.
What are you going to do?
Here?
Yes.
There you go.
You have to put your head forward.
Does it feel good? Feel it.
Feel it.
Keep going.
You are a good boy.
Did you drink?
Show me your face.
You were cute.
You were so cute.
You listened to me.
You've heard a lot of good things.
Let's go take a bath later.
Okay.
Come on.
Who did you belong to?
I belong to Matsuyama-san.
Matsuyama-kun, you've been raised so well.
That's amazing.
I've decided to give you to Kenzaki-san.
I decided to give it to you.
No way.
You still don't understand.
You belong to me.
Please take care of me.
Matsuyama-kun, are you sure?
Yes, please.
Look at me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's the best, isn't it?
Do you like to use this place?
Please tell me.
It's Matsuyama-san's.
What is it about Matsuyama-san?
It's not mine.
Yes.
Do you want me to tell you?
Okay, so if you're going to give it to me, you're going to have to break your body right here, right?
Okay, so the three of us are going to have fun, right?
Sounds good.
That's good, isn't it?
Is it good?
I'll give you a massage.
Look at me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
This is the most sensitive part of your body, isn't it?
Please tell me in words.
This is the most sensitive part of my body.
It's getting messier and messier.
Is there anything else you can feel?
Show me, show me.
Up here, too.
Your nipples are...
amazing.
I can tell you're sleeping.
Are you okay?
I love the way you look when you're going crazy.
Can you show me that?
Feel good and go crazy.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
You've been raised well.
I feel like I want to bite you.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
You're a good boy, aren't you?
Show me what you've got.
You're a good talker.
Oh, you can see it well, you can see it well.
You can't let go of my hand.
Shimari is also good.
Shimari is good.
Thank you very much.
Hey, do it for me.
Please use my manko freely.
Hey, do it properly one more time.
Ah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Let me show you where you're going to go.
I'll pick you up there again.
I'll give you a lot of money.
It's a mess over there.
You look good.
Look this way.
Amazing.
You look like a mangrove.
I'm going to take care of you.
I'm going to take care of you
Oh, this feels good.
You're good, aren't you?
You've been taught a lot, haven't you?
It's good, isn't it?
It's the best.
Let's do it while looking at my face.
You don't like it?
This hand is open.
There are two of them, so you have to do them alternately.
Look, you have to move your hands.
That's good.
Um
More talk money I know
So much my car
So they're so they're so easy to get on
Show me your face when you get in the house.
Show me your face.
Why are you putting it in yourself?
Did it grow?
Show me your face.
Oh
Chinko, Iりました yeah
Motoki
Koguro
Scala
I don't know what you're talking about.
You have to be careful not to hurt her.
Now, come into my arms.
Look at her face and shake her head.
Let's do it.
Good boy.
That's the best.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Come on, let's see if you can do it.
There you go.
Do you want to see?
Good girl.
Do you want more, Chinko?
Do you want more?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
You did a good job.
Can you see the exhaust?
That's right.
You're a good boy.
Oh
Oh my god, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore.
Do you want some?
I want it.
Where do you want it?
I love you so much.
Hey, open your mouth.
You don't want to feel pain, do you?
Do you still want to be tortured?
Do you want to eat it?
Look at this.
You're going to be released.
I have no choice but to talk to you.
Do it more firmly.
Hey.
Hey
I told you to be quiet
Huh?
You are too big
I'm going to save you
Come here
You are too big
Come here.
What are you doing?
I can't breathe, so I'm going to do this.
Hey!
Look at me, I'm about to cry.
Huh?
It's not easy at all, isn't it?
Hey!
Huh?
Do you like Kinpo?
Come here!
You're happy, aren't you?
Hey!
Huh?
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
It's been a while since I've had a baby, so I'm worried about the baby's health.
I'm worried about the baby's health.
Do you want to taste it?
You are happy, aren't you?
How is it?
I don't know what to do with you, but I'm going to take care of you from now on.
I don't know.
You want that, don't you?
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
Hey, open your mouth.
Thank you.