Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's been a while since I came back to Tokyo today, but you're the only one here, aren't you?
Yes, that's right.
It seems that everyone went up first.
That's right. I haven't heard your name yet.
I haven't heard of it yet.
I recently joined the company.
My name is Kurata Keiri.
I'm sorry I didn't notice it earlier.
It's okay, I don't care.
By the way, the chief of staff said that a new Keiri child would join.
It doesn't look like a countryside like everyone says.
It's great to be still working until this time.
You're excellent at talking.
How is it?
Do you want to go out for a meal?
I still have a lot to do.
Just a few words.
That's too bad.
I'll go get something to eat.
Hello.
There's a cute mouse in the office.
I called to ask for a little help.
I called you because I wanted you to stand up for me.
I'll be ready, so please take care of me.
Please wake up, cute mouse.
Hey.
What is this?
I'll sue you for sex.
You'll sue me?
Please.
Please untie me quickly.
I just want to know who you are and why you are doing this.
What are you talking about?
You are a stubborn woman.
I don't want to hurt you.
You just need to tell me who you are.
All you have to do is look at it.
You don't have to be stupid.
You were looking at the management budget with a password that only I knew.
That was before the settlement, so I was just checking the information.
So that's fine.
It's not a lie.
I'm the only one who can see that.
I'm the only one who can do it.
You opened your own computer.
What does that mean?
It's a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
I'm the one who misunderstood.
Kei.
Stop it.
Who asked you to do it?
Who's the spy?
Spy?
I'm just Keiri.
Please stop.
Why were you looking at me?
Who are you?
Tell me!
You're hurting me.
I don't want to hurt you.
You're burning me up.
Who's the spy?
I'm not a spy.
It's not a Y.
Please let me go.
You're really strong, aren't you?
As expected of Spider-Man.
That's how you were educated, right?
You're not going to tell me
even if you're being treated like this, are you?
Hmm?
What are you going to do?
Let's get started.
Don't say that, it's not the time to say it.
What are you talking about? Please stop it.
You know, as a woman, I don't hate it.
I can imagine what you're going to do.
Why do I have to do this?
Because you're a spy.
I know.
Open it.
What's wrong with you, Koujyou?
What's wrong?
Stop it!
Let me go!
Hurry up!
Or do you want me to burn your nipples?
If you can bear it, then bear it.
No, stop it.
Let go of me.
You're so strong.
Hey.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
You do.
Who asked you to do it?
You're right.
Let go of me.
You're misunderstanding me.
What?
You're so big.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
You don't think you can take it anymore?
It's okay.
I'm enjoying it.
What's wrong with you?
It's just a crime
If I were you, I'd say you're the criminal
For me, you're the one who committed the crime
What?
What's wrong?
It's easy to bite, isn't it?
I won't stop.
Come on.
No.
That's it.
I thought it was impossible.
So, I'll call a torture specialist.
I'll call for a specialist, so be prepared.
What do you think?
You can't even move your body.
Hurry up and tell me.
Please stop.
I won't tell you who you are until you tell me.
It's about time.
I have a specialist for torture.
I'm going to make you
I'll do it.
What are you talking about?
You said you don't know what you don't know.
Please.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is the corporate spy.
It's a new drug that just arrived from Mexico.
I'll test you with this.
You're so annoying.
Please stop.
What do you think? It's beautiful, isn't it?
Can you tell?
It's a bit dull.
Should I shoot here?
Stop it.
I'm looking forward to it.
What kind of spy are you?
Do you want to be shot?
You said I'm not a spy.
I told you I don't want to do it.
It can't be helped.
Hey, it's going to feel good.
What is this?
You know what I mean.
What did I do?
I'll ask you right away.
It's getting hot.
What do you think, Kikime?
Are you excited?
Do you want to play hide-and-seek?
Where did you get hired?
You still don't like it?
Your pants are open!
You're crying, aren't you, sis?
You were writing something like this?
What's wrong?
Can't you feel it?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Your breathing seems to be getting worse.
It hurts, doesn't it?
You're a bad girl. Don't push me.
I didn't do anything.
How is it?
I'll grab you tight.
I can even see the wrinkles on your butt.
How is it?
Oh, your body is getting warm, isn't it?
It's working.
Right?
You must be tired.
What have you been looking for?
Taku...
Yes?
I didn't do anything.
See?
Your shoulders are getting stiff.
It's different, isn't it?
Do you hear it?
Do you hear it deep in your body?
Do you want me to continue?
I'll cut it for you so you don't have to go home.
See?
You don't need this.
What are you going to do?
What's wrong with you?
Did you like it?
You're so messy.
What is this?
It's wet.
You can't help it, can you?
What's wrong?
It doesn't hit.
It seems that there are quite a few people in Mexico.
Shall we go again?
Kune-chan
Oh, my God.
What are you going to eat?
To make her move.
Say it!
Who asked you to do this?
What's wrong?
Do you like it?
Hey, where are you going to continue?
Does it feel good?
Remember this vibration.
No
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I can't stand the smell of the medicine.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Does it feel good?
Let's go.
Are you going to go?
I can't believe it.
What's wrong with you?
It's been so long.
Are you okay?
Your baby is out.
Can I lick you?
I'm going to lick you.
How is it?
Have you ever been trained like this?
I'll give it to you.
Are you clear now?
Did you get better?
Yes.
Let's take some medicine.
Let's have more fun.
Your eyes are already open.
Look.
Look at this.
Don't cry.
That's a lot of people, isn't it?
You're crying, aren't you?
You've been licking my ass, haven't you?
You've been arresting my subordinates, haven't you?
My important guards.
You've been exposed.
It's not over yet.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't lose to you.
Is this okay?
I'll make you confess with a new medicine.
It'll be even harder.
Or are you just looking forward to it?
Hey, stand up straight.
What's wrong? You're out of breath.
It's all over the place.
What's wrong with you?
You're already tired, aren't you?
You're always so sensitive, aren't you?
You can't run away, can you?
Hey
What's wrong?
Look, this is dangerous.
How is it?
What's wrong with your hand?
It's getting hotter than before.
How do you like it?
Which one do you like better?
I like this one.
Does it feel good?
Come on, run away.
What's wrong?
Do something with your own strength.
You're going crazy.
This is torture.
What are you going to do?
Oh, you're going to hit your head.
What do you think?
It's the best.
You can't run away.
What do you think?
Are you happy?
Are you scared?
What do you think?
Did you like it?
Are you reacting to the sound?
Come on, get closer.
Look, it's going to hit you.
Look, look.
Can you still not lose?
You're strong.
Did you just say you were going to hit me?
What?
You're going, aren't you?
You haven't gone yet, so it's a pity.
You've gone, haven't you?
Alright, look at this side.
Look at this side.
Look!
Does it feel good?
How is it?
How is it? How is it? How is it?
Now, exhale.
Exhale.
I'm going to put it on your head.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Thank you for watching!
If you admit it, how is it?
Do you feel good?
How do you feel?
I've said it many times.
I'll put it in again.
Look here directly.
You want to feel good, don't you?
What are you going to do next?
You've already fallen down to the point where you're going to fall.
You want to have a lot of fun, don't you?
It's not going to be easy with just your fingers.
I want you to do a lot more.
Well, that's it.
Let's see how much you can do.
It's a pity, but you can do it.
You can do it.
It feels good, right?
How is it?
It's good to be in the beginning.
Yes.
You're in.
This is it.
How is it?
I'm going to suck it in.
Look.
Can you do it?
It feels good.
It feels good, right?
You have a lot of power.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
You're going to get hurt, aren't you?
Now, it's your turn.
Look. How is it?
What's wrong? What's with those tears?
Your tongue is crying, too.
You're crying, aren't you?
That's good.
You shouldn't have said that.
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
You got in here as a spy, didn't you?
You got in here.
You got in here, didn't you?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Get out of here!
How is it?
It's good, isn't it?
Hey!
Female spy!
If you're going to cry, stop being a spy!
How is it?
Isn't this what you want?
No, it's not.
You don't want it, do you?
Look, it's coming.
You wanted this, didn't you?
Is it good?
Oh
It's all wet.
You're a good boy.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It was good, wasn't it?
Oh, oh, oh.