Oh, yes.
Your mistress likes that.
I need to ride your face.
Will you worship my pussy?
Oh, yes, pussy.
Yes, lick that pussy.
Yes
Taste the mistress
Yes, yes.
Yeah, let me ride your face.
Oh, my stomach.
Yeah.
That's good.
That's a good slave.
Licking mistress's pussy? Yeah.
I want to see your face. Let me have you lick it. Over here.
I want to watch you lick my pussy.
Worship that pussy.
Yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Lace your face.
Thank you, Master.
Thank you.
Only in the camp.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
I like that.
hmm nice long legs yes just how I like it
get on all fours
now lick it nice
and slow
I'm going to use your little slave mouth
I want you to make me come
put your finger in my pussy
yes mistress
oh thank you
that's good
yes
oh yeah
see
yes let me rub your face
like that
use your face
Is this on the messages?
Yes, messages.
Oh, can you make it go harder?
Please, please.
That's really good.
I'm gonna come on your fingers.
I'm gonna come on your same fingers.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
oh such a good slave yes
Now what do you say?
Thank you, Mistress.
You taste so good.
Such a lucky boy.
I'm so lucky.
Now get back to your cage.
Yes, Mistress.
Thank you, Mistress.
Ah.