not gonna blow you but I will fuck you just your ass I'm gonna make you my
Suck my cock.
Can eyes.
Choke on that fucking cock.
Good little sling.
I'll smack you with that cock.
Yes, mistress.
You like when I smack your face?
Good little sling.
Thank you, mistress.
I'm gonna take your ass now.
Yeah, I stroked my calf because it's nice and hard for you.
Get it nice and wet for you.
Spit on that asshole.
Yes, mistress.
Yeah, get it wet for you.
You're so tight.
I'm going to take the mistress's cup.
Yes, mistress.
Ready?
Push it deeper.
I feel it going into your ass.
I see.
Oh, you're swallowing.
Oh, I'll take that off.
Back in my tight ass, my middle leg.
Thank you, Mr.
Let me get it back in the side.
Slave.
A tight slave asshole.
Thank you, mistress.
Let me see.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
You want to take that?
Take that cock of mine?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, you fucking little slut.
Take that cock in the ass so well.
That's why you're my favorite slave.
Okay.
Deep in your ass
Yeah
Welcome
let me put it back in
yes
Oh, yeah. Turn around for me.
Good little slave. Keep that tick in your ass.
Thank you, Mistress.
Fucking cum on my cock.
I love your cock mistress, I love it when you stretch my ass
Mm-hmm
Oh fuck
Yes
Oh fuck yes
Oh
You're gonna make me cum
You're not allowed to come yet.
Yes, mistress.
The mistress didn't say you're allowed to come.
Do you want to be punished?
No, mistress.
I'm sorry, mistress.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm going to mark my fucking territory because you're my little slave.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, you're so deep.
Oh, fuck.
Going around and around your tight little asshole.
Want to loosen it up?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, I love you, cock in my hand.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, fuck.
I love how your ass was around my big, fat cock.
Yeah, yeah.
Here, you take that cup, you take that cup, you take it nice and clean.
Thank you, mistress.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my fucking God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
I haven't fucking come yet.
Not until Mistress comes.
Yes, Mistress. Yes, Mistress.
You little stupid slug.
Look at you.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck.
Are you going to loosen it back up?
Oh, yeah.
Hands back in.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to come on you, you fucking asshole.
I'm going to come on it.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That was quite a workout for me.
But you're nice and hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
So come suck my cock.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, deep throughout that cock.
Oh, yes, yes.
So good.
Oh, so nice.
Oh, so good.
Oh, you're such a good boy.
Oh, you're so good.
Look at my sweater.
My nice mistress.
Good boy.
Oh, yes, take it.
Oh, nice and fast.
Now I want you to get down on the floor
and lick the sweat off my ass.
Yes, mistress.
Good boy.
Yes.
There's more.
Good little slave.
Okay.
Thank you, mistress.
Let me see.
This is what happens for bad little slaves
who try to come before the mistress tells them to.
Yes, mistress.
I'm sorry, mistress.
You deserve this.
Yes, I deserve it.
All right, now get back in your cage.
Yes, mistress.