come on little bitch it's dinner time assume the position
i'm sure you've worked up an appetite
you ready to worship your queen yes miss jizz yes queen
You hungry?
Yes, my queen.
Dinner's up.
You are a hungry little bitch, aren't you?
Stick that tongue out.
Good boy.
I've been waiting for this all day.
Hoping that you'd get a treat.
Don't forget my asshole.
That's right.
All right, eat that up, right up.
Gain it for me.
I think you can stick your tongue in deeper than that.
All the way from my clit to my asshole, come on.
I'm going to ride your fucking face.
Yes, fucking take it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Come on, you can do better than that.
mmm
Fuck!
Worship those holes.
Stick that tongue in deep.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
You're getting fucking tired.
Come on.
I think you should make your mistress calm.
Focus on that fucking clip.
Make me fucking calm.
And you just fucking lay there wish someone would touch you
Fuck, yes, yes, yes, come on, fucking give me that tongue.
Fuck.
Oh, look at your little fucking cock all squished up in that chest, baby.
Tiny fucking cockle.
Did you enjoy that?
Yes, Mistress.
Would you like some more?
oh yeah this is what I deserve
oh you look at that
you're bulging through there
turning all purple
purple
Maybe I should let you out
Mmm come on you can do better than that. You can do better than that.
So squashed up there, look at that.
So much you can fucking take.
Keep licking.
really sensitive right there huh what about right here
here even just the slightest touch
stop bitching just keep that tongue out
yes
yes.
I don't want my clit.
Oh, you're such a little fucking wuss.
Such a little wim, whinging and moaning about everything.
Huh?
What do you have to complain about
while you're licking your mistress' fucking pussy?
You have nothing to complain about.
It is a privilege to be able to touch me.
And an even bigger privilege
to be able to put your fucking tongue
on my pussy and ass.
I do like to watch you squirm I do like to watch you struggle
oh I barely even touch you your swollen balls can't take it
you're not willing to do anything for your fucking mistress
You're complaining then.
You're going to start complaining more in a second.
Silence in anticipation.
All right, move on to the asshole.
Get that tongue in there.
Oh, you can take this quite well, huh?
I'll make you all red.
Oh, you handled that well.
What about here, huh?
What about here?
Oh.
Yeah, you're sticking that tongue nice and deep to shut yourself up.
I think you just like attention.
I think you can handle it.
Oh, look at you squirming.
This body is mine.
I'll do whatever the fuck I want to it.
Spread your legs.
that?
That was very good.
Good boy.
I like squeezing. I want it swollen like that.
You can take way more than you give yourself credit for.
Well, that was a pretty good job.
I'm sure you can learn to do better, though.
I bet you would love to come, wouldn't you?
Hmm, I guess you did enjoy that, huh?
Turning all interesting shades of purple.
Well, I'm sure you would really like to come.
and for every 100 times I come you can come once so we're gonna have to go
through a lot more training a lot more on your back