and then we'll sacrifice.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Mm, don't they look pretty in these red heels?
Yeah, they do.
I know you want them.
Mm.
Not yet.
Let's see how much pain you can take first,
what you're willing to go through.
Yes, ma'am.
To be able to suck
on my perfect little toes
oh i like the little muscle ease right between the ribs there
Mmm.
Oh.
Why don't you suck these heels this time?
Mmm.
Oh, good boy.
Straight to deep threading, huh?
Yeah.
See how far you can take it down that thread?
Wow.
Are you going to try and impress your mistress today?
Mmm.
Those eyes are already tearing up.
Oh you want more?
Oh yeah.
Look at the sole. Look at the bottom of that shoe.
Good boy.
Nice long tummy.
Clean both of these heels.
Mmm.
Ahh.
Polish it up for me.
Mmm.
When it's so shiny, you can see my reflection in them.
The other side.
Mmm.
Good boy.
Ahh.
I like the way you look up at me for approval.
You just want my love, don't you?
Mm-hmm.
You have to earn that.
Take my hair off.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Nervous, huh?
You want a little bit of that?
No?
No.
Oh, look at that, now I can see my little toes, don't they look pretty?
They're the perfect little toes, aren't they?
The best.
Yeah, I'll stick them back in your mouth.
Oh, it's so nice and wet and warm in there.
Mmm.
Oh yeah, those eyes are starting to tear, huh?
Yeah.
Keep those eyes open.
Keep them open.
Yes, keep them open.
I'd like to see one eye.
Yes.
Yeah, that's it, keep that mouth open, keep that hole open, good boy.
Take this heel off now.
Yes ma'am.
toes all wet.
Oh yeah.
I see you tear again.
Yeah.
Keep those eyes open.
Look at me.
Yeah.
You love it, don't you?
Like being beaten up at my feet?
Yes.
Let's see if you can fit both in your mouth.
Open that mouth wide.
Oh yeah, that's nice.
Nice and warm in there.
Oh, what a slutty little mouth you have.
Yeah.
See how far you can take him down?
Keep those eyes open.
Keep looking at me. Keep looking at me. Yes.
I'm going to stomp all over you.
Bring that cock up here. I want to stomp on it.
Bring it to me. Bring it to me.
Oh, you're so scared already. I haven't even done anything.
Mm.
Oh, that's nothing.
That's nothing.
That's a little something.
It's nothing.
Mm.
Oh, it feels so nice between my feet.
Oh, thank you.
But anyway, that's not what we're here to do.
We're here to make you wash at these feet.
Now I'm gonna rub your cock all over your face.
Yeah, you like that?
Take that cock, rub it all over your face.
Go on, suck your dick.
Yeah, you like the way your dick tastes, huh?
You like the way your cock tastes, yeah.
Now come up here and take my stockings off.
Stand your knees.
I like seeing your eyes all watery like that Thank you
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Now slowly roll it off.
Feels so nice.
You want to kiss my leg?
Kiss it.
Kiss it all the way down to my perfect feet.
They smell good, don't they?
Yeah.
Smell them.
Smell these.
Right up your nose.
Yeah, you really smell them, huh?
Yeah, you're really strong, huh?
Right up that nose.
Now suck your nose off.
Get that snot.
Fuck your nostrils.
Yeah, eat it off.
Like between those toes.
Every single one, right in between there.
Fuck, I love that.
Try and fit it all in your mouth now
Yes, deep throat it oh my god
Fuck yeah
Don't breathe. Don't breathe. Keep your eyes open. You can do it
Oh good boy
Good boy, you're so fucking sexy when you push yourself for me. I love it.
So sexy.
Yes.
Oh, so good.
Let me do that.
Take this off too.
Yes ma'am.
Such a good boy today.
Thank you.
You're such a mess, I'm about to spit all over your face.
I am a mess, I'm sorry.
Sloppy little mess, I love it.
I'm sorry.
No, I like it.
Come on, you're a sloppy little mess for me.
Go on, slide it off.
Slowly.
Oh, that feels so good, fuck.
Okay, fuck.
Clean up any dirt between my toes.
Mhm.
Yes.
Wow.
I don't want to put your face
together with my
feet.
Put it in my mouth.
I don't want your fingers.
Oh!
Oh, fuck, yes.
Come on, take it as deep as you can.
There you go.
Yeah, yeah, I wanna see you cry for me again.
Come on, come on, come on.
Try harder, yes.
Harder, go.
Deep, deep, yeah.
Yes, yes, yeah.
Don't breathe, don't breathe.
Keep your eyes open, keep, look at me.
Look at me, look at me.
Stay looking at me.
I think we get more spit when I use one foot.
Yeah.
You can go deeper that way.
Pull you onto that foot.
Yes.
Keep those eyes open.
Open.
Give me all that spit all over my foot.
Yes.
Such a good boy.
Yes, yes, yes, such a good boy, fuck, covered in spit.
You'd do anything for me, wouldn't you?
Anything for these perfect little feet.
Oh, it's so beautiful, messed up like that.
I'm gonna stick my fucking toes up your nose again.
I like that I can do whatever the fuck I want to you.
Look up your snout.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Open up.
Yes.
Oh, good.
Good.
Oh, so pretty.
Lay back down.
I want to step all over you.
Mm-hmm.
if I want do I have permission yeah yeah you don't give me permission for
or anything, I just take it if I want.
I know you'd let me.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh, look at all that pre-cum.
Oh, you like when I abuse you.
Let me get it for you.
You can taste it.
I bet you'd love me to shove my fucking foot up that arse with you.
Yeah, you would.
I'm gonna taste your fucking arse off my foot.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Good, good.
That was stumped right on your head.
Put it back in that mouth.
Yeah.
Oh, I know you can get it deep, but come on, you can do it.
Yes.
Oh, I love when you show up for me.
Yes, keep that mouth open, keep those eyes open, yes.
Almost there, yes.
You look so beautiful when you try hard for me.
So, what should we do with you next?
Whatever you want.
Whatever I want.
That's a good answer.
You want a red one?
Yes ma'am.
How much weight can I put on that cock?
Squash it down.
It is my cock after all.
Yes ma'am.
Yes, that's right.
How much weight can I put on those balls?
I like seeing you squirt. So sensitive, huh?
Come on. Up you go.
Put your hands in these.
Yes ma'am.
you