I like to see you all tied up like this.
Yes, Mistress.
You ready to be my slave today?
Do you like your cock in the cage?
Whatever pleases you, Mistress.
It's getting pretty hard in there.
You can't come out yet.
Yes, Mistress.
Do you want to come out?
Yes, I do.
Not yet.
Oh, come on, please.
You've had me in here for a while now.
That's how I like it.
You're going to stay in there
until I'm done having my fun with you.
Yeah.
See?
I want to play with your wholesome body.
Yes.
That's so nice.
You're being really good right now
Tell me what you want
I want you
I want to be inside you
You can't have that yet
You want to see it?
Yes, mistress
Let me show it to you
But you can't have it yet.
It's as close as you're going to get to my pussy right now.
Let me see this cock of yours, how hard it's gone for me.
Thank you, Miss James.
Do you like when my body is close to yours?
Yes, mistress.
I like it too.
Let me see.
Teasing your cock, right against my ass.
He's supposed to be in the stress.
Do you want me to smack it off?
Yes, mistress.
If it pleases you.
Is that too hard?
It's perfect.
Thank you, mistress.
Thank you.
I'm going to grab it.
Yes, mistress.
I don't want to come out of it, mistress.
Me too.
But it's not time yet.
Mistress didn't say so.
Yes, mistress.
So tight against the cage.
I feel like I'm going to burst out of there.
It's so bad, please, don't put it away.
It's so bad.
Good little slay.
I like it.
Me too.
Oh yeah.
It's so good.
Going in and out of your slug mouth.
Oh, what a tasty
kind of taste in my hair.
Let me spray in your mouth.
Thank you, mistress.
Good slay.
I want to try a little toy on you.
What do you think?
Yes, Mr.
My magic wand.
Put it faster.
Let it tease your car.
Make it come out of that cage.
Yes, Mr.
I do.
You're making me so wet, watching you struggle, do you want to taste it?
Are you okay, son?
How is it?
Just a little bit.
Watch how hard it's making you.
just one sip
just one sip like that
like that
not quite yet
not yet
I'm not done
playing with you
you like that
I like it
too
Get up nice and wet.
Nice and wet.
You know about Harvard?
Oh, yes.
I like that.
Please.
Let me see.
Do you want to fuck this?
Yes.
One more time, little pussy.
Do you want it?
Yes, mister.
Well, you can't have it.
I'm going to keep you right there.
Locked up.
Oh, no, mistress.
Please.
It's my pleasure.
Just like that.
I want you so bad.
No, Mrs. Comer, please. Come on. I've been good.
Good.
Have fun.
In there.
Oh, this is dope.