You're already so happy to see me.
Yes, ma'am.
This cock is so happy to see me too.
I'm just trying to decide whether I should please you or punish you.
Ah, thank you.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I do like seeing you hard for me already.
You have been such a good boy.
Thank you.
Maybe I should touch your cock.
Yes, baby.
Yeah.
I bet you would love me to milk you.
These balls haven't been drained for a while.
No, they haven't.
Oh, wow.
These balls are so filled with cum.
cock is compared to yours, hmmm, oh, it's a heavy dick isn't it?
Makes me think about sticking two dicks inside your asshole.
Maybe I should invite one of my studs around.
I can both fuck that tight little ass of yours.
Yeah, I bet you would fucking love that.
Don't you fucking come yet.
Okay, yes ma'am.
Yes, there.
More.
Keep your eyes open.
Look at me.
Keep them open.
Oh, good.
Good boy.
Give me that spit.
Oh, you like that, huh?
Sucking dick off like you're drunk.
Come on, you can do it.
Yeah, give me that spit.
Spit it. Spit it out.
Would you like to eat this pussy too?
Oh, yes ma'am.
Come and get it.
Oh, here. Is this easier? Come and get it.
Come on.
Drag yourself together.
Stick that tongue out. See if you can reach it.
Stick it out. Come on.
I like the way you push yourself for me.
I don't want to eat it.
Come on.
Get it.
Stick that tongue out.
Come on.
Get it.
You want it? Come and get it. You want it?
I love to see you struggle.
Come on. Open up like I know you can.
Come on. Again. Again.
Good boy.
Such a good boy.
Listen.
Fucking try hard.
You want to keep your eyes open this time?
Eyes open.
There.
Oh, yes.
Eyes open.
Oh.
Oh, did you give up?
You gave up?
Too much?
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Try one more time.
Don't give up this time.
Don't give up.
slut.
Yes ma'am.
respect. Not a big stud, but you do try.
I bet you'd love to feel these tits around your dick, wouldn't you?
Oh, gosh, yes.
Yeah.
Yes, really?
Oh, my gosh. Try and get it in. No, never.
But just to tease you, I can titty like this.
Titty fuck my own dick.
Can you imagine?
You know what it'd be between these perfect natural tits?
Yeah, yeah.
You want that, don't you?
You want that so bad.
Yeah, you're never gonna have that.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
But you can have this big dick rubbing on yours.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You can have that.
That'll feel good.
Yeah.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, I like watching your body react.
You're getting close, huh?
Not yet.
Not yet, not yet.
Oh, squeeze this fucking dick.
That's all I've heard.
Oh, yeah.
Right in that eye.
I'm going to penetrate every part of you.
Hold your cocks there for a good talk.
Hello.
I wish I was bigger.
Oh.
So should we milk these balls?
Yeah.
Oh, it's being so warm.
Tell you what.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll let you come.
Yeah.
As long as you eat up every last drop.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Mmm.
I love watching this go down.
Yeah.
Oh, I can feel those fucking balls getting even more swollen.
You know?
Yeah.
It's fucking comfy.
Yes, yes.
Do it, do it, do it, do it.
Give it to me.
Yes, there it is.
Oh, fuck yes.
oh it's so long oh it's so much oh you're gonna have so much to eat
oh is it sensitive now yeah i guess what i don't give a fuck
oh oh yes squeeze out every last drop
oh yeah oh wow look at all of this fucking cum
it's a lot i'm gonna get it all over this cock
it's gonna be a delicious little snack for you
oh there's more coming out look at that
I hope you're hungry
Oh, you're reaching.
Come on.
Look at that.
Look at that cock.
Cove it in your fucking cum.
You're a good boy.
You're all...
Come on.
Lift up.
Get it in deep.
It's not clean you better do a better job
I guess next I have to bring in one of my studs.
I'm trying to fucking destroy your asshole.
What do you say?
Thank you. Thank you.
Good boy.