I have a nice big surprise for you.
Nice big cock.
I know you've been craving it, haven't you?
Yes ma'am.
Graving tuck in your halts.
What do you think of this dick, hm?
It's huge.
Yeah, it's much bigger than yours.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
How's it feel to be the man in the room?
Yeah, I have a bigger dick than you.
I guess I hold all the power, huh?
Yes ma'am.
Yeah.
oh yeah take it down deep
oh yeah let's warm up that little mouth
I think you can take it down deeper don't breathe don't breathe well you
down your throat
you can do it good boy
wet for your arsehole.
Are you ready to take a big dig in there?
Yes ma'am.
Let's have a look, what have we got here?
Oh, look at that arsehole.
It looks ready.
You're such a little anal whore.
Yeah, wink it for me.
Yeah, keep winking it.
Yeah, make it dance for me.
Keep winking it.
Keep winking. Keep going.
Wink it.
How much do you want this dick?
Let's explore inside this hole, huh?
Oh, I can already tell one finger isn't enough for you.
Mm-mm.
You're a fucking anal slug.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
So nice and warm in there.
Oh, here comes a third finger.
Oh, four already?
stroke this big dirt right near your arsehole
it's easier with that
that arsehole wants it so much
look at that
oh look how easily you take it
oh you moan but it's so fucking easy
look at you
that little arse just opened right up
I said I'd be nice but
only nice with the lube
I didn't say I was going to go easy
on you when I fucked this wall
such a nice big
fucking
I can give you a tight also, let me see it.
Here it comes.
Fuck, yes.
I like these long strokes.
I want you to take it right into this.
Yeah, you're just trapped.
All you can do is fucking take it.
You're gonna fucking love it.
Yes.
What do you say?
Thank you.
I love that you just give up your fucking body to me
I want to.
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Mm.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
yes, that's what I like to fucking hear, I like that.
Mmm.
You're welcome.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
eyes.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Give me that spit. Yes.
this.
Oh, such a pretty pink oz ho, look at that.
Thank you.
Oh, it's so sexy in there.
But here it was, it looks better in there.
What do you say?
That's right.
Oh, my.
Yeah?
Yeah? Yeah what? Huh? Does it feel really fucking good, does it?
Yeah, you're gonna fucking cum? Yeah!
I didn't give you permission to cum, though.
I didn't give you permission to cum.
Did I give you permission to cum? No? No, I did not.
right in there nice and tender in those inner thighs
you want this cock again?
huh?
yes
you want that cock again?
yes you do
I know you do
oh
Oh, fuck, you're bouncing back on it, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
I like seeing you all fucking open for me like that.
Taking everything that I give you.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Hmm
Get it nice and red
Take that fucking dick. Yeah
Sit here and enjoy. Yeah. Oh, what a fucking good anal whore you are.
Keep going. Keep fucking going. Come on. Fuck it. Fuck it. Fuck it.
You know if you want more of this dick, I think you have to earn it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yes, thank you.
You're welcome.
You're such a good boy.
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
Thank you.
Ah, yeah.
now it's hard with these luby gloves can't go hard enough
oh right here looks very sensitive yes
Yes ma'am.
Yeah, it isn't even just that scary, isn't it?
Yeah, but you trust me, don't you?
Yes ma'am.
What about these sensitive feet?
Should I be really cruel to him?
Should I be that mean right there?
I think I should.
I'm just gonna pet you.
Thank you.
oh you're ready for it look at you already
Are you already fucking grinding on it?
No, I'll bounce on it then.
I'll just sit here.
Relax.
I shouldn't have to do all the work.
I am a queen after all.
Yeah, using that big fucking cup.
Are you going to fucking come on it for me?
Come on, you little slut.
Use it.
Come on. There you go. Come on. Come on. Do it.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
Get that mouth ready.
Eat your fucking mouth, Jeeves.
Yeah. Slow it all down.
Good boy. And again.
Oh, that's good.
Right there. Right there. Right there. Right there.
Oh, nice. Nice to wipe your ass again.
I like the way your cock moves for me, huh?
Come on, make it dance, make it dance.
Come on, make it dance for me, entertain me.
Yeah.
At least your dick can dance.
I mean, it can't be, it can't be like this dick.
I mean, let's see the size comparison.
Aw, you're a tiny little dick.
This is nice there, prep these dicks together.
Yeah, you feel how fucking big that dick is?
Yeah, you feel how much bigger it is than your dick?
Yeah, that's right. I have a bigger dick than you.
I'm more manly than you are.
And that's why I get to fucking take your ass.
Oh yeah, that was a little soon without lube, wasn't it?
Yeah, you can fucking take it. You can fucking take it.
Stop being a little bitch. Stop being a little fucking bitch.
You can finally take it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Do it. Do it. Do it.
Yeah!
Go!
Look how hard you pushed that dick out.
Yeah. Again.
Again, you little fucking slut.
Fuck!
Oh my god.
Oh, look at all that fucking ass cum.
You're going to fucking eat this up.
Look at that, huh?
Look at all that booty jelly.
All that fucking ass cum.
That's for you.
You're going to eat that.
Swallow it.
Does that taste good?
No, I bet it does.
Mmm.
I think that's enough ass-fucking for you to go to bed with.
You don't deserve that much pleasure.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm just going to leave you like this for a little bit.