How's my little bitch doing?
You got a bone, huh?
Little bitch has a bone.
Makes nice and tight.
Yes.
all in life because your job is to pleasure me to serve me but at the same
the thing is if we don't milk those balls they get bigger and bigger and
bigger and they make your cock look even more pathetic
come when you want to you get to come if I allow it and when I allow it
of chastity like that.
Right there on the head, right on the tip there, on the eye.
Are you getting closer?
Let's put it right under those balls.
Oh, it's bouncing on it.
You can just stare at my perfect ass.
Yeah.
I'm sure it'll make you come quickly.
But don't you dare come until I give you permission.
No fucking way.
for a while now.
Oh, look at you squirming, clenching those butt cheeks.
They still feel freshly fucked.
my fucking cock
to do whatever
I want with
I don't like watching it
bounce around
he looks so desperate in there
so desperate to come
Oh, is that cock getting close?
Oh, it's turning purple.
This is the only way your cock looks good.
I want to make sure it's milked good.
Oh, I can feel the heat emanating from it.
Mmm.
Oh, it's really starting to bulge out the sides there.
Mmm. Oh, shut the fuck up with your
moans. I want you to stare at my asshole.
Yeah, stare at that puffer tall.
bucking. Your cuck's really trying.
What was that, huh?
You're getting closer.
You're getting close?
Please, please, please.
You want to come?
Yes, please.
Really?
Let's see it, huh?
You have permission to come.
Let's see how much cum this little bitch has for me.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, there we go.
Yes, milk those balls.
every last fucking drop out it comes ew got on my finger that's disgusting
didn't mean to be so kind
oh fuck that is disgusting
Disgusting.
Gross.
Thank you so much, Mistress.
Well, I'm glad we got that out of the way.
Oh, thank you.
Anyway, I'm just gonna leave you here in your filth.
And, yeah.
Well, thank you very much, Mistress.