I've got a special treat for you today.
Yes, Mistress.
I've been walking around all day, and I want you to lick my boots.
Because I know how much that turns you on.
Yes, Mistress. I love your boots.
You like them? They make me so tall and Amazonian.
Yes, Mistress.
Wow, they're very dirty, Mistress.
Is this how you like them?
Anything for you, Mistress.
Oh, you're doing such a good job.
Taking care of this one.
Lick my dirty boot.
A good little sleigh.
Get the heel.
Yes, mistress.
It feels so good.
Can you lick the heel?
Yes, mistress.
Can you feel it?
What a good little slave you are.
I think I want you to lick the bottom of the soles now.
Yes, Mistress.
Nice and clean, please.
I've been walking all day.
It might take a little while.
Let me see your oral skills.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Oh, you're so good.
Taking it so deep like such a good little slave.
Watching you suck those heels is turning me on.
Oh wow.
like the filthy bottom of my shoes
yes mistress
I love cleaning your boots for you
thank you mistress
it's my pleasure
Oh, wow, boo.
Oh, it's turning me on.
Oh, you're such a good little slave.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes. Oh, this pleases the mistress so much.
Thank you, mistress.
I bet those taste pretty good.
Good. After I danced in them all night.
I was dancing with so many boys last night.
You don't get to dance with me.
You just get to lick my boots.
Thank you, Mistress.
Yeah.
Do you want to lick my ass?
Yes, Mistress.
Oh, too bad.
Yeah, you can just lick the bottom of my shoes.
I think someone spilled a drink on them.
I can taste it, mistress.
I think it was a pina colada, mistress.
You're tasting someone's cum instead.
Well, this cum tastes good, mistress.
Thank you, mistress.
I think it's time we get you on your back. Yes, mistress.
I want to walk on you like my doormat.
Yes, mistress.
take these off and have you lick my bare feet?
Yes mistress.
Let's see.
Yes, mistress.
I'll do it for you, mistress.
Good little slave.
Oh, mistress.
They're nice and stinky and sweaty for you.
Yes, mistress.
They're dancing for hours in the club.
Ah.
Clean for me.
Nice and fragrant.
Oh, it smells delicious, mistress.
Yes, so good in between there.
Oh, your mistress loves that.
oh yes such a good slave
you just love pleasing your mistress don't you
Mm-hmm
Thank you mistress
Good job.
All right, I'm gonna go walk around a little more,
leave you here, come back for more later.
Yes, yes, yes.