Well don't you look good.
Do you know why I've put you in this straitjacket?
No mistress.
Well the chastity wasn't enough.
I know you were tempted to touch that little cock.
you to be tempted and look it's like you're giving yourself a big hug like
I don't want you to be tempted to touch them.
We wouldn't want that, would we?
No.
No, mistress, no.
No, no, no.
You won't be touching this.
No, you won't.
It's quite sensitive like that, isn't it?
Oh, yes, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Look at this one, bulging up like that.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
What was that?
Oh, it's sensitive, oh, mistress.
Oh, it's sensitive, is it?
Oh, yes, it is.
All the more reason you can't be touching it.
Yes, Mistress. Thank you for correcting me.
That's right.
You are going to be in chastity for me forever.
Look at your cockle crimped in like that.
A little wrinkled there.
It's going to shrink in there.
Yes, Mistress.
But you didn't need it anyway, right?
it'll be uncomfortable I'm afraid you think so
wouldn't that be a shame
what about those balls
this one bow down
shut the fuck up
I beg your pardon
there's something pinched mistress
it's too bad you don't have a cock
that works
yes mistress
It would be lovely.
Fuck my divine pussy.
Oh, it would.
You're never gonna get it.
Oh, you're so beautiful too.
Perfect.
Perfectly beautiful.
Oh, that pussy is so close.
Oh you're such a whingy little bitch can you feel the heat from my pussy
Excuse me? What?
I beg your pardon, Mistress. I beg your pardon.
So frustrating.
Do you deserve anything more?
No, Mistress, I don't.
No, you don't.
Thank you for correcting me.
I do enjoy your suffering.
knowing that cock is mine and I can do whatever I want to it
should I feel sorry for you
oh please no
you little bitch, you can't take it?
I think you can take a little bit more.
Oh, give me a moment, please, please.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, mercy, mercy, mercy.
Excuse me?
That is not a word that you're allowed to use.
Yes, mistress.
This is the most action you've gotten ever in your life.
Why would you want it to stop?
It's so excruciating.
You're such a little bitch.
Help.
If you're just going to fucking complain, maybe I should...
Go out to my date.
I do have a date tonight.
With a real man.
You know what?
I'm going to be fucking him
all night long.
With a little chastity key on my ankle.
Oh.
can't wait to have that cock inside me
and i'm just gonna leave you here and just think about me taking that cock
hmm oh look you got so hard just thinking about me fucking a real man
All right, let's really position this on them.
Get your balls and your cock.
I'm going to fucking leave you like this all night.
Don't you dare fucking call.
Come on, cock.
You don't even want to know what I'll do
if I get back and you've come.
That's vicious.