Are you ready to be a good slave for your mistress?
Yes, mistress.
After everything I've put you through,
I think it's time for you to come.
Yes, mistress. Thank you, mistress.
Only when I'm ready, though.
Yes, mistress.
Be a good boy.
Let me see this cock of yours.
How soft it makes you.
I'm just barely stroking your cock, barely touching it.
I feel this fucking cough.
Let me see, do you want to get it hard for me?
You can't have my pussy though.
I feel like you're enjoying that too much.
Thank you, Mr.
Oh
Yes, mr. Sears
Lick your mistress my name
Blink brings the mistress pleasure
That's enough
stroke it.
Please stroke my cock mistress, please stroke my cock mistress, please.
Yes, Mistress.
You want to put it in?
Yes.
Oh, so bad.
Well, you can't.
Because that's not what the mistress wants.
Yes, mistress.
Suck on my fucking tongue.
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
Good boy, good boy, good boy.
Thank you, mister.
Oh, I like how hard you're getting.
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
Take it, take it, take it.
Oh, thank you.
Good little sleep.
I have to wipe your face.
You're not allowed to kiss me?
Yes, mistress.
No, no.
Do you want me to lick it?
Yes, mistress.
Please.
The mistress doesn't do that.
Oh, yes, mistress.
Kiss it.
No, not that either.
Would you lick it?
Look at that.
You're pre-coming.
Did the mistress say that you could cum?
No, mistress.
It's not good.
Think that means you deserve a punishment?
I've been stroking your cock all this time,
but I think now you should try to fuck my hand.
Yes, mistress.
Let me see.
Fuck my hand
Good boy
Fuck me through that wooden hole
Oh you're such a good little slave
Oh
Oh yes
Oh that's it
I wanna fucking
Touch that pussy while watching you
Fuck that hole
Yes mistress
Oh yes
He is so wet.
Oh, he is.
Stop.
Taste my pussy.
Good little slave.
Thank you, mister.
Thank you.
Oh, fuck you.
Pleases the mistress.
Spit on your own cock.
Yes, Mistress.
Good boy.
Oh, yes.
I'm like...
I like stroking your cock with your own fucking spit.
Yes, Mistress.
It feels so good in my hands.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I stroked that fucking cock.
I'll make it come all over this fucking floor.
Yes, mistress.
The mistress wants to make you lose it on the fucking floor.
You're gonna make me cum, mistress.
Yes, you're gonna make me cum.
Oh, fucking come off, fucking come off.
Oh, yes, come in my hand.
Oh.
Fucking eat your tongue.
Thank you, mistress.
You good fucking slave. Look at this
This time, on the floor, over my wife and all of them.
Thank you, Bethany.
You're welcome.
Look at all of them.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, you good fucking boy.
Thank you mistress. Thank you mistress.
Is that sensitive? Yes mistress.
Thank you mistress. Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.