this. Oh. Isn't it beautiful? It is. Perfect pink lips.
And look at that pathetic little cock.
It's useless, isn't it?
Yes, mistress, especially locked in the chastity.
It's always been useless.
And now I'm going to have it locked up forever.
Man, you didn't need it anyway, right?
It's not like you were putting it to good use.
to fuck it.
Look at you licking your lips, salivating over it.
Oh, you're so beautiful, mistress.
Perfect.
What am I?
You're perfect, miss just, you're perfectly beautiful.
Tell me how amazing I am.
You're the most amazing thing I've seen.
You're more amazing than a beautiful sunrise.
From my toes to my head, tell me
about what a perfect goddess I am.
Oh, and you are, because you have delicate feet,
shapely legs,
A curvy figure that's just amazing.
What's amazing?
Amazing or perfect?
Perfect! Perfect!
You're very perfect.
Is that all you have to say about me?
Well, continue.
Oh, and your ass is just amazingly perfect.
And?
I'm at a loss for words, see, perfection is beyond words.
Beyond words.
What about these tits?
They're...
I can't think of a word to describe them properly, they're so excellent.
Pathetic.
No, they're not. I am, but they're not.
Yes, you are.
No words, huh?
Maybe I should make some words into you.
Oh, they're magnificent!
That's fucking right. What are they?
Magnificent. Perfection.
What else?
Perfect. Soft.
Oh, they're so soft.
They're so soft and beautiful.
And what were you saying about the sauce?
Hmm?
Perfection.
What was that?
It's absolutely perfect.
That's right.
Amazing.
Stick that tongue out.
Clean my arsehole.
I didn't wipe just for you.
Clean it good.
That's right.
Get in there.
Clean it good.
Mm-hmm.
Go on.
Walk that fucking tongue.
Is that all you've got?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
Do I have to do everything myself?
Come on.
Come up here.
All right.
Mm-hmm.
Stick that tongue out is that as far as it goes stick it all the way out
It's your only use.
You're pretty shit at that, too.
Spread those cheese.
You can really get in my asshole.
I didn't say you could lick my pussy.
I said lick my asshole.
I'm sorry, missus.
Yeah.
Clean every little spoke.
I didn't say you could lick my pussy, I said lick my arsehole.
Oh, I'm sorry, missus.
Yeah.
Yeah, clean every little spoke.
I fucking love you.
You've taken all that weight?
Now you can't breathe?
Ha ha.
Wow.
Oh, fuck you.
I struggle.
There.
Oh.
Thank you, bitch.
Mm.
That's what I call a good hug.
Oh.
Mm.
See that tongue out?
Yes, that's right.
You're going to give me all the pleasure I want while I deny you.
Mm.
Get in there.
Mmm, such a comfortable seat.
Did I say you could breathe?
I needed to, I'm sorry Mistress.
I don't see why you needed to.
I thought you said you live to eat my arse.
I do Mistress, thank you.
You can die for it too.
If I so choose.
Oh, yes.
Mm.
Smother that face.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
You make me feel so fucking good.
Mm.
Yes.
Mm, while all of your pleasure is denied.
Mm.
Let's see how long you can hold your breath for.
Oh, there you go, struggling.
Almost, almost, almost.
Oh, thank you, mistress.
She's a pathetic little cock moving, huh?
Trying to move in chastity.
It's not going anywhere.
What's that little cock moving, huh?
Trying to move in chastity?
It's not going anywhere.
Your worthless little dick is mine.
Smack down on that fucking post.
Okay, you can lick my pussy too now.
Oh, that's delicious.
I want you to make me come while I deny all of your pleasure.
That's a good sleep.
Mmm, feels so good. Do not fucking stop.
Oh, is that distracting you?
Good.
Is that getting a little too much?
It hurts, mistress, that's all.
The answer is no, it's not hurting too much,
whatever you wish, mistress.
Yes, that's it.
Ah!
Fuck!
Okay, that's enough.
Get down on your knees.
Pray to my ass.
Be thankful.
Be grateful for what I've given you today.
Thank you, mistress.
Pray to that perfect ass.
What do you have to say to it?
Oh.
Hmm?
Thank you.
Thank you for letting me worship your perfect ass.
That's right.
My perfect ass.
Mm.
Yes.
There's the true way to salvation.
That's all you're fucking good for, kissing my ass.
Mistress, it's divine perfection.
That's fucking right.
Now, come with me.
Getting in this fucking cage.
Head after me.
Yes, Mistress.
I will only worship your perfect divinity.
Now, get in there.
Oh, yes, Mistress.
Who do you belong to?
I belong to you, mistress.
That's right, you do.
See you soon.
Yes, mistress.
Thank you, mistress.
Thank you so much.
You