Oh, I figured out what I want to do with you.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you ready to eat some ass?
beautiful little mouth, that tongue of yours.
I'll be quite a treat for you.
Fuck yes. Oh yeah, that tongue's already going deep in that asshole.
Oh, you're going to clean it so well for me out here.
You're such a good boy.
Little Oz-eater.
That's all you are?
Toilet paper, huh?
Yeah.
Hi, down here.
Put your head up there.
You want it?
Yes.
Beg for it.
Can you clean it?
Yes.
I'm a good ass boy.
You're a good ass boy?
Yes.
You better do a good job.
Oh, yes.
I was going to tease you the right way.
Get that perfect pussy in us.
Oh, yes.
I was going to tease you the right way.
You've got that perfect pussy in your ass.
You want it so badly, don't you?
Yes, babe.
Yeah, there you go.
Fuck yes.
Yes, mmm, this is what a true queen needs.
Good little beauty eater, just there
to lick my asshole clean whenever I need it.
Who needs toilet paper when I have you?
Oh, let me put a little more weight on you.
Lift those legs up.
There we go.
Oh, God, yes.
Fuck.
Oh, you're getting so deep.
Let me take these boots down.
Yeah, keep licking.
Oh my god, this is so relaxing.
if you think that you can't do the job. well that guy's moving
Okay.
Fuck.
Good.
I love seeing that cock move around
while you eat that asshole.
Oh, I know it's sensitive.
Oh, you're such a little pussy.
You have the most sensitive balls of cockle.
Yes, you do.
Come on.
Lick.
Deeper.
It's harder.
I love seeing you squirm around.
I think you can get still deeper.
Come on.
That's what I'm talking about.
I love seeing you squirm around I think you can get still deeper come on
Oh, that's what I'm talking about. Yes.
Ha.
Yeah.
Oh God, that's good.
Keep going.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, yes.
You sit right there.
Oh, oh yes.
I'm getting more weight on that fucking face.
you know I will.
Come get it, show me how much you fucking want it.
Deeper, deeper, deeper, deeper.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I got you.
That's my fucking asshole in that face, you dumb little pussy, yeah.
Leave that little pussy here.
Yes, from my alpha all the way to my cross.
That's right.
I'm gonna fucking wipe my genitals all over your face.
Keep that fucking tongue out. Keep that fucking tongue out.
I didn't tell you to fucking stop.
Fuck.
with my little fucking sex slave.
Mmm, you're just here to pleasure me.
Clean my fucking shoes, make me fucking comfy,
make me feel like I can do whatever the fuck I want.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, suck on my little clit, suck on it, yeah.
Here, here.
Hm.
Here.
Yeah, keep your fucking face in there,
keep your fucking head in there.
Get, get.
Oof!
Oh, fu.
Yeah.
Should I get another swig?
Prove yourself to me.
Oh, God.
Damn it.
Fuck.
You want more?
Yes, please.
No, I don't believe you. You want more?
Uh-huh.
Mmm.
Yeah.
You made me cum one last time on that fucking face of yours?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah.
Use your fucking face.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, good boy.
Good boy.
Time to get back in your cage, yeah?
Yes ma'am.
Get in there.
I'll come back and get you when I need to use you again.
Yes ma'am, thank you.
you