I'm so happy to see you again.
You don't have to do it.
Please take a look at it.
It's out.
I didn't take it out.
It's out, isn't it?
Hey, if you like pants, try this on.
It's all-in-one.
I've never worn something like this.
I don't have it.
That's why I'm asking you to wear it if you like it.
Hurry up.
From now on?
That's right.
Hurry up.
You have to wear it if you like it.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
Are you really going to wear this?
Are you really going to wear it?
Yes, take off your socks.
You like it, don't you?
You're used to it.
No, I don't know.
Have you ever worn it?
No, I haven't.
Is it okay?
Yes, it is.
It looks good on you.
I can't show you this.
You look like you're having a hard time.
How do you feel about wearing pants?
It's not cool.
Not cool?
Does that mean I'm not cool?
No, that's not it.
It looks good on you.
No.
How do you feel?
No, it's not like that.
Oh, do you like pants?
Hey, you're shivering from the top of your pants.
No, it's not like that.
It feels good to rub it, doesn't it?
You're going to get fat again, aren't you?
No, it's not like that.
Jinpo and Pansuto are rubbing against each other.
Look over there.
Hurry up.
How is it?
My mureta mango.
Do you want to taste it?
Do you want to taste the boiled egg?
Take a good look at it.
It hurts.
How is it?
Does it smell good?
Are you all right?
Make sure you lick the floor.
Make yourself comfortable.
Make more noise.
Stand up
It's hot
It hurts
You're so good at it.
Then I'll do something better for you.
How is it?
It's amazing.
I can see it.
Blow it up.
Ai-chan! Mei-chan!
Please take care of yourself.
It feels so good.
You're so good.
I'll make you feel better.
Come on, get up.
How is it?
Touching like this from the top of the breast.
Does it feel good?
It's tickling.
Where does it feel good?
I feel good in my body.
Chimpo?
Yes
I heard you were wondering where you were
Look
The neck
The neck feels good
Here?
The neck
The back of the neck
Yes
It feels good
Gradually
The balls
See, it's already crushed, but it's still hard.
How is it? Can you feel it?
Oh, it feels good.
Does this place feel good?
See?
Oh, I can't wait to go to bed.
It's getting harder and harder.
How is it?
It feels good to rub it, doesn't it?
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It's already like this.
How does it feel?
I'm sure it's not good to be rubbed.
It's not good to be rubbed, is it?
This feels good.
Rub it.
What's wrong?
Why are you silent?
Please stop.
What?
Your body says stop.
Wait a minute.
Do you want me to stop?
Yes.
I see.
It's okay.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep?
Okay.
I'll make you look more embarrassed.
I'll give you a lotion.
What do you think?
I'll make you look so embarrassed.
Even if you say you don't like it, you're standing up.
Look.
It feels good to rub it, doesn't it?
Oh, it feels good.
How about this?
Oh, it feels weird.
Oh, it's getting bigger and bigger.
Does this feel good?
How about this?
Oh, it feels good.
Are you going to have a muscle cramp while being stimulated by KITO?
Oh, it's hard.
What are you doing to your body?
It feels good.
Can't you stand it?
Yes.
You can't go yet.
No.
Oh, please wait a minute.
What?
If you feel like going, don't say you're going.
You have to tell me that you're about to go.
Oh, I'm about to go.
Wait a minute.
I can't let you go yet.
Yeah.
Wow, you have a lot of blood.
You're really holding back, aren't you?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
You're so sensitive.
You can't go yet.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, wait a minute.
Please wait a moment.
You're about to go, aren't you?
Yes, I'm about to go.
What are you waiting for?
I'm not waiting for you.
You can't go yet.
What do you think?
You said you were about to go.
Are you okay?
If you don't say it, you're about to go.
I'm about to go.
It's too early.
Hang in there a little longer.
Yes, I'm ticklish.
You're ticklish, aren't you?
Does this feel good?
I don't know.
It feels good.
I want to go
You don't want to go, you want me to go
Please let me go
You want to go?
I don't want to go
It's okay
It feels good
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's starting to feel good.
It's starting to feel good?
Yes.
Please let me go.
Oh, please go.
I'll watch you.
Here I go.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, my God.
It's all over the place.
Hey, it felt good, didn't it?
Yes.
Well, I'm going to get back to work.
I'm going to get back to work.
Yes.
Oh, you were sleeping again, weren't you?
Are you that sleepy?
Then, to wake you up, lick my soles.
Teacher's soles.
Do you want to smell it?
I've been wearing this all the time.
Smell it.
How is it?
You smell it, don't you?
Are you awake?
Your pants...
You smell it, don't you?
It's good.
Smell it more.
Between your fingers.
Smell it there.
How is it?
I'll bring it closer to your face.
You can see your pants, don't you?
Can you see it?
Are you worried about your skirt during class?
You couldn't concentrate on your study, right?
Are you eating your pants and your bag?
Do you know that your pants are also eating a lot?
Teacher, I always teach in this outfit.
I'm teaching here.
If you think so, you'll wake up, won't you?
It's okay.
Even if you bring your face closer to your butt.
Please bring your face closer.
It's close, isn't it?
More and more.
You can see the bite, right?
It feels good to rub the bandage on the baby.
You can touch it.
Do you want to rest your legs?
With your teacher's feet?
With the bandage open?
Keep it like this.
It's okay.
I'll massage you a lot.
How was it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Or like this?
Oh? What's this?
I'm so tired
Do you think you can go?
No
You can still go
You're so sensitive
Do you want to go?
It's okay, you can go
I'll watch you
You're so cute.
I'll squeeze you to the end.
How was it?
Did you feel good?
You're so cute.
Did you eat?
Did you feel good?
Yeah?
Hey, don't sleep.
Come on, wake up.
You were sleeping again?
Wake up!
Are you always sleeping?
Are you so sleepy?
If you're sleepy,
I'll wake you up.
What do you think?
I'm full.
Are you awake?
I'll wake you up more.
Don't look at me.
Roll your chin down.
How do you feel?
Are you awake?
You're awake now, aren't you?
I'm sorry, I was a little worried about you, right?
Today is a special day. I'll let you lick it.
Please relax.
Please make it feel good.
Yes, it feels good.
What?
How is it?
It's soft, isn't it?
I'll do something better for you
Can you see?
Do you want to see?
I've been wearing pants for a long time.
Oh, more.
Oh, it feels good.
Clitoris.
More, more, more.
Oh!
Yes, more clitoris.
Velocity.
Look.
Yes.
Let me touch you
It feels good
Don't stop
Don't lick like a dog
There, there
You're so good at this!
More! More!
You can see a lot of it, right?
Even the hole in your butt.
I can't do this anymore...
I'm gonna get used to it...
I'm gonna go to the bottom of the floor!
Right there!
It feels so good!
I'm so good at this!
I'm gonna wake up my teacher with this!
I can hear the sound of the door opening...
So, sui tsuite o manko ni...
O manko suiagete...
Kimochiii...
So, sutte o manko sutte...
Bila bila mo, so, zenbu suiagete...
Oh, kimochiii
O makkoi chaname!
Sensei no makko
Uchimichou nan chante
Oh, jousou
I want to do something better to make you feel better.
Really?
Come on.
Go to sleep.
No, Gomi.
Yui-chan
It feels good. You can lick it well, right?
It feels good.
There.
Yes, it's a lot of clitoris.
Can you see a lot?
It feels so good.
My nipples are so crispy.
It's so intense.
Look down like this.
Look down.
Look down more.
Give it to my mom, please.
I'll lick it with my tongue.
Get up.
Good boy.
You're good at licking.
I'll do something good for you again.
Ah, sir, what are you doing there?
You've been looking at my feet all the time, haven't you?
Do you really want to see my feet that much?
All right, I'll show you.
First, how is it?
It's an edgy look, isn't it?
It's a mess.
I know it's a mess.
Do you want to comb your hair?
You like to comb your hair, don't you?
It's an edgy look, isn't it?
How is it?
Please take a closer look.
The pants are all wrinkled.
If the customer stares at me like that,
It's all wrinkled.
Do you want to see it?
I'll put it on.
Can you see my fresh pants?
It feels good when the dress rubs.
Please look at me. I will follow you closer.
Will you look at my nose?
Do you want me to take a closer look at you?
Please take a look at me as soon as possible.
Do you want to see how I feel?
It feels so good to be close to you.
It feels so good to be able to do this on a day like this.
I can't do this...
It feels so good when I do this...
It feels so good...
I was looking at you without permission, so this is what it looks like.
No, please don't look at me like that.
You're so excited.
What's wrong with you?
How do you feel when you touch me with your feet?
How do you feel?
No, I can't. Please don't.
You don't want to?
Even though you're like this?
Your body is honest, isn't it?
You don't have to be like this.
No.
It's embarrassing.
You don't have to be like this.
Do you understand?
It feels great to stimulate the spine like this.
Does it feel good?
Customer
No, I don't like it.
You don't like it?
No
Oh, the customer doesn't like it.
I'm saying I don't like it, but I'm so angry.
I don't like it.
Let me do it myself.
Why are you doing this to me?
Ah...
You're out.
You're so big.
Please stop.
What?
Why do you stop?
You don't like it?
Are you going to do this to me?
Ah...
I'm sorry.
You put up with my pants, didn't you?
Ah...
What are you doing?
Please stop
You look weak
Why are you making that face?
Please stop
Why?
Doesn't it feel good?
Please take off your shirt
It's going to get dirty, so let's take it off
Yes, it is.
It's out.
Look.
How is it?
Can you move your neck with your pants?
Look.
It's being moved.
Ah.
It's getting more and more serious.
People are bleeding.
Ah.
Poor thing.
It feels good.
It feels good when you look at me like that.
It feels good to be treated so cruelly with your feet like this.
And your nipples are going to stand up soon.
I'm not scared anymore.
No, please don't.
What are you feeling?
Do you feel it?
I feel it.
It's really sensitive, isn't it?
Let's do more.
Come closer.
More.
This is?
Oh, I want to come out again.
It becomes hard as soon as it is rubbed with a band-aid.
Do you like it?
If you don't like it, you won't peek at it, will you?
You haven't spoken at all since a while ago.
You're as cute as a girl.
Do you want to tickle me that much?
Or does it feel good?
Which one?
Are you okay? Do you want me to stop?
If you want me to stop, I won't do it.
You don't have to go. You want to go, don't you?
Your body is tingling.
Does it feel so good?
What?
No, no, no
You wanted to go, didn't you?
No, no
You can't go yet
Okay
You're such a pervert
You can't go until I tell you to
Okay?
Okay
You look good
Ah
Even though I'm just being teased, I'm already so nervous.
You're not excited about this, are you?
Even though I'm excited about my pants,
Oh, I'm being teased by that pants.
Oh, how is it?
It's about time to go. Come here.
You want to go, don't you?
You're too patient. You look like you don't want to go.
You're being treated like this.
Look at your blood vessels.
You're getting bigger.
Ah, what is it? Does it feel good just by looking at this?
With the texture of the pants, does it look that good?
Look
What? Do you still say you don't like it?
I'm wearing it like this
Like this, look, it's old
I feel like I'm being tickled with my feet
Pants, does it feel good?
Do you like it?
You like it, don't you?
See?
It's wet.
I'll tickle you.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It looks like it's about to explode.
See?
There's a lot of bacteria.
You have a lot of dandruff, don't you, Kintama?
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
No, you can't.
You have a lot of dandruff on your chin.
Your underwear will get dirty.
Please forgive me.
What?
What's wrong with you?
It's okay. I'll take care of you.
You can go on your own.
You don't have to go on your own.
I want to look like a girl.
I don't want to be a good girl.
Your nipples won't stop bulging.
I think you'll get rid of your nipples.
I'll do a lot of things for you.
Don't stop.
Don't give up until I say it's okay.
How does it feel to be rubbed like this?
Rub it when you want to
Are you going to go?
It feels good
Stop it
You don't want me to do it, do you?
If you want me to do it, please do it
With your pants and legs
I want you to do it with your pants and legs.
Please say it properly.
How do you feel, sir?
Your throat is getting hard again.
I'm sure it's all red.
Cute
How do you feel, sir?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes.
The back of your head is rubbing.
How do you feel?
I can't wait to see you again.
I'm going to squeeze out all the bacteria that's accumulated in your face.
That's right.
You have a very pleasant face.
I love seeing that kind of face.
It's okay.
Don't be embarrassed.
You're getting full again.
It's amazing, but your face is coming out.
Oh my god, the shape of the pillar has changed.
Oh, it's coming.
Oh, it's okay. Please let go of your teeth.
Oh, it's out.
It came out like this.
Please come again, customer.
Dear customer, please come again.
Even though you are practicing, why are you only looking at my underwear?
Do you like underwear?
You want to see it, don't you?
If you want to see it, you can see it closer.
You can take a closer look.
Can you hear the sound of the pants rubbing against each other?
You don't like this kind of thing, do you?
You're getting excited, aren't you?
You're such a pervert.
You're just looking at it.
You're just looking at it, but you're so excited.
I can't help it.
This side?
You've been looking at my chest all this time, haven't you?
Even though I'm in training, I've been thinking about it.
Don't you want to see it?
Do you want to see it?
I'll show you.
I haven't had a surgery yet.
Even so, you're getting so big.
You're such a pervert, aren't you?
If you like panties,
you should take off your shoes.
Panties,
the soles of your feet,
the soles of your feet.
Do you want to try them on?
What do you think?
Do they stink?
But you like it, don't you?
This mure mure buster.
The mure mure buster is rubbing against each other.
It's disgusting.
You can look at it closely.
I'll push it against your face.
Why are you so happy?
How is it?
You're excited, aren't you?
You want to see me get my nipples done, don't you?
You can see it.
My nipples.
It's been five years.
Can you see it?
I got my nipples done, too.
I think your nipples are moving, too.
When I see it, my nipples grow so much.
I have a sensitive nipple, don't I, Jinpo?
Looking at my underwear, it's like this.
Oh, it's big.
It's annoying.
It feels good, isn't it?
I'm sure it's going to be like this for a long time.
It's getting bigger again.
Does it feel good?
It's really hard.
How's my mouth?
I can't stand it anymore.
This hard, hard gimbap.
Please put it in my crumpled mango
Come on, put it in my mango
Come on, put it in
I'm sorry
You can see it, right?
My mango
I'm so scared...
Ah, chimpon!
Ippai!
Ah!
I don't know
Aikuu
Kisushite
Kondo shirukatsuite
Kanto geshikatsuite
Jempo katai
It feels good, it feels good
More, more, more
It hurts
I'll give you a karaoke from above
I can't breathe anymore.
Can you see where I'm in?
Oh my god.
There's something in the first step.
Look at this.
Can you see it?
It's hot.
I heard there's something in here.
It feels so good.
Please lick my feet.
You like it, don't you?
And my pants.
That's right.
Please lick me more.
It feels so good.
My nipples are getting stiff again.
I really like Bust.
Look at me.
My nipples feel good.
This nipple is the best.
It feels so bad.
I can't go on like this.
Jason!
Um...
I feel like I'm going to puke.
My nipples are also pimping.
How do you like to be touched?
Like this?
What are you doing with your nipples?
Oh, your hands are getting faster.
It's okay. It's okay anytime.
I'll be messing with your nipples.
It's okay. You want to go, don't you?
I don't want to eat it.
Look at this.
It's a rotten sea urchin.
Take a lot of mine.
I'll watch you.
I'll touch you, too.
Oh, I'm so excited.
You're eating a rotten sea urchin, aren't you?
My hands are getting faster and faster.
I want to be more like you.
I'm touching your nipples with my first height legs.
I'll watch you.
Wow, there are a lot of cute things out there.
What are you going to do with so many?
Did you feel good?