Yeah, my name's Flash.
Flash? I'm Natasha. Nice to meet you.
Same here. Likewise.
So, what do you do?
I play ball.
Oh, do you? You're very tall.
Yeah, my part-time, I film a lot of movies.
Oh, you film movies? Are you a director?
Oh, of what?
Oh, really?
Really?
I kind of always wanted to do one, but I wasn't sure.
Like, I was scared that people would see me.
No, no, don't worry about that.
Don't worry about that.
You don't put it on the internet?
No, I don't.
Oh, well, can I do one with you?
I can make it exclusive.
I can make it just private.
Yeah, yeah, exclusive.
Or for your own collection or my collection or whatever.
Can we do that?
Yeah.
You promise it won't be on the internet though, right?
I promise.
Like I won't see my ass all over my computer one day?
Well, let me check you out.
Turn around.
Okay.
Your boobs are real.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
And I'm of age.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, someone can sound dude to me.
Sweet.
Leave it with.
The camera's always on.
Oh, really?
I didn't know.
Yes, indeed.
You like my outfit?
Yeah.
Since the camera's rolling, let's, uh, shit, play around a little bit.
Like what?
You're too shy.
I'm not shy.
I've just never done this before.
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to guide you a little bit.
Okay.
How about you, uh, spread your legs open.
It's always a good thing to do.
Like so?
Play around.
You can stand up.
You can twirl around.
You can do what you want to do, really.
Okay.
Can I jump on the bed?
Because your body's so lovely.
You can, baby.
Yeah.
Well, porn is pretty easy.
I'm going to take my shoes off.
Do you like my pedicure?
Take the dress off.
Let it go with that.
I can't believe I'm actually getting naked.
Thank you.
Sure.
They clap.
I came with tricks.
Take them panties off, Nick.
Thank you.
Look how big my clit is.
That's really big.
It's huge. It's like the size of my face. It's bigger than my face.
The last guy I was with didn't even make it up to here.
He's a white guy.
I can literally hide behind a banana.
My plan is always to get comfortable.
What can get comfortable is a dick.
I can't say I've ever been with a dick this big before.
It's like a foot.
It probably is like my foot.
It's bigger than my foot
This isn't going to be on the internet, right?
You promise?
Cross your heart?
I promise, baby
Don't show it to your friends
Or anybody
It's just for us, right?
It's just for us
Don't put it on the internet
Fuck.
Fuck good, baby.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh.
Look at that fat ass dick.
Mm.
Is that right?
Good?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Mm, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, you know it's a lemonade dick?
Huh?
You know it's a lemonade dick?
How far can you go down on it?
Halfway?
Mm, yeah.
Oops.
Sorry.
Yeah.
No, I like it like that.
Mm.
You might be ready to hop on this dig, are you ready to hop on it?
I think.
It's almost the size of my forearm, that's crazy.
I forgot porn is filthy
Can I f**k it now?
Yes indeed, yes indeed.
Oh my god.
That's a big d**k.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's a big day.
Oh
I've never had something that big in my pussy
Can I flip around on it
Oh, that feels good.
That's good.
Oh, that's a good dip.
Oh, big dip.
Oh, shit.
I like jerking it baby that's my favorite actually should I get in the
oh my god
oh yeah
oh give it to me
oh my god
oh fuck it
oh my god yes
Do I feel good?
Yeah, you fucking do.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you feel that big blood there,
stretching that pussy out.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, yes, you do.
Oh, shit.
More.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay, okay, okay.
Mm, baby.
Oh, shit.
Mm.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Mm.
Oh, my God.
Here we go.
I love it.
i want to swallow that shit oh it's such a big day i want the reward
You made me cum.
I want it so bad.
I can't wait to have a mouthful.
You're nasty.
I want to get filthy dirty with your cum.
Oh
All right
Keep doing it like this.
Here you come, boy. Get down there. Get down there. Here you come.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Mm, mm, mm, so perfect, so lovely.
You got it all.
Am I a pro or what?
Oh, yeah, you a pro now.
You're not going to put this on the Internet, though, right?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, okay, cool.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, good.
Hi.
Hey, y'all, so we had a good, good time together tonight.
So, you know, what do you think about doing this porn shit?
What do you think?
So, I don't know. Maybe. I guess I'll just have to watch it for now.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Alright.