先生、話って何ですか?
それで、何ですか?
僕はね、先生、ずっと君のこと可愛いな。
え?
Are you...
a thief?
Eh?
No, that's...
I wonder if you can give me that thief.
Eh?
But...
But?
I don't hate it, but...
Isn't it bad?
There's nothing bad about it.
Are you sure you don't want it?
No, I don't want it.
I hope so.
Hey, give me your hand.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Are you nervous because it's your first time at school?
I'm nervous.
It's okay. Let me see you.
Look at me.
I'm nervous.
It feels good.
From now on, do more and more comfortable things.
You have a good body.
I can't do it anymore.
It's very soft.
The doctor is also touching your neck.
It feels very good.
It's very soft.
You are sensitive, aren't you?
Over there.
Over there is embarrassing.
No, it's embarrassing.
What are you embarrassed about now?
It's embarrassing.
No, I can't.
Really, show it to the doctor.
Hey.
It's okay, just leave it to the doctor.
Put your hands away.
You're so tired.
You woke up because you were a virgin?
Yes, because it's my first time.
That's right. Everything is your first time.
Show me your change.
Your body is fine, but your chin is also fine, isn't it?
It would feel great if you had this chin, wouldn't it?
It feels so good, doesn't it?
Right?
And you know...
I feel like I'm getting a lot of muscles.
I want a lot of these muscles.
What?
Does it feel good?
I'm so tired, and my body is shaking.
You're doing great.
Look, your waist is sagging.
It's so cute when you blow on it.
Is it hitting you?
Yes.
It's hitting you.
It's hitting you, right?
Yes.
Sugoi yataru.
Sugoi.
Chimpa pampan dekitsusou.
Don't move your head too much.
You can see the teacher's back well, right?
It's okay.
It's okay even if you make your face loose.
Sensei, you haven't taken a bath yet.
Of course you haven't. You were working.
It's your first time doing this, isn't it?
I'm shivering.
Your chin is sore, isn't it?
Yes.
Stand up.
It's just the right height.
Can you feel it?
Yes, I can.
Your...
Why are you rubbing my back?
I want to die.
Have you ever been teased before?
For the first time
Amazing
I'll do the same for you
Does it feel good?
I feel like my muscles are getting harder and harder.
It's amazing.
Like this.
My muscles are getting harder.
It feels good even if you touch it with your feet?
It feels good.
Look at me closely.
I want to be among the sweet things.
That's dirty.
Dirty?
Hot.
You're just like your teacher, aren't you?
It doesn't matter if it's dirty, or smelly, or whatever.
You just have to put this chimp inside your teacher,
and make him cry inside you.
I don't want to make it too intense.
Why?
I want to taste it a little more.
I don't want to make it too intense.
How did you do it?
You did a great job.
I'll give you a hug.
You can touch your teacher's shoulder.
You don't have to worry about it, it's okay.
You came from above, right?
Yes.
I'll do the same thing for you.
Does it feel good?
You're so cute.
What?
Kiss me.
Do you want to kiss me?
Yes.
Come and kiss me.
I don't know what to do, but I'm going to do my best to take care of him.
You're so cute.
Put your eyes on your nipples.
Ima no desukkoi sensei no oman-ko atsukunatta no.
Nei, mite.
Sukkoi oman-ko atsui.
Motto yoku misete ageru.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it.
Yes, smell it.
Does it smell different from when you just smelled it?
Yes, it smells different.
Does it smell like you're drooling?
Yes, it smells like I'm drooling.
Yes, that's right.
You know, I'm getting more and more like a teacher's child.
I don't know if you call me a mess.
That's right.
I'll show you what's going on with the teacher's child.
Big butt.
It's big, isn't it?
It's big.
Try touching the ground.
Yes.
Sensei, do you like being hit?
Being hit?
Yes.
Like this?
Stronger.
Stronger?
Yes.
Both.
Hit the left side well.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it hurts.
Hey, can you change your underwear directly?
It hurts.
Put it down.
Put your pants down.
This is how a woman's manko is made.
You're a good boy.
Look at me from the front.
A woman's manko.
I'm Marumie.
Marumie?
Yes.
Ah...
Hey...
This is your place.
You can play with it as you like.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
You can play with it as you like.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll make you feel better.
It's so warm.
Is it warm?
It's hot.
Let me move you!
Teacher...
It's okay now, right?
Teacher, can you give me your handkerchief?
Stand here.
Come here quickly.
Come here.
Turn to the side.
I'm going to put your chest here.
Look at where you're going to go in.
Oh, my God.
It hurts so much.
It hurts.
I have a big penis.
It hurts so much inside.
Ah, Iiih!
Ah!
Dou?
Hajimete no omaiku wa?
Ah!
Kimochi ii?
Motto omaiku hajimete ageru.
Ah!
Iiih!
Do you want more?
What's wrong with you?
Where are you going?
I can't do it anymore.
Come closer.
I'm out of here.
Stop it.
Look at me.
You're still breathing.
You can do it, can't you?
I'll make you stand up more.
Look at this.
More, more.
You have to lick it properly.
Look at this.
Good.
I can do it!
See?
You're still standing like this.
You want to feel better, don't you?
I can't hold it.
I want you to do it more and more.
You're young, so you can do it more, right?
Lift it up from the bottom.
Lift it up.
Do it like this.
Yes, do it harder.
Yes, like this.
Do you feel good?
One more time here.
This angle feels the best.
Let me have some fun.
Are you ready?
Are you studying?
Yes, it's almost time.
Then I'll teach you how to study.
Really? There's something I don't understand.
Teacher, what are you doing?
Eh?
Study hard.
I don't think I can study if you make me do that.
It's okay. I'll teach you the mechanism of a woman's body.
But if you don't study, it's really close. Study.
You say that?
What are you talking about?
The teacher told me to teach you politely.
But the student body is for study.
I don't like it.
I'm especially concerned about the boy of the teacher.
But study, study, study.
You want to know, don't you?
知りたいけど勉強しなきゃ。
そんな真面目にならなくていいじゃない。
ねえ。
あなたのおちんちんすごく苦しそうよ。
いや、だって。
こう言ったって。
かわいそうにおちんちん苦しいだろうなあ。
先生、僕、恐れそう。
ねえ。
I feel sorry for you, Chinchin.
I feel sorry for you.
No, no, no.
I don't feel good at all.
Really?
Are you going out already?
I have to study.
You have to study.
Chin-chin, this way.
It's because you're old.
You can't take it out yet.
何?
手回し
まだ行っちゃダメよ
自信ない
え?
ガマンして
ほら
先生の中に出していいから
ガマンして
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'm so scared.
Isn't today a lie?
It's not a kiss, is it?
Just like that.
It's soft.
Is it soft?
Yes.
It's a big stereotype.
You can't take it out yet.
Lie down.
What are you doing?
Do you want to know?
Are you going to say it?
I'm going to say it.
You can't say it so easily.
Sensei no omagu no naka ta kusai dasu n da mono ne
Sensei, itchai sou desu
Ikitakatta?
Ikitai desu
Ikitai, ikitai
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I'm going to massage your feet.
It feels great.
You're amazing.
I'm sorry, I can't see.
I'm sorry.
What? Do you want to touch your butt?
Yes.
Are you okay?
It's getting better.
Hang in there.
You'll get a lot more.
I'll be there for you.
Does it feel good?
That's why you can't go.
Why not?
Of course you can't.
Why do you look like you're about to cry?
Because...
You still have to study your body.
Go to sleep.
What do you think about being petted on the soles of your feet like this?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Kintama no nuka ni takusan zamen tameru na yo.
Tawatta zamen wo sensei no manko no naka ni chodai ne.
Demo, kimochiyosugite.
Kanatta ga dechau kamoshirenai.
Hold it for me, please.
Sensei, it feels so bad.
It's coming out, it's coming out, it's coming out.
Again?
Not yet.
I told you to sleep there.
Do you think I can let you out so easily?
It feels good.
Your hands are open.
How is it?
It feels good.
Sensei no okki yosuri ni hazomarete
Kimochii?
Hai
Sensei no okki yosuri ni takusan nonde
Yorokai
Sensei
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Shake your hips.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't breathe.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
I'm feeling too much.
If you put it out, you can't get in touch with the teacher, can you?
I'm sorry.
Then, let's continue this tomorrow, okay?
We'll continue to study tomorrow again.
Is your club over?
After all, you're doing a club, so you're in a good shape, aren't you?
Teacher, what is it?
What are you talking about?
I was crying and it was hot.
If you have such a good body,
I think sex would feel good too.
What are you talking about?
Hey,
I'll train you one more time.
What?
It's okay, right?
Come on, put your tongue out.
Are you nervous?
It's okay. Relax.
That will make your training better.
Come here.
Come over here.
You've never done this kind of training before, right?
I'll teach you a lot of things.
Here, take a sip of your own.
Even deeper.
Ah, it's okay, drink more, drink more, drink more
Ah, more.
I feel dizzy just by looking at you.
I feel like I'm going to puke just by looking at you.
Hey, do you want to see my boobs?
I want to see them.
I'll show you.
Look closely.
It's amazing.
Your nipples are standing up.
Your tongue feels so good.
It's so soft.
Open your mouth.
Put your tongue out.
Drink your teacher's tea.
It's delicious.
Are you satisfied just by looking at it?
You want to touch my boobs, don't you?
I want to touch them.
No, don't do that. Please do it properly.
Please let me touch them.
Not yet.
Please let me touch your boobs.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
I want to hug you more and more.
How do you like my boobs?
It's amazing.
How is it amazing?
It's so soft.
It's amazing.
I'm excited.
Yes, I will.
Are you excited?
Yes.
Hey, where is the doctor's office?
Over there.
I want to see it.
You want to see it?
It's not that I want to see it.
Please, do me a favor.
I want to see your baby.
I'll show you.
How is your baby?
Can you see it?
Yes, I can.
Don't touch it yet.
Just look at it.
I want to touch it.
I don't want to touch it.
Then please.
Please.
Let me touch it.
More.
Please.
Let me touch it.
No.
What?
I won't let you touch it.
Let me burn it in your eyes.
You want to touch me, don't you?
I want to touch you.
I want to touch you more.
No.
It's enough just to look at you.
It's enough for me.
I see.
Do you want to look at it from a different angle?
Yes.
If you look at it from this angle, you can see two holes, right?
Yes, I can see them.
Yes, it is.
Can you see it clearly?
You can see my big butt, right?
Yes, I can.
Like this.
Can I touch you?
I don't like that way of saying it.
I don't want to touch your butt.
Please let me touch your butt.
I beg you.
Where?
My butt.
Is that all you want?
Yes.
Please touch my butt.
Touch my butt.
Make me feel good.
More, more.
Stronger.
I see.
That's good too.
Shake it a lot.
Sometimes try to hit it.
You can try to scratch it.
Your butt is shaking, isn't it?
Touch your navel.
Is it okay?
If you don't want to touch it, it's okay.
I don't want to touch it.
I want to touch it.
Is it here?
Is that so?
Yes, the clitoris, the manco, and the manco of the doctor.
Thank you very much.
Do you know that you are sleeping?
Yes.
Yes, make a lot of noisy sounds.
Make a lot of noise of the doctor.
こうやって
あの調子
あそぅ
あぁ
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat a lot of it with my tongue.
With your tongue?
I'll give you a lot of this too.
Rub your nipples.
How is it?
Does your nipple feel good?
It feels good.
Say it feels better.
What's wrong with your waist?
What?
Please touch my bottom.
Do you want more?
Ah, what's wrong with this?
I can tell from the top of my pants.
It's so big.
I'm being watched.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm watching you so close.
It's cute to move your chin.
I'll let you go.
Huh?
Can you move your chin more?
I can't do that.
Your chin is smelly today.
Because...
Because it's the month of February.
Did you wash your chin properly?
Are you laughing?
I think you're drooling.
But I love your stinky drool.
I'll clean your drool.
I'll clean your mouth.
Does it feel good?
I'm cleaning your mouth with your mouth.
I'm taking a good picture of your penis with a mouthful of gums, okay?
You're crying too?
You're a good boy, raising your feet by yourself, aren't you?
Do you want me to lick you that much?
You like the back of your head, don't you?
How about here?
It feels good there.
It's tingling.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
Did it feel good enough to make you feel weird?
Yes.
Let me massage your back this time.
I'll massage your nipples with my boobs.
Look.
Your nipples are in your boobs.
Oh, it feels good.
It also makes a nasty sound.
It's grumbling.
Oh, it feels so good.
Do you want me to do it faster?
But if you do it faster...
What?
Do you want me to do it faster?
I can't do it.
My legs hurt so much.
Are you trying to do it?
What are you trying to do?
Let me rub it.
My hair!
I'm sorry. I'm going to go to the bathroom.
No.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
No. I'm going to go to the bathroom.
It's not a good story.
I want you to have more fun with my nipples.
Do you understand my nipples?
I've been puking all the time.
It's terrible.
Can you put a pin in your teacher's chest?
It's really stuck in my chest.
And my neck, too.
Your muscles are really stiff.
I think you're going to have a lot of muscles.
Yes, I'm going to have a lot of muscles.
You're going to puke already?
No, that's not good.
Put it in your belly.
What?
You're going to puke a lot, right?
But, it's okay.
Here, chinko.
In your belly.
Chinpo is hard.
You have a good body.
Chinpo is the best.
I'm sorry.
It's so itchy.
What do you think of the inside of your belly?
It's amazing.
It's hard and hot.
Can you see where it's in?
Yes, I can see it.
Ah, there are a lot of soldiers, aren't there?
Please give me plenty of those soldiers and teachers' women's clothes.
What?
I'm going to go right away.
Not yet.
What?
It's intense.
It feels good.
Ah, ah, ah, I want to go to the doctor.
I've just been there, so I can't go to the doctor.
If you want to progress, you have to go in, don't you?
Yes.
I see.
You have to do your best.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Let me go a bit more...
Harder! Harder!
Feels good!
I'm going to continue.
This time from the back.
Wait a minute.
You put it in yourself.
I'm in the teacher's room now.
I hope you feel good together.
It's okay. It's okay if you feel good together, isn't it?
See? See?
It feels good.
Make it intense.
What are you resting on?
I told you earlier, didn't I?
Keep shaking your hips until the teacher says it's okay.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
What?
Please give it back to me.
What are you talking about?
Look at your penis.
It's still standing like this.
I'm just taking it out.
Look.
You can still take it out, right?
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it, right?
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
You won't know until you try it.
Is it that easy to give up a match like that?
I get it.
I won't stop until you say you'll do it.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Really, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Did you understand?
I'll do it.
Choco-san, go to bed.
Make me more satisfied with you.
It feels good.
I feel so good.
See?
Chikurin is still waking up like this.
I feel so good.
Do you know that it's rubbing?
At the same angle.
Raise your legs.
That's good, right?
You can do it if you do it.
And you're still so stiff.
I've gone crazy.
What?
You've gone crazy?
Yes.
What's that?
I can't do it anymore.
You're so stiff.
You can do it again, can't you?
I can't take it anymore.
Miss...
Miss, really...
Why?
Thank you very much.
Hey, what are you looking at?
Don't you think you're lacking in training?
Hey.
What's wrong, Ara?
I feel a little hot.
Then...
If you sweat, you'll have bad muscles.
I'm going to get a bad muscle.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, why are you taking it off?
What?
If you sweat well, bad muscles will come out right away.
You said you were going to have sex soon, didn't you?
So, if you have sex and sweat well, you'll get better soon, right?
What? What do you mean?
Hey, I'll disinfect you, so you can get to the bottom of your body.
It's hot.
I'll disinfect my boobs, too.
It's properly disinfected.
Nå...
Ah, I'll give you a little more.
You should change a lot of things.
Yes.
Because bad bacteria will come out.
Is this bad?
Yes, it's a little dry.
I'll put your ear on this side.
Don't run away.
Can you feel your ears?
Yes.
What's wrong with you, Moji-moji-chan?
It feels good.
Oh, it's so hard.
I need to get out of here.
Show me your chin.
Wow, you're getting bigger.
Does it feel good?
I'll warm it up for you.
Let me do more.
What's wrong?
出したの?
出ちゃいそうです。
出したらどうなるか分かるよね。
ねえ、さっき先生言ったよね。
中にたくさん雑面出してって。
はい。
ほら、我慢して。我慢。
ほら。
ああ、すみません。
何?
そんなにされたら?
じゃあ分かった。
Wow!
Like this...
Amazing!
You can even see my butt.
See?
You can even see this part.
Surprisingly,
you have a lot of hair.
How is it?
What do you think?
I feel like I'm being watched from this angle.
It's embarrassing.
Ufufufu...
Eh?
Ah...
If it was from this angle,
I'd be able to see everything.
Ufufu...
Ah...
Give me a kiss.
Give me your chin.
You can see the part where the doctor talks about your chin, can't you?
Doctor...
Wow, you're getting more and more patient.
Are you excited to see the hole in your buttocks?
Doctor...
I'm sorry.
Now, please step over here.
Lift your hips.
I'll give you a lot of my boobs.
You can get even closer to me.
You can even move your hips on your own.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It feels great.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels great.
It feels so good.
You're so excited.
I'll give you a massage with a lot of boobs.
I'll give you a massage with this.
It's amazing.
I think your big and soft boobs are amazing.
You have to feel your boobs with your nipples.
Your nipples will make your nipples harder and harder.
You can put your hands on your chest as much as you want.
Move your hips more and more.
If you do that, I'll get angry.
It's okay.
But I feel bad.
I'm getting sick of it.
I'm getting drenched in sweat.
Get down again.
This time, I'll make you slimmer than before.
You like it more, don't you?
Yes.
You're going to get better, aren't you?
You're getting better and better.
You're going to get better and better.
You can't go.
It's hard.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry, but...
The remaining life is coming out.
If you can't listen to me, I'll continue tomorrow.
Okay?
Come here.
Let me make you feel good.
Make me feel good a lot.
No.
But what?
Don't you care about me?
Why did you wear such a dirty underwear?
For you.
What? Is there no one outside?
No.
No, I don't want to.
You can hold it.
I'll rub it on your back.
My nipples are hurting.
Hey, Mikai.
Hurry up and write everything down.
Oh, what a disgusting chimp!
I've been waiting for this chimp for a long time.
I'm going to tickle you.
Hes a mero mero stella, kedo.
Ega, kono chimpu hossi.
Let me do it with my fingers.
It feels good.
Let's do it together.
ah
Please give me more sex than last time.
You still have more sex than last time, right?
I can still do it.
I can still do this.
I can still do it, right?
I can't breathe.
Can you breathe?
What the hell are you talking about?
Hold my waist.
Hold my waist and move it.
It's so hot.
I can't do this!
Hey, you're still coming out.
You're still coming out.
Hey, don't run away.
Come on, come on, come on.
This time.
Put it in.
Ah!
Ah, that's right.
It's okay, it's okay.
Let me out.
Ah.
Ikon, ikon, ikon!