I'm going to take a shower and then I'm going to clean up.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you cleaning up?
Have you finished the store?
I've finished the store.
I'm a little drunk.
Are you okay?
I'm a little dizzy.
I'm fine.
Mr. Nakamura, you're always having a hard time, aren't you?
No, no, no.
That's great.
There's a lot of dirt on the floor.
Wow, there's a lot of dirt on the floor.
Wow.
This is the toilet.
It's so dirty.
It's shiny.
Are you drunk?
I'm drunk.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It's dangerous.
Can you go home?
I don't think I can.
I don't think I can go home.
You look so happy.
I don't know.
I don't know how to touch you.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's transparent, isn't it?
Yes, it's transparent.
It's popular now.
Do you know it's popular?
It's transparent, isn't it?
You're so cute.
You're wearing a t-shirt.
Yeah.
Am I cute?
Yes, you are.
Don't do that.
Oh
My shoulder is stiff.
What's wrong?
What? Did I do this to myself?
Oh, it's this.
What's this?
It's embarrassing.
Why don't you tell me?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so stiff?
What's wrong with me?
Because you were touching my throat.
You were touching my stomach.
Yes.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
If it's a place like this, someone will come.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Can you hear me?
It's dangerous. Let's go to the other side.
Be careful.
I'm shaking.
It's hot.
It's hot today.
I'm sweating.
It's dangerous.
Ah, I'm so sleepy.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
Your butt is so sexy.
Sexy? My butt isn't sexy.
I'm going to sleep.
Mhm.
He's alive.
Oh, oh.
Ah, ah, ahhh.
Mhm, hm, hm, hm.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Hmmm, he's already sweating.
I'll clean it up for you.
It's salty.
Your ears too.
I'll clean it up for you.
It's salty.
Mm.
Mama.
Your tally got to show you.
Mm, it's all gone.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's been a long time since I ate this.
I feel bad for Nakamura-san.
I've put salt on my heart, too.
You're a nasty person.
I'm sorry. I'll do it again.
Oh
Do you like it?
Do you like this way of eating?
Yes.
How about this?
Oh
Um
What do you think?
You know what I'm talking about, right?
It's a secret.
I know.
Kamila-san.
Did you want to do this with me?
Of course you did.
You always looked at me in a nice way when I was cleaning.
I did my best.
You always made me laugh.
I can't take it anymore.
You can't take it anymore?
Here?
Yes.
Then...
I'll lick you.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Lie down.
Wow!
That's amazing!
You look like you're in pain.
I'm so scared.
But...
I'm already in pain.
You can't touch your feet with your pants.
Because you look like you want me to lick you.
You wanted me to lick you, didn't you?
You lick me so well.
Really?
That's how you do it.
You're so good.
I can't help licking you.
I can't take it anymore.
What? You can't take it anymore?
What do you mean?
I'm licking you.
I want you to lick me directly.
You want me to lick you directly?
Yes.
I'll lick you directly.
What should I do?
Do you want some?
No, no, no.
You're going to spill it.
You're going to spill it here.
Do you want some?
He's shaking.
You're so salty.
You're throwing up.
It's so good.
It's so hot.
Do you know that it's good for your throat?
Yes, I do.
Ah, delicious!
Ah, I didn't expect it to be so big.
I didn't expect it to be so big.
You are really good at licking.
Oh my gosh!
Oh?
The ice cream...
No!
Why are you trying to go to sleep?
Hey.
No.
Are you done?
I want to get up.
You want to get up?
Here?
No.
I won't let you stay here.
What?
I don't know.
Then...
Let's go to another place.
Where?
To a hotel.
A place where no one comes.
Let's go.
I want to go.
Which one do you want to go to?
I want to go to a hotel.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
Oh, it's getting harder.
Let's take a bath.
It's okay.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
It's hard.
I can't take it off.
Can you take it off?
I might not be able to take it off.
Ah, I took it off.
This is difficult.
I can't take it off.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Wow.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle.
My back is moving.
What's wrong?
I don't want to.
Your nipples are exposed.
What's this?
I don't like exposed nipples.
Exposed nipples?
Do you like exposed nipples?
It's better to have exposed nipples.
I don't like it.
Huh? He ran away.
How do you feel?
It's good.
Do you want to go in?
You don't want to go in?
It's hot.
I'm going to do something sexy.
Wow.
It's so slimy.
It feels good when it's slimy, doesn't it?
It's too hot.
I'm getting tanned.
Look at me.
Hold this.
It feels good.
My nipples are standing up.
I'm going to massage your buttocks as well.
More.
OK.
This is my favorite.
This?
That's right, that's right.
Can I have some more sake?
OK.
It's okay.
I want to hug you.
Oh, you are amazing.
You are amazing.
Can I hug you?
Yes, yes, yes.
Aw, so good.
Do you want me to massage it?
So good.
Ah!
Uh-huh.
That's amazing.
Mmm!
Thank you.
Oh, that's amazing.
Come here, look at that.
Ah!
That's amazing!
Ah, you're getting so much.
Ah!
Oh!
I'll clean your ears.
Ah!
It's so soft!
I'm going to scratch your ears.
Oh!
You're scratching your ears.
Are you sleepy?
Do you want to drink some tea?
I'm going to sleep now.
Why are you making such a weird sound?
I'm ticklish.
I can't believe I'm doing this to you.
Ah!
Oh!
I feel good when I rub my mom's head.
What are you doing?
I'm going to massage your back and shoulders, and your boobs as well.
I wish I didn't have to die.
Really? That's not good.
You want to do a lot of things, so you shouldn't die.
That's how good it feels.
Oh
It's so hard!
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
It's a little hard.
I'm sorry. It's so dry.
It's dripping.
You can do it!
Look at you!
You are so strong!
I can't do it.
You can't?
It looks painful.
You can't do it!
That was close!
Oh
That's amazing.
I wonder what will happen if I rub it with my butt.
You like butt, don't you?
I want to rub my butt.
You want to?
Okay, let's do it.
I'll rub it a lot.
Oh
It's so heavy.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy too.
It feels so good.
I have a question.
What is it?
Can I play with this here?
Sure.
How is it?
It's so hot!
It came off.
Why are you so happy?
Wow.
It's stuck.
Ah!
It came off.
Oh.
Oh, wow.
What happened?
It's like a booboo.
It's okay.
It came off.
Let me see.
Wow, it's beautiful.
It feels so good.
...
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, you're so good.
Yeah, you're so good.
You're so good, boo.
Oh.
Get up.
Ah.
Oh
ðŸ•ðŸ“ðŸ“ðŸ’—
ðŸ‘ A drop of water!
ðŸ‘ The water's left in your jacket!
ðŸ‘ Look how dirty it is!
ðŸ‘ Oh, this is hard!
It's warm?
Yeah, it's warm.
Oh, wow.
You're all wet.
I don't know how to do this.
Have you ever done this before?
No.
This is my first time.
I've never done this before.
I told you it's a secret.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I love you.
I love you so much.
You are so cute.
Oh
It's hard, isn't it?
It's painful.
It's really hard.
Is your back moving?
My back is moving.
I'm so tired.
What's wrong with you?
You're so cute.
I think you need to take a bath.
What?
Can I just rub it in?
You can't put it in.
Just rub it in.
I'll rub it in for you.
I want you to rub it in with your hands.
I can see the mango and the iron.
I can see it all.
But I don't have any hands.
You can see it well because you don't have a beard, right?
Mama's manko is erotic.
Really?
I don't like it when it's shiny.
It's an erotic manko.
I want to rub it.
Feel good?
Feel good!
Feel good, right?
It's gonna get in your ears.
It's gonna get in my ears.
Ah ha.
Oi, Oi.
Ah!
Ah ha ha ha.
Ah ha.
Oh
Nakamura-san, come to my shop sometime.
I will.
I'll give you a great service.
I'll be there tonight.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay.
Yes.
Mama.
You came.
Mr. Nakamura.
I'm happy.
You kept your promise.
I wanted to see you.
You are beautiful today.
What do you think?
It's amazing.
Show me.
You can show me with this?
Yes.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I don't wear underwear.
You don't wear underwear?
Yes.
But I can see you.
I see.
How do I look?
You look like a baby.
You look good.
What are you doing?
You're eating it.
I'm eating it.
You like it, don't you?
It's the best.
Yes.
You like this, don't you?
You're the best.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Mom.
What?
You always look so cool.
I know.
What's wrong?
I can't see the audience.
Maybe you can see them.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Nakamura-san?
Well...
I'm a little...
What?
Well...
What do you mean, well? Are you jealous?
I'm so jealous.
You're so cute.
I wish I had a dog like you.
Look at you.
You're so cute.
I can see your butt hole.
You can see everything.
I can even see the wrinkles.
No, you can't.
Don't count the wrinkles.
It smells good.
It feels good.
I'm jealous.
I'm the only one who lost.
You can't do business.
Are you not happy to be petted by other cats?
You are so cute.
I'm sorry.
Ah...
Mm...
I can't help it when I smell the smell of your sweat.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I'm so happy.
Ah...
It really smells like you.
Yes.
You don't have a fever, so it must smell.
Ah...
Do you like the smell?
Yes.
Ah...
You're sweating so much.
I can't stop.
I'm drooling all over you.
All over me?
Yes.
You're drooling so much.
I want you to stop.
You're drooling.
I'm gonna kiss you.
Your hat is salty.
Salty.
You smell like a man.
Oh
I love you, Chikubi.
I love your cute belly.
Is it here?
Do you have your tip?
You have your tip, don't you?
It's hard.
It's really hard.
It's so hot.
It smells so good, doesn't it?
Is it fresh?
I wonder what it smells like.
Ah, it stinks!
Wow, it's amazing!
This smell makes me shiver.
The smell of sweat and pee.
You're so cute.
You're wearing underwear again.
I can tell just by looking at your underwear.
Your sweat.
And your sweat smell.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you okay now?
I want you to lick me directly.
What?
You want me to lick you directly?
Yes.
Like this?
What should I do?
Please.
You want me to lick you so much that your hips are moving.
Yes.
Right?
Show me your face.
Wow!
It smells so good.
I can't help it, Nakamura-san.
I was so surprised.
ah
oh
Oh
It's so good.
This is so good.
I'm still hungry.
Oh
I feel so good that I can't say anything.
I can't do it anymore.
I don't know how to do it.
Oh
I want to do it more.
I want to do it with my thighs.
You want to do it with your thighs?
Yes.
That's good.
You like it, don't you?
Then, this way.
Oh, you like it, don't you, Nakamura-san?
How is it?
It's so soft and fluffy.
You love soft and fluffy, don't you?
I love it.
It's so soft and fluffy when you pinch it like this.
Like this.
It's a messy bed, so if you put a lot of stuff in it, it'll fall out.
See?
Aw.
Mhm.
Awe.
Ehhh.
Hahaha.
I'm a story.
Again, I'm making it up with him.
Awe.
Mhm.
Hah.
That's all I have left.
Hmm.
But.
There you go.
I'm going to tuck you in.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
A kiss.
Oh wow.
Oh wow. There's a lot of hair.
It feels good to have a lot of hair.
It's pretty thick.
There's a lot of hair.
More? Here?
Hey, I can't see because I'm covered in tofu.
Oh, it's coming out.
I'll wipe it off for you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Amazing.
Ah
Oh
It's okay.
I want to go to the other side.
You can go to the other side.
I'll rub it on your forehead.
That's amazing.
It's hot.
I'm sorry, I might have gone out.
You're so cute.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm so sleepy.
You have a lot on your face.
I'm sorry.
Nakamura-san.
You're going to fall in love with me, aren't you?
I'll come every day.
You have to come every day.
It's a promise.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
Good morning, Yutaka.
I'm just a little drunk.
Are you going to work?
Yes, I'm going to work.
Good luck.
Oh, my God.
How long have you been drinking?
I've been drinking quite a bit.
I'm running a shop.
Oh, I see. You're running a shop.
Yes, I'm running one right now.
It's tough, isn't it?
Oh, but please be careful of the steps.
Yes, I'm fine.
It's like this.
I'm so drunk.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'll hold you if you touch me.
Really?
That's so nice of you.
That was close.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for holding me.
I'm going to pass out.
I'm sorry, I'll be out of breath soon.
Did you drink a lot?
I drank a lot.
Does it smell like alcohol?
No, I don't care about that.
Climbing stairs is tiring.
It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
I'm in the same position as you.
I cut the string.
Really?
I'm sorry.
It's true.
It's dangerous.
I'm fine.
It's so warm.
What's this?
There's something red on it.
It's a cell phone.
Cell phone?
Oh, it's a cell phone case.
Anyway, let's check it out.
Is this a cell phone?
What's this?
Cell phone?
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
What is it?
What is this place?
Is this really a haunted house?
Hey.
It's not a haunted house, is it?
What is it?
Did you see it?
Wait a minute.
Here?
Hey.
What were you looking at?
What?
You were looking at a man's butt, weren't you?
Don't you always look at it?
No, I just happened to look at it.
You just happened to look at it?
You were looking at it a lot, weren't you?
No, I just happened to look at it.
You just happened to look at it, right?
No, that's not it.
What? Did you fart?
Hey, you're young, so you grow up quickly.
You're energetic.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
I'm touching your butt.
What did you want to touch?
Do you like my butt?
I don't know what to say.
You don't like it?
No, but my husband is here.
I don't know if I like it or not.
Oh, really?
Can't you see this?
Look.
It's burning.
If you do this in secret, it will burn, right?
It's burning a lot.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm sorry.
You like me, don't you?
What?
I can tell.
I don't like you.
You don't?
Then...
I thought I'd kiss you, but I guess I won't.
Will you kiss me?
Do you want to?
You don't like me, do you?
I like you.
Why do you like me all of a sudden?
Because you want to kiss me?
No, well...
This distance is...
I know.
It's hot.
I have a bad feeling.
Maybe someone is coming.
There is a flash.
It's not good.
I'm nervous.
I'm a bit scared.
Can you see?
Is it below?
Yes, it is.
Why don't you do it properly?
What's going on?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What's going on?
I don't know what to do.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Are you scared?
Yes, I am.
What if you get hit by a car?
I don't think I'll get hit.
I'll just run away.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
You're smiling.
You're late for school today, Yuta.
I think it's early.
Oh, it's early.
What's early?
Going home?
It's early?
I see.
Will you come to the store?
The store?
Come to the store.
I will.
I think I will.
I promise.
Will you come?
Okay.
Good luck.
I'm smiling.
See you.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, Yuta-kun.
You came.
May I?
Of course.
Where are the customers?
They're not coming anymore.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've been waiting.
I promised you I'd come today, so I've been waiting.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Are you done with work?
Yes.
Good job.
I had a lot of work to do.
Thank you.
I thought you'd be late because you left early.
Are you tired?
No, I'm not that tired.
That's good.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Yuta.
What are you looking at?
I'm gonna hit you.
No, no, no.
No!
No, I'm not.
I'm just looking at you.
See?
You want to touch me, right?
Can I touch you?
No, I'm not.
No, I haven't seen it yet.
I haven't seen it yet.
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I like it.
Oh, you like it.
Yes.
You told me this morning.
You couldn't wait, could you?
Ken, I didn't know you were so stubborn.
I'm sorry.
What did you expect?
What did I expect?
You didn't?
No, I didn't expect anything good.
What do you mean?
I see.
Can I keep this a secret from my husband?
Of course.
Don't keep it a secret.
Where are my panties?
Panties?
I can see them.
You can see them.
You're a pervert.
I'm sorry.
I can see your boobs.
I can see it. I can't see it.
You can't see it, right?
No, I can't see it.
You can see it?
Yuta?
Really?
Oh, you just opened it, right?
No, I didn't.
You just turned the card, right?
Really?
You're so naughty.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
Don't make a mistake.
You're so naughty.
You're so sweet.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
Really?
Thank you.
I didn't mean to.
Your hands are cold.
Is that bad?
You wanted to be cold, right?
Yes.
Have you been thinking about me all this time?
I couldn't find a job.
I thought you would understand my butt.
I was wondering if I could touch your butt.
I'm glad you're letting me touch your butt.
I'm sorry.
My hands are shaking.
Calm down, calm down.
What's wrong?
I don't know what to do.
Why?
I can't calm down.
You can't calm down?
Oh my god.
Oh, my god.
Are you all right?
No one is coming.
What should I do if they come?
You'll get in trouble if they come.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know you were doing such a terrible thing.
But I could almost see you.
But I couldn't almost see you.
I know.
You're a good boy.
You're getting warmer.
Yuta, do you want to see that many boobs?
I want to see it.
You want to see it?
Oh, it's out.
It's already out.
Look.
Do you want to touch it?
Yes.
It's okay. Touch it.
It's dangerous.
Ah, it feels so good.
It's so soft.
He's staring at me.
He's getting closer.
Ah, it feels so good.
Why?
You ate so much.
You wanted to lick my boobs.
Come on.
That's it.
This one too.
You're so gentle.
Oh
Let me kiss your neck.
Why?
I don't want to.
So you say you don't want to?
So, I am not going to kiss you.
You're so weak.
It feels so good.
It's so hot.
Where is it?
The part where I'm touching with my fingers.
Come here.
I don't know what's going on.
Here?
What?
What's going on here?
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on here.
Why is my neck so weak?
What is it?
It's okay, it's nothing.
Ah, it feels good.
This part is bad.
It's hard.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Here.
Here, of course.
You are amazing.
You have a lot of hair.
Do you want me to pet you?
Like this.
Yes.
Oh
It feels so good.
Do you want me to lick you more?
Yes, yes.
I want you to lick me more.
Okay, I'll lick you directly.
Wow.
Your cheeks are so big.
They look delicious.
Oh
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, my stomach is getting harder.
Oh!
Oh...
I can't eat that much...
I'll go...
You're going?
You're going to be late.
Oh...
Oh, it feels good.
I'll go...
Ah...
ah, ah...
Oh...
Ah...
It's coming out...
Ah, ah.
Ah...
Ah.
Er, ah...
Oh...
Ah, ah...
Brrr...
Hold on...
Brr...
Oha..
Oof...
Uh...
You're amazing.
You're the best.
I'm so happy.
I drank it all.
It was so good.
That was fast.
I need to go to the bathroom.
You need to go to the bathroom?
I'm going to take a shower and then go to bed.
What's wrong?
I need to pee.
You need to pee?
Did you feel refreshed?
Yes, I did.
That's good.
You feel refreshed.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I can do it.
What?
Oh, I see.
Can you see his butt from the mirror?
It's a really big butt.
Can you see his butt?
Yes.
It was shaking a lot.
I can't do it.
Touch it more.
It's so hot.
You can still do it?
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good to be tickled like this?
It's in the way.
I'm sorry.
It's so itchy.
Here, here, is it okay here?
It's okay.
Then it's okay.
It's the bathroom of the shop.
It's okay. Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
I want to pee.
I know.
I'll clean it for you.
Do you have pee on you?
It smells like pee.
It's embarrassing.
I'll clean it for you.
I just peed.
It tastes like you just peed.
I'm sorry.
Your hands are so dirty.
I just took it out, so I don't know if it's going to stand up or not.
It's already standing up.
It's already this plump.
You're so young and energetic.
Does it feel good?
Oh
Why?
It feels good.
I don't know what to do.
You don't know what to do?
Yes.
What do you want to do here?
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
I want to put you in my arms.
I want to put it in.
You want to put it in.
I'm so excited.
I want you to put it in.
Let's put it in here.
Really?
You want to put it in, don't you?
Come on.
My baby.
I am so tired.
I'm so sleepy.
I cannot speak.
I'm going to kill you!
uh
Oh
Oh, kimchi.
I want to do it again!
I want to put it in.
Do it.
Hurry up.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, that's good.
Huh?
Oh
Hurry up.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
Let's sleep soon.
What was that?
Wait.
What am I gonna do?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
ahhh
ahhhh
ahh
ahhhhh
oh
I don't like you.
Oh no.
I can't.
oh
Oh
Mm-hmm
Sorry.
It's okay.
You can do it.
Ugh.
Ah.
Oh my god.
What do you want me to do?
Ah, ah, ah.
I can't look.
It.
I'm so sorry!
Where'd you go?
I didn't do anything.
You don't have to apologize.
I know.
Where'd you go?
I said I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
How about you go . . .
Of course I'll talk to him!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I'm so sorry.
I swear I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
I'm so sorry!
You were supposed to go to the café.
I was supposed to go to the café.
So.
You had me.
I worked so hard.
I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
it's okay.
It's okay.
I want to go further.
I did it.
No!
I didn't mean for it...
т
I'm sorry.
I haven't said anything yet.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, God.
You're not serious?
Oh.
Oh, oh!
Oh, God.
Oh.
It was disgusting.
I don't want to do this.
It feels so good.
I'm so sleepy.
Can you come to my house tonight?
I'll be waiting for you.
I was waiting for you.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
What about your husband?
He is fine.
He is a nice guy.
Would you like to come back later?
No, I don't want to.
What should I do if you come back?
I'm afraid of other places, so I'm taking you with me.
It's a secret. Don't say that.
You have a lot of secrets.
Do you want to know?
I wonder if there are other off-logs.
You want to know, don't you?
You have a lot of secrets.
It's so cold!
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm going to put it on your ears now.
Does it tickle?
um
It's so hard.
It's getting harder and harder.
I can't get up.
It's heavy.
Of course it is.
Let me sleep.
You're so cute.
I'm sleeping here with my husband.
What do you think?
The pillow is a bit weird.
I sleep here.
You worry too much.
But...
In a bed where you sleep with your husband...
doing something like this...
isn't it the best?
You understand me well.
oh
um
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
You want me to pet you, right?
Pet me.
Pet me all you want.
I can't help it.
I just can't do it.
It's so hot.
Oh
Mmm
ah
mm
It's so big I can't fit it in my mouth.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Ah, it's so good.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I can't breathe.
It's coming out.
Ah, you can't.
You were about to vomit.
You can't.
I can't?
No, you can't.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
You're not crying yet, are you?
It hurt, didn't it?
My body.
Here you go.
How is it?
I'm going to give you a massage.
Look.
It's so big.
Is it good?
It's so warm.
What do you want me to do here?
I don't know.
I'm going to rub you a lot.
It feels good.
It feels so good to be rubbed so hard.
It really feels good.
Your nipples are getting harder.
They're so soft that they're getting harder.
It's good to have soft nipples, right?
Wow, you have a lot of hair on your face.
It feels so good.
Your hair is so soft.
It's slippery.
It's slippery because of the oil.
Open your mouth.
Is it good?
You spilled it. What a waste.
Oh
Do you want me to rub you?
Yes, rub me.
I'll rub you.
Rub me.
I'll rub you more.
Oh...
Ah...
It's so hot.
It's hot and hard.
It's so hot that it's about to hit my neck.
Oh...
This side too.
Ah...
It's so hot.
Ahh!
Ah!
Ah, it feels so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Shall we go to bed now?
Let's go to bed.
Oh, awesome.
Oh, how great!
Ah!
It feels so good.
You pinched me.
Look.
It feels so good.
I'm going to throw up.
No.
You're going to get sick soon.
I can't do it anymore.
Wow.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Do you want me to take it out?
Yeah, take it out.
No, no.
Oh, it's coming out.
Don't do that.
You said no.
You can take it out like this.
No.
Don't you want to do more?
I want to be with you.
Me too.
I've been holding it in for a long time.
It's all messed up.
My wife is going to lick you.
Lick me.
You want to be licked, don't you?
Look, you're twitching.
Wow.
Oh
Ah
Hey
Oh
It's so gross!
You're so gross!
Can I lick you?
Yes, please.
You're so gross!
Oh my god.
Yes.
Ah!
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm going to...
Ah!
Ai!
Come on, look at me.
You don't have a hair.
It's smooth.
Oh, I see.
It's because of the hair.
I didn't know that.
You didn't know?
Not even once.
I haven't seen you this serious.
Look at me.
Look.
You look like a baby.
Oh
Ahh!
Ah!
It's already this big.
It is.
Can you hear it?
I can hear it.
It's really rustling.
See?
You want to have a tail, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'm going to put a tail in your hair.
I'm sorry.
Let me have a tail.
Yes, please.
Why can't I do it?
Rub it in.
Oh, wow.
It feels so good.
I think I'm too big.
What is this muscle?
It's bigger than your nose.
It's bigger than my nose.
It's so big that it feels good.
Stop it.
It feels good.
It hurts.
It's so hot.
It's so deep.
It's amazing.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
Ah, it feels so good.
You're the best.
I feel so good too.
I
Oh
What happened here?
The baby's a pile of dog shite.
We only got a turn.
Are you left-handed?
It feels so good to scratch your back, Aki-san.
Oh, that's amazing.
If you keep doing this, you'll die soon.
I can't. I can't do it yet.
Onee-chan, I want to do more.
I have to...
I have to do more.
Please don't do that.
Please.
Please, don't.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Yes!
Let's go over there.
Wait.
I can't go over there.
You always eat over there, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Do you watch TV here?
I always watch TV here.
Ah!
Ah, ah!
**clapping and crying**
**moaning and heavy breathing**
**thud**
**heavy breathing**
What is this?
You're always relaxing here, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
And now you're being woken up by Chimpo.
Please, hurry up.
I'm so shocked.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Look at your face.
This is how your husband looks like.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Your wife is crying.
I'm so sorry.
You're still a beginner.
I'm sorry.
You look so sad.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're a beginner.
Are you okay?
I am okay.
Lift your leg up.
How can you dress up like this?
I am so angry.
Don't be angry.
But it's not cool.
I am so angry.
It's nothing.
A man and a woman have sex and then they fall in love, right?
Ahh!
Ahhhh!
What is today's dinner?
I see, it's abalone.
Abalone, abalone.
I'm going to eat abalone.
Wow, wow.
Abalone and meat.
Thank you, my baby!
They all like it
Everyone!
They all love it!
Love it!
I'm going to get you.
This is unbelievable!
I'm so angry!
I'm going to be in trouble!
I'm going to get in trouble!
What are you going to do if we break the cable?
What are we going to do?
I'm going to get in trouble!
Hey, hey, are you going to be okay?
Don't be mean.
I'm not being mean.
What?
Your wife said she wanted to do that.
But I feel so bad.
Oh
What are you making?
You're making it again today?
Squids!
No, I'm making batter.
Batter?
When did you make batter?
Where am I?
You're here, right?
I'm going to kill you!
Oh my god.
Ah
Oh
It hurts!
Have you ever done this before?
No, I haven't.
I'm so happy.
You said you're happy yourself.
You should be happier.
I'm so happy.
You're so happy.
It feels so good.
No!
Come on my dear.
Just keep going.
No, you can't touch me.
I'm being hit.
You're being hit, aren't you?
I'm being hit, I'm being hit.
What are you being hit by?
I'm being hit by a cane.
I want to take a picture of you while looking at your butt.
No, I don't want to.
I like my butt.
This is good, too.
You have to scratch your butt like this.
I want to drink a lot of milk.
It's 4,000 times more.
Oh, no.
I'm going to spill it.
Ah!
It's all over my face.
See?
It's all over your face.
It's getting worse.
Ah!
I want to go to Ochinpo.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to my pervert dog.
To your pervert dog?
I want you to put it in your stomach.
I don't want to.
Look.
I'll put it all the way to your stomach.
It's so warm.
Oh, wow!
I'm going to cry.
Feels good.
It feels good, right?
It feels like I'm getting tickled.
I feel sick. I feel sick.
I feel sick.
You have a nasty butt.
I'm sorry.
Wow, your butt is huge.
How is it compared to your husband's sex life?
How do you feel?
I feel so good!
You feel good because you have a big butt?
I have a big butt!
I can't do it!
I see.
You love having a big butt, huh?
I love it!
Oh, it feels so good!
It feels so good!
Ma'am, I'm starting to feel sick too.
I'm sick too.
Then I'll put a lot of dirt on your butt.
Put it on. Put it on.
Put it on my butt.
It's hot!
It feels so good!
What do you want?
I want a lot!
A lot!
Aw!
Oh!
Ah!
Aw, it feels good...
Ow!
I'm going to let you out.
Let me out!
Ah!
Ow!
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to get my phone.
Oh
Ugh!
Ugh...
Phew...
It's too hot...
Yuki-san...
Ugh...
Did you want to sleep?
I can't...
Ugh...
I can't do it anymore...
I can't...
Can you take responsibility for me?
I'll let you do it next time.
Come anytime.
I'll be waiting.