Kimpa's tengoku
Yeah, that one that I was always talking about
He is so hot
Too bad he has a wife
Mm-hmm
Okay
Okay, maybe I'll come over after this.
Bye.
Let's pour water on him.
Oh, hi Melody.
Oh my God.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Oh my God, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
I didn't expect you, you're gonna be taking shower
in my bedroom. I should have asked, I know.
No, I was just swimming in the pool and I had to shower.
Yeah, of course.
I think they're sleeping right now.
Yeah, they're sleeping?
Great.
That's good.
Yeah, go ahead.
Finish your shower.
Are you sure?
Yeah, of course.
I guess you don't mind that I'm going to be watching you, right?
I mean, as long as you like what you see.
I mean, yeah, you look beautiful.
Really?
You've got the most beautiful boobs.
Thank you.
That means a lot coming from you. I've had a crush on you for a while now.
Oh really? I didn't know.
Ever since you gave me the job.
Wow.
Do you want to join me?
Yeah, I think I can use a shower as well.
Your wife's not home?
No, she's not here.
I don't think so, Michael.
Perfect, perfect.
Do you want more stuff on your knee?
No, no more stuff.
Do you want more stuff?
No.
Oh
I don't know what I'm doing.
I think you needed this more than I did.
Especially big fat cocks like yours.
Um
Wow
Thank you for letting me suck your cock.
Yeah.
I love it.
Mmm.
mmm
ah
oh fuck
oh my god use this pussy
use this pussy
yeah
mmm
ah
yes
oh this guy is so
Pussy, because you're a teen pussy.
Right there, right there.
Oh my god.
Yeah, you're like a teen.
You're like a teen dog.
Fucking pussy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's so sensitive.
Oh, you're so weak.
Oh, my God.
Oh
It's so hard to focus with your tongue on my clit, oh my gosh.
I'm getting so messy over here.
Let me start on your cock.
You're open I guess, you just want to go to sleep.
Yeah, I'm gonna make you come over and over and over and over again.
Would you like that?
Yes, oh fuck, oh fuck yes, take control, take control.
I love that cock.
Oh, I kind of want to feel it.
Wow.
Uh-huh.
See?
Wow.
Yeah.
Isn't that hot?
Oh, it's so fucking hot.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, your cup is huge.
Oh, I'm taking it.
I'm loving it.
I need it.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, yeah. Oh my god.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
oh my god you're the best babysitter
thank you I can come babysit again soon
Yeah, sure.
Here comes the book.