In the night, you wake me up when the sun goes down
Feelings right, you wake me up when the sun goes down
Sleepless nights, you wake me up when the sun goes down
I can't help it, baby, not myself when the sun goes down
When the sun goes down
Wake me up when the sun goes down
It hurts, doesn't it?
Are you feeling better?
I can't help it.
You know how I feel, don't you?
Of course, I know.
I can't do this anymore.
Are you crying?
No, I haven't taken a shower yet.
I'm sweating.
Oh no, I really got a cramp on my back.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but please listen to me.
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Oh, I'm so tired.
I
I feel like I'm going to puke.
It's amazing.
I haven't seen an orange in a long time.
I want to look at it from here.
It's so dirty.
It's going to look like this.
It's going to go away with my eyes.
It's so dirty.
Look at me.
Why are you moving here?
I'm sorry, I can't move.
If you're moving like that, put it in from the back.
The rubber is bitter.
Wait, wait.
I haven't put this in yet.
Is it this way?
I was waiting for you.
I'm sorry.
It was a very attractive teaching, so I licked it a lot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I understand.
I got it.
It feels good.
What is this? Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be a watchman from now on.
I don't know how to do it.
I'm going in.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Here, here, here!
Choco
If only I could do it.
You haven't cut it all out, have you?
I still want to do it.
Is it okay, Fujima-san?
Are you sure you don't want to do it?
Yeah.
Ah!
Oh!
Mom, you know,
your hair is stuck in this part.
I don't know.
Men don't really know that.
It's fine.
It's still stuck, right?
I'm still...
I still don't have enough hair.
It's a mistake.
It feels good.
Yes, it feels good.
The other side too.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't breathe.
It feels so good.
I'll send it to you.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
Wait a minute.
My shoes are dirty.
What are you doing?
I haven't done anything.
I can't stand it.
I'll do it, too.
I've never done this before.
Please don't get wet.
What's going to happen if I drink it up?
I'm going to get out of here.
Why are you going to get out of here?
Wait a minute.
I'm going to cry.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? I'm not going to die.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I've said too much.
No way, didn't I tell you not to cry?
Didn't I tell you not to cry?
What did I tell you?
I told you not to cry.
You made my throat hurt.
Sorry, what should I do?
I don't think I can sleep with my mouth open.
Let's do it one more time.
I got it. I got it.
It's so good. There's more here.
Yes. Yes.
I want to lick it, but...
Then lick it and make it harder.
Okay.
It feels good.
This is bad.
Give it back.
How's your butt?
Yes.
Do you like your butt?
Yes?
Yes, it's good.
Just put your chin in.
Do you want me to give you a massage?
It feels so good!
I feel like I'm going to get a cramp.
I'm so crampy.
That's not true.
Isn't this crazy?
I can feel it in my eyes and ears.
Oh
I can do it.
Please don't close the door.
It's coming out.
It's just a guitar.
It's coming out. You can't move it.
No, it's not like that.
Ah!
I didn't have enough from the back earlier, so please put more on.
Okay, I'll put more on.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
You want to do more, don't you?
No, I just don't feel like it.
Then I have something for you.
What?
Do you want to know?
I want to know.
What is this?
I don't know.
I want to do a lot, so I brought it.
Open it.
Give it to me.
What?
Ah.
I have a good feeling about this.
Okay.
You're going to come back to life soon.
No, no, no.
That's not...
Ah.
Then, do you want to try it?
This is amazing.
Look at this.
It's getting hotter and hotter, isn't it?
Yes.
This is amazing.
Okay.
Ouch.
More?
Dad, this dance is amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good because it hurts, right?
Can you do it one more time?
I'm going to puke.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
It hurts so much.
I'm not done yet.
I'm not done licking it.
Hey, didn't you go faster than Manco?
That's not true.
No, that's not true.
It's not going to be hard, right?
It's not going to be hard.
I won't give it back to you today.
Oh, okay.
Open your mouth.
You still have it, don't you?
Oh, I see.
Chomo-san, what was that just now?
I didn't even touch it, but it was tickling me all day.
I feel better after drinking the alcohol.
It feels good.
Go this way.
It's completely different.
This is really...
It's more painful than before.
I feel like my stomach is going to explode.
Look at me.
I love you.
Yeah.
This is the first time I've been sandwiched like this.
It feels good.
Yeah, it feels good.
I get even more excited when I see your face.
Really?
Do you like it?
No, it's my first time.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to go into my nipples.
What?
My nipples don't feel good at all.
Really?
You've been in there all this time.
I can't do this anymore.
Are you reacting?
Yes, I am.
You are moving.
Yes.
It feels good.
Tighten your tongue.
Yes.
Tickle it.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this anymore.
Oh my god.
I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because I feel so good.
I can't do this anymore.
Of course it is!
My sweet potato!
It feels so good!
It does!
Can you hold it for me?
Of course I can!
Please let me hold it for you.
It hurts!
I don't want to do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore, what am I going to do?
I love you, Shino.
You're amazing.
I'm so happy.
My hands hurt.
I'm scared.
I can't do this.
I can't take it anymore.
Mmm.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore.
Wait a minute.
My nipples too.
I can't move anymore.
It hurts.
Ah, it feels good, doesn't it?
Thank you very much.
Please let me release everything that was in my body.
Please.
Oh
It's okay, it's okay.
It's so good!
Please, eat more.
Okay.
I can't take it anymore.
This is amazing, isn't it?
Yes.
My mouth is burning.
Oh
It's good, isn't it?
I don't know what to do, but I can't move.
You can't move?
You don't want to eat it?
You know what to do, don't you?
I'm going to eat it all by myself.
Do you like it?
Please give it to me.
I can't open my mouth.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to stop?
I can't even stretch my legs.
Really?
It feels so good.
I'm so excited to die.
I'm going to go crazy.
I can't do this anymore.
My head hurts!
Can I touch your head?
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Hurry up!
Okay, I got it.
It's so hot!
Oh
I can't feel anything.
I can't breathe.
It's good even if you eat slowly.
My face is melting.
Don't worry.
Your face will be fine.
Oh
Oh, my God.