Hey.
Oh, hi, how are you?
You're still here.
Yeah, I've still got your presentation to finish.
Yeah, I'm working on a lot of things too right now.
Pretty tired, actually.
Yeah, me too.
Um, do you want to maybe go get some coffee?
Oh, I'd love a coffee.
Yeah.
Let's do it. I need a break.
Yeah, I, um...
I really like it here in Paris.
Yeah?
Yeah.
It's like, kind of sexy, almost.
I don't know what you mean.
I'm so glad you come over from America, you know?
Yeah, me too. It was kind of boring compared to this.
Yeah.
Yeah, this place is really...
Yeah, it's good, isn't it? You don't like London, do you?
No.
That place was a bore.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm really happy you came over here.
Yeah, are you?
Yeah.
What was that?
Well, I just got the hots for you to be honest.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know why. It's so foreign.
I think I really like her. You must know that. I like her a lot.
I'm guessing like you too.
Look at those big tits. I love them.
Do you?
Yeah.
What do you like about them?
I love these tits. They shine off so well.
I think they're real, you know.
Really?
They're real.
You just keep showing them off all the time.
Maybe.
Maybe I want to catch her attention.
I'll say.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Oh yeah.
Do you want to see the red hair again?
I'd love to see it.
Can you show me?
Can you say please?
Please.
Pretty please.
Oh fuck yeah.
Wow.
Look at that.
Oh, let's see, look at this.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Wow, look at that.
Fuck yeah.
Oh
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Can you see this?
Yeah.
Can you suck it?
You want me to suck it and you take my cock?
Yeah
Oh, fuck
Mmmmm
Oh
Fuck yes
Mmmmm
Oh
It's so good
Not too strong
Don't be like that
Ah, f**k it
F**k it now
What are you doing?
Do you know what I'm doing?
F**k it, f**k it
What are you doing?
Don't f**k with me
F**k it, don't f**k with me
Nice
Oh
Oh my god
Good girl
You're a good girl, eh?
Oh
oh
you like that
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, that's so...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck, yes.
Oh.
Mmm.
Oh my God, ok.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Oh, oh my God.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, get it...
Oh shit!
Did he take...?
Yes!
Oh my God!
Oh...
Yes!
Mmm.
Oh
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Thank you God.
Oh, you look good. You look like a little sweaty pussy.
Yeah.
Little pussy.
Oh.
You look so good.
Yeah.
Oh.
You're so little pussy.
Please.
Oh.
Sucker, sucker, sucker.
Oh god, oh yes.
Oh god, yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh man.
Fuck, fucking, fuck.
Put the shit out of that pussy, please.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, yes.
JOANNA Please.
CLYDE We have to get out of here.
JOANNA Please, oh, hey.
Oh, oh.
Oh, cut.
Cut, yeah, oh, my god.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
Oh, oh.
Oh my god, it's so hard.
Hey, what's up?
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh
Oh, yes!
Oh!
Oh, oh!
Yes!
Oh, yes, yes!
Yes, yes!
Yes!
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
It's so hot.
Oh. Oh.
It's so...
killer.
Oh.
I love you so much.
Oh you love that pussy don't you?
Oh my god, he's gorgeous.
Oh good God, what's going on?
Yeah, I just want it so bad.
It's in there.
Oh my God, yes yes.
Fuck, oh it's fucking good.
Fuck, it's in here.
Oh, oh, oh my god, it's so deep in there.
Oh, oh, yes, fucking pound that, pound that pussy, fucking pound it.
Oh, fucking pound it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, oh shit, oh shit.
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
Like that.
Something like that.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
You like that.
Oh fuck.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
I can't touch my tits.
I can't touch my tits yet.
Um, mmm, mmm, oh, oh, mm, yes.
Oh, yes, mm, yes, mm, yes.
Yes, mm, mm, mm.
Oh, my, yeah, huh, ah, yeah.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Ohh, oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh my goodness, ah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh my god!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh my god, yes!
Oh!
Yes!
Oh god!
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Just a bit more, just a bit more.
Oh yeah, just like that, yeah, just like that.
Yes. Oh, yes.
Oh, fuck me, please.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God, yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, shit, yes, please, please.
Please, fuck me.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yes.
Yes. Oh, God.
Ooh.
Oh
Can you finger up my ass, please?
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you're fine.
It's all right.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, treat me like a good girl.
Yes, make me a bad girl.
Give him the baptiste, give him the baptiste.
No, I'm fucking up.
Pretend that you're sleeping with me.
Yeah.
Oh my fucking God.
Oh my God, so close to making me fucking come.
Oh my god, so close to making me fucking crazy.
Oh, fuck it.
Look at that.
So fucking close.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Oh
Oh my fucking...
Oh yes yes yes yes
Oh my gosh oh you f**k me
Yeah
No way
You're so dumb
Oh no, come just yet
Come just yet
Oh no
Oh
Oh my God
Oh yeah, I should probably get back to work.
Oh yeah, we have a lot of work to do.