🎵
Welcome! I'm Haruka.
I hope you feel good today.
Excuse me.
Thank you for your invitation.
Thank you for the recommendation.
Are you going home from work today?
Yes.
Then I will heal your tiredness.
Please.
Do you like kissing?
Can I take off my tie?
Please.
Your body is warm.
It's so warm.
I'm so excited.
It looks hot, so I'll take off your shirt.
Please.
Do you like it here?
I like it.
It looks good.
I'll lick your mouth, too.
Okay.
Can I open this one?
I have to open it, right?
Yes.
Can I take this one out too?
Please.
It's so hard.
Can I see how hard it is?
Can I look at you?
Can I touch you?
It feels good
Please relax
Is it okay if I heal it with my mouth this time?
Please
I'll wipe it
There's something salty
I'm sorry
It's delicious
Do you feel good in your body?
It feels really good
Can I touch your butt?
Your butt?
Are you okay?
It's okay.
You like this, don't you?
I'll give you a lot of it.
Do you like your butt?
I love it.
Please touch it.
Okay.
I'm going to lick a lot.
Is it okay if I take it out?
No, it's okay.
Did it feel good?
It felt good.
Please come again.
Thank you for your hard work today.
I'm a little tired, so I want you to heal me a lot.
Okay, I'll heal you a lot.
Thank you so much for coming to see me.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
Do you like it?
It's really good.
Thank you.
I'll give you a lot of massages with this.
Can I kiss you?
I kissed you a lot.
I'm getting nervous.
I'll give you a massage.
How do you feel?
I'm going to give you a lot of massages.
You're really angry here.
Right?
Yeah.
How about your waist?
My waist hurts a lot.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
I'll be nice to you.
How about this side?
How's your butt?
Your butt is also stiff, isn't it?
The customer is warm.
Are you nervous?
I've been nervous since a while ago.
Don't be nervous.
Relax.
Then, I'll do something more comfortable for you, Haruka.
What? What?
Get on my lap.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
Can I touch you?
Do you like being touched here?
I'm not good at touching.
Oh, really?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you want to take off your pants?
Yes, it feels good.
Then, let's take off your pants.
It's embarrassing.
Come here.
You have a lot of hair.
Do you have a lot of hair?
I'll make you feel better.
I'll give you a massage.
Can I touch your nipples?
Can I?
Sure.
I'll touch your nipples.
Your nipples are very tight.
When I touch your nipples,
I get nervous.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good to move?
It feels good.
I want you to come closer to me.
It's okay.
Can you see me from here?
I'll look at you from a distance.
I can smell your scent.
It's getting harder and harder.
You look good.
It feels great.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
I'll do something more comfortable for you.
Turn your head.
Do you like your nipples?
Oh, that's great.
You like your nipples, don't you?
It's getting harder.
Does it feel good?
Then I'll touch this nipple, too.
It feels good.
Do you want me to make your nipples feel good?
I'm going to lick the other nipple.
I'm going to tickle you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it feels really good.
Put your tongue out.
It's good.
Haruka-chan, you're so close.
Since when have you been so close?
It's a secret.
A secret?
It's true.
What are you going to do next?
Next, I'm going to give you a massage.
It's harder than before.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
It's gotten really hard, hasn't it?
It's really hard.
Right?
I'm going to pat your head.
How do I do this?
Haruka is going to give you a massage.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It's really good.
Do you want me to lick you?
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
It feels so good.
It's moving.
It's amazing.
It's like a bathtub.
I don't want to see Haruka's face.
It's like a cloud.
It feels so good.
Do you want to see your baby?
Then, I'll show you my baby.
It's beautiful.
It's good, isn't it?
Ah, it feels good.
San, Shobu-san, can you pet me?
Ah, there, there, there.
Ah, it feels good.
Can I massage your nipples with my hand?
Yes, you can.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Can you massage your chin?
Yes, it's very stimulating.
Make your chin feel good.
You have a lot of wrinkles.
Look at this.
You're rubbing your butt from the top of your swimsuit.
You're so cute.
It feels good.
Your butt is amazing.
It feels so good.
I did it
Hey
Kano
Don't you want to do a massage in your belly button?
What?
A massage in your belly button
Is that okay?
It's okay
It's okay for the customers
Really?
Really
Do you want to put it in?
I'm going to put it in
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
You can touch it a little bit.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Touch your nipples and your heart.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Touch it a lot and be healed.
I can't do this anymore.
Oh, my God!
Is there a bell in there?
There are a lot of bells in there.
Do you feel good in Haruka's belly?
It feels so good.
I think it's okay.
How do I do this?
Did you get a cramp?
Let's start from the back.
From the back?
Don't you have a cramp in your waist?
It's too tight.
I can't move my shoulders.
Should I spread it out?
Your butt is pretty too
No, it's embarrassing
Try to make it more intense
Haruka, look this way
I want you to feel good
Let's feel good
Feels good
Let's feel good together
Together?
I want to feel good
I feel so much better now!
Can I take it out?
Sure!
Oh crap!
It hurts!
I'm getting excited when Haruka looks at me.
Look at me a lot.
Look at my nipples too.
I'm standing up.
Look at me a lot.
I'm about to cry.
Can you look at me closer?
Thank you.
I can't breathe
I can't talk
I can't talk so
I can't breathe.
I'm all wet.
Can you make me more excited?
It's hot.
I'm scared.
Look at me.
Feel better.
Do you want me to massage your feet a lot?
I can't do it.
Look at me.
I can do it.
Let's get comfortable together.
It feels good.
This one is good too.
I'll give you a lot of food.
Come here.
Do you like it too, Tsukubi?
Yes, I like it.
Wow, it's so cute.
Tsukubi, come here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll make you feel good too.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I can feel something coming out.
You like this part, don't you?
Yes.
Let me tell you something that feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Look at the mango.
Yes, I like it.
You like to be touched with your feet, don't you?
I like it.
You're a pervert.
Yes.
I'll do this for you.
This feels good, too.
Does it?
Yes.
Your feet feel good, too.
I'll make your hands feel good, too.
You like this part.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Do you want me to be strong?
Yes.
Oh, that's great.
I'm going to touch your head, too.
Yes.
Can I look at your chin up close?
Yes
It looks like it's going to rain tonight
It's so hot
It feels good
Let's smell our blood
This feels good?
I'll give you a lot of blood
Do you want me to take it out?
Yes.
It's okay. I'm watching you.
You can take a lot out.
I'm watching you.
It's okay.
Please.
It's okay. Take a lot out.
It smells really gross.
You took a lot out, didn't you?
Yes.
Haruka also felt good.
Welcome to J.K. Imekura.
There are three courses.
The first one is the sister kinda ichaicha course.
The second one is the maid gohoshi course.
The third one is the J.K. train chikan course.
Which course would you like to take?
Well...
Then...
J.K. Chikan Course.
Okay.
This way, please.
Let's get started.
Okay.
Welcome. Please take a seat in this chair.
Please take a seat in this chair.
First, I will massage your stomach.
Yes, please.
Please sit down.
Excuse me from your back.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Excuse me.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It's nice to have a sailor girl play with soap.
Really? I'm glad.
I'm glad you chose this course.
It's a pretty popular course.
It is.
Of course it is.
Can I give you a more comfortable massage?
Yes, please.
I'm going to take it off.
You're going to take it off.
You're so cute.
It's embarrassing.
Can I do this side?
It's already there.
Is it comfortable?
Yes.
Is this side comfortable too?
Are you happy?
Is there anyone who can do this?
Sometimes
There must be someone who can do this
This feels good
It looks good
You look good
This feels good
Can I do this too?
Your arm?
Do you like it?
Does it feel good?
Yes
It feels good
Move your hips more
How was it?
It feels good
Does it feel good?
From this side
Can I massage your feet too?
Yes
Oh, that's how you do it
Like this?
This feels good
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Let's try to make this side more comfortable.
Does it feel good?
It looks very comfortable.
Yes, it does.
I'm going to put on my underwear.
I'm going to massage your buttocks.
That's crazy.
I'm going to wash the bubbles cleanly this time.
I'm going to wash the bubbles cleanly.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Do you feel any discomfort?
Yes, I'm fine.
Let's go to the bath together.
Would you like to take a bath with me?
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I hope it makes you feel much better.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Your body is getting warm.
Let's make a phone call together.
Okay.
I'm going to apply lotion on your back.
Does it feel good?
This feels good too.
That's good.
I'm going to put on some lotion.
You're putting on a lot of lotion.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
How is it? Does this feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good for me too.
It feels so good.
I'm going to massage your feet too.
It feels so good too.
It feels so good.
Next time, would you like to get a massage?
I'm going to put it on.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'll be the other way around.
Sir, would you like to apply lotion to my butt?
I'll do it for you.
Okay.
I want you to lick my butt too.
Let's do it one more time.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You guys are getting excited.
You've gotten used to it, haven't you?
It's so hot!
I want to put it in as soon as possible.
I'll put it in.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's all in.
It feels good.
It hurts so much!
Let's go
It feels so good
It feels good. Please, come on in from the back like this.
Please, can I?
It feels good.
Here I go. Here I go.
I can't stop thinking about you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't do this!
It feels so good!
It's so hot!
Did it feel good?
Please show me your face.