Thank you.
I'm going to show you what a good teacher can do.
Teacher's underwear.
Do you want to see the back?
Teacher's underwear is big.
Can you see it?
Do you want to touch it?
It's getting bigger and bigger.
You're excited, aren't you?
Come closer to me.
Your chin is getting bigger, isn't it?
Show me your tongue.
It's delicious.
How's the soba?
Do you like the soba?
It's getting harder and harder.
Does it feel good?
Go to sleep.
You've gotten so big.
I can tell from your pants.
Are you that excited?
Are you excited?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's very tight.
Does it feel good?
How does it feel?
I'm full, right?
This time,
I'll rub it on your big butt.
Do you know that it's touching your butt?
Yes, Dr.Megwin is also on your back.
How can you bear it if you get so puffy?
I'll make you feel better this time.
Look at me.
It's okay.
You'll feel better.
I'll make you so puffy.
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
Do you know?
It's very refreshing.
Are you embarrassed?
It's okay.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Show me more.
It's very big.
Look.
Hey, do you feel good about your teacher?
You're sensitive, aren't you?
Do you feel good?
Your tongue is hot.
Which part of your tongue feels best?
Do you feel good?
Tell me how you feel.
It's very swollen here.
There's a lot of it.
It's very hard.
What's wrong with you?
Are you going to be okay?
But you can't do it if you keep doing it.
Please be patient.
Please put up with it a lot.
It feels good, right?
It was really hard, right?
I'm so nervous.
I can't do this.
Hang in there.
It feels really good.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's so hard to breathe.
Oh my god, dad.
There's a lot of it, isn't there?
Does it feel good?
It's so full.
It feels good when you put it in your stomach, doesn't it?
Here, give it to me.
That's right, isn't it?
Give it to me.
Give me a lot of it.
We'll be right back.
Today is a special day.
Sit down. Did you bring your study tools?
Then let's get started.
Put your study tools on the desk.
Let's start from the previous one.
Can you open the page?
Do you remember it properly?
That's right. It's from here.
Solve this problem.
Try to solve the problem.
Do you understand?
Why don't you understand?
You studied before, didn't you?
Read it properly.
Hey, your hands are frozen.
How is it?
Hey, are you concentrating properly?
It's no good if you don't concentrate.
I'm here to study today.
どこ見てるの?ダメでしょ?ちゃんとノート見て。
そう、こら、全然集中できてないじゃない?さっきから。
先生のことばっか見てるでしょ?ダメ。ちゃんと勉強しないと怒っちゃうよ。
Hey!
You can't do that!
Focus!
Hmm?
Hey!
You can't do that!
You can't!
Hey!
If you don't study,
your test score will go down.
Can't you focus with this?
It can't be helped.
It's just a little, so I'm sure you'll make it a secret.
How is it?
A kiss with your teacher.
Does it feel good?
Let's do it again.
You wanted to touch your teacher's boobs, didn't you?
It's okay to touch it.
How is it?
Eh? You can't tell from the top of your clothes?
It can't be helped.
I'll take it off for you.
You wanted to see it, didn't you?
How is it?
Is your underwear cute?
I'm so happy.
Here, touch it.
Do you want to touch it?
Is it soft?
You can touch it a lot.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to see it?
It's okay.
Because it's special.
Touch this too.
It's very soft, isn't it?
It feels good, it feels really good.
Hey, can you hold it for me?
It feels really good.
Please inhale more.
Is it good, Sensei?
Do you want to see the bottom too?
It's embarrassing, but I'll show you.
Look closely.
How is it?
Do you know that I'm using it?
It's okay.
Do you know that I'm angry?
Do you want to see more?
It's okay.
Take a good look.
How do you like it?
Do you like it?
This feels good.
Touch it more.
Can you touch the bottom too?
Here.
Put it in slowly.
Feels good.
It feels so good.
Move a lot.
Look behind you.
Can you see me?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's embarrassing to look at me like that, isn't it?
You can't do that.
Touch me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you miss me?
Did it hurt at all?
It feels so good.
I'm so tired.
Do you want me to lick you?
I can't help it.
Then I'll make you feel better.
Wow, you can't wait that long?
I can tell that you're wet because of your pants.
Show me more.
Why are you wet here?
Oh, you're embarrassed.
It's okay.
This is how you feel when you're angry.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to make you feel better?
Show me how you feel.
You're so hot.
Does it feel good to be a teacher?
It's so hot.
You're all wet.
Look at your face.
It feels good.
Does this feel good?
I'm surprised.
Does this feel good too?
You can't go there yet.
There's a lot of alcohol coming out.
It's no good, right?
There's something more comfortable.
Come here.
It's warm, isn't it?
It's really crumpled.
Do you know that the teacher's clitoris is also warm?
It feels really good.
It's tickling me.
Does it feel that good?
I went to the toilet.
Hey, Sensei.
I want to go to the toilet now.
Let's go to the bed.
Come here.
Here, sleep here.
Do you want me to put it in your ear?
Here.
You want to put it in.
Do you feel the tickling?
You're so used to it, aren't you?
I'm excited too.
Why are you staring at me?
I'm going to puke.
Look at me.
How is it?
I'm going to puke.
Does it feel good?
Is this not enough?
You don't want to go in?
More?
Where? Around here?
I went in here
Feels good
Is it warm?
It's really hard
It's hard, isn't it?
Be patient.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to lick here, too.
How is it?
I want to lick you.
Does it feel good?
Look at my butt.
Look at me.
How is it?
I can't see you.
You can touch me.
Can you touch me from behind?
Come closer.
Are you angry?
I touched you a lot.
A lot.
Even though I was here, you don't hate me, do you?
The doctor is gone.
I can taste the doctor's rage.
Hey, let's get better together.
You feel better now, don't you?
Do you feel better now?
When you get better, I'll do more for you, okay?
I'm a boy, so please be more manly.
Come on, hurry up and be manly.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Come here.
Shiki-chan, come here.
I'm going to make you look like a man.
Here.
You understand, right?
Hey, look.
What does this mean?
It's not good at all.
It's here, here.
Hey.
Look.
Then take it off.
What?
Take it off.
It's not what, take it off.
Look at this.
It's a jersey.
No, it's not.
Look at this.
You look a little manly.
You too.
You can't do it, right?
Do you want me to take it off for you?
Look at this.
You can't be manly.
Do you understand?
Like this.
Hold this.
Be more manly.
More and more manly.
How is it?
You are becoming more and more manly.
You understand, don't you?
Does it feel good?
Do you feel good?
Come closer
What's wrong?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
It feels strange, doesn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
How do you feel?
But you don't look manly at all.
Don't worry about it.
Be manly by yourself.
Keep an eye on him.
You are so manly.
Do you feel good?
Keep an eye on him.
What's wrong?
Your teeth are all messed up.
I'm sorry.
You look so happy.
Wow.
How do you feel? Do you want to be manly?
Yes, I want to be manly.
If you want to be manly, come over here.
Wow, you're getting caught.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Then, let's say you want to be more manly.
What?
Turn your butt to this side.
Put your hands here.
That's right.
Put your hands in front of you.
That's good.
Look.
You can take it off one by one.
How is it?
Have you become a man?
Yes.
I'm looking this way.
Does it feel good?
Wow.
You look like a grandma.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
You don't feel like you're going to be a grandma?
No.
Do you want to do this too?
Can you make it more manly?
How is it?
You can see it clearly, right?
Yes, I can see it clearly.
Wow, that's amazing.
You have a lot of pimples.
You are a very manly man.
Thank you very much.
Now, please turn this way.
Okay.
Yes
Are you happy now?
Come here
Is it good?
Wow
How is it?
How do you like it?
It feels good.
You're becoming more manly again.
How do you become manly?
Do you want me to do anything else?
What?
Do you want to see it?
I want to see your boobs.
You want to see my boobs?
Yes.
I can't help it.
I'll give you a massage.
Like this?
How is it?
Is this okay?
It's so beautiful
Do you think you can be a man?
Wow
Something is coming out
What's wrong?
Are you at your limit?
Do you want to touch it?
Is it okay?
Then, stretch your hand while moving
I'll touch this side too
How is it?
Come over here.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
Like this?
Do you want me to do it like a man?
Yes.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Open your mouth.
Amazing.
How is it?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
You should do it in a manly way.
Do it in a manly way.
I will.
You guys look like a great couple, don't you?
Okay, you can go back now.
Ken-kun, you're up.
Your fever has gone down, right? You have to go back to class.
I don't want to study.
You don't want to study?
But if you don't study, everyone will leave you.
Did you study?
I studied.
Really?
Yes.
But I don't think your fever has gone down yet.
Really?
Yes.
It's okay.
Is that so?
Yes.
Cheer up and go to class.
There are only two teachers here now.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
What kind of man do you have a crush on?
What's wrong with you?
I thought your clothes were cute today.
Is that so?
It's the same as always.
You have a big chest.
What's wrong with you?
Why so suddenly?
Don't touch me.
If you do, I'll go back to study.
No way.
Then I'll stay here forever.
What should I do?
Just a little bit is fine.
If I touch you a little, will you leave class?
Yes.
Then just a little bit.
That's all you have to do.
Since when did you start growing up?
I was in the 4th grade of elementary school.
What?
Do you want to know?
I want to know.
It can't be helped.
D cup.
Wow.
It's a secret to everyone.
How are you?
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I feel much better.
But it's because of the clothes.
Is it bad?
Yes.
I feel dissatisfied.
It's really just a little bit.
You will go to class, right?
Yes, I will.
Just a little bit.
You are wearing such a stylish underwear.
Isn't it cute?
Your underwear is cute, isn't it?
There are people in my class who wear this kind of blusher.
Why do you know that?
Because I often peep into their underwear.
What?
You're an H, aren't you?
Yes.
Sensei.
Do you know how to make your breasts look beautiful?
Is there such a thing?
Yes.
It's one way to make your breasts look beautiful.
Why do you know such a thing?
What are you doing?
I was on TV the other day.
Oh, I see.
How should I do it?
Here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Do it like this.
You can see it.
If you do that, your cheeks will come out well.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Can I lick it?
Please.
Will you take a class?
I will.
I see.
It's just a little bit.
That's all I can do.
You're so desperate.
How did it go? Did you finish your class?
You're not done yet?
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
I couldn't do it well when I was about to have sex.
Really?
How about you, Tamata?
Well, I wanted to be a good boy.
Is this your first time?
I don't have much experience.
You can't be a good boy.
Please, tell me.
The teacher?
Yes.
No one is coming, right?
I don't want to be embarrassed again.
It can't be helped.
Will you promise me that you won't tell anyone?
Yes, I will.
Then,
what should I do?
What do you want me to do?
First,
I want to know
what's going on with women.
You want to know that?
Do you want to know such a place?
I can't see well, and I don't know where to put it.
Well, it's embarrassing.
Then I'll show you.
Open it.
Can you do it?
What are you doing?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Look at the back of your feet.
You can't smell it.
Your feet are covered in sweat.
It stinks.
You can't smell it anymore.
It smells salty.
You like the back of your feet.
You want to see here, don't you?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You can touch it.
Does it hurt?
Don't look at me like that.
You've been injured this far.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Why are you showing off?
It's embarrassing because I'm sticking out.
You're so arrogant that you stick out.
How old were you when you got hurt?
How old was I?
I was in 6th grade.
That's early.
It feels so good.
Can I put my hand in?
Sure.
I don't know what it is.
What does it look like?
The part I'm touching right now is clitoris.
What about this?
What is this?
There is a hole in the bottom.
There is no hole.
It's a little lower.
I don't know.
Show me.
I'll show you.
It looks good, doesn't it?
How is it?
There.
That's where it's supposed to be.
That's where the clitoris is.
You were supposed to put it in here.
That's right.
What about this hole?
That's the hole in the butt.
Hmm.
How is it?
I want to see it closer.
Sure.
Come here for a second.
Oh.
Can you see it?
Is it good?
It's good.
How is it?
Do you like it?
Did you see it clearly?
Yes.
Do you like it?
Do you want me to make you feel good?
Make me feel good
I want you to feel good
How do you want me to make you feel good?
I've been reading recently
Have you ever been taught to play with a pie?
Playing with a pie?
Do you want me to pinch your cheeks with my boobs?
Yeah, I want to try that.
I've never done that before, but I'll do my best.
Wow, you're so chubby.
Does it feel good?
I'll make you feel good.
I'll check it out for you.
Wow, it's hot.
Were you that excited?
Can I lick it?
I can feel the heat in your mouth.
Does it feel good?
I'll massage your boobs.
It feels good to touch your nipples.
It's here, right?
How do you feel?
Are you feeling better now?
Yes, I feel better now.
I feel so good.
Yes, it feels so good.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Will you go to class with this?
I can't.
You can't?
Why not?
Can you let me have sex with you once?
What?
Do you want to have sex with me?
Yes.
I want to.
Then, will you promise me?
That you will get good grades in class.
I will.
Really?
It's just one time. Can you put it in?
Put it in first.
I got it.
It's here.
Here?
Slowly.
Is it warm?
It's warm.
It feels good.
It's so hard.
But if it's like this, it's not in here.
Yeah.
You know, right?
What should I do if I put it all the way in?
Like this?
It's in.
Wow, you have a beautiful face.
Is it painful?
Yes, it's okay.
Wow, it's amazing.
I want to touch you more.
It's very painful.
It feels good.
Can you see? Can you see my back?
Can you see properly?
You want me to take a picture from behind, right?
The position of the hole is so big that I can't see it well.
Don't make a mistake.
Please open it a little.
It's here.
It's big.
Do you like your big butt?
Oh, it's so good.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
Is there a lot of it here?
Yes, there is.
Oh, no, doctor.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
Are you okay?
I can hear your voice.
Do you like me that much?
Let me put you on the bed.
I want to move too.
Come on, lie down there.
I'll make you feel better.
Can you do it again?
I'm scared.
I'm so tired.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
I'm sure you like your teacher's butt too.
Right?
Oh, my uterus.
Are you feeling good?
Yes.
Oh, you're hitting it so hard.
What's wrong? You have a big butt.
Right?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I'm so happy.
Yes, you are.
It feels so good, doesn't it?
Can you follow me from behind?
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
Put your hands in front of you.
Like this.
Wow.
Amazing.
Do you like your butt so much?
Yes, yes.
Don't just look at your butt.
Look from behind.
Yes.
Oh, it's full of water, isn't it?
Do you want to kiss me?
Is it good?
I can't do this.
It's hot.
Did you have a good time?
You can go to sleep.
元素記号を勉強する科学式とは、 化学物質を元素の構成で表現する表記法です。
例えば、水だとH2O、 水素Hと酸素Oの元素から成り立っているわけです。
この様々な元素を歌で覚えていきますよ。
それでは、いきますからね。
I don't remember at all.
What?
I don't know.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
What's this?
H.
No, it's Sueso. It's written, right?
Yes.
Did you write a notebook?
Really?
Yes.
H is in front of I.
First, the scientific formula is H2O.
Hydrogen, oxygen, what is this?
There is a lot of English written on it.
Yes.
You are studying science, not English.
Do you want to go again?
I learned it.
Then please say it.
Mr. Kento on the right side of the edge.
What are you doing?
I don't know that.
What is Clark in the first place?
What does Clark mean?
Clark is...
In the old days...
You don't care about that, right?
Let me teach you an easy way to remember it.
Okay.
I think everyone can understand this song.
Edgy pervert
Rich bed
It's a bed with cute boobs in it.
That's easy to remember.
One more time?
Here we go.
Continue.
Echina
Echina?
Hentai
Rinchina
Bed
Boinde
Cute
Oppai
Feratte
寝る
変な
漫画にある
シコシコ
ビュー
精子が
クリトリスに
アラアラ
かかった
分かった?
何か棒読みすぎるな
Sensei, you don't seem to have any feelings.
What?
You always say you have feelings.
It's easier to remember when you use your body.
How is it?
I can't dance.
How?
Sensei, if you do it like this...
What?
If you do it like this...
What do you mean by doing it like this?
You're an edgy pervert.
An edgy pervert?
What?
What do you think?
I'm going to dance like an edgy pervert.
Hurry up and dance.
Like a cute pervert?
No, like an edgy pervert.
You don't have a rich bed, do you?
I don't have a rich bed.
I thought this was a bed.
This is a desk.
I'm going to clean it today.
Wait a minute.
Like a cute pervert?
What's wrong?
Do you want to learn it?
Boiner
I learned it in the middle
Say it
Echina boiner
No, what are you saying?
Echina hentai
Try to remember it
Remember it?
Sensei, go ahead and say it.
Echino Hentai Richina Betto
Richina Betto
Boinde Cute Na
Sensei, what's this?
Boinde Cute Na Oppai
Cute Na Oppai
Sera Te Neru
You need to study properly.
It's easier to remember while you're doing it.
That's right.
Do you really remember?
It's so cute.
It's cute.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
It's easier to learn while you're doing it.
Please help me.
Let's go.
I can't take this.
It's scary.
What?
It's getting wet.
It's all over.
My pants.
What's wrong, Sensei?
It must be painful.
F is good.
What was it again?
F to the end?
But isn't it okay to go all the way to the end?
You should change it, Sensei.
All the way to the end.
F. All the way to the end.
Like this. All the way to the end.
That's right.
See, Sensei.
All the way to the end.
Put your back out, Sensei.
Sensei, stand up.
All the way to the end.
What is N in Japanese?
What was it?
I forgot.
I'm going to sleep.
Sleep?
Is this how you sleep?
No.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep now.
You're going to sleep, aren't you?
I'm going to open your head.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
Thank you.