Jangan lupa SUBSCRIBE, LIKE, KOMEN dan SHARE...
What are you doing in a place like that?
Were you playing around and playing alone?
Rather than such a picture book, Rina will be your side dish.
You've been married, haven't you?
It's almost time.
I don't know why I'm doing this
That's how it is
I'm so tired
I don't think I can make it this month, Norman.
Do you think you can achieve your goal with that?
I'm sorry.
It's like you're saying goodbye to your mother.
Why are you so excited, Yamada-kun?
Do I have to say it?
Tell me.
My husband has a big chest.
My eyes hurt
What?
Mine?
Hamada-kun
You were so excited to see my boobs
Do you want to touch my boobs that much?
What?
I want to touch them
Then
From now on
You can't quit your job and get married
Okay?
How is it?
It's really big and soft
I'm getting excited again
Touch it
It's okay
How about my boobs?
It's softer than I thought
Does it feel good?
More than anything
Then, can you achieve this month's standards?
I'll do my best
If you do your best, you can touch my boobs more.
What are you doing?
This side is very good.
It's unfair.
Do it like this.
It's getting better and better.
What are you doing like this?
What?
Do it as usual.
That's right.
You always do it, don't you?
Hurry up.
Excuse me.
Wow.
Are you going home early?
Chief, I'm close.
What are you doing?
Oh.
Somehow I came here excited.
Look at me. I'm excited.
What?
How's your day?
How do you feel?
A lot
How is it?
It's very beautiful
Really?
It looks very good
You wanted to be looked down on like this, right?
Yes
I want to be looked down on by you
Do you want to see more?
I can't do this anymore...
What do you want to do, Chin-chin?
I want to go into the kitchen.
You're so big.
Chin-chin, open your mouth.
My back hurts.
It hurts!
It feels better now.
I'm scared.
Please look down.
Can you see me?
It hurts a little.
I'll do it like this.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
Can you see where it's open?
Can I take it out?
I can't
I feel refreshed
I can do my job
Does it feel good?
Can I peel it?
Look closely at Rina's skin.
How is it?
The gums are getting harder.
I want to touch Rina's boobs too.
Does it feel good?
I feel like I'm going to be born in a day.
Can I put some ointment on my nipples?
I feel like I'm going to puke.
I feel like I'm going to puke in a day.
I'm sorry, my chin is so sticky now.
My chin is also very sticky now.
Can I touch your belly button?
Feels good.
Your chin is so plump.
I can feel your chin.
Does your belly button feel good?
It's amazing.
I'm going to do a lot of it.
I'm scared.
I'm shaking.
I'm cold.
Don't look down on me.
I feel a little dizzy
Welcome home!
You came early
Hey, hey, hey
Let me show you
This
Camera
What is this?
It was a little cheap so I bought it
You bought it?
We are still newlyweds
So
Let's leave a lot of memories of the two of us
Take a picture
Why are you so close to me?
I think I'm going to puke
You're amazing
When I look down, my boobs are like this
It's like a mountain
It's nostalgic
Where do you want me to touch?
Can you show me with your fingers?
Here
I can't move my hips
There's a lot of saliva
It's dripping
It looks like it's going to explode
I'm going to mix it from the bottom of the kitchen
It's so hot
I'm tired
I'm used to it.
What were you doing during the day?
I can't do it because it's so visible.
Oh, my God.
I can feel it.
I have to go before it gets dark
I'm so tired
It feels so good
I wonder if I can come out more
This is amazing
Can you move?
It's wet.
It's too wet.
It hurts.
Look at this bra
I can see your boobs
It's fashionable, isn't it?
You can lick it right away
Does it feel good?
It feels good
I'm sorry.
I'll give you something to eat.
I'm scared.
It's getting harder and harder.
Take off your pants.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
I don't need it, don't need it
I don't need it
I want it
Touch my tongue
Here?
Do you want me to pet you?
Yes, pet me
Yes
It feels good
Do you want me to pet you?
Yes
Shhh
Mochi
Jinjin, do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good
Put your fingers in the bag
It's hot, isn't it?
It feels good.
It's getting hotter.
I can't eat it.
I can't take it anymore.
You can eat a lot.
Koko, do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
How is it?
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's so hot.
I can't do it
It's so hot!
Does it feel good to be rubbed like this?
I want you to do more
It's hot
I want you to take care of me from now on.
I'm worried about you.
I just took it out now.
I can't take it anymore.
Why?
I can't do it.
No, you can't.
You're still so weak.
I can't do it.
Let's do it again.
How about this?
I can do it.
You can do it, right?
I can't do it.
Are you still going to do it?
I still want to do it.
It hurts
What should I do?
Do you want me to do it again?
I can't
You want me to do it, don't you?
It hurts
I'm so sorry, my baby.
I can't do this anymore.
Terima kasih telah menonton!