Jangan lupa SUBSCRIBE, LIKE, KOMEN dan SHARE video ini.
Aaaaaa
Sampai jumpa di video selanjutnya
Tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak.
Aaaaah!
Tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak.
Aaaaaaaaaa
Tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak.
Jangan lupa like, share dan subscribe channel ini.
I can't stop crying because I'm so tired.
I'm sorry.
Bujuan, jian, jian, jian, jian, jian, jian.
I can't do it.
When did you drink that?
hmm
Horsi desu
I'm going to take it out.
You have to take it out a lot, don't you?
Who's going to take it out?
I'm going to put my neck down.
I don't want to say it.
You don't want to say it?
I don't understand.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry, mom.
Then I'll give you a lot of water.
It's almost done.
What is it?
It's okay, right?
I thought it was a baby
Terima kasih telah menonton!