Oh
Oji-san hentai.
Ii yo, suki no you ni kaede mite.
Sonna ni oshiri suki na no?
Oji-san no hanaiki de kusubuttai yo.
Sawatte mo ii yo, oshiri.
Sukino you ni sawatte mite.
Uji-san, you are so close to me.
I want you to do that much.
Do you want me to step on your butt?
Yes.
Then, Uji-san, try to lie down there.
Is that so?
Uji-san, I have something to tell you.
How is it?
It's good.
You didn't want to touch it, did you?
You're touching it yourself.
You're doing this, but you're excited?
Uncle, can you breathe? Are you okay?
Can you see?
Are you okay, Hoshi-san?
You feel good, don't you?
Does it feel good?
You like this kind of thing, don't you?
Then I'll give you a massage.
I'll give you a massage.
You like your butt, don't you?
You've been touching it all the time.
It's unfair that you're the only one who feels good.
Please make me feel good, too.
Let's make it feel good together.
Make it feel good.
It feels good.
You're good.
Even if you make a strange sound, it feels good.
I can feel the pain in my stomach.
I want you to make a sound that sounds like a dog, and lick it a lot.
It's so hard.
You made me feel good.
I'll make you feel good this time.
Please.
It's already like this.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to sit down and lick it.
What should I do?
Do you like my nipples?
Then drink a lot
Does it feel good?
Yes
It's getting more and more
You look cute when you smile
Please show me a lot of cute faces
hmm
What do you like to do?
I like to do a lot of things.
A lot of things?
Nero?
Kouyaku?
Sakepokkara yoroshio jiton
I want to get out of here as it is.
I want to get out of your butt.
Butt?
You like your butt.
Rub it.
早く擦りつけて 硬いの当たってる
おじさん変態 元硬くなってきた
太くなってる ねぇおじさん
変態チンポ汁 どれぐらい溜めてきたの?
3 days?
I have a lot of pain
I'm so tired.
I can't do it anymore.
I can feel the pain in my body.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh my god.
I'm going to make you feel better.
I haven't touched you yet.
Do you feel it even though you haven't touched your nipples yet?
Why are your nipples so big?
Why are you standing up?
Look at this side.
You are so sensitive.
You are cute.
I can feel you so much.
Show me your face more.
It's a very sensitive nipple.
It's cute.
Does it feel good?
See?
I love you so much
Are you okay?
Yeah
Or...
This?
What about this?
You like to be hugged?
You're such a pervert.
What? You don't like it?
You don't like it?
You can't touch it by yourself.
I'm going to make your chin like this.
It's amazing.
Even your chin is pink.
You don't like it?
What do you want me to do with this chin?
Jinpo, what do you want me to do?
What do you want me to do?
How do you want me to do it?
Like this?
You're so sensitive.
You're so cute, Jinpo.
You're so nice, Jinpo.
Hey, what is this?
What is it?
Hey, I haven't done anything yet.
From the tip of the Hentai Chinpo.
There's a lot of slimy juice coming out.
I like this kind of thing.
Does it feel good?
My body is shaking.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's coming out.
Amazing.
It's coming out when you eat it.
There's a lot of energy in it.
It's so cute.
You don't have to hold back.
Yes.
Make a lot of noise and feel it.
Feel it.
Ippai jutta...
Daiseishi...
Konno ni ippai tamete tanda...
Omae wa ga kareru...
飲んじゃった
気持ちよかった?
仕越えてあげる
いいしんどい
気持ちいい
本当にいいしんどい
I love you so much.
What do you like about him?
I like to be hugged by him
You are so soft
Ah, it smells good.
What's the smell here?
It smells like a dead body.
It's a beautiful hole, isn't it?
You don't have any hair at all, do you?
It's beautiful and delicious, isn't it?
Ah, I'm getting a little tired.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's a really good shiitake, isn't it?
Both of them are good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's the best shibito.
Oh, it's coming out.
Be careful.
I can't do it.
I can feel it.
I can hear it.
It's amazing.
I feel like I'm going to burst into tears.
Oh, directly?
Directly?
It's amazing.
It's like this.
Do you want me to lick you?
Nammete, ippai nammete
Nani kore?
Koi ka monte
Ah, it's hot.
Do you want to go?
I want to go.
It's hot.
I want you to go.
I want to go.
Oh, that's bad.
Oh, that's painful.
My neck is in trouble.
Shin-ko, it's getting harder.
It's getting harder.
Is it better to be hard?
Yes, it's better to be hard.
Oh, it's getting harder.
Ah, my eyes.
My eyes.
It hurts so much.
It feels so good to be in such a good place.
It feels so good.
Ayu-chan
No, no, no, no, no
Feels good
How is it?
Ah, that's not good.
It's not good to turn it.
Ah.
Hey, your butt is shaking.
Hey.
Great.
That's right, put your butt on.
That's right.
Ah, I want to do more.
Can I hit you in the back?
I want to do more.
Ah, I want to do more.
Ah, it hurts.
Look, raise your leg.
Look, your throat hurts.
Can you see it?
It hurts so much.
Your throat hurts so much.
It hurts.
I want to go home.
It's so painful.
It's over.
I'm so sorry.
Kimchi.
Åh, åh, åh, åh, åh, åh.
Ah, it feels good there.
Does it feel good?
I'm happy.
Ah, it feels good there.
I can't take it anymore.
Will you go with me?
I'm so happy to see you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I had a lot of fun.
You look cute after so much hard work.
Please don't film me too close.
近くで撮らなきゃいけない
はい、じゃあ本日は以上です ありがとうございました
ありがとうございました、イェーイ
どうだった?
撮影、すごい楽しかったです
あっという間、こんなに早く終わるとは思わなかった
そう、結構ボリュームが
いっぱい、いろんなコーナー撮らせてもらって
いろんなお尻いっぱい撮ってもらってたんで
こんな早くあると順調で何よりでしたすごい楽しかったんではいありがとうございます
あんまりおしりももってそんなにないんですよ私
あんまないんだよね
あのねバンコーナーでそういうバッグを目とかおしりをフューチャーってのがあったんですけど
おしりほんとまるまる1本ってほんとにもう全然数えれるくらい
二本目ぐらいじゃないですかねたぶん確かにこんなにかわいいとさ後ろから撮ってもらってないよって思うよすごい近い近い
すごい近いそうなんでなんか少なくてだからすごいお尻がなんかあんまりこう自信なかったんですけど
でもちゃんとシリコキとかでガンガンみんな発射してたよね
Thank you very much.
ちょっと自己紹介しておこう自己紹介今今今はいマリオン専属女優の友田彩香ですともちんて呼んでください
はいえっとまあ先ほども言ってくださった通り
マリオン初の専属女優ということでえっとあとマリオンの宣伝部長というかありもいろんなとこで広めていけるように私が
今中なんですけども、マリオンすごいフェチ系だったり、いろんな作品がありますので、それにも私がバコバコいろんな作品に出ていって、
まだまだ現役でいたいので、なのでぜひマリオンと友田彩佳を応援よろしくお願いします。
すばらしい。
Yoroshiku onegai shimasu!
Hai!
Haha
Jaa
Hai
Surisazu yuttokkai
Tsurunde!
Hahaha
Ima ka? Ima?
Hai!
Eto 85
Hahaha
Ue kara ue kara
Hai
Dei
Tabu
S62
Kana?
Dei
Hippu ga
Eto
Tei
Itte
Tan desu kedo
Hmm
Konkai no
Sakuhin de
Ni
Henko
Toi
Koto de
Hai
Profil o
Naoshitai
Tomo
Ima
Ha
Hai
またひとつおしりこれからおしりを武器にまた武器を増やせたということで
これからもおしりをフューチャーした作品にまた出ていけたらなと思います
あたしのおしりいかがでしたか
ぜひイベントとかもサイン会も各地でたくさんやってるので
ぜひぜひ作品の感想とかもぜひぜひ聞きたいなと思いますので
会いに来てください
Thank you for watching!
This was Ayaka Tomoda!
Bye bye!
Let's take a look at the back.
I don't want to lie.
Please look back.
How much is it?
It's 88cm.
Oh!
Hip up!
It's a little growth.
成長した方がいいんじゃない?
こんなに痩せた?
今ですか?
今結構太ってますよ
いいお尻です
ヒップアップ成功しました
ずっとヒップアップの運動してたんですよ
バイク漕いだり
ジムで
他には?
What are you going to do next?
I'm going to do something like this.
Thank you very much.