見て。たくさんおもちゃがある。
嬉しい?
はい。
今度おしりじめになっちゃう。
好きでしょう?
はい。大好き。
ここに止めたら?
はい。
ここに持って。
It's hot, isn't it?
Are you feeling good?
Yes, I feel good.
I'm going to rub you.
I'm going to massage you.
I can't take it anymore, so I have to drink a little more.
Put it in
Suddenly such a thick one is put into your mouth
Are you happy?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
You are having a good time, aren't you?
Ume hikkoi kusou shite.
It's easy to put it in, isn't it?
Yes
Next, I will put the cold one in here
It's cold and hard
It's bumpy
How is it?
It's very cold
I want to go to the bathroom.
No, you don't have to.
You can go in here.
It's a bigger one.
It looks like it's going to hurt a little.
It feels good.
I put in a lot of water.
How is it?
It feels good.
Ui, ui, ui, ui, ui, ui, ui, ui, ui, ui, ui.
I don't know what to do.
Your butt is twisted.
Are you okay?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Do you want to take a nap?
Yes.
Nå, nå, nå, nå, nå, nå, nå, nå, nå, nå, nå.
Oh, oh, oh.
My cat is very sleepy right now.
He looks very sleepy.
I think this is good for him.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
It hurts.
失礼したい。
四つん這いになって。
もっと大きいやつ入れてあげる。
はい。
見える?これ。
はい、見えます。
入れるかな?
入れてみようか。
はい、入れてください。
お尻壊れちゃうかもしれないよ。
I wonder if I can fit such a big one in here.
I'm going to put it in my ear.
I don't want you to fall down.
Don't look at me like that.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Show me your face.
Turn around.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It looks like it's going to fall down.
It's this big.
Do you want me to pet you?
My chimp is delicious.
You wanted to eat it, didn't you?
Eat it well.
I'm so happy to see you again today.
Mamma, erik du?
Erik du?
Erik du, no?
It hurts?
I can do it again.
You can do it again.
Mr. It hurts, doesn't it?
Mr. You have to shake your butt.
Mr. It hurts.
When you tap your butt, the hammer will snap. It looks good, doesn't it?
It's getting red.
高くなって来た。 It's getting higher and higher.
全然する。 It's all done.
見てるでしょ。 You can see it, right?
舐められるとたまらないでしょ。 You can't stop when you're being petted.
Natchi-chan, I'm sorry.
Hahahaha
気持ちいい?
本当に気持ちいい。
大きいの入れてあげる。
はい。
ホントなら広げてあげる。
気持ちいいでしょ?
気持ちいいです。
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
You feel good here, don't you?
Yes.
Come on.
You are so kind.
Chinko, you are so cute.
Your nose is open.
I want you to be more selfish everyday.
Chinko, you are so cute.
便便にね
今からそういうこと想像してるから便便にさせてるんでしょ
ちょうど前の位置だったね
どうぞ、手締めてあげよう
どうして欲しい?
It's okay
Ah, I don't feel good about that
Is this okay?
Is there a stronger stimulus?
I don't want you to be so strong
I want it
What is it?
Do you like my hair?
Yes
Does it feel good?
Which do you prefer, being touched or being licked?
It feels good
Does it feel good?
Let's do it again
I can't do it.
I'll massage your head.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's too hard.
I can't do this anymore.
What's wrong?
Do you like my legs?
It's easy to touch.
Hold it.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Oh, my God.
I feel good.
I feel like I'm getting something in my body.
You have to get a lot of lotion.
I'll give you a lot of lotion.
I heard it's good to raise your hips.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Are you okay?
Yes, it feels great.
It's not enough, is it?
You want to recover, don't you?
I feel good because it feels like I'm on a stage.
Oh, my God.
It's so nice to shake your hips like that.
Yeah, it's so nice.
Kom igjen, kom igjen, kom igjen, kom igjen.
Må kjævla så kväll.
Tid på konsulatet medan du er med på det, det er kjævligt, ikkje?
Ja, så gode kjævla så kväll.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's very intense, isn't it?
It's very intense.
I can't do it.
I'm so happy to see you again.
I'm going to sleep now.
I want you to wake up.
You're so cute.
How about this side?
It's sad, it's so heavy and cold.
It feels good, isn't it?
It feels good because it's hard, doesn't it?
It's really hard, isn't it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm going to wash my face and go to the bathroom.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
It's time to go to bed.
I'm going to sleep.
Kittaino no gono.
Polo dote koi.
Tanto sumete anu.
Kajichan suru no.
Tanto yare yare no kete moko sumedasai.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to give you a massage.
I can't do this anymore.
Ah
You always look like this when you lie down
Sa'ki podre korsi la metta aine.
Sa'ki korsi la metta.
Åh, jævla bra.
Jævla bra.
Åh, koko.
I'm so happy to see you again.
I'm going to show you how it feels to be in a wheelchair.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's big, isn't it?
It's hard. It won't go in.
If you put it in, it'll tear apart.
It's going to melt, isn't it?
I think it's going to melt.
Can you put this in?
It's in.
Do you feel painful?
What is it? Do you feel painful?
There is a lot of blood in your body.
Did you do it?
You went a lot, didn't you?
Did you have a good time?
What should we play next time?
It felt really good.
It's hard to stand up, isn't it?
It's really hard to stand up.
Take your time, take your time.
I can't hold it in.
No!
Why are you like this, Captain?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's hard, isn't it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ah, it feels so good.
Slowly, I'll draw you.
Don't cry.
You can't do that.
Why are you doing this to yourself, Guri-chan?
Ah, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
Ah!
I have to do this for you.
Ah, it's so hot.
Ah!
It's so hot.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
It feels so good.
You can do it later if you want.
Let's do it together.
I can't do it.
Yes.
Hang in there.
You can do it.
Aikuuu! Aikuuu!
Daichi-chan
Aaaaaa
Ah
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
I feel like I'm being rubbed by a fart.
I want to tickle you.
You want to tickle me?
It's not like you're going to be tickled by a fart.
You don't think you're going to be rubbed, do you?
I can feel the pain in the back of my head.
It feels good when you tighten it like that, doesn't it?
I'll rub your stomach.
Do you want me to give you a massage?
You want more, don't you?
Is it hard? You like it, don't you?
How is it? This hard one?
How is it?
Koko? Koko ga iu?
Koko ga osurareru no ga iu?
Oshime tsuke te hanoshite kuremono yo?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Tetsu-chan?
Tetsu-chan is a little bit stiff.
Tetsu-chan, are you okay?
I think it feels really good.
I'm going to pet you now.
You miss me, don't you?
I miss you.
Mom, I miss you so much.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Do you like it, Kyo-chan?
You want me to pet you properly, right?
I can't do it.
It's too big.
Ah, ok.
Ok.
Ah, stangere.
Sugoi, sugoi, okkiii
Sukkoi, kono okkumae haerimasu
Yawashii katsumo okkudai
Shibunagotte ikeru?
Aaaaaa
Jibunze, chotto shikari gao shikari gao, ne?
Ikku!
Oh, Shilu-kun!
Oh!
Is it a small hand?
Oh, wow!
Oh, it hurts!
It hurts!
Oh, wow!
Oh, it hurts!
I love you. I love you so much.
I want you to put your feet in the umbrella.
My feet?
Then I'll put them in the umbrella.
Yes.
Put them in the umbrella.
Is that okay?
You can put your feet in the umbrella.
Why?
Do you want to put your feet in?
Wow, it's warm.
It's warm.
Wow, it's amazing.
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I'll give you a massage.
I feel good.
Ah, 私はさ、きっちり向きですよね。
皆さん気持ちいいです。
行けー!
Thank you for watching!