It was kind of a boring party at first, but then I got a little slutty and I let them all fuck me.
Pussy.
It was basically their little sex toy.
My ass one at a time.
Let me play with my clit.
Hey guys.
Hey.
Are you enjoying the party?
Well now we are.
Now that you're here.
Oh, it wasn't good before?
Not as good as it is now.
I think I'll stay.
I enjoyed the party.
Yeah.
Before I go over home.
Don't be scared.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
Oh, God.
Show me what you're gonna do with my dick, with his dick.
Fuck, yes.
Ooh, grab it again, do it again, do it again.
Show me how nasty you're gonna be.
Show me how nasty you're going to be at this.
Look, I love it.
Here we just won.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Okay, you look cute.
You're fun.
Oh shit.
Shit
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Not more than two dicks though, man.
Falling in the middle.
Go to that one. Go to that one.
Get it.
There's another one over there too.
You want me to fuck your face?
Is that what you're looking for?
Tell me.
Tell me again.
Open.
Oh my god.
Fuck you.
Yes, get it.
Keep going, keep going, keep going.
Yes.
Get him off, get him off.
I can't breathe.
Go, go, go.
Wait for me.
On the hip.
Get it.
Right from my cock to his.
Go.
Yes.
Yeah.
On to you.
Yes.
Go.
Get your next dick.
Next one.
Yeah.
There you go.
Mm-hmm.
Come on.
Oh my god, yes! Yes, put me, oh my god, yes!
Oh f**k you!
There are three guys over there.
There you go.
Get your ass up over here. Yes.
All these dicks are around you. Yes.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh my god.
I want more dicks, I want more dicks, I want more dicks, keep that ass up, keep that ass
up, keep that ass up, yes, and tell us what you want, there you go, get them off, get
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
Tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him,
tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him,
tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell
him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him, tell him,
Oh, fuck, yeah, come on, spank me again, spank me again, please, oh, fuck, yes, oh, shit, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
Keep that ass up in the air, the dicks will come to you, you keep that ass up in the air.
Oh shit, yes, oh my god, oh my god, yes.
Turn that ass around, turn that ass right there, just like that.
Get that ass up high, and you keep that ass where the rubber's stuck and you won't do it, okay?
Okay, I'll stay right here.
Good girl.
Suck on this car. Suck. Suck. Suck. Suck.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God.
There you go, keep stroking, keep that ass up in the air, yes, go, stroke, and jump, yes,
Oh fuck me, oh my god, yes, oh fuck.
Get over here, get over here, get over here, get over here.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I want that fucking ass.
You want my ass, you want my ass, you want my ass?
Oh.
Give me the ass, give me the ass, give me the ass.
That's a little slow.
You seem slow like this.
You seem slow like this, baby.
Hold me like this.
Oh, yeah.
That's a good ass move.
That's what she does.
Hold me like this, baby.
Hold me like this.
There you go, you got two dicks there, you got two dicks there, grab them both, there
you go, and throw one to the next, throw one to the next, there you go, there you go,
there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go,
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I love that, keep saying that, I'm talking about you.
What was that?
Oh, shut up.
Yeah, you're insane.
This is the reason I'm such a slut.
Yes, ass or pussy, what do you want, huh?
What do you want?
Ass?
Yeah, tell me.
I want, I want it in my ass.
Say fuck my ass, tell me, come on.
Fuck my ass.
Tell me.
Fuck my ass right now.
There you go.
Oh my god.
You talk like that, you'll get whatever you want.
Oh my god, fuck my ass.
Fuck my ass.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Show me your clit. Show me your clit. Show me it. Show me it. I want to see it.
You want to see it? You want to see it?
Tell him to fuck you good. Tell him to fuck you good.
Fuck me good. Fuck me harder than that. Fuck me harder than that.
You. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Yes. Oh my god. Yes.
Fuck my ass. Oh my god.
Give me the fucking pussy. Give me that pussy.
Give me the fucking pussy.
Oh my god, this is fun!
Yes!
Yes, from my heart!
Oh, oh my God.
Good girl.
Oh my God.
You guys get that ass up in the air.
Arch it up.
There you go.
Like that.
Stay down.
Stay down on him.
There you go.
That's good.
Oh, shit.
Oh my God.
That feels so amazing.
You got an open hole, don't you?
You got an open hole?
Yes.
So my hole.
Which one's open?
So my pussy and my asshole.
Oh my God.
What open?
There's something in my mouth.
Good girl.
There's something in my mouth, please.
Ah, fuck.
Holy shit.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Please, please, please.
Oh my god.
Shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit
Oh my god, yes!
Close your eyes.
Yes, like this.
No, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes.
Look at this, look at this.
Oh, fuck yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
We want to fuck it. You keep that fish right there.
And let us all have fun with your horse.
Let us all just have fun with this horse.
Good girl, tell us. Come on, look at me. Look at me and say something.
Look at me.
And I'll just say what you want to hear.
Good girl.
Oh my god, you want your ass baby, you want to taste your ass?
Yeah I want to taste my ass, put your cock in my mouth, leave me in my ass baby.
Stay there, we'll bring it to you, bring it to you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
There you go, like that, there you go, show us what a whore you are, show us what a fucking
whore you are, yes, go, go, go, go, oh my god, yeah, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god,
This is so fucking good
Oh my god
It's just because there's a dick knot in it
Yeah
Oh shit
You fucking my ass.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
I coughed so hard. Oh fuck.
I can't put it in my mouth.
Oh my god.
Go on, go on.
Go on.
Oh my god, yeah, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
Yeah, are you gonna put it in my pussy?
Yeah, put it in my pussy, put it in my pussy right now.
Please?
Oh god, yeah, I need it, I need a nice cock inside me.
Every time there's a dick on you, you're just so quiet.
I want to hear you scream when there's no dicks in you.
I want to hear you beg.
I want to see how much
you need of dick.
I'm sorry.
I'll help you.
Oh my god. Yes.
There you go.
Fuck you.
Oh my god, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
Come here, come here, come here, come here, you feel so good, yeah, oh my god, yes, oh god, that's good, oh fuck, yeah.
Oh shit, yeah, oh god, oh my god, you fuck, you, oh fuck, this feels so fucking good, oh my god, yes, more, more, I need, I need, yeah, yeah.
Oh my god, yes, oh my god, yes.
Oh my god, yes, oh my god, yes, oh my god, yes, oh my god, yes, oh my god, yes, oh my
god, yes.
You listen to
You come here.
Oh, fuck.
No.
Open.
Show me.
Oh.
You open up.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
It's so fucking deep.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, fuck, it feels so good, oh my god, fuck my holes, fuck my holes, yeah, yeah, yeah, you like my tits, yeah, put your coffee in my mouth, please, put your coffee in my mouth.
Oh, fuck, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, yes!
Oh, fuck this shit!
You wanna stare at me when you choke me?
No, no, no, come on.
Help me.
No, choke, choke, choke.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Fuck, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, shit!
Oh my god, give me another drink in my mouth. Please, please, please, please, please, fill up my mouth.
Oh my god, yes! Oh god, yes!
Oh, fuck yes, it feels so fucking good, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh shit, ah, ah, oh, fuck yes, yes, yes, let's take turns fucking around, let's take turns fucking around, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more
YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES YES
Oh my God, oh my God, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh my god, yes, fuck my ass off, fuck it, okay, oh fuck my, oh shit, oh my god, oh my god, yes, oh, fuck, yes, oh, you, you hit me, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh my god, I'm such a slut, yeah, oh my god, I'm such a slut, yeah, fuck my ass, fuck this little slutty asshole, come on, get on your line, you fucking perverts, fuck my asshole one at a time, then you're gonna fucking come all over me, yeah, you fuck my pussy, you fill me up, cause I'm such a little slut, you fill me up, come on, fuck me, fuck me, come on, fill my ass up, oh my god, yes, oh god, that feels so fucking good,
I'm such a little sl- more, more, yes, oh, oh yes, oh, oh fuck, oh fuck yeah, oh, oh shit, yes, oh my god, yes, it's also wet, ah, ah, ah, yes, oh my, oh fuck, fuck yes, fuck yes, give it to me, ah, ah, ah,
Give me another drink in my ass
Oh, fuck
Yes
Uh-huh
Oh, shit
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Uh-huh
Fuck my ass
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, God, yes
Uh-huh
Fuck you
Oh, fuck you
Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me
Oh, my God
Oh
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, God, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, fuck my ass.
Uh-huh.
Fuck my ass. Oh, my God, that feels so good.
So I'll just take turns coming on your face, too.
Okay. Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God, please, yes.
I don't want to hear you. I don't want to hear you.
I don't want to hear you.
God, yes, I want you all to take turns coming on my face.
Yes, yes, get on your knees, get on your knees right here.
Give it to me please, please give me that cum.
Please give me that cum, all over my pretty face.
Give me that cum, I want it.
Oh.
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Are you hungry?
Yes, yes, yes.
Can I have more?
Watch those tits up in the air.
There you go.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
I'm ready for you. I'm so fucking ready.
Push me up.
Oh my god.
Oh, that was fun.