I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
It feels so good.
I love kissing.
What were you looking at?
Do you want to kiss me?
That's why you've been looking at me for a long time.
I want to kiss someone like you instead of doing it myself.
Do you want to kiss Arisa?
What should I do?
It's dirty.
Did you think you could kiss me?
There's no way I could do that with you.
Why do I have to kiss you?
It's disgusting.
There's no way I can kiss you, right?
You don't have it, do you?
You're just right if you're dirty with my dandruff.
What do you think?
What's with that face?
Are you sad?
You're not really sad, are you?
You've been so excited to see my dandruff.
It feels so bad.
I love you so much.
I love you.
Kusai no daisuki nandesho, hora.
Hora.
Kusai no hontou suki nandesho,
hora, saki kara koufun shiteru kuse ni.
Ah, kitanai kao
namechatta.
Ah, kitanai.
Wow, your face is very salty.
I have to disinfect it.
Come on, disinfect.
I'll disinfect you with my saliva.
Wow, it's still salty.
How much sweat are you sweating?
Come on.
How is it? My saliva.
I love you so much.
ほら、わかる?あなたみたいな気持ち悪い人は、 頑張ってあげられるの私だけよ。
わかった?
Hattan?
Hentai no aiteshita to atsuku natte kichotta
Anta no douze mitai n desho?
Tsukebe dakara
Kimuchi warui hentai no anta
Shouwa nai kara misete ageyou ka na
Atsui
Because it's so disgusting.
Really.
Hey, what do you want me to do?
Maybe it's more sticky and smelly.
I want you to put on dirty clothes.
Do you want me to put on dirty clothes?
You're such a pervert.
It still feels so bad.
What are you looking at?
Amazing.
It's so messy.
For your sake,
For the sake of you, I gave you my wings.
For the sake of you, who are so disgusting.
It hurts, doesn't it?
I wanted to put a lot of it on your face.
It's so sticky.
Your face is so sticky.
I'm getting so sticky.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You're so sticky.
You're spitting on a girl.
Hey, you're so smelly.
My leber leber matuba
Do you really want it that much?
Do you like it so much?
You look like you want it so much that you can't stop.
I'll put a lot on your face.
You like it, don't you?
It's in my mouth all the time.
I'm about to laugh.
Should I put all this on your face?
If you like it, you'll be happy, right?
It's time to take a bath.
It's so hot.
It's so cute.
Does it feel good?
Why?
Can I smell it?
Do you want to smell it?
I don't like it
What do you want to smell?
Just a little
It's okay if it's just a little bit.
What do you smell like?
I don't smell anything.
You don't smell anything? Really?
It's the first time I've seen you like that.
Is it cute?
Do you like my nose?
Have you ever seen this?
What?
Your tongue is a tool to make your tongue clean.
Is that so?
Yes, it will be cleaner.
How do I do it?
Put your tongue out like this.
Hold this.
Wait, let me take it out and pull it out from the top like this.
Did you clean it up?
Please do it again.
It's all over the place.
But it doesn't smell that bad.
I don't think it's dirty.
It's not dirty.
It wasn't that dirty.
Really?
Then maybe it was clean.
Maybe so.
Can I try it one more time?
Yes.
Wow.
One more time?
Yes.
I don't like it.
I love your dirty tongue, so I'll have some yogurt.
Did you bring yogurt?
That's a lot of energy.
Did you get dirty?
Oh, that's good.
Really?
That's amazing.
Is it delicious?
I'm sorry, there's a lot of dirt on the floor.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean it up.
There's still a lot left.
I got a lot of dirt.
Did you eat?
I'm so happy to be able to take a video like this.
I think it feels good to lick your face.
Do you want me to lick your face?
Do you want me to lick you?
Do you like it?
Do you want me to lick your face?
Wow, it's amazing that my licking makes your face shiny.
I'll stretch it out for you, okay?
It's so good to see your bright face.
How do you feel?
I'm so happy.
Really?
I can't breathe.
It's so bad.
I can smell someone's urine.
Hey, you liked yogurt, didn't you?
Yes.
Aji hensutei?
It feels so good, isn't it?
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
I spilled it.
It's all gone.
I'll put it all on for you.
Your face is so shiny.
My armpits are shiny.
It smells so good.
I'm going to dry it and coat it for you.
Wow, amazing!
It's getting drier and drier.
I might not be able to smell it anymore.
Wow, amazing!
Ippai, ippai, ippai, ippai, ippai, ippai, ippai, ippai.
Are you okay?
Let's get rid of this part too.
Let's get rid of it.
It hurts a lot.
Wait a minute.
It hurts so much.
Let's get rid of this part too.
It hurts a lot.
Oh, you're standing up so high.
I'm standing up so high, too.
This is amazing.
Open your mouth.
I'll stretch it out for you.
You like it, don't you?
Ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja.
I love drooling and
It's so good!
It's amazing!
I want to eat more and more
It's all over my face
My favorite tooth
I have a lot of teeth
It's all over my face
I don't want to eat it anymore.
It's all over the place.
There's a lot of it.
Look at this.
You are a great boy, aren't you?
I wonder if you like this kind of thing too.
Because you like to be chubby, don't you?
Oh, you peed on your butt.
I wonder if you can still come out.
I'm going to clean it up for you.
I put it in your mouth.
I'm going to put it in your buttocks.
もう洗わないで帰ってね。
私、氷アイス大好きなの。
あなたも好き?
美味しいよね。
でも、これだけじゃ足りなくて、もっと青い方が好きなんだ。
だから、いっぱい青くしちゃおうかな。
But it might turn blue.
What should I do?
But I like blue, so I'll put a lot of it on.
Wow!
Did you get a blue one?
Isn't the blue one cute?
Look!
Smite, smite, Aino.
Oishiii.
Akiyoi oishikunatta yo.
Aino oishii.
Ui, stawakunatta?
Uihou ga kawaii yone.
Akiyokunatta?
Is it blue now?
Isn't the blue one cute?
It's delicious.
But it's my favorite tea.
I don't want it to get dirty.
Can I take it off?
It's so cute, isn't it?
The inside is so cute, isn't it?
Do you want to see it?
It's important, so keep it.
Is it cute?
What does it taste like?
I don't want to eat it.
It's okay.
What does it taste like?
It's sweet.
Sweet?
I want you to lick it in various places.
In various places?
Like your fingers.
It's okay.
Does your tongue feel good?
I want you to lick more here.
Then, put your feet out.
Put your feet out here.
Oh, my feet?
Yes.
I'll lick your feet too.
I'll lick you with this long bed.
Is it hot?
Is it nice? Do you want me to tickle you?
It feels good.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's fun, isn't it?
I'm going to take a shower.
Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo-Kyo.
It's so hot in here, I'm going to take a bath.
I want to be a good warrior, don't I?
I have a blue belt.
Take a look at my blue belt.
Nero, look at me.
How are you feeling?
Something got burned.
You look so beautiful.
What are you doing?
You woke up from the beginning.
Do you care about me that much?
Do you care?
Do you want me to show you?
Do you want me to kiss you?
寝てるところをこんなふうに出さして I'm going to put you to sleep like this.
変態なの? Are you a pervert?
女の人の体見たことないの? Haven't you ever seen a woman's body?
どうせ童貞なんでしょ? It's the same, isn't it?
Do you want to see my nose?
I feel like I'm going to close my eyes.
I'm going to cry a lot because of you.
I feel like I'm going to cry.
I want to see you a lot more.
Where are you looking at?
Your tongue is so soft.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Uchin-koo
Chikuriniko-san
Itte?
Uchin-koo
I don't know what to do.
Oh, it feels good.
It's getting warmer.
You want to see it up close, don't you?
Oh, it smells so hot.
I'm so happy.
I was so sleepy last night.
You're happy, aren't you?
You're a slimy cat.
You're a shy cat who eats bread.
気のしない子にチンと言えちゃうよ
見たかったんでしょ?
ああいうとこ見ていいよ
いいよ
吠えちゃった
ごめん吠えちゃった
ああぐちゃぐちゃな顔
I don't know what to do.
Oh, I was so excited to see the drama.
I was so excited to talk about the drama.
I was so excited.
Let's sleep together.
Kutsi-kutsi-kutsi.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm sorry.
Emojenis...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It feels so good.
It feels good, right?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good.
It's so good!
Is it good?
I can't eat it.
No, it's not good.
What?
What's wrong?
I want to put it on your head, but I don't know how to do it.
I don't know how to put it on my head, but I don't know how to do it.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better?
Do you want to sleep?
I want to sleep.
How about you?
What do you want to do?
I always wanted to sleep.
I want to sleep.
It feels so good.
I don't want to do it.
I'll put it on you this time.
Okay.
Open your legs.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Don't stop.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I can't breathe
Ah, it feels good.
I feel like I'm going to die.
気持ちいい、かわいい。
気持ちいいよ。
ちょっと気持ちいい。
いっちゃう。
いく、いく。
いく?
いっちゃう。
いく、いく。
ちょっとね。
気持ちいい。
全部気持ちいい。
I can feel it in my body.
I love you, Sushi.
What?
One more time.
I love you, Sushi.
Please.
Which eye do you want?
I don't know what to do.