Oh
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I can see it.
I can't talk at all.
You can't talk at all?
What?
Do you want me to talk?
That's right.
You want me to talk?
Then let's talk.
Is that so?
I want to take a picture of that today.
Do you feel like you don't have to be so formal today?
Yes.
You don't have to be so formal.
You may have done it many times, but can you introduce yourself again?
Yes, I'll introduce myself.
Yes, by yourself.
I'm Kururugi Mikan.
Can you show me how it looks?
I'll show you.
What should I do?
The three sizes are...
96,
58,
no, 92, 58,
86.
You're really good at this.
What's your chest size?
92cm
What's your cup size?
G cup
Can you introduce yourself?
My charm point is my mouth.
What's wrong with your mouth?
I have a long tongue.
The last one is Charm Point.
I see.
Do you want to use Charm Point?
No.
Charm Point.
It's not Charm, it's a weapon.
It's a weapon.
It's a weapon of MikaPon.
By the way, I really want to see it.
Really?
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
Do you want me to show it to you?
Yes, please.
What should I do?
I'm going to tease you a little bit.
What do you think about being teased?
Yes.
What do you think about it?
No, it's okay.
What do you think about the works so far?
What do you think about the number of models you've worked with so far?
Hmm, the number of models I've worked with so far...
Which one do you think is the most popular?
Hmm...
I think the number of models I've worked with so far is the most popular.
I tend to be more aggressive.
But that's the pattern, isn't it?
Most of the time, you get attacked during your debut,
and when you get used to it, you get attacked.
Is that what you call the darkness of AV?
I guess so.
In the past, there were a lot of high school girls,
so I was often attacked.
But recently, I've become an adult.
It's been about 5 years since my debut.
Yes, it's been about 5 years.
What do you like about your work?
What kind of work do you like?
What do you like?
What do I like?
What do you like about your work?
In terms of play?
Yes, in terms of play.
I like pretty much anything.
I'm not that particular about what I like.
On the other hand, do you like anything?
Yes, I'm basically a pervert.
Basically a pervert?
Yes, I want to match my opponent.
You want to match your opponent?
I want to step on a man's foot.
That's a bit of an empty dream, isn't it?
Maybe.
You don't want to step on a man's foot, do you?
But it sounds fun.
You're going to laugh at it, aren't you?
Yes.
Yes?
That's weird.
That's a bit weird.
You don't do that in private, do you?
I do do that in private.
Do you cut your hair?
I'm quite...
You have a lot of faith in people like that?
Well, it's kind of...
Emohoihoi.
Emohoihoi?
You mean Emohoku is coming to you?
That's right.
I see.
Does he look like an S?
I wonder.
How do you do it? Is it the most charming one?
Well, how do I do it? I'm looking for it.
I was looking for it.
You were looking for it?
Yes.
Can you show me yours?
I took a picture of it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Your face doesn't change even if you stick out your tongue.
What?
Usually, if you stick out your tongue that much,
your face changes a little.
It's like the bottom of a flower is growing.
It's normal, isn't it?
Wow, it's moving a lot.
If you look a little to the side, it's like a velo.
Do you do it like that?
Do you look at the feeling of a man?
Yes.
What are you doing now?
Did you take your medication?
I'm getting tired.
Can you take it out from now on?
I'll do that from now on.
What about today?
No, I can't take it out today.
Really?
You're amazing.
I'm happy just by taking a bath.
Really?
Is that true?
You can also attack men with this body.
Please stand up.
Your body is beautiful.
Yes.
Normally, when I wear this, I feel like I'm in danger.
Do you feel like you're in danger?
But it's cute.
You have a neck.
Do you want me to provoke you?
We are also provoked.
Why are you standing there?
It's like a magic show, isn't it?
Wow, your butt is so nice.
It's so beautiful.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Oh, from yourself?
Yes.
Oh, good. Please show me.
Oh!
It's a little too much.
Yes.
Oh, it's a little too much.
All the staffs are on their feet.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Oh, the front is also beautiful.
Oh, it's amazing.
The anime is also amazing.
It came out.
No, it's okay.
Why did you pull it in?
I thought it was a little bit.
No, it's okay.
Please take it out.
Will you take it out?
Yes.
For service.
Oh, you've already taken it out?
Yes.
Oh, it's scary to stop here, isn't it?
Is it like this?
Yes, like this.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's good.
It's a double weapon.
It's like taking out a tongue.
There are a lot of weapons.
If you don't attack with this, the guy won't like it.
Are you listening to me?
Do you want to turn around and look at your tongue in a back pose?
That's a good one.
Wow, your body is so soft.
My body is so soft.
Can you show us your favorite pose?
A soft pose?
I wonder if there's anything.
Oh, you mean like this?
Oh, I see.
Wow, that's nice.
And then, tongue.
You have a lot of weapons.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Did you start wanting them?
Do you miss your mouth?
What?
Yes.
If that's the case, what would you do?
I don't think that's a good way to say it.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
What do you think?
It's great.
It's great?
Do you like it?
Yes.
I like you.
You are a good person.
I am a good person.
I want to see you.
I've been watching you for a long time.
That's good.
Do you feel good when you sleep?
I want you to tell me more about you.
What do you want me to say?
It's delicious, right?
You look cute.
Does it feel good?
The back of my hand.
That's good.
It feels good.
Really?
It's so hot.
Yes, it is.
It's like crab meat.
It's so hot.
Yes, it's so hot.
It's like crab meat.
There's a lot of meat coming out.
I'm getting excited.
It's my line.
Are you getting excited?
It's delicious.
I'm getting excited when you say that.
I get excited when I see you.
Are you excited?
Yes.
You look good.
I'm so tired.
Are you okay?
What?
I thought you were going to look at everything.
Oh, really?
Wow, you're so cute.
That's a good one.
It's good, isn't it?
Are you going to eat this?
No, no.
This is how you do it.
Yes.
Mikan.
It's like this today.
It's like this.
Please go to your favorite nightclub.
Are you listening to that?
It stopped.
It's the 10th floor, isn't it?
Management company.
What should I do?
Is this the right place?
I think I should call them.
Huh?
It's a bit late.
Yeah.
This is bad.
Are you in a hurry?
Yes, I am.
I have to go to work in a hurry.
What should I do?
Can you move it a little bit?
It doesn't move.
There's no pressure button.
I wonder where it is.
Yes, it doesn't move.
I don't think so.
Can you get out of the ceiling?
From the ceiling?
Yes.
There are quite a few.
I'm going to check.
Can I sit down?
You're going to sit down?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Yes, please.
Can you lift it?
Yes, I can.
How is it?
It doesn't seem to come off.
I see.
I'll put it down.
I'm sorry. It was heavy.
It's heavy, isn't it?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Really?
Yes.
I'm embarrassed to see you two together.
No, that's not it.
What should I do?
I'm in trouble.
It's getting thicker.
I feel like I'm getting used to it.
I agree.
I just bought some water.
Are you sure?
Thank you very much.
I'm happy.
It's delicious.
How are you feeling?
I'm in trouble. I can't reach you.
What should I do?
I'll wait for you.
Isn't it hot?
It's very hot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay if it's hot.
Oh, because it's hot?
Yes.
Excuse me.
You see, you're sweating a lot.
It must have been hot.
I think it stinks.
Is it that bad?
It smells like sweat.
Is a tie pretty hot?
Is it hot?
Yes, it is.
I don't know if it's because of dehydration.
What are you doing?
You asked me what I was doing.
What's wrong with you?
Is it because it's hot?
It's because it's hot.
Because it's hot?
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm sweating so much.
I'm sweating so much right now.
What's wrong?
My body is shaking.
Oh
I'm scared.
You don't like it?
You're not serious?
You're just sitting there like that.
It's so hot.
I can feel the cow dung coming out of your mouth.
Your hands are all sticky.
I can taste the cow dung.
I'm getting a lot of pimples.
My skin is getting really dry.
I'm so tired.
It feels good to be rubbed, right?
Yes, it feels good.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to have to go to the bathroom and get it fixed.
Let's see if it's good.
I'm going to try a lot of different things.
It's good.
It's so hot.
It's so hard for me.
It's delicious.
It's good, it's really good.
Does it feel good?
What's going on?
I can't breathe.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm so tired.
I can't believe it's a pie.
I'm going to have to have a lot of ramen.
I'm so nervous.
Ah, I have a lot of dark circles on my eyes.
What a waste.
My stomach is so dry.
It's so scary.
What are you doing?
I'm lonely.
No, no.
This is not good.
You don't like it?
How are you feeling?
Please stop.
Mr. Takahashi, I'm a little lonely.
I know that, but...
Is this it?
Is it hard?
Oh, my God.
I love you so much.
ah
It's so delicious.
I think you're going to want to lick your dad's gimbap.
I'm going to make your dad's gimbap messy.
Your gimbap is delicious.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's so hard to chew.
Does it feel good?
It looks good.
Looks like you're feeling good.
I'll give you a lot of
It feels good, doesn't it?
Are you feeling hot and ticklish?
Do you feel like you're drooling?
It's all hard.
Don't you want to take a bath?
How is it?
How do you feel?
My cheeks are so puffy and my nipples are so flat.
Please look at me a lot.
How do you feel?
Does this feel good?
Does it feel good to be tickled?
Is it too tight?
Can I move it to the other side?
It's so hard.
Dad, can you give me a hand?
Hurry up.
My butt is so tight.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to let go of your hand?
I can hear the sound of your breath.
I feel good when you rub my hand.
I feel good when I hear the sound of your breath.
It's getting worse.
Is it bad?
No.
I don't want to do it.
Ah, it's so hard.
I'm going to blow on it.
Ah, it's so embarrassing.
Ah, it's so uncomfortable.
Please look at me for a moment.
It feels so good.
Does your stomach feel good?
I'm so happy.
I hope you feel better.
My stomach...
Amazing.
I'm going to show you a little bit of it.
It's amazing.
Can you see it?
It's a place where you can feel good.
It's embarrassing.
I don't know what to do.
Oh
I don't know what I'm doing
I'm so tired
Oh my god.
See? It's amazing.
See?
Oh, my God.
Oh, I feel good.
I feel good, too.
I feel like my legs are going to fall off.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
You've been doing this for a long time, haven't you?
Like this?
I thought I would do it with my other hand.
Do you want me to do it with my other hand?
Yes.
Or do you want me to do it with my other hand?
I want to do it with my other hand too.
No, I want to do it like this.
It feels good.
I feel good.
I can feel it.
Do you feel good?
Do you want me to rub your head?
Yes, please.
Hold my hand.
Kiss me.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Yes, I feel good.
Your ears?
Yes.
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
It feels good.
Ah
Do you want me to pat you on the back?
Yes.
Oh, that's great.
Chin-chin is coming back to me.
Can I pat you on the back?
Yes, sure.
You look like you really like it.
Turn around.
Like this?
Yes.
More.
More?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to do it slowly.
It's clear now, isn't it?
It's very shiny.
I can see it.
I'll do the same for you.
Okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Tintin is very shiny.
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Oh
It's so good.
Is the sticky rice delicious?
I can't breathe.
Ah, it's so good.
It's so good.
Mm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh
Oh, my God.
One, two, three, four.
I can't breathe.
Oh
I don't know what to do.
I want you to put it in here.
Don't look at me like that.
Save me.
It's so good.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's all right, it's all right.
I'm so full.
Oh, my God.