🎵
I'll see you next time.
Stay still.
Keep it quiet.
Look.
You can't move, can you?
Is it hot?
You're sweating a lot, aren't you?
It's so sour.
I'm going to lick you.
Do more.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Do you want me to do this side?
You're so cute, but what's wrong?
Did you do this?
You want some water?
I can't hear you, you have to say it clearly.
Are you okay?
Do you want to eat directly?
Do you want to eat it?
It's delicious.
I'll give you more.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
I don't know what to do.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to massage your back?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you moving your hips?
It's so hard.
It was hard.
It was hard to move your hips.
I'll give you a massage.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking to you.
Shut up.
It feels good, right?
I'm sweating.
What?
What is it?
Shut up.
Wow, baby.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I had a hair cut just now.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel like I'm going to cry.
Okay, I'm gonna do it again.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll do it again.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore, I can't do this anymore
I'll wipe it off for you.
Why are you going to go to the bathroom so soon?
Why?
I told you not to.
Hang in there until you go to the bathroom.
Okay?
Okay.
It feels good, right?
I can see it clearly, the part where it's open.
Let me help you.
I'm sorry.
No!
Why are you trying to go there again?
I told you not to go there.
But if you go there, you'll get a reward.
I have a lot of stuff to carry with me.
You're not going to sleep, are you?
I'm going to sleep.
Why do you have to sleep so much?
Hey.
Yes, yes, I'm going to sleep.
Can you bear it?
Yes, I can't bear it.
Really?
It can't be helped.
I'll let you do whatever you want.
But you can't move on your own.
Come out.
It hurts.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I can't do this.
Oh
How was it?
It felt good.
Right?
It's a good thing that you're just getting attention, isn't it?
What are you doing?
I was following the director.
What do you mean?
I was following the director on Twitter.
You're not easy.
I'm not easy.
There's a reason why I came here.
What is it?
I can do anything, so I think it's amazing, but I think it's not interesting to do something that can be easily done.
So next time, it's not a trial, but it's a trial.
I want you to decide what you want me to do.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to be a man.
I want you to go to the bathroom, but I don't want you to put your hands, legs, and mouth in here.
What about your boobs?
It's not good.
That's why I want you to do it.
I wonder if I can do it.
I'm not confident these days.
What?
The world?
It's Hata.
But I think I can't go up without something.
Without something?
Like a reward.
Then I'll do it somewhere else.
Really?
Then I'll do my best.
What's wrong? Look at me with that face.
Are you excited because you can see me?
Do you want to see my nipples?
You want to see me, don't you?
I think you've already recovered.
It's kind of hard.
Chin-po
Let's rub your nipples.
I'll rub it on your neck.
It feels good.
Rub it a lot.
Do you feel it in your neck?
You were surprised, weren't you?
Your whole body is reacting.
How about your armpits?
Do you want to tickle them?
Your body is reacting very well.
It's been 4 days since I started drooling.
I have a lot of dandruff on my head.
Does it feel good?
Oh, you turned your head.
Towel.
You have a lot of dandruff on your head.
I can see it.
You are so soft.
It feels so good.
Does it feel so good?
You can take a closer look.
Do you want to lick it?
No.
You haven't licked it yet.
You're hitting it so hard.
You're a hot person.
You're doing fine.
Let me take this off.
Amazing.
Wow, it's so shiny.
It's so nice.
What's this?
It's a gold ball.
Does it feel good?
It's so fluffy.
You can't take it out yet.
I'll rub it on you.
Look.
My nipples are sticking out.
Both of them are sticking out.
You can look at it up close.
It's a waste.
It's too tight.
I think I'm going to hit you.
Do you want me to hit your chin?
Then, please.
Put it on.
You have a lot of hair on your chin.
Your chin is shiny.
You want me to hit your chin, right?
Look.
I want you to rub it all over your body with this.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Rub it quickly.
I'll do it for you.
Your belly is very wet.
It looks like you had a bath.
Did it feel good?
I'll make it more messy.
Oh, it's so soft.
It's amazing.
I'm holding it in my dress.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I'll make it faster.
Wow, it's so fluffy, but I don't feel good.
Does my waist feel good?
Look at this.
You can see it well, right?
It's so black.
It's good, isn't it?
Oh!
Something just popped out.
It's transparent.
Did the gauze fly away?
What's wrong?
You have a great face.
Do you think it will go away?
All of it.
Just rub it on.
Are you going to get a lot of pimples just by looking at me?
Do you want to go?
You look like you're going to get a lot of pimples.
If you want to go, give me a lot of pimples.
I'll rub you a lot.
Are you going to get a lot of pimples?
I think I can do it.
Let me see.
I can do it.
Did you have a lot of white hair and had a lot of hair loss?
Did you get rid of all your hair?
Oh, that's great.
You got a lot of hair again.
How was it? Did you feel good?
My waist.
You had a lot of hair loss.
I'll do it again.
Nice to meet you, I'm Yui.
Nice to meet you today.
Can I put my bag here?
Oh, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it right away.
Please don't move there.
The man is quiet and still.
I'll make you feel good all over your body.
I'm taking a neck massage.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to clean it up because it's going to get dirty.
I'll make you feel better, too.
It's amazing.
It feels good to be licked, doesn't it?
Do you want me to lick this too?
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
If you lick the tip of your tongue, you'll be scared.
I'm going to lick your balls too.
You're drooling a lot, aren't you?
I'll make you feel better.
Does it feel good?
It's delicious.
You're drooling a lot, aren't you?
Why are you making that face?
Maybe you want me to rub your butt?
But before that, please look at my butt.
You want to see it, don't you?
Please keep looking at it.
How is it?
My butt.
Do you want me to bring it closer to you?
Do you like panties?
Do you want me to rub it like this?
I'll take this.
Rub, rub.
This is the first time for me to do this, so I hope you enjoy it.
It's very sticky.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
It's very sticky.
It doesn't feel that good, does it?
How about this one?
It feels good when you listen to my running, doesn't it?
Please breathe more.
My head is still cramping.
Next is this side.
I'm going to make you feel a lot better.
Let's make you feel a lot better.
Wow, you're so plump.
How is your tibia?
It's so plump.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
Do you want me to massage you?
Then let's take it off.
It's good.
It feels better when it's raw, doesn't it?
I'll take it off here too.
Please look at me.
Please lie down.
Oh, you have a lot of dead skin cells.
It's all the way to the inside.
I'll use the dead skin cells to make your back more tense.
Do you know that you're stressed out?
It looks like it's going to go in.
Do you want to put it in?
No.
I'll make it more wrinkly.
It feels good.
If you feel like it, please tell me.
It's okay. You can go anytime.
Ouch!
Wow, it's so dirty.
There's a lot of it on your belly.
There's a lot of it.
That's what you were thinking, right?
I'll clean it up for you.
It's delicious.
How did you like Yui's back massage?
You're so busy.
Does it feel good?
It's big, isn't it?
How tall are you?
It's very high.
I'll get you some oil.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you for waiting.
Please put your hands on your head.
Isn't it cold?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Please relax.
I'll put it on your feet, too.
Yes, ma'am.
We're going to start a full-scale service from here.
Oh, I see.
It will be a special course for our shop.
Special?
Yes.
Then I'll get ready.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me from my arm.
How is it?
Oh, it's amazing.
It's warm.
Does it feel good to rub?
Are you okay?
Next, I'll massage your feet.
Your feet are very plump.
I'll massage your feet a lot.
Are you okay?
I'll massage one of your feet as well.
Are you feeling good?
How are you feeling, customer?
Your feet are cold, right?
You are feeling better, right?
Yes.
Customer,
do you want to take a face pack?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'll wipe your face.
Okay.
I'll put some oil on your face.
It's good for your skin.
Customer,
Your face is so bright and shiny.
Your face block is gone.
I'm going to massage this side as well.
Please close your eyes.
You're doing great.
I'm going to massage this side as well.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm going to put a lot of cream on your face.
I can hear the sound of your nose.
Mr. Customer.
Please come over here.
Yes.
I'm sorry to put cream on your face.
I'm sorry.
Please take a good look at the oil on the cat's body.
It's good for your health.
You're licking your cat.
You're doing great.
Is it good, Mako?
Yes.
Now this side.
I'm going to massage you.
Wow.
It's so soft.
Does the massage feel good to you?
Yes, it does.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good to me too.
Please come here for a moment.
Your chin is touching your butt.
This feels good, doesn't it?
See, it's more comfortable to hit directly on your forehead.
It's hot.
It feels so good.
I'm starting to feel pain.
I'm going to put some ointment on you.
Is that okay?
But it's really not good.
I'm going to put it in.
But if it's like this,
it might get in.
It might get in, right?
It's not good if it's like this.
Ah, I ate it but it got in my throat.
This is an accident, isn't it?
I want to do this a lot of times.
Are you okay?
Yes.
How is it?
It's okay.
It's so hot.
It feels so good to be able to sleep.
Now I'm going to massage your body.
How is your butt?
It's so big.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You look like you're in a good mood.
Are you happy?
You're in a good mood.
I can feel the pain in the back of my head.
I feel like my back is going to explode.
I can't move.
I can feel the pain in the back of my head.
Are you okay?
It's been a while.
I've been holding back.
You've been holding back, haven't you?
Yes.
Your chin was very tight.
Would you like me to show you a good talk?
Yes.
Please show me the last part.
I'm going to massage you while it's off so that you can come out easily.
Show me! Show me!
I think it's amazing.
You've come out a lot.
You're going to come out more, right?
You can come out a lot more.
I'm putting in a lot more.
Ah, more.
I can't take it anymore.
You can't take it anymore?
You've put in a lot more than you expected.
It took a long time, didn't it?
How was the special course at the store?
After a month of that car accident, I finally retired and was able to return home.
My body is still numb and doesn't move properly.
Maybe I'll stay like this for the rest of my life.
No, let's stop thinking about it now.
Let's not do that, because thanks to this body, there are so many good things.
Hello.
How do you feel?
I feel much better.
That's good.
She is Yui, a home helper.
She takes care of me when I can't move.
Thank you for taking care of me.
It's been a week.
Then...
What?
Nothing.
Your body is itchy, isn't it?
Well...
Is it itchy around here?
Are you okay?
Then I'll do it with my hands.
Where is it itchy?
I'll massage it.
How is it?
Is it itchy?
No, it's not.
Here?
I'll draw the itchy part firmly.
There?
Is it itchy?
Are you okay?
It's hard not to move your body, isn't it?
Yes.
You can't do anything, can you?
But it's okay.
It's okay. I'll do everything for you.
Anything.
Hey, shouldn't you draw it more directly?
Because it's itchy, isn't it?
I'll let you go.
Around here?
Are you okay? Your body is tingling.
Is it itchy?
It's itchy, isn't it?
Leave it to me.
I'll draw it for you.
How does it feel?
You're sweating a lot.
I'll smell it.
It's amazing.
It smells like sweat.
It's still itchy, isn't it?
It was tough, wasn't it?
I'll make sure to clean it up for you.
It's so sour.
I'm sweating.
I'm going to puke.
Does it feel good?
Is your body feeling better?
It's been a long time.
Are you okay?
This is bad, isn't it?
No, it's not.
You want to get it out as soon as possible, don't you?
You've been eating a lot for a week, haven't you?
If you eat too much, your body will say it's bad for you.
I'm going to hit you.
No, you can't.
It's only just started.
Hang in there.
Show me more.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, wow.
It's stuck.
It's so full.
It's hard.
This is it.
Wow.
You're so energetic.
I'll rub you more.
Oh, yeah.
It feels good to have a lot of muscles in the back of my body.
I'll put it here.
It feels good.
It feels good to have a lot of muscles in the back of my body.
Can I do the other side?
Yes, you can.
I'll do the other side, too.
ah
Are you okay?
I can feel it.
I can feel it, too.
It hurts.
I can still feel the pain.
Drink a lot.
Take a good bite of this.
You have to put a lot of nutrition into your body.
If you take a good bite of this, you might feel better.
Take a good bite of this.
Take a good bite of this to the hole in your buttocks.
I can't take it anymore.
It's okay.
I don't want to do this anymore.
What are you doing?
You're doing it well.
I know you're in a hurry.
Feel a lot.
ah
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it
Can you see it?
I can't see the tip of my nose.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's delicious.
I can't do this.
What's wrong with your voice?
Do you feel like you're going to pass out if you keep going like this?
I can't do this.
It's so painful.
What? Are you going to do it again?
You're telling me not to, right?
Relax.
Does it feel good?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
If you don't turn around, you're going to break your cheekbone.
Are you okay?
Can you bend your legs?
Does it hurt?
It hurts
It feels so good
Your hands are big and soft.
Are you okay?
I'm here for you.
I'm not done yet.
You're really about to explode.
I can't take it anymore.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Oh boy, you're still sleeping.
I'll clean you up.
Did you have a good time?
When I see a man who can't move his body, his body moves on its own.
So you don't have to heal as it is.
I don't know why.
I don't know why, but she's always like this.