🎵
Teksting av Nicolai Winther
Very much umai
Umai
Echua, nanka shizumon seien no?
Shokurepo? Taka umai yo
Uwari, tori ga umai
The way it's fried is good.
The saltiness is nice.
It's crunchy and delicious.
The batter is delicious.
What else is there?
It's the most stressful thing to be told what's delicious.
It's delicious.
Because it's delicious.
Grilled meat.
Sushi.
Fugu karaage.
Crab meat.
Chinese food.
It doesn't go well with pasta at all.
This is too delicious.
It's delicious.
But this video can only be seen by the person who bought the DVD.
I can only see it by the person who is the founder.
Yummy!
But the meat is a little small.
I like carbonara.
It smells good.
It's delicious!
Eh?
Carbonara is delicious.
Masakano umai!
Chicken ga umai!
Meccha oishii kore!
Nandemo umai!
Oishii!
Yasai curry ni half ikka to half scrambled egg o ireta yatsu ga umai!
Soko ni ikitsuite teichaku shita!
Umai!
Is this enough?
It's delicious. Thank you for the meal.
Thank you very much.
Haa!
Otsukaresama deshita.
Nagagatta.
Honma ni atsui shi.
Ano, betabetta suru shi.
Kaminoke sekkaku kawaiiku shimashite mo
sugu yoreru shi ya na.
Zen da tte shimai niya iwaremasu ya nka na.
Horide nugouto shita ra
ase betabetta de nuginikui ya nka.
Tanei yo.
Nga unga atte mite iru yatsu.
Nga unga dekitan kai?
Honnan ee wa.
I just wear clothes all the time and take pictures.
I don't look good as a sexy actress.
No, I look good as a sexy actress, but I don't look good as a sexy model.
So if it's a gravure, it's a gravure.
I don't want to sell my calendar with a gravure.
No, no, no.
I'm attached to it, and that's why you guys are taking pictures.
So I'm attached to it, and I'm going to be bald.
I don't like it. I'm always bald.
At least I have a lot of cute clothes.
I don't usually wear clothes like this.
Seっかくこんな衣服を用意してもらってんねんから
着てる状態を多めにとってほしい
講義ですこれは
そんなことばっか言っとるから
いつまで経っても
みんなにバカにされる職業であるやん
確かにそれは言えてる
確かに
なんかめっちゃ優しい人とかいい人って
バカにしこやん
アホ
もっと買え
ほんで
民度がいい人たち
いつもありがとうございます
ありがとうございます。これからは脱がない赤ちゃんも応援してね。
おい、アホ、お前は何でもいいから全部買えよ、作品。わかったか?
言いたい放題のまるでYouTubeみたいなイメージ撮影でした。ありがとうございました。