Oh
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Oh
It's hot.
Your hips are moving.
It's not sweat.
What is this?
I don't know.
Look at me.
Look.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating more on your back than on your back.
Here.
Don't move.
You can move now.
Uhhh...
What's going on with you, Senko?
I can't breathe.
Do you want to pee?
Oh
It's okay, it's okay.
What's the matter with you?
Dad...
Why are you doing this?
I can't...
You can't?
Oh
Put your hands out.
Oh, it's hard.
It's hard.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
Wait a second.
Are you okay?
Don't do it.
Stretch it out.
That's right.
Do you feel it?
Do you feel it when you stretch it out?
Yes.
Be careful.
Do you feel it when you stretch it out?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh
I can't do this anymore.
What do you do at that time?
At that time, yes.
Do you really call someone?
No, I don't call anyone.
Really?
Yes.
It's fun and lonely, isn't it?
I'm a little frustrated.
It's different after all.
Yes.
Drink it, drink it, drink it.
If you hear such a story.
When I heard it, I thought it was hot, but it was really warm.
I don't even know that place.
It's hot, so can I go to the side?
I'm sweating.
I can smell it.
I'm sorry.
You look like an adult.
You look like someone who likes kindness.
Are you really different?
I don't want to be bullied.
You're making a mess.
You should drink it.
Really?
I want to be beaten.
You want to be beaten?
Isn't that a line?
It's not a selfie, is it?
No, it's not a selfie.
It's funny, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
Can I roll it?
Yes.
It's so hot.
You're sweating so much.
Take it off.
Take it off, take it off, take it all off.
All of it?
Are you okay?
Why did you say that?
Are you going to bully me?
Do you want to be bullied?
Yes, I want to be bullied.
You've grown up.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to touch me more.
Where?
I want to ask you a question.
Where do you feel comfortable?
In my stomach.
In your stomach?
Don't you want to sleep? Do you want to drink a little more?
Are you shy?
What are you doing?
You like Sanpito, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Do you want a kiss?
Do you want to take a shower?
No, I don't want to.
Then you can take a shower.
It's getting late.
I want to take a shower.
It hurts.
I can't breathe.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Why am I embarrassed?
You look like your favorite dog, Yotsumba.
You look like a dog.
You really look like a dog.
Where are your eyes now?
I don't know.
I can't do it.
It's getting hot in here.
I'm getting excited.
Can I touch you?
I don't know what to do.
I love you, JinJin.
JinJin, what's wrong?
I want you to rub it on my back.
You don't have to do that.
It's not enough.
Your hips are moving.
I'll just rub it on.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Where?
Over there.
Sonny...
I'm so sorry...
Can you look this way?
What are you doing?
Look at me.
Touch me.
I want a kiss.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
Oh, my God.