Thanks for watching!
私は葵、OL3年目。広告代理店の仕事をしている。
プランニングの仕事を希望しているが、現実は使いっ走りな営業である。
なかなか就職しない彼氏とは3年前に縁を切った。
おかげさまでセックスはご無沙汰ではあるが、まあストレスからは解放されたから良しとする。
学生の頃は毎日が刺激的で、きっと絵日記にしたらカラフルだったんだと思う。
社会人になってからは1年があっという間に過ぎていく。
先のことを考えると少し不安になることだってある。
今は働いている人が多い。
ちょっと近い。
This is the first time I've ever done this, so I'm excited to see how it will turn out.
I've never done this before, so I'm excited to see how it will turn out.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You touched it, didn't you?
What?
You have a bag, don't you?
How can I touch it?
But now...
What?
Hey, hey, don't bother me.
You're so sticky.
Sticky.
After that, I ran to the bathroom.
The stockings had a lot of lotion on them.
Did you feel it?
No, not at all.
I shouldn't have said it. I shouldn't have said it.
Why do I have to change my bike?
You can change it normally.
Don't touch me.
Everyone is the same as yesterday.
You'll get wet soon.
You're wet, aren't you?
Don't touch me.
Is your voice going to leak?
You don't like it?
Your voice is so quiet.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do that.
It's obvious that you don't want to do either.
Shut up.
Move it.
If you want to do it, do it.
Do it.
Move it.
But...
Don't stop.
I won't move it.
I won't let you get away with it.
I'm going to take a different train tomorrow.
It's too late. Give up.
Give up.
I'm going to get out of here.
It's over. It's over.
I don't know what to do.
It's starting to break down somewhere.
When I'm with my boyfriend who likes to decorate,
I can't get used to my daily life.
Is this okay?
It doesn't work at all.
It's not like that.
It's so big.
I don't want to do that.
I can't do it.
Do it by yourself.
What are you doing?
Are you messing with me?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to quit?
You don't want to, do you?
I don't want to, but...
If you're going to quit, then do it.
You're going to quit, right?
You're going to sleep, aren't you?
You're going to move normally, aren't you?
I don't want to do this anymore.
I can't take it anymore.
Are you okay?
The sound from yesterday was terrible.
It's the other way around.
They let me do the flatulence and just let me get in.
They tried to test me.
There's nothing I want to do.
But I moved my hips.
Even though I'm a stranger.
Even though he's a nice guy.
I can't do this anymore.
It feels weird.
I feel weird.
I'll see you in a bit.
I might have wanted to live like this all my life.
Let's go shopping on the day after tomorrow.
I'm going to buy a mini skirt.