Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
What do you want me to do first?
I want you to kiss me.
Do you like my hair?
Yes, I like it.
Don't go.
Can you make a promise?
I can make a promise.
Then I'll kiss you.
Don't get up until you say you're tired.
Yes, until you say it's okay, don't puke, okay?
It's painful, okay?
I want you to put more pressure on your chest.
You're not puking, are you?
I know, right?
Yeah.
Let's take care of it.
Don't move.
You'll get a cramp.
Use what you like.
Let's make you feel better.
Can I ask you one more time?
Do you have an abortion?
No, I don't have an abortion.
Really?
Yes.
Then, I don't have an abortion.
I don't feel like doing anything.
Then you don't have to do anything nice.
You don't have to do anything nice.
I want you to do something nice.
Then, what is the truth?
I'm feeling down.
I know.
You're right. It's starting to overflow.
I wonder what this is. Wow, it stretches so much.
What is this?
I could feel it coming.
What do you think this is?
It's hot.
It's not hot, is it?
What?
I'm going to the beach.
Are you going to the beach on your own?
No.
I can't do that.
What's wrong with your feet?
I'm going to the beach.
You can't go because I'm telling you to.
You can't go there, can you?
I don't want to go there.
There's no other place to go.
Oh, I see.
It hurts.
Don't do that.
Don't do that so fast.
Do you feel like going there?
I feel like going there.
You look like you're going to cry.
No, I can't.
You're my toy, aren't you?
Let me have a lot of fun.
You look like you're going to cry.
I feel like I'm going to die.
You're still okay, right?
No, I can't hold it in.
What's wrong with your waist?
I can't see well.
I'm going to give you a reward.
Do you want a reward?
I want a secret.
What do you want to see the most now?
I want to see your boobs.
Too bad.
Was it here?
Do you want to lick it?
Yes.
Yes, I want to lick it.
You can lick it but
you can't say that I'm fine.
You can't say that.
I can't.
Damn it!
You can't do that.
I'm not saying it's not enough.
Ah, it's really painful.
Oh!
Ah, it's painful.
It's painful!
Ah, it's really painful!
Do you like this kind of play?
I don't like it.
I can't do it.
Oh
Don't do this to me, please.
I think I can do it.
You can't.
I really think I can do it.
Stop it.
Do you want me to stop?
I think I can do it.
You can't do it.
But I can't do it.
I can do it.
I'm tired.
Are you tired?
Yes.
What do you want?
I can do it.
I'm coming!
Why did you leave?
I left.
Why?
I told you not to leave.
I can't get out.
Stop it.
Forgive me.
Please forgive me.
It's still this hard.
Tell me why you couldn't hold it in.
My legs hurt.
Your mouth is on the floor.
I'm sorry.
Can you hold it in for the next time?
Yes.
Really?
I'll do my best.
Yes.
Hmm
It's a promise
You want to see what I'm feeling, right?
If so, you can show your lower body
Show me the part of your body that you want to show me.
Do you want to see this part?
Then come here and lower my pants.
Do you know that it's already wet?
Come closer to me.
If you were looking at my pants, your nipples would stand up.
Imagine that your pants are inside me.
I think it's in there.
Like this.
Look at her face.
I can feel it.
Move it from behind.
Come closer.
I can feel it.
Oh
Do you want a reward?
Do you want it?
You don't want it?
I want it.
Then I'll give you a lot.
Put your tongue out.
Do you want to do something that feels good?
I want to.
Do you want to do something?
Where do you want to lick?
Does it feel good?
It looks delicious.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to lick this part.
I'll do it.
Let me taste the grass.
Let me taste it.
I'm embarrassed to look at you like that.
Because it looks so delicious.
Is it bad?
I'll eat it.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Do you feel your boobs touching your feet?
Yes, I do.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
But you can't go there.
You can't do that.
Sakai, you can't do that.
Does it feel good?
Sakai, does it feel good?
I can't do that.
Do you feel the pain in your neck?
It feels good.
Oh, I can't.
You're weak here.
Okay.
I'll do something more comfortable.
You can lick mine, too.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this anymore.
What should I do?
I don't know where it is.
Oh
Let's see how Miya-chan is doing.
Ah, feels good.
Ah, no good.
Amazing.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
Do you want to see your butt more cleanly?
I want to see it.
It's amazing.
It looks clean.
It's going to be weird.
Is it going to be weird?
It's going to be okay.
I can't do that.
You couldn't hold it in?
I couldn't hold it in.
You're tired.
I'm sorry.
I haven't gone yet.
I'm sorry. I got stuck.
Won't you let me go?
Are you okay?
I'm a little dizzy right now.
It's okay.
I'll make it hard for you.
Put it in from the back once more.
Put it in your mouth.
No, it feels good.
It's amazing.
It's really narrow.
Is it narrow?
I'm going to take you out of here.
Oh, my God.
I'm out of breath.
I'm still out of breath.
You can do it one more time, can't you?
Let's do it.
Are my boobs touching yours?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Do you want some water?
Put your tongue out
You can drink it
Good girl
I'll make you feel better
I like being seduced
I love you, Hirano.
Can you feel it?
I'll show you something better.
Please lie down.
Are you making progress?
Do you want to take a deep breath?
If you don't take a deep breath, I won't eat you.
Take a deep breath.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, my God.
Oh
Look at where it's going to go.
Make it feel good.
Oh, my God.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Why did you go away?
I haven't said it's okay yet.
Why did you leave me?
My mom still wants you.
Do you want me to do it again?
I can't do it.
Oh