Miss Angela White. I love how you're on the floor ready for me.
Ready.
You're ready and waiting for me, aren't you?
Yeah.
What are you going to do with me?
I'm going to play with you.
Please.
You're a sexy little bitch, aren't you?
I want to be your little toy today.
You want to be my fuck toy?
Yes, please.
Really?
Yeah. Oh, I see that fucking pussy there.
I got a juicy fucking thing. You're looking at it now
So delicious tell me what you're gonna fucking do to it sit back sit back
What are you gonna do to my pussy whatever you asked me to do
Did I tell you to get your fucking tits out yet?
Put them fucking away
now
these tits are amazing
take your earrings out i want to be able to grab your throat
open all right always look into the camera that's my only fucking request
as you look into the camera with those big,
fucking, beautiful eyes.
Let me see that fucking butt.
Oh my God.
Let me fucking see that.
Oh, fuck yes.
What is this in your fucking ass already?
Wipe it on your face.
Let's start this fucking...
Yeah, fuck.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Sit back on that fucking sofa.
You want me up?
I want you up.
Hurry the fuck up.
No time to fucking waste, Miss White.
Shake that fucking big juicy butt for me.
So are you going to be a good little slut for me today?
Yes, I am.
I'm gonna do whatever you want me to.
Whatever I want.
I am.
I'm gonna squeeze you.
Yeah, do it.
I love jerking fucking bitches.
Open eyes.
They're not little tits.
They're fucking huge tits.
That's it. Spit on it.
Spit on this one as well.
Squeeze.
I'm squeezing you.
Show me how you like to wank. I like to see how girls wank.
How do you like to wank?
It's too fucking cold.
Mmm.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm gonna fucking stick my fingers in your fucking hole.
Like this.
Oh, it feels so good.
Mmm. Feel that butt plug?
Yeah. Feel it in my asshole.
Fuck.
Fuck. Yes.
Oh, fuck. Ooh.
You pushed it right out.
I can't try to taste it.
Oh, fuck that.
What about slapping that fucking pussy?
You want to stick my fingers in there?
That feels so fucking good.
Yeah, you like fingers inside your fucking pussy?
Mm-hmm.
Come here, taste them.
That's it, fucking.
I want to control you like this.
I want to move you around with my fucking fist.
Oh
Squeeze it really fucking tight
Push that fucking push it out. Oh
Pull it out like this
Fuck yeah, and push it back in look at that
Have you taught yourself there? Or do you just have no f***ing...
You can't breathe. I'm not letting you f***ing breathe.
Like this.
You have to slap me if you want to breathe.
Yeah, you have to slap me.
Huh? You want to breathe, Angela?
No? Are you good?
Does that make you f***ing...
makes you oh sit up let me see that
it my hand see how you like to do
Let me see if I can get it in there.
Spit.
All the way down your fucking throat.
Look at the fucking tongue in there.
I like it when you look at me.
Bite my fucking hand, come on, bite it, bite the fucking hand!
I'm so fucking excited right now.
You wanna eat it?
I wanna fucking eat that pussy. Please let me eat that pussy.
Please let me eat that pussy.
Come here.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Those fucking beautiful lips.
I just drool on them.
cunt.
Yeah?
That's it.
Fucking cunt.
All the way down.
Spit all over my fucking pussy.
All that fucking spit.
All that beautiful pussy.
Holy shit.
Do you like to eat fucking cunt?
I love eating pussy.
Gagging and then you can spit.
Gagging you like a fucking whore bitch.
In and out, in and out, in and out.
I love it.
Oh my God, your pussy's so fucking juicy.
You got big fucking cunt lips.
I fucking love it.
So fucking juicy.
Bite it.
Grab it.
You know that fucking sandwich right there.
Oh.
Fuck! Fuck, yeah!
I'm on that clit, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I want to eat up something.
Let me make it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh!
That big fucking clit,
I can suck on.
You know what I want?
Yeah, you tell me.
I want to get on the fucking floor
So I can get up nice and fucking high
So I can eat my fucking shit up
Get on the fucking floor
Oh my god
Look at that fucking asshole
Look at my fucking shithole
Get my fucking tongue deep inside that asshole
Oh
Let me spread those little butterfly look at those butterfly
Fucking like that
Look at that pool of fucking spit dripping down your pussy.
Oh, fucking watch it drip down.
You need to eat it all.
Oh, yeah, watch it fucking drip.
Yeah, that's fucking hot.
Look at that.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm.
Lick it all out.
Yeah.
Oh, that looks fucking good.
the fucking ass?
Deep inside that fucking hole.
Do you like eating shit hole?
Uh huh.
Yeah, you're like eating fucking dirty fucking shit hole.
I'd be a little fucking slut for you.
Smell, smell.
Smell my fucking hole.
There's a little nose in there.
Oh yeah, you smell so good.
Fuck you with my nose.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck it.
Oh my god, that's so gross.
You are making me fucking wet.
I want to sniff your face.
I want to smell your fucking arse on my face.
Fuck in the middle of the house.
Stay fucking.
Fuck in there.
All the time.
Fuck on you.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh.
bite your fucking tongue
fuck
oh my god
I'm gonna touch you, I'm gonna grab you
these fucking tits
Grab these fucking tits.
I want to see these fucking tits.
These fucking fucking tits.
I'm grinding myself.
I can smell your armpits.
I can smell them.
Fuck yes!
Is it you?
Oh my god, I'm so fucking tired right now!
Smell your arse in my face.
Smell your arse. Can you see that arsehole?
Put your fucking toes in your mouth.
Yeah, like you're fucking grinding yourself on.
Rub it on there, rub it on there, rub it on there.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck you.
Oh my god. Oh my god, you're so fucking sexy. So fucking sexy.
Big fucking cunt.
Get your fucking face in there. Get your fucking face in there.
Hold your fucking nose. I want you to fucking... Yes.
Don't you dare let go. Slap me. Slap me.
oh god i could just fuck you all day
let me just see that tongue
right in that fucking pussy
let me rearrange my hand on the on the thing yeah
fucking wank
Yeah, I want that fucking car
Let's do this shit man
I'll be like where the fuck is my pussy my ass
Fucking ready for that day
Marcus come in
yes that's it
Oh, that's the fucking one.
I can hold my hand right there.
Dribble in my fucking hand.
You like fucking with those?
Yeah.
Fuck her!
Let me fucking stick my fingers in her ass.
Look at me, Angela.
Let me see your fucking eyes.
Look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
Fuck.
Let me fucking sleep.
I feel so fucking good between the two of you.
You look so fucking sexy.
Hold her fucking mouth like that.
You fuck her tits.
I fucking love it, look at this.
Stick your fucking cock back in there.
I'm going to fucking choke her.
that fuck hole.
Oh my god, he's so fucking good with that dick.
Do you like his fucking dick?
I love it so much.
I love that fucking dick so much.
Fucking white nut fucking pussy.
Oh, fuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, god.
It's fucking good.
Let me wipe all that fucking sweat all over your face.
Look at you.
Look at that, look at this, just look.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fucking love it.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, that's good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Fucking love it.
Fucking love it, yes, yes, yes.
You know what I want to do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to stick my foot on your fucking face.
So good, so good.
Yeah, right, fucking face like that, look at that.
Look.
And then he's fucking you.
I fucking love it here, keep it in that house.
Yes, like that, just like that.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
shhh
keep looking at me
look inside the sass
yes yes yes
come on pull up let me fucking see that hole
oh look
I'm gonna get my fucking toy
you keep fucking
because I'm gonna shove it right in there
Yeah?
Mm.
Look at this.
Fucking love this.
Oh.
Yes.
You two fuck each other.
Show me how you want to fuck me.
Fuck.
Go on.
Choker.
Look at this.
Show me.
Oh.
Shit, that's fucking.
Look at this fucking ass.
Ooh.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Let me stick my toy in there.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, that feels so fucking good.
Oh, now stick your fucking toy.
Stick your dick back in there.
Yeah.
Man toy.
Stick that fucking man toy in there.
Oh, God, yeah, I love having a fucking manta right in front of my eyes.
Oh, shit.
Look at this.
Yes.
Fucking sexy.
One by one.
One.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
One.
Yes.
Put inside her pussy.
Yeah, I want to be DP'd.
DP.
Yeah, like this.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Go, go, go.
Look at me fucking as well.
I can see your fucking face, Angela, you dirty little fucking slut.
Look, look, look.
Yes!
I love it.
Oh, mi jorden.
Oh, fuck.
Let me stick that fucking back in there.
Yes, yes.
Now taste my fucking dick.
This is my fucking dick.
My dick I brought all the way from fucking England to fuck you with.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck, yes.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
I want you to taste it.
Taste it.
It's a fucking, ooh.
Oh, fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
i'm gonna get my fingers his dick my fingers
Oh, yes.
Oh, dick.
Jiggle that spit under there.
Right out.
Stick your tongue out.
Yeah.
No.
Fuck you.
Jump.
Jump here.
Just like this.
Yes.
Fuck you.
Just like this, my love.
Just like this.
You're gonna fucking...
Fuck, that's good.
Are you gonna fucking laugh?
Look at that.
Oh my god.
You look so fucking good.
Go, go, go, go.
You like the way he fucks you?
Yeah.
Do you know what I wanna do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wanna fucking eat that pussy.
Look at that fucking pussy.
He's about to bounce a fuck on his dick.
Hurry up.
Oh my god.
Oh my God.
Fucking horny.
I love it.
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Fuck!
Come on.
You just squirted all over my...
Look at my fucking head.
Look at it.
Fucking squirt all...
Grab it and fucking squirt.
Lick it off my fucking head.
Uh-huh.
Lick your fucking squirt off my fucking head.
Yes.
This is the best.
Yeah.
You hate dreaming
You have to wipe this fucking camera
What is he doing to you? Is he fucking you?
Is he fucking you?
Blood in my eyes
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You're fucking dead
Oh my god
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck
Go, go, go
I'm not fucking calm like that
Just keep fucking
Oh shit
Yeah, my fucking toy when I look at this go look at this go
wait there you keep fucking you keep fucking i need to wipe the camera
oh my god that looks so good
oh yeah yeah yeah that in my house is so good let me see my fingers now
And I wanna like all move you around
Like this, like this
Move you all fucking around
Like a little fucking puppet
Like a little fuck puppet, that's what you are
Fuck puppet
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oh fuck yes
Oh my god
I want my fucking toy
Where's my fucking toy
I wanna fuck you
Yeah I want you to fuck me with your big dick
Put that big fucking dick inside me
Big fucking dick right in there. Look at that. Oh, God.
I'm going to go from your fucking ass to my butt.
I want that fucking...
You want it in your pussy?
Ass, yeah.
Mmm, look at that.
Yeah, fucking twit.
Yeah.
Mmm, spit on that fucking hole. Spit on that fucking hole for me.
Mmm.
Look at this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck.
Look at this.
Yeah.
Oh, look at that.
Fuck.
Yes.
Yeah, there it goes.
Oh, my God.
Look at that, look at them fucking it real hard
Fuck yeah, hold it fucking down
Oh fuck, yes, yes, yes
Show me this there, show me this there
Show me the fucking
Look at that
Look, let me see if I want to fucking gape her, look.
Fucking gape her, fucking gape her.
Let's do it like that today, one by one.
Go on, like this.
Oh, I love the way you both fucking tick.
The way you both fucking tick.
I was sneaking.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh shit, that's fucking good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck you like this.
Suck my fucking dick.
yes
holy shit yeah
just like that
you can see right inside my ass
yeah i can see right inside that
fucking big fucking
juicy tits all on your face
smothering you with his dick right inside there
yeah
go back
stick it in there
stick it right back in there
oh my god it feels
so good i love it
I'm going to stick my foot on the floor.
Stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
Still is it.
Fuck!
She can't speak properly because I've got my foot on a fucking map.
Look at that.
Look how fucking good that looks.
One, one.
I'm still looking at you.
Go, go, go.
Just like this, just like this.
Open your eyes, spread your eyes.
Spread that fucking heart.
Spread it like that.
Look at her.
She looks so fucking good.
Spread it wide.
Spread it.
Oh, fuck.
Put your fucking fingers in there.
I want to spread you.
Go on, spread it.
Put your fucking fingers in there, Marcus.
Spread it. Go on, spread it.
I can see your face as well.
Oh, it's f***ing wide.
I'm going to stick a f***ing tip in.
I'm going to f***ing squirt all over my face.
It looks like f***ing tears. Squirt tears all over my face like that.
I'm going to rub it all in there.
Look at this.
Just like that.
I wanna make my squirtle live in my face
I wanna make my fucking squirtle live in my face
I wanna know, I wanna know, I wanna know what I am
in my face
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Oh my god, these eyelashes are so dark
Look at this
Look at this.
In.
Let me get my fucking toy.
Where's my fucking toy?
Look at this gate.
In.
Out.
Look at this.
Ah, there's the fucking toy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eat that.
Get some spit on it.
Spit on it.
Stick it right in there.
Oh my god, that's fucking good.
Yeah, it'll fit.
It'll fit.
No.
Stick it.
There we go.
Now you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, go on.
Oh, fuck, no, it's too full, too fucking full.
Where are my fucking assholes?
Yeah, I want that big fucking clothing.
That fucking squirt all over my big tits.
Lick it off, lick it all fucking off.
Lick it off.
Oh, you sassy little bitch.
Sassy little fucking bitch.
Look at this.
Look at that, look, this is what I wanna do.
I wanna fucking do this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go on, fucking stick it back in there.
Stick it back in there.
Out.
Push it down.
He's out.
Oh, fuck.
That's so fucking good.
Look at this, look at this.
So fucking good like that, oh my god.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck. Yeah, fuck those pictures.
I like that.
Love it, love it, love it.
Love it.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
His face is so pretty.
Interesting scene.
Oh my god.
Yes!
Fuck.
Yes.
Fuck yes, yes, my god you fuck me like fucking crazy, fuck this
I want to sit on your fucking face
Show me the set, show me the set, show me the set
What I fucking want, I want to sit on your fucking face in a minute
Oh yes
When you're fucking her, yeah?
I want to grind my cunt on this pretty little fucking mouth
Wherever I'm fucking told.
Let me see if I can do it.
Turn sideways.
This way or the other way?
I want to fucking sit.
You tell me.
I want to sit on your fucking face.
Yeah, whatever you want.
Whatever you want.
I might even take my fucking skirt off.
Yeah.
It's in the fucking way.
Yeah, I'm going to sit.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, and then you're going to get fucked.
So we're not even going to be able to fucking...
Oh, my arse hole is right in your fucking face.
Come on, Marcus. Come on, fucker.
Oh, fuck.
Come here.
Like I get fucking thrown around.
I just get thrown around, get fucked.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Fuck. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look at this. Look at this. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Are you okay, Angela?
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
It's so fucking good, look, look.
Oh, look at, yeah.
Look at this, yeah.
Fucking grinding myself right on the pit.
Yeah, I fucking love it. Oh my god, it's so sexy.
Oh my god, it's so fucking hot.
There's my fucking pussy.
And then in your fucking mouth.
And in your fucking mouth.
Stick your fucking tongue out, I'm gonna grind on it.
Let me fucking see that.
Look, look.
Whoa, look at this.
I'm gonna show you that fucking asshole
Feels so good
Oh look I've got one of those
One
Look at that
Oh my god
I love it
You know I love the way you fuck me
I love the way you fuck me
She's choking you
Look at this, look at this, look at this, look at this.
Yes.
You've got squares all over you.
Yeah.
Look, look.
Look at that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Keep fucking looking at me.
Oh, you're so fucking good with that thing.
How does it feel good?
Does it feel good inside there?
Oh, Marcus, fuck off.
Nice and fucking hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, you're fucking taking me.
Oh, my god.
That's fucking good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're going to make me fucking cum all over that dick.
I'm just going to fucking cum all over that fucking dick.
I tell you to do you hear me? Don't you fucking?
I'm fucking ready
Let me stick that fucking spit up inside that
I'm not going out. In, out.
Oh, fuck.
Who wants to get cocky?
Let's do it.
Oh, it's so good with that fucking dick.
Oh, yes.
They fucking dig me like that.
Holy shit.
All the way, Angela.
All the way.
Oh, fuck you. Jesus Christ.
Fuck you.
Let me fucking stick my toy in there.
I want a fucker like you.
The egg wants to get the fuck out of you.
Oh, fuck!
Fuck you!
You motherfucker!
Let me fucking take it, go on.
Spread it.
Let me get it.
Spread it, I want to gape it for you.
Oh my god, I want those to eat me. I want you to fucking eat me.
I'm sick and tired of you fucking eating me up.
Ugh, you're gonna eat this fucking person's ass.
I'm gonna fuck her face into my hole.
I'm gonna fuck her face into my fucking hole, like this.
Is he pumping his fucking, is he pumping his dick inside you?
Oh, I can see you fucking her as well
You look so fucking slutty
She's so good
So fucking good, you know that
How's your fucking head doing?
How's your fucking head in there?
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Fuck. Fuck you. I'm gonna cum.
Oh, fuck.
Come here. Come here.
Yeah, I want that fucking cum.
Yes. Yes.
Please give me that fucking cum.
Look at me when he fucking comes.
yes oh my god I just want to see you
Let me scoop it, scoop it all.
Yeah, I want it.
Oh, my God.
Sexy little bitch.
Let's see this fucking.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Sit the fuck up now.
Look at that, you see all that?
I should've wring it into my fucking mouth,
I don't know if I can.
Oh, wring it on your fucking face.
Let me do it, let me just fucking squeeze it.
Yeah, wanna squeeze it in my face?
Yeah, squeeze it, oh, look, oh, I'm squeezing it,
oh, that's it, squeeze it, oh, fuck.
Let me suck it out.
Oh, suck it, oh, this is a perfect ending,
look, on your fucking knees.
open them eyes
thank you
dirty slut