O-he-yo gozaimasu.
From the opening, you're wearing a lot of clothes.
Ah, yes.
I was told to wear this.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed.
By the way, have you heard about today's shooting?
Where are you going to be shot today?
Yes?
Breasts.
Ah, yes.
Do you like to be touched?
I like it.
You seem to like it.
Can I interview you as it is?
Then again
Can you tell me the size of your chest?
It's an eye cup.
Is it easy to feel?
Does that mean to touch it?
When did you get so big?
I grew up in high school.
見られてるのは分かるんだ。
じゃあ今まで痴漢とかもあったことはあるのかな?
痴漢はありますけど。
どこ触られるの?
お尻。
触られてどうだったの?おっぱいは触られなかったの?
ダメだもん、ダメかも。
まだダメだ。
えー、つらいよ。
何がダメなの?
分かんないです。
おっぱいどうされると興奮するの?
分かんないもん。
じゃあその大きいおっぱいで、今まで男の人何本ぐらい挟んだことあるの?
I don't have that many.
How about 50?
I have about 3.
You must be kidding.
I don't know.
It's hard.
Can't you hold it in?
I can't hold it in.
I don't want to do this to you.
It hurts.
Can I bully you two more?
I can't do it anymore.
NEMOTIEN
It feels good, doesn't it?
Please wait a little longer.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
I can't do this.
Is it okay if I put it in?
Why did you put it in without permission?
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
It hurts.
Oh my god!
I feel so good!
I can't believe I'm doing this for the first time in my life.
I'm so happy.
I'm so sleepy.
I feel like I'm going to pass out.
Please make yourself comfortable.
I want to play with a lot of toys.
It feels good.
It feels good just by touching it.
Thank you for making me feel good.
I'll do it for you next time.
It's getting really big.
Look at this.
Look at my chin.
Look at my upper lip.
It's gotten so big.
It's a secret.
Are you okay?
I'm surprised.
I'm feeling good.
You made me feel good, so I'm going to start.
I'm getting wet.
Do you feel good here, too?
It's getting hotter and hotter.
Does that mean it feels good?
Do you want me to lick your tail?
In my mouth
It's getting bigger and bigger
Does it feel good?
Wow
It's hard
Does it feel good?
Shall I eat you to the bottom?
Hey, I'll feed you until you wake up.
Did you feel good?
Your mouth is messy.
Your mouth became like this because of my drool.
Because your mouth is messy.
You can drool more.
Is it hot?
I wonder if it's good?
I put it all in.
Is it good?
It feels good to rub it gently.
Which one is better?
Ah, my hips are moving.
What's wrong?
I'm going to rub it over there, too.
Rub it on your neck.
There's a lot of it over there.
It's getting bigger and bigger, isn't it?
Do you feel like you're about to go?
Do you understand?
I told you not to eat it.
I'll clean your boobs.
It's still hard.
It's so hard.
You put it out so much.
Why is it so hard?
Do you want to die?
It's amazing.
Did you feel good?
Thank you for giving me a lot of food.
Do you want to eat a lot of meat?
Yes.
Why are you taking it off?
Because it's hot.
Is it hot?
This is cute, isn't it?
It's not clothes, it's cute, isn't it?
Hey, don't do that all the time.
This ring...
Did it hurt?
Oh, I got it on my back.
Does it hurt?
Did it hurt?
I'm sorry. Don't get mad at me.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
Does it hurt?
Oh, it's delicious.
I think I'm going to eat a lot of it.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, are you okay?
Do you want to do it again?
It's all messed up.
I wonder if I'll mess it up again.
Do you want to do it again?
You're moving.
Does it feel good?
Your nipples feel good, don't they?
Hey, can you touch mine, too?
Hey, I want to hurry up, so can I put it in?
Isn't it too early?
No? I want to sleep.
It's too early.
It's dangerous.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
Why?
I can't do it.
You want to go to bed, don't you?
No, I can't.
You don't want to go to bed, do you?
I'm going to bed.
We're both in a good mood.
No, I can't.
Are you going to eat it?
I'm hungry.
Are you full?
Why don't you put it in right away today?
Oh, I can't do it. I can't do it anymore.
Oh, it feels good. It feels good.
Do you want me to put you to sleep?
Do you want me to pet you?
Yes.
I feel good.
Please.
I want to sleep.
Can't I sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to pee.
I can't do it. I can't put it in yet.
I want you to put it in.
Ossi
It feels so good!
Kimchi
Ah, it hurts so much!
It hurts so much!
I can't breathe!
Bye bye!